m 0 0 l 0 27 l 2 27 l 2 0 l 0 0 m 2 0 l -4 0 l -4 6 l 16 6 l 16 4 l -2 4 l -2 2 l 0 2 m 2 2 m 16 0 l 16 27 l 18 27 l 18 -1 l 16 -1 m 22 0 l 22 0 l 24 0 l 24 11 l 19 11 l 19 9 l 22 9 l 22 2 l 15 2 l 15 0 m 6 18 l 6 12 l 12 12 l 12 14 l 8 14 l 8 18 l 6 18 m 12 18 l 12 20 l 6 20 l 6 18 l 10 18 l 10 14 l 12 14 l 12 18 m 5 7 l 8 9 l 7 10 l 4 8 l 5 7 m 10 9 l 10 9 l 13 7 l 14 8 l 11 10 l 10 9 m 3 24 b 3 24 3 23 3 23 b 7 21 11 21 15 23 b 15 23 15 25 15 25 b 11 23 7 23 3 25
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
[ This is a parody segment of NHK's
"Professional: Shigoto no Ryugi" ]
World's first OL and Idol at the same time
World's first?
Nogizaka46's Shinuchi Mai.
Professional, huh?
In 2013, she started her activity as...
... an Idol of Nogizaka46's second generation.
APRIL 2014
And she is still continuing as one
whenever the chance presents itself.
Now, she's just not an Idol,
but she also has another profession, an office lady.
NOGIfessional
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Shinuchi's Way
[ Nogifessional = Nogizaka + Professional ]
So, Nogifessional, huh?
NOGIfessional
Profession
Idol, OL
- Were you working?
- I seriously was.
Sato Kenji
Narrator
Tight rivalry era of Idols
In this tight rivalry era of Idols...
... in order to survive in such harsh world...
In order to survive
... this woman has chosen that road.
Golden Chance
Shinuchi Mai.
Then, she has gotten the chance.
Selected to be a
Senbatsu member of 12nd single
Since I'm selected as Senbatsu member, of course...
... I think it will be hard to do both.
Idol
As an Idol and an OL...
Heavy Burden
... those two things will definitely be very difficult to do.
Guess I need to redo everything from scratch.
I feel like giving up here.
Desperations
Why are you giving up?
Hardships
As an OL, she's ready with having such burden.
Never Happened Before
That's because she wants to see
good things this world has to offer.
She can only step forward.
Tonight, we will reveal another side of Shinuchi Mai.
This is so OL.
Nogizaka46 - Shinuchi Mai
Kennin Idol and OL with "Super Saving" principle
What does it mean,
Super Saving principle?
Good morning! Good morning!
Good morning.
Shinuchi Mai...
... as an OL, this is what she does everyday.
So you're working for real?
Yes.
Can you show it?
Eh, it's embarassing.
My ID card...
... I use my photo from 10th single.
Good morning.
This is legit.
Ah, I have lots of works today.
Shinuchi, there is always one thing she does
when she arrives at her workplace.
Turning On The Computer
Start from that?
Since we had a slow start,
I'll turn on my computer first.
My office is not just here,
I'll go next door.
Good morning...
One of Shinuchi's job is...
... delivering documents.
The table layout got changed this April,
so I still haven't remembered it yet.
I don't know where to put this.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
This is Ebina-san.
Eh, no, this is Inaba-san.
You were wrong.
- Oo.. I was surprised!
- Sorry! Sorry!
As we can see, Shinuchi is good at recognizing her co-workers.
Clearly that's not the case!
She mentioned his name wrong, didn't she?
The place where Shinuchi works is a radio station.
She works at management department there.
This is my senior, Ida-san.
I make a lot of mistakes, but...
Management Department
Ida-san
... she handles them for me.
Hello, how can I help you?
She's receiving
a call seriously.
Ah, he's not present at the moment...
Not present?
Okay, I will relay that message.
When there's a phone call, I need to be careful
so I don't pick it up too fast.
I pick it up after about two rings.
Her job as an OL
Shinuchi's important task is...
... making company's invoices and arrange them.
There's also another task, where she has to write 200 pages many.
Mistake is not allowed in arranging documents.
When everything has done, she delivers them to each departments.
"Financial system" here handles the sale record,
then releases the bill...
... and also the agreement of the financial plan,
it's all being trusted to them.
Although her task is quite difficult,
there's one important thing Shinuchi does.
What? What?
Getting Water
What is this?
On the fifth floor, there's a spot to get water.
I always get water here.
This and...
... hot water.
This is the thing that has supported Shinuchi's job,
an adequate water intake.
Keeps Moving
Then, for Shinuchi who often moves around to different floors...
... there's one special way she uses.
Does Not Use The Elevator
Why though?
Well...
... it's for saving the elevators' electricity power.
And it's good for my diet too.
And today, starts from 12 o'clock,
a meeting is being held every week.
I'm not really involved in company's transaction meeting now.
I'm still new here even though it's been 2 years already,
but someone who's in his first year is attending it.
Basically, I'm just listening to them here.
Alright, let's start.
But in that meeting, Shinuchi...
... starts to do something.
I make notes, this is my habit now.
I write important things.
Shinuchi's Note
Then, what is Shinuchi writing?
She's just
doodling around.
She's making
a heart.
What's going on?
As an Idol...
... Shinuchi never wastes her time,
not even a second.
I'm heading out.
When I'm having a break, I do some vocal training or stretching...
... in a studio my boss leads.
Even though I'm working as an OL,
I can't abandon my status as a member of Nogizaka.
I'm very thankful to be able to work in a place
where I'm allowed to do this.
Then, Shinuchi's free time finally has come.
It's lunch break.
Shinichi's lunch menu is...
These are what I always eat.
This is "My Dressing".
I wrote Shin from my name, Shinuchi.
So you wrote
Shin there?
I keep "My Dressing" in the office's fridge.
I think it's a waste
if I have to buy small salad dressing everyday.
Thanks for the meal! I'm hungry...
You can say that I always buy salad.
Although I want to eat it a lot,
the price of vegetables is on the rise now.
So I only buy the small one, every single day.
This feels like
an actual OL.
Now onigiri, I bring my own.
What kind of
shape is this?
I just put ume inside.
Prefers Onigiri
Inside the onigiri...
... Shinuchi only puts simple ingredients.
We only need a short time with ume, don't we?
For example, if I use salmon...
... I need to use chopsticks to pick it.
If I use chopsticks when I'm making the onigiri
with my own hands...
... the chopsticks become dirty.
Which means, I have to wash them.
That's why after a consideration,
ume is surely the best choice.
I want something more practical.
"Saving time".
As an OL, time is highly needed.
Then, in her remaining break time...
Medical Room
... she always ask something.
Can I get some eyedrops?
- Like the usual?
- Yes, eyedrops.
This is nice.
Since I'm wearing contact lenses,
my eyes are dry and I need this.
If I feel unwell, I also ask for vitamin here.
We're allowed to use them and it's all free too.
I'm very thankful.
After a break, Shinuchi instantly heads to one place.
Getting Water
Didn't you
just go there?
However...
It's out.
Shinuchi's fountain of life is empty!
But, inside of Shinuchi...
... there's a strong will.
You refill it
by yourself, huh.
Because Shinuchi needs water,
she refills it herself.
For the sake of getting water.
That effort of hers deserves a praise.
That has molded her as an OL.
The Water Thief
Of course, that seems
like a water thief.
Many people don't talk about this.
But I got called as "The Water Thief".
If we buy the 500 ml mineral water everyday...
... it's 160 Yen, isn't it?
That's why I do this to save money.
That day was the last day of the month.
Shinuchi always utilizes her time as best as she can,
because it's the most important moment for a company.
However, when it was about to finish...
... an unexpected thing happened.
Why?
Ida-san...
- ... I just realized, there's a problem.
- What's wrong?
I put 20th as Saturday.
It should be 19th.
That?
What?
I have to start from the beginning, huh?
What? Why?
The bill release date...
... was wrong.
The bill payment date...
... I put it on a holiday,
of course it can't be done.
It should be one day before.
I feel like giving up here.
She has to redo everything.
Don't make mistake this time, okay?
Eh, but...
... clearly this is my fault because I didn't pay attention.
Hold on, it's going to be done soon.
Shinuchi's gaze...
... has changed!
When she's having a mistake...
... Shinuchi The OL,
is finally showing her seriousness.
As an Idol or an OL...
... she's giving her everything!
That's the marvel of Shinuchi!
Onegaishimasu.
Your Definition of Professional
Trying our best to use the chance we've been given.
This is where we are not allowed to give in.
That's all?
He's laughing at me!
Look, he's laughing!
What does Shinuchi's senior have to comment about her?
Production Division Head
Tomiyama-san
If we're looking at her right now,
she looks tidy just like an OL, but...
... usually, she doesn't look like this.
Usually, she looks boring.
What kind of comment was that...
Her last task today is copying.
This is perfect!
Perfect!
I've done good as an OL today.
NOGIfessional
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Shinuchi's Way
Finished
Nogizaka Koujichuu
BANANAMAN
Himura Yuuki
Shitara Osamu
Okay, Nogizaka Koujichuu is starting,
and here are the present members today.
Onegaishimasu!
- Okay, today we're discussing Shinuchi!
- Yes.
- You hadn't seen Shinuchi's activity
as an OL before, huh?   - Yes.
How often do you work?
When I'm not having a job in Nogizaka,
I work everyday.
- You got nicknamed "The Water Thief"?
- Correct.
It can be said that you're quite frugal in everything.
Seems boring, doesn't it?
Basically...
- ... I'm a type of person who has a boring life.
- Boring type?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Boring Life.
Truthfully, do you really want to work as an OL?
From the beginning I was considering
to have a work with steady income.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Playing it safe.
- What field did you choose
when you were looking for a job?   - IT.
IT?
I wanted to work in SI field.
- What's SI?
- System Integrator.
- What's system integrator?
- Never heard that.
It's a job where we do treatment on infrastructures
that are used by many people.
- That's amazing!
- So you wanted to do that.
But it's boring, isn't it?
Uh huh.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
- Interesting, right?
- Indeed.
We saw people on the second or third row
just like "Koi no Kara Sawagi" show...
[ Koi no kara sawagi = a variety show
where girls are trying to find their love ]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
All agrees.
- True! That's true!
- I saw it too.
The first row wasn't like that, right?
You look slender.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Tonight... The Queen of Horror Story Will Be Back!?
A real & strange phenomenon happens in studio!
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
Does it show?
- It shows so much.
- Yeah, you look beautiful.
Eh, seriously?
- Noujou is beautiful, isn't she.
- She's gorgeous.
- I'm very happy.
- So slender.
True.
- Are you drooling?
- A bit.
Nogizaka Check!!!
This is a segment where we find out about members
using informations from other members, staffs, and viewers.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
We will reveal Shinuchi Mai's capabilities
with various informations we have received
m -1 5 b 3 5 3 0 -1 0 l -28 0 b -32 0 -32 5 -28 5
Nogizaka Check
First, information from
a second generation member, Watanabe Miria.
She reuses oden's container.
- What does this mean?
- Unbelievable.
In lesson, members bought onigiri
and bread, then we ate them...
... she slowly took out an oden's container
gotten from convenience store.
She put the salad and mozuku into it, then she ate them.
[ Mozuku = some kind of seaweed ]
Did this really happen?
When I went to a convenience store,
I thought "I need some plate"...
Then I asked the clerk there,
"Can I take this oden's container?"...
... she said "Ah, yes",
so I took it...
After that, if I put salad and mozuku here,
I thought it would be one delicious meal.
But Maichun also...
There's a wrapping on salad, right?
She just put the salad's dressing,
and ate it from there.
But I didn't put the dressing in.
- You didn't?
- I didn't put it in.
- Ah, you mean the plastic wrapping?
- Precisely.
- You just ate it from there?
- Yeah.
You just ate it?
Do I look weird that way?
That's right, huh?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
He agrees too.
But basically, there's a lot of such informations.
She always carries few cucumbers.
- She carries cucumbers?
- Yes.
When we were in a bus after we were done filming PV,
and everyone was having dinner with their bento...
... Maichun was the only one who was busy
looking for something from her bag.
Then she took out a cucumber and just ate it.
- Raw?
- When I asked her, she said "Without any extra"...
"It can remove the cucumber's nutrition~"
while putting on a smile.
- So the nutrition can be removed.
- That sounds like a kappa.
[ Kappa = Japanese mythical creature who loves to eat cucumbers ]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Experience as a Kappa?
Why did she have to be like that?
"It can remove the cucumber's nutrition!"
"I didn't cook this!"
So there's something like that too.
Info from Kitano, when I thought
she'd be having a rare and expensive yoghurt...
... she preferred discounted products instead.
She's good at choosing products.
So you usually don't eat expensive yoghurt?
No...
Why are you that cheap?
I'm not saving too much.
Compared to the result of my hard work...
... if I just receive it like that,
isn't it unfitting?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Yoghurt  >  Her hard work
How come?
I would eat it if it was me.
She really resembles a wife.
I thought so too, she's like a housewife.
How many bath towels do you have?
I don't use bath towel.
You don't?!
Instead of bath towel, I use this one...
- Small towel?
- The small one, I use it like this.
Why?
I don't really like the big one like that...
There it is, her frugality.
I thought you have at least few bath towels, like normally.
What about underwears, how many?
I don't mean it in a weird way.
Yamasaki Ana only had seven.
She washed all of them on Sunday,
then when she needed it, she could just wear it everyday.
And she'd wash them again on Sunday.
She said, there's no such person like that.
- I only have five...
- Five?!
How do you survive one week
if you only have five?
Ah, I wash them.
Of course it won't be enough.
So, the panty you wear most often...
Pardon, I ended up talking about panties.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Not interest in that.
Clearly that won't be enough.
This seems like a Q&A segment of panties.
- The underwears that Himura-san wears are girl's panties.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Seriously not interested.
He is such a freak guy.
Let's know second generation members more with...
SUMMER HORROR STORY COMPETITION
IN 30 SECONDS, SPECIAL EDITION!!!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Hori has formed "The Second Generation's Scary Story Trio"
to do the 30 seconds scary story challenge
This time, Hori has formed
a trio of second generation members...
... to take on the 30 seconds horror story challenge.
Will the queen of horror story emerge?
First we have Yamazaki Rena, with her story...
"Summer Training..."
Alright...
Start!
This is a story when I was doing a training in summer.
Just before the bedtime,
suddenly from the wall of my room...
... I heard "Bang, Bang, Bang!" sound
like someone was banging on it.
... I heard "Bang! Bang! Bang!" sound
Then I went out to take a look.
There was also the same phenomenon in next room...
... everyone was too scared to check outside.
Even though we thought someone was
pulling a prank on us, but...
... in the recorded video of that building...
... that was recorded by the surveillance cameras...
... that was recorded by the surveillance camera...
... no one was there.
Okay, it's over.
What was that?
- "No one was caught by the camera",
is there more?    - No.
Oh come on!
Hori, was her story perfect?
Ah, that was perfect!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Perfect score according to Hori.
Hori, seriously?!
Moving on, personal experience of Shinuchi,
"On Way Home At Night."
Ready, start!
This story took place in a summer holiday,
in my first year of college.
When I was on my way home,
I could feel someone behind me suddenly.
I thought,
"Ah, perhaps I'm being stalked."
I stopped to check it myself.
And when I was stopping...
... the person behind me stopped too.
"Ah, I'm totally being stalked right now!"
I was wondering how to prevent him
from knowing my house.
I decided to make a run to a big house
at the side of the road.
Then, when I was almost giving in...
... about 5 minutes in, I started to panic
and didn't know where to escape...
... then...
It's over!
I want to hear more!
- Next part is the climax of the story, right?
- Yes, it is the climax.
- But you can't tell us.
- It's making us curious.
What do you think, Hori-san?
It's not scary enough, is it?
When it got cut at the last part
right before the climax...
- ... it leaves us with questions, right?
- Right.
- On the contrary, that's way better.
- This girl, always thinking positively!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
An OK for Hori.
Next, it's time for Hori the leader...
... the title is,
"After School"
Ready...
... start!!!
This after school story of mine
is not something to be laughed at.
That time, I was alone in the classroom.
I wanted to go to toilet,
and somehow I went to the closed school toilet.
But the toilet there was dark.
Just before I went back, I heard footsteps.
"Did I just see something?"
I thought, "Nope."
When I calmed down,
something suddenly appeared in front of me.
There was someone with a bloody face
staring down at me from above.
That's all...
Okay.
Hold on, did that actually happen?
I saw it in my dream.
- Ah, dream?!
So it was a dream. Surprising.
But the beginning of the story was interesting.
She just suddenly got immersed into the story.
It's because I saw a lot of narrators...
... so I thought I had to set the atmosphere right,
but it failed.
- That's fine.
- But Hori is known for that kind of soul.
Known for that kind of soul?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
An Idol who gets possessed easily.
After hearing them,
do first generation members have stories?
Takayama, do you have some?
- Do you want to share it?
- Ah, if this is going to happen, I should prepare it...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Serious.
What did you just say?
Hoshino, do you have a spooky experience?
I do, but it's not about spirits...
- We heard one that has no spirit just now.
- Give it a shot!
Surprisingly, Hoshino joins in.
What will she tell us?
Ready... DON!
A while back, my mom and I
were eating together in our home.
Then, my mom noticed that
I was doing something else beside eating.
My mom said,
"Aa, eat quickly!"...
... I got scolded!
Ah, scary! Scary!
How cute~ !
That was so cute!
You're brave enough to tell such story.
- That was great. Takayama, have you gotten one?
- I have.
- Really?
- Gang boss!!!
As expected!
- But it's quite creepy.
- Seriously?
What kind of creepy story that Takayama
who suddenly joined in will tell?
Ready, start!
When we were recording yesterday,
I saw Ikoma's VTR where she drank cider...
... which was taken in her house.
It was interesting in a glance, but...
... I thought I saw it before.
Her face when she was drinking the cider
was kinda unclear...
... when I was little,
there was an old lady.
When I looked outside,
near the telephone pole...
... an old lady was always standing there.
Then when I told it to my mom...
... she said,
"No one is standing there."
But I saw her, and Ikoma-chan's face
when she was drinking the cider...
... was identical to hers!
How was it?
- How was it?
- It was quite creepy.  - I know, right?
What's with Ikoma's face
when she was drinking cider?
Sorry...
... my face is ugly as sin.
Can you make the face you were making
when you were drinking the cider?
What kind of face was it?
- Is this the old lady's face in your story?
- A little bit more, her eyes are a bit...
- Like that?
- The chin was more protruding...
Protrude your chin, do that Ikoma.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Loads of requests.
In order to make Takayama's story clearer.
Opened, poured, then...
... drank...
Was the chin this protruding?
Her chin!
And her eyes too?
- A bit more.
- A little bit more.
The angle is different!
No, more to...
... the other way, the other way!
Waaah, that! That!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Embarassing.
Just like that!
What does this mean?
Are you saying that Ikoma, in future later...
... will show up when you drink foamy beverage?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Sci-Fi story?
That's too much!
Alright, who must go to a haunted place this time?
Members with non-scary stories...
... but essentially, everyone's fine.
Well then...
- ... Shiraishi, and...
- EH, WHY?!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Unexpected topic.
Your story was not scary at all.
- It wasn't scary at all, Shiraishi.
- But I didn't even say anything!!
- That one part when you got cut...
- I see.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
You were saying?
Anyone can go.
Member who didn't say anything scary,
like Shiraishi...
- ... is Hashimoto, right?
- Eh, no, no! Wait! Wait!
What's wrong, Hashimoto?
Your love talk was delicious.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Why does it become a food story?
- You said you want more, didn't you?
- No I never said that!
I have a terribly scary story if I were to move forward.
Way scarier than everyone else's.
That story of mine will win here.
Then, a story chosen by Hashimoto
to avoid the punishment will be...
Ready... DON!
Summer last year when I was having Ohakamairi,
I visited Noukotsudou.
[ Ohakamairi = tradition of visiting family's grave ]
[ Noukotsudou = Columbarium, a place to store deceased's cremated remains, mainly families ]
There was only me alone
on the first floor of that Noukotsudou.
When I walked to the area I was going to visit, there was
"DON! DON! DON!" sound even though no one was there.
Since the atmosphere was ominous,
I just kept going my way...
... went in to the elevator, and press the close button.
Then suddenly from the direction of Noukotsudou...
... even though I got everything on my view...
... I heard DON! DON! DON! sound three times
from the opposite direction.
Three times... after three times...
Her hands are sticking out.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A story of sticking out hands?
What is this?
It stopped at three times part.
When the sound entered, the door closed.
- That was absolutely not scary.
- That's right.   - It was!!!
When your hands were sticking out in the last part,
Ikoma laughed at you.
- That's true, then...
- Second generation.
Miona for example, she told a story
of her dream, right? It's not a reality.
Look, Hori seems lost.
She's like, "What, me?"...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
What's wrong with me?
- "So me?" like that.
- What's with that expression?
After this,
there will be a strange phenomenon in studio!
- Ikoma and Shiraishi, so it's three people.
- WHAT!? STOP!
- You two are utterly not scary!
- It's not like that.
Since your stories weren't scary,
we had to cut it.
Woah.
- KYAAAAA!!!
What? What? What's wrong?
A dragonfly fell.
- Huh?
- Why?
- This is impossible!
- How did it get in here?
- So big!
- I don't like that.
- Why did it fall here?
- Where did it come from?
Why did it fall here?
Why do we have a dragonfly on last part?
At the very last, it fits the theme.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Members who'll get the punishment will be announced next week!
Sakurai Reika will hold a meeting just for female Idols!
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
What is this?
Okay, we have decided the date.
And Wada will tag along too.
Eh, no, no way.
You shouldn't bother.
Wada's story was completely not scary.
Don't worry, you'll get hypnotized later.
Eh, she's admiring me ~
Next episode, Sakurai's new character arises!
You get it, don't you?