Translator:Mr.Reika
Timming/Typeset:Tamami-chan
What this? What's this?
Ah! So she was wearing a dress!
Sakurai Reika's Feminine Idol Gathering!
That's so cute!
This segment is about holding a meeting with her senpai idols,
and includes learning about idol wisdom that is usually hard to ask.
So cute!
The senpai idols who'll be hearing my concerns for today are these people!
Pleased to be here!
By the way, do you know who I am?
Of course!
We know you!
Yeah! We know you!
We've already worked together in the past right?
-Yes
It's just that we thought that the our entrance
during the opening was too half-assed.
A sudden bad comment
Like yeah..You have to be like "Let's go!"
But when we entered you're like "Fuwa fuwa fuwa"
Right?
As a leader you shouldn't be too lukewarm like that.
Ah! So you also knew that I was the captain?
Yes, yes.
We know.
I also want to enter nogizaka.
Joining motive
So you wanted to join them?
You're kidding right?
On this episode's girls talk, just like what Captain Sakurai hoped for,
To ride in a limousine and circle around the area
This is really expensive!
28,000 for only two hours!?
Feminine Idol Gathering, Start!
First of all,
A toast of greeting from this night's organizer Sakurai.
To our first girls' gathering!
Wait, it wasn't first time
Girls' gathering...
This is bad! You'll get scolded!
Can you speak a little bit more louder?
You're losing to the aircon!
Yes! I'll do it!
A toast to our Limousine Girls' Talk!
Pleased to be with you!
Kanpai!
That's very nice.
Ah. It's champagne.
Genuine Champagne
Yeah! It's really champagne!
Champagne.
What your personality within the group?
[Ponkotsu - Clumsy/Airhead]
I'm the ponkotsu character in the group.
Eh~
As the leader?
You really have reliable and diligent image.
But having a ponkotsu personality as a leader, isn't that bad?
-Yes, that's right.
But I can't stop being ponkotsu.
Sakurai wrote the questions she wanted to ask from her seniors on a card.
Okay! Let's go with this.
As we talked from a while ago,
How can I stop the members from calling me ponkotsu?
Ah~ i get it!
I really want know how stop it
Why do they call you ponkotsu?
Just like what you saw at the opening,
Like being silly and laughing.
Is it because you're too light and buoyant?
Hmm, maybe.
And also, like I made a mistake on the title
when I was introducing our new song.
Well that's a thing you can't do.
-You've really done it.
When they call you ponkotsu, how do you respond?
"Eh, no I'm not"
That's it!
That's not good!
I see.
[Gyakuresu - Being angry at someone who should normally be angry at you]
Then how about being "gyakuresu" on the contrary?
Only on the moment when they call you ponkotsu,
"Don't forget that I'm the leader around here!"
Scary! Scary! Scary!
But that's the most awful type.
Maybe they'll stop immediately.
But it's not like you really want them to stop right?
-Yes, that's right.
We're actually on good terms.
So you guys are in good terms
If I could just become a bit more respectable,
Reika-chan, do you have an assistant person or something like that?
Ikoma Rina.
Ah, Ikoma-chan?
She looks really proper and reliable!
-Yeah.
Ikoma's the one who pays attention on some things on my part.
Isn't that nice.
On the title call, you're the one who has to announce it right?
-Yes
You can just let Ikoma-chan handle that.
Make Ikoma-chan say all of it,
Only if you made a mistake,
since you're the leader and they call you ponkotsu
Push all of it to Ikoma-chan,
and if Ikoma-chan stutters,
"Hey that's not good, do it more properly!"
But if I did that, my position in the group will lose all of its meaning
It's okay, it's okay.
It's just to warn them.
Kikuchi's been teaching her nothing but horrible wrongdoings
A statement that would make impact!
Eh~
During our circle formation, were supposed to do something
But on times like that, as the captain
I have to say something to wrap it all up,
Ah! That kind of thing!
-Yes
Well I'm doing my best, but it just doesn't work.
Like for example, today all of us are noisy and all over the place
I want something I could say to them with a loud voice to conclude things,
that would get them "Huh? Reika, you're really fired up today."
They're underestimating you!
Like when you did your best, they'll be like "You're too pumped up!"
-Yes, that's right.
Something like, "What's up with you today?"
By the way, how do you usually do it?
Then for example, we're on the circle formation
Onegaishimasu!
The venue for today is very large,
and I believe there are many people among the audience besides our fans,
But, in order to fire up those people also, everyone let's do our best!
Uhm, what do you mean by "people among the audience besides our fans"?
Annoying members
Look, it's like an event where other archists will also be performing
[She mispronounced "Artist" with "Archist"]
"Archist", do you mean "Artist?"
It's called Artist.
Ah! This isn't good!
-This hopeless
If this was the leader, I'd definitely go boycott!
I'd rather follow Ikoma-chan instead.
So here, Kikuchi will show us her methods during her Idoringo days.
Everyone! Since today's the final day,
On the final day,
-Yes
I would like Reika-chan to wrap it all up!
Okay! Reika-chan! Would you please!
Bring up a reason, and push it to the other members
I see!
Go for it!
I often did it in the past,
when it was like "Okay then! Kikuchi! Wrap it up!"
"Since today's the final day, and as a special occasion,
"let's have Ririka-chan wrap it all up!"
You push it to your seniors.
That's dirty!
It seems that this can't be used for reference,
Let's move on to the next question.
On TV shows, how can I get more attention?
Ah! This,
I also want to ask this.
Usually on a talk show,
They say "If you want to say something, please don't hesistate to talk."
Yes, that's true.
-Right?
But when the moment comes, you'll find it hard to speak right?
-Yes! It's difficult!
Like because of the big celebrities, it's really difficult.
On times like that, when someone is speaking
like when they're talking about a certain episode,
If you're somehow related to it and you have something to talk about it,
with a big voice,
N"Ahh! I can relate! I know that!" like that.
Correspond with a big voice in an exaggerated manner
I often see her but maybe she did that a lot!
and the MC will be like "Eh? Relate? Do you have something to share?"
On the opposite, if you don't have anything
"I don't really get what she's saying!"
and if they ask you "Really?" and
"Then do you have a particular episode?"
you'll just have to correspond with a big reaction.
If it was Sanma-san, they'll really ask you!
You know, we did that just now!
We did that just now!
This is a very good thing to do if the MC was Sanma-san.
-I see
The next question is,
What are the means to get along with your co-actors?
I'm really shy around people!
When I interact with them, there's this wall
Then give us back the time we spent so far!
It's not like that!
Really?
Indeed
Like for today, you came to this show right?
But I, myself can't really open up completely.
On this special occasion, let's change the setting and have an actual practice.
Okay then, for example we're on a music program
and we're all from different groups.
Then, I'll go with Sekaowa.
Sekaowa - SEKAI NO OWARI/ A famous japanese band
Shiori-chan.
No, you're Saori-chan.
Okay then, I'm Yuzu.
2 people per 1 person?
What the heck is this?
Thanks for your hard work.
Your performance today was very splendid!
Thank you very much!
There are many among the members who really like you guys.
Eh? We're happy to hear that.
It was a really good harmony!
Wait a minute,
Isn't she looking down on us from above
Yeah, that's right.
The arrogant gaze from above
They're Yuzu!
It was a really good harmony!
That was really damn cheeky!
The next question is,
How to obtain more laughs on her only one-shot gag
You look like you're not much into gags.
-Yeah, you look like you don't do these things.
Actually I have one.
Is it okay?
Can you show us that gag?
Is it alright?
-Yes.
Hoppu, Steppu, kara no Hoippu!
Thank you very much for flunking every time.
I always get responses where they don't even say a thing,
If I could just get nice responses, It would've made me happy doing it.
In regards to this, their suggestion will be...
"Hey! Respond to me! Respond to me!"
Let's try using that one!
Hey! Respond to me! Respond to me!
When it becomes completely silent,
Let's try using that one,
Hoppu, Steppu, kara no Hoippu!
Wait! Hey! Respond to me! Respond to me!
Ah! That was good!
Isn't that great?
It was really great, you can get laughs from that.
You can pressure the respondents also.
Just like that, the enjoyable moments have passed.
The Idol's gathering is also about to end"
You somehow probably had a gasp of how I usually am
From now on, I would want you to see my points of improvement.
In the end, it's how you want to be right?
Do you have a goal in mind like an idol that you wanna be?
None.
So it was not us!
In the end, still ponkotsu
Atleast choose one between us!
She didn't even hesistate to reply "none" to that question!
We had our expectations just for you to know!
I really learned a lot!
- Sakurai Reika
About today's segment, was it really alright with us?
I'm really happy that you came.
Well, anyone would've came.
Nogizaka Kouji Chuu!
We have now started! This is Nogizaka Kouji Chuu!
These are the members in the studio for today!
Onegaishimasu!
So this time, it was Sakurai's segment.
Those two were quite opposites from Sakurai.
-Yes, that's true.
It was really a surprise for me.
I didn't expect that they'll be listening to my request.
But the things like, "I know that!
Isn't that good?
I've thought of using that.
But the image of you saying that just doesn't fit.
-Ah~ Yes, that's right.
Can you do that?
-Yeah, you'll have to say it.
Yes, that's right.
Then if it gets completely silent,
you'll say "Respond to me! Respond to me!"
You can also use that!
Yeah! That's how you use that!
But like on that circle formation you were talking about ,
Do they usually make fun of you? Underestimate you?
"What with you? Aren't you pumped up?"
"What with her? She's fired up! This idiot"
So that's what you're talking about
Well that one just now was just exaggeration,
Good at Hyperboles
How about doing "Fighting Spirit! Fighting Spirit! Fighting Spirit!"
Here comes that pumped up teacher again!
You'll have to do that,
When they say "Aren't you pumped up?" then you'll be like
"Fighting Spirit! Fighting Spirit! Fighting Spirit!"
"Teamwork! Teamwork! Rio! Rio! Rio!"
It's not like they're aiming for the olympics.
Himura-san's willing to do anything he's told to.
That's right. Just say it even if you don't know what it is.
Into that world.
So first of all, I'll just have to say something right?
-Yes
Like for example in your lives, when you're fired up
"What's the matter? You're really pumped up today"
Slow! Slow! Slow! That's so slow!
That's so slow just now! You'll be too late!
If Himura's there he's gonna crash on that moment!
I'll steal that moment of yours!
Why the heck are you there?
For some reason, Himura also at the stage
Why are there on Nogizaka's live?
I'll take that moment!
You get these things?
Waa! I'm so excited!
Poor-skilled
Why do you sound like an onee!?
Yeah that's right, that's how onees are like.
"No way" or "I know", Can you say that?
No way, I know
No waaay
-so that's right
Wait, wait.
Why are you trying to teach her to be an onee?
Onee Training?
No waay, No waay. Whaat!?
Cuuute, Amaazing, No waaay
And just now you look like you're alone
So you can drag the person beside you.
Yeah! You can do that!
Hey, you know that? you know it right?
Got dragged into it
you can relate right? you know that?
And like that they're gonna draw away
They're drawing away.
Yeah, that's how it usually is.
The customers they pull goes like "charin" that's how the money goes in.
You can say "charin" afterwards.
One charin, got in!
Thank you very much! ~
Vulgar! Vulgar!
Vulgar! Vulgar! That's too vulgar!
That can't be helped.
You don't really have to retort.
Just repeat the words they say.
Then, let's try it.
Himura-san's gonna talk about his recent trip.
-Yes
Listen to this.
Listen to what!?
Too impatient
Wait wait that's too soon!
Just do a normal conversation.
Too soon. Too soon.
One more time.
The other day,
I went to Guam.
Ah! You went to Guam!?
-Yes, that's right.
I was open for 2 days, so I figured going.
Ah! You were open for 2 days!?
Yeah, yeah.
So interesting,
Nice,nice!
As expected, it was really warm.
Yes, it's really warm there on Guam!
and the food was really delicious.
-Ah! I agree!
Even the sea was really beautiful.
-It's really beautiful there!
You can stare at it while going easy.
Ah! That's so wonderful!
and like I even played Golf.
-Ah! Golf!
But it rained while I was playing.
-Eh!? It started to rain? Too bad!
It was really terrible.
But I want to go again sometime.
Ah! That's so fantastic!
Nice! Nice!
That was good!
-That was great!
So you can do it after all.
I was doing my best to keep up.
But you'll get used to it.
-Yeah, you'll just get used to it.
I don't even remember any of the details just now.
Priorities Backwards
TamamiCheeks.blogspot.com
Translator:Mr.Reika
Typeset:Tamami-chan
Tumblr: Horistardust.tumblr.com
Twitter: @Mr_Sakurai46
A survey was also held to the other members except Sakurai
who wants to showcase their one-shot gags
First up is Akimoto
What does she want to showcase?
The thing I want to showcase is,
after said something, at the end
I'll say "Manatsu ni" and everyone will say "Muchuu"
Ah. That's easy.
Okay.
Here I come!
Chuu, Chuu, Chuu
Kore de minna mo
Manatsu ni
Muchuu.
Huh? Does everyone hate you?
The members doesn't want to do it.
"Respond to it! Respond to it!"
She's using your move!
Reika! Reika! She's using it!
That would be a problem.
Say it louder.
Use the rhythm earlier.
That's a problem! That's a problem!
You can't do that.
and the charin, the charin.
I received the charin!
She's becoming more of a guest entertainer!
But that was good.
This is bad, this is bad.
What about the thing that I did?
What was that again?
Sorry about that.
Next up,
What does Kawago want to showcase?
The thing I have in mind is this "Kawago chop",
Kawago chop?
It's called Kawago chop.
I've been doing it for a year now.
So you're already doing it?
Yes, that's right.
But it just won't become popular.
How do you do it?
At the Handshake event,
When a person comes for the first time,
I always do it to grab their hearts.
Eh?
Himura-san, can you..
Can I see that?
-Is that okay?
Let's do it in an actual Handshake event setting,
"Kawago Chop", What will it be?
Pleased to meet you.
How do you do?
Do you like strong things?
What?
Kawago Chop!
Bye bye! Later!
Meaning Unknown
Eh?
Wait, wait.
What was that?
Do you do this all the time?
Yes, I always do this.
Upon saying, pleased to meet you
I always do the chop before they even say anything,
and just let them leave like that
Eh?
So, what do you want to do?
I wanna be able to use it during shows too.
During shows, you want to do that chop of yours?
-Yes
The Higuchi cutter was made by a woman too right?
Higuchi cutter, that one was very unexpected.
Higuchi cutter.
Yeah, it's also used at the introduction.
Ah, that's right.
For example, like today when you guys are introduced
There's that short interval right?
When everyone is waving their hands,
Yeah, maybe they're also figuring out what to do.
This is where you should use it, right?
-Maybe, you'll...
Want to try it one time?
-Yes, I'll do it.
These are the members in the studio for today!
Kawago Chop!,Kawago Chop!!
Kawago Chop! Kawago Chop!
You'll probably get scolded by the manager.
Sermon Afterwards
"What are you doing?"
Next up,
The thing that Hori wants to showcase is?
I really love Ghibli movie
Ah, that witch thing.
And since it's summer now,
"Mimi wo sumaseba",english title
"Whisper of the Heart" From Ghibli studio"
I always watch "Mimi wo sumaseba",
Yeah, that's good.
-Very nice
I can do an imitation of that.
Ah! You can do that?
-Yes
Mimi wo sumaseba" Imitation", What will it be?
Ah! The book!
"Is this your book?"
"Here you go, Tsukishima Shizuku."
My name..
Ah! My library card!
"I think you should stop reading that concrete road"
You peeked!
What an awful person!
Awful person! Awful person!
What an awful person! Awful person! Awful person!
Awful person!
"You'd better stop reading that concrete road"
With what!?
That's it.
That's amazing!
That was great!
So you want to do this at the Handshake event?
Not really.
But you wanted to popularize this right?
-That's right. If I could do this with everyone...
at the Handshake event,
With everyone?
How about doing that "Awful person! Awful person!",
Can we see that?
Let's try that a bit.
[Mimi wo sumaseba]
"Handshake event version"
Then, ready.. start!
Awful person! Awful person! Awful person!
Awful person! Awful person!
Awful person!
That was bad!
He looked so pitiful!
That was the worst.
You'll lose fans if you did that!
She'll lose fans if you did that!
But this is the "Mimi wo Sumaseba"
But she just badmouthed the moment I entered,
"Awful person, Awful person" all along.
She didn't even let me talk.
After this, Takayama's gag intensifies!
Next up, the thing that Takayama wants to showcase is?
It's not like I want to popularize this gag, but
I have this dajare that you've never heard before.
Dajare - Feeble or Lame joke / Bad pun
You frequently hear the futon dajare right?
Yeah, pretty often.
-Yes, that dajare.
But recently, I developed this dajare that you've probably never heard before.
Seriously? I want to see it.
But it's not like I want to popularize this.
It's just that I want to warm it up.
But at some place..For example, announcements..
-Yes,
No, things like that you just want to warm up
Someday, at some point it'll get popular.
Is that so?
So, today will be the day you'll reveal it
Until now,Only one person heard this before.
I only showed this once to Naa-chan.
So Nishino, you already know this?
We talked about it before.
During that time when you heard, how was it?
I thought it was amazing.
Nishino approves
"A dajare you've never heard before", What will it be?
3..2..1.. Go!
Word play - "Mousho" rhymes with "Mou shouganai"
"There's nothing you can do about this fierce heat."
Well done!
Wait a minute!
Good point!
Good point!!
Maybe I revealed it at the wrong place.
Not at all. It was good.
That was great.
No, no. Not at all.
Takayama, how about using that "Good point!" just now.
Isn't that good?
Ah, that is very well accepted even on the fans.
Ain't that great?
It's convinient.
The other day, when we were filming for a drama
there were some fans on the area.
When I was about to take a break,
The fans, three of them were like, "Good point!"
Ah! Isn't that awesome?
It's when I was taking a break.. the three of them..
It's make your happy,right?
On lives, "Takayama here!"
when you introduce yourself, they will all say
"Good point!
Ehh? That's amazing!
I want to do it at the Jingu!
-Do it! Do it!
and probably it's gonna be hot at the jingu.
Ah! Is that so!
Note: The word play earlier
"Mousho wa mou shouganai!"
Good point!!
That's great!
-Isn't this good?
Want to try it one time?
I'm really happy.
-Yes
[From Mousho "Heatwave" Dajare] to the ["Good point!"]
It's really hot today, isn't it?
"Mousho wa?"
"Mou shouganai!"
"Takayama here!"
"Good point!"
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
After this,
"The second generation, Kitano boasts on his superhuman strength!"
Second Generation: Deep Investigation
Who is the person for today?
Today is the investigation for Kitano Hinako!
Ah, you already opened it.
You opened it the same time you said the name.
Ah. I'm really sorry.
One more take please.
-It's okay. It's okay.
It's alright Hori.
According to Hori,
Kitano Hinako's charm point is that she's the strongest in Nogizaka.
So today, we will have her bend a fry pan.
Bend a fry pan?
Bend it?
Can you really do that?
Fry pan bending.
Go ahead.
Here I go!
Oh oh oh!~
Ohh!
Amazing! It bent!
You really bent it's shape!
Furthermore,
She won't lose to anyone when it comes to 'Tug of war' using towel.
What's that?
What do you mean?
Then, anyone who is confident...
Ah, one on one battle pulling from both sides?
You're saying you won't lose?
-Yes, I won't lose.
-Really?
Wow, you've got some strength there.
Like, you can beat everyone here?
Yeah, let's do that.
So with that,
She challenges to beat everyone on "Tug of war" using towel!
First up, Ikoma!
Ready.. Start!
Oh!
Already?
It's over.
Next one, next one.
Seriously, she was strong
That's some amazing strength!
Second person, Nishino.
Ready.. Start!
Kawaii!
That was cute!
Next one! Keep going!
Third person, Kawago.
Ready.. Start!
Oohh!~
Eh?
Huh?
Kawago won!
Battle ends on the 3rd person
Eh?
Kawago won.
One more time please!
Eh?
What's the difference?
One more time.
-What was wrong?
That now was just a bit..
It was different?
-Yes
What was that?
-Is there a technique to this?
Since you're the one being investigated this time,
Only this once.
-There's no last chance, okay?
Ready...Go!
Let's see!
Kawago, you're strong!
Superhuman Strength Title goes to Kawago
Kawago, you're strong.
Yeah. She's really strong.
That's great, Kawago.
You lost.
-Yes, I lost.
It's over.
What now?
Then Kawago gets to beat them all now?
That would be interesting.
Manatsu Zenkoku Tour 2015 is still ongoing!
The next ones from Sendai, Nagoya, and Hiroshima is,
Fukuoka, Osaka and Tokyo!
TamamiCheeks.blogspot.com
Translator:Mr.Reika
Timming/Typeset:Tamami-chan
Tumblr: Horistardust.tumblr.com
Twitter: @Mr_Sakurai46
The Summer hype is not yet over!