m 0 0 l 0 27 l 2 27 l 2 0 l 0 0 m 2 0 l -4 0 l -4 6 l 16 6 l 16 4 l -2 4 l -2 2 l 0 2 m 2 2 m 16 0 l 16 27 l 18 27 l 18 -1 l 16 -1 m 22 0 l 22 0 l 24 0 l 24 11 l 19 11 l 19 9 l 22 9 l 22 2 l 15 2 l 15 0 m 6 18 l 6 12 l 12 12 l 12 14 l 8 14 l 8 18 l 6 18 m 12 18 l 12 20 l 6 20 l 6 18 l 10 18 l 10 14 l 12 14 l 12 18 m 5 7 l 8 9 l 7 10 l 4 8 l 5 7 m 10 9 l 10 9 l 13 7 l 14 8 l 11 10 l 10 9 m 3 24 b 3 24 3 23 3 23 b 7 21 11 21 15 23 b 15 23 15 25 15 25 b 11 23 7 23 3 25
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
DEKIRU TV with Maaya!
DEKIRU = I can do it
[Ikoma]: What is this?
In this segment, Maaya will show many things she can do.
On Dekiru TV with Maaya this time,
we have guests who will assist me. Here they are!
[Ikoma]: I wonder who's the guest
Hello everyone!
CHUUEI
TAKIUE SHINICHIRO
GUEST: NAGAREBOSHI
[Ikoma}: Eehh!! Good!
We're Nagareboshi, Takiue and
- Chuuei!
That guy looks weak~
and I'm Chuuei~
Banana-san~
ROPE JUMPING SKILL
DEKIRU TV
with
MAAYA
The first thing Wada Maaya will exhibit
is rope jumping.
How will you do it?
- How?
Cross jumping twice.
- Cross jumping twice?
[Matsumura]: What? Amazing!
Jumping like this?
- Yes. Like that, but the twice version.
CROSS JUMPING TWICE
DEKIRU TV
with
MAAYA
So let's watch the cross jumping twice!
[Shitara]: Wow, great! [Marika]: Great!
Woah, impressive!
- She can do it!
Something fell there. It's like...
[Matsumura]: Amazing!
FALLEN LIP BALM
[Ikoma]: Lip balm?
There's something there. Your lip balm!
It's even fell!
- Yes!
But it was impressive!
- It sure was.
So you actually can do it?
- Yes!
KARATE SKILL
DEKIRU TV
with
MAAYA
The next thing she will do,
She did this for seven years,
KARATE!
I've trained since I was five
until twelve.
That was quite some time.
- Yup!
This is like my specialty.
Here she has a challenge to knock
the paper balloon off
held by Chuuei who's scared
of high kick technique.
And here we go, please!
Yaa!!!
Aaaaa!!! Incredible! Perfect!
Aaaaa!!! Amazing!
[Takayama & Matsumura]: Incredible!
[Ikoma]: Her legs can reach there.
PIANO SKILL
DEKIRU TV
with
MAAYA
DEKIRU TV with Wada Maaya.
Next, PIANO!
[Shitara]: You can play piano?
You play piano?
- Yeah!
How long have you been doing this?
- Since I was two until thirteen!
You invested quite amount of time!
You surely practiced hard all those time, huh?
Of course!
- I see.
[Shitara]: Quite some time!
You're quite busy, huh?
Yes, that's true. After school,
I practiced immediately.
[Shitara]: Routinely?
But in Nogizaka alone, is there someone
who good at piano? - Of course there is!
I see.
- Because I have never been talked about,
today I want to show it.
- Understood!
But there's a particularity
in her piano play!
I can only play the intro.
Only the intro? - Yes!
Eh? You can't do the whole song?
INTRO SPECIALIST
SONG'S INTRO
[BUTTERFLY] - KIMURA KAERA
DEKIRU TV
with
MAAYA
Let's see how this Intro Specialist Pianist
plays Butterfly.
[Chiharu]: This is good!
[BUTTERFLY] - KIMURA KAERA
Go ahead!
[Himura]: Very good! [Shitara]: Good!
[Shitara]: Oh, very nice!
Bbbaaa... no, no, wait a sec!
JUST UP TO THIS PART
[Shitara]: Why? Why didn't you continue?
- Why was that kinda unclear?
You're finished?
- I can't play the whole song!
[Himura]: This is interesting!
Were you not interested in continuing?
- Just a little bit more and you're going into the lyric.
[Shitara]: He was going to say "Butterfly.."
You're bored with what comes next?
- Yeah, that's right!
SONG'S INTRO
[HANAMIZUKI] - HITOTO YO
DEKIRU TV
with
MAAYA
Then, let us hear the intro from next song.
[Himura]: Oh, this is good.
[HANAMIZUKI] - HITOTO YO
[Shitara]: Oh, she's great!
Nice. Very nice.
[Shitara]: Very nice!
[Shitara]: Oh, amazing!
Hu~
Eh? Eh?
WAS ABOUT TO SINGING
Don't make the "It's over!" expression like that.
That's scary!  - I can only play the intro.
[Himura]: Interesting
So whatever it is, you can only play intro.
Yes! Just the intro.
- Just the intro? - Yup!
[Shitara]: Eehh??!!
[Chiharu]: Impressive!
A genius who can cure
stress with piano.
You surely can play "Kimi no Na wa Kibou".
"Kimi no Na wa Kibou"?
[Himura]: This is good
[KIMI NO NA WA KIBOU] - NOGIZAKA46
Do it!
- You must know the melody!
Can you do it?
[Himura]: Surely she can do this!
[Himura]: Can you?
THE HOPE IS GONE
[Shitara]: That's different!
Really different from the beginning.
F
A
I
L
MENTION 15 NAMES OF SHOGUN TOKUGAWA
DEKIRU TV
with
MAAYA
Shogun Tokugawa was a military leadership system, built by Tokugawa Ieyasu around 1603-1868. (Wikipedia)
Next challenge, a skill to
mention 15 names of Shogun Tokugawa.
[Himura]: Extraordinary! [Akimoto]: Amazing!
IEYASU
HIDETADA
Here we go. Can we start this?
- Alright! - Please!
Ieyasu, Hidetada,...
IEMITSU
Ieyasu, Hidetada, Iemitsu,...
IEYASU
HIDETADA
IETSUNA
Ietsune, tsune, eh, tsuna?
"Ito" in its left "Oka",
HIDETADA
IEMITSU
IETSUNA
TSUNAYOSHI
Unexpected, so you can't read the kanji?
- You remember it from the characters? - Yes!
Next, "Tsuna", like that,
then there's "Yoshi",
IEMITSU
IETSUNA
TSUNAYOSHI
IENOBU
"Tsunayoshi", then "Ie..."
[Shitara]: If you use Tsuna here, it's gonna be Tsunaie right?
Only "Tsunayoshi" has the "Tsuna".
Come on, try harder!
"Ie..." what?
It's almost come out here (head)!
- Almost remember?
She pointed here, usually it's "It's almost
come out (throat)!"
IT'S FROM THE MOUTH
This is impressive because it came from her head!
"Ie.." - Yeah?
Ah, yes! It has to be "Ie...Ieyoro"!
YORO?
It's "Ieyoro"!
- "Ieyoro"? Like "Yoro" in "Yoroshiku"?
[Himura]: Ieyoro?!
[Shitara]: Ieyoro from Yoroshiku?
IETSUNA
TSUNAYOSHI
IENOBU
IETSUGU
You remember "Ieyoro" from that?
- "Ieyoro", then...
Eh? This is a different "Yoro" with "Yoroshiku",
IE YORO
IE NOBU
The character is different, you read it wrong!
[Shitara]: It is similar!
Then "Ie" with "Kei" from "Chuukei (connecting)".
- What a unique way of remembering!
[Shitara]: Huh? Why was that so messy?
TSUNAYOSHI
IENOBU
IETSUGU
YOSHIMUNE
- Really! - So, his name...
[Takayama]: Amazing!
[Nanamin]: She remembers using that!
"Ie...kei"? - Clearly not!
Ah "Iekei", - "Ietsugu".
"Ietsugu",
- "Iekei" is a ramen shop!
A HEAVY FOOD
Keep going!
- "Yoshimune"
[Shitara]: Iekei!
IENOBU
IETSUGU
YOSHIMUNE
IESHIGE
"Ieomo"
[Shitara]: Ieomo?!
That "Ieshige"!
- "Ieshige",
IETSUGU
YOSHIMUNE
IESHIGE
IEHARU
[Matsumura]: Amazing!
Because "Ie(house)" "Omo(broken)" so "Naoru (fixed)".
Ah, "Ienaoru".
"Ie..Nao"  - "Ieharu"
"Ieharu",
[Himura]: Great!
[Shitara]: She can imagine it like that
YOSHIMUNE
IESHIGE
IEHARU
IENARI
"Ie" with "Sai" like in "Saitou"
This one? - Combined?
Right.
So "Ienari"
- "Ienari",
IESHIGE
IEHARU
IENARI
IEYOSHI
"Ie.." with... Ah! That, that, that!
- Amazing, she only remembers "Ie" and
then connects it from there.
He had a poor life, but... Ah!
Hold on!
- He went to Keiou University! Means "Ie"
plus "Kei" from "Keiou".
SCHOOL AND WORK
Hold on, something's wrong.
- Something's wrong!
Please don't change the history
of Tokugawa Clan as you wish!
"Even he was poor, but he went to
Keiou University", Shogun like that didn't exist!
A SUPER POOR SHOGUN
- It's like that so I remember.
So that's why he went to Keiou University.
"Ie..", with "Kei" like in "Keiou",
That "Ieyoshi"!
- "Ieyoshi",
IEHARU
IENARI
IEYOSHI
IESADA
And then...
Umm...
Then the character in "Sadamaru (assigned)".
- That's "Iesada"! - "Iesada",
[Himura]: I see!
IENARI
IEYOSHI
IESADA
IEMOCHI
Then "Iemochi",
IEYOSHI
IESADA
IEMOCHI
YOSHINOBU
This one guy was amazing,
a guy with broken teeth.
- Last one!
TOKUGAWA IEMOCHI
m 0 0 l 0 0 l 17 0 l 17 7 l 0 7
He said to be dead in his twenties,
because he loved sweets which made his teeth broken.
Eh? Is there any some kind of information like that?
We learned lot of new things about these leaders.
[Ikoma]: Now that's a new trivia!
You're maniac with this thing.
This feels like she's giving them a curse or something.
Go on!
- And lastly, because he successfully accepted into Keiou,
he "Yorokobu (thankful)!
And how do you call him?
- "Kei..yoro"!
[YORO] AGAIN
That's like "Keidoro (cop & thief)".
- There was no such man in Shitoku history.
[Shitara]: She said she can!
[Himura]: What's with this girl?
So you made up a story
to be able to remember it easier?
Exactly, with story...
- Like "Ie (house)" that "Omo (broken)",
"Ie (house)" that "Omo (broken)",
YOSHIMUNE
IESHIGE
IEHARU
Since it's broken, then it has to be "Nao (fix)",
so "Ienao".
YOSHIMUNE
IESHIGE
IEHARU
IENARI
And someone who lives there is
Saito-san, so I took "Sai".
[Takayama]: Ah, good!
[Matsumura]: Amazing!
IESHIGE
IEHARU
IENARI
IEYOSHI
Then since he's poor,
I thought his parents advised him
to study harder,
so he may went to Keiou University, so "Iekei".
IEHARU
IENARI
IEYOSHI
IESADA
And finally he's "Sadamatta (decided)" to be accepted
into Keiou.
IENARI
IEYOSHI
IESADA
IEMOCHI
Decided to be accepted succesfully,
"Sadamatta" - "Sadamatta"?
Then "Shi", which one is that?
- Maybe it's from "Shikeru (rich)",
"Shi..."
- That, "Iemochi"
IEYOSHI
IESADA
IEMOCHI
YOSHINOBU
Right, after it's been decided, here I can only
remember about broken teeth.
UNRELATED STORY
Why that?
- I guess since it was his habit.
[Himura]: Why?
[Shitara]: Why did she think about this?
Suddenly the story takes a different turn here.
- Yes, and lastly...
[Himura]: Menarik sekali, ya!
IESADA
IEMOCHI
YOSHINOBU
"Yoro..." that, since he got accepted by Keiou,
he's "Yorokobu (thankful)". - I see.
F
A
I
L
Then she also sharpened pencil
beautifully with scissor.
[Ikoma]: She can do this too!
[Himura]: Can she?
But this thing is not suited
for the segment on this TV.
[Shitara]: This is bad
[Himura]: Why do we have to look at this?
Gindango = food made from rice flour,
greased with sauce from Gingko peanut
There's a moment where she ate Gindango with
a very delicious way more than anyone.
Since it's not that interesting to be shown in front of camera,
then this segment is over!
NOGIZAKA KOUJICHUU
Alright Nogizaka Koujichuu is starting,
BANANAMAN
HIMURA YUKI
SHITARA OSAMU
and here are the present members today.
- Onegaishimasu~
This time it's Wada.
- Yes, Onegaishimasu.
WADA MAAYA
This time Wada did a
"I can do it if I'm serious" segment? - Yes!
What was that?
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
SUPER UNIQUE VTR
Why were you that relaxed?
It's like, since everyone think
I can't do it
I see.
- I want to say "I can't do it" with that VTR...
The way you remember Tokugawa names was
very interesting. - Ah, really?
The way to remember like that,
did you make it yourself?
I made my own story
to be able to remember all those names.
Then there's also piano.
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
JUST THE INTRO
What was that?
It was actually pretty good, but it's only the intro.
- Actually you can, why wouldn't you continue?
When you're about to finish you can, like, slow it down.
- Ah right. There's that way.
Like that.
- Right, right. "I am done~~!",
you can say it to anyone.
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
READY TO GET LAUGHED AT
You also played slowly.
Today too...
- Yes!
We will do a lot of things
related to this topic. - Okay!
Himura-san, - Yes!
Please!
If we're serious, don't you think we can do it?
NOGIZAKA CHALLENGE!
No matter who wants to do it or not
We will find out, are the members
can they do it if they're serious?
The said members will do
one challenge without practice beforehand in the studio!
IKOMA RINA
If you're serious, you can do it!
First turn, Ikoma.
NOGIZAKA CHALLENGE
IF WE'RE SERIOUS, WE CAN DO IT FOR SURE
What Ikoma wants to do is...
Perhaps I can do Saka Agari now...
Saka Agari = an exercise to lift our body
using horizontal bar
THINGS THAT SURELY CAN BE DONE IF WE'RE SERIOUS
SAKA AGARI
Couldn't you do it before?
- I never could.
Not even once?
- Not even once.
But since I entered Nogizaka, maybe
my muscles are defined a little bit.
That's why maybe I can do
Saka Agari.
IKOMA RINA
Can she successfully do it?
Here's the Saka Agari challenge.
SAKA AGARI CHALLENGE
Give your best!
- Do you believe you can do it?
Yosh!
- Do you wear pants under your skirt?
Ah, she just lifted it like that.
- Don't worry, everything is safe.
There you go, the full spirited Ikoma.
Ready? - Yes!
- You only have once chance.
"If you're serious, you can do it", one time challenge
for Ikoma, Saka Agari. Please start!
Aaa~~!!!
Careful! Careful!
Unexpectedly Ikoma let her hands
go when she did Saka Agari.
Something every ten years old kids
can do, but she...
Okay, finished~
Why did you let your hand go?
Yeah why?
- You clearly can't do it!
Ikoma can't do it at all!
Wada can you do Saka Agari?
- I can!
Really? - Yes!
- Alright, this you surely can do it. - Yes.
Can you?
- I don't know. Yeah probably.
WADA MAAYA
Sudden challenge today, Wada will do
Saka Agari challenge once too.
SAKA AGARI CHALLENGE
- There you go, Maaya!
Wada, Saka Agari challenge once.
- I'll start!
Start? You okay?
- Here I go!
Okay!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
SPASTIC FEET UP IN THE AIR
You can't do it!
- Feet movement like that
is not how you do Saka Agari!
Try to not move your legs.
- Once more! Here I go!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
CAN'T STOP
Eh? You can't stop?
- Again!
So I can't do it.
Can you?
- I can't.
Could you do it before?
- I did it few times but...
I was using that climbing board.
No, of course you could do it with that.
If you wanna use that...
You can just use
those people in black.
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
STEPPING ON STAFF
That's not allowed!
CONVERTED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
If we're talking about bar like this,
of course there's Higuchi. - Right!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
HORIZONTAL BAR GIRL
Yeah.
- Higuchi surely spins forward.
Spins forward with my feet.  - That's your specialty?
Yes!  - I wanna see!
What's with this girl?
You were quite scary when you did it!
- Scary?
HIGUCHI  HINA
Thing Higuchi can do with horizontal bar.
Her specialty, spinning forward with her feet!
SPIN FORWARD WITH HER FEET CHALLENGE
She went forward smiling!
Oh! Oh!
Oh, that's good!
- So quick. Great! She can do this!
- Here I go!
Careful!
Beware, do not let your hands go.
- Yes!
Alright, Higuchi will spin with her feet. Start!
This is some scary stuff!
-  No! - She's pushing herself!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
SO MUCH EFFORT
Almost there!
- Stop!
Come on, pull! Ah...
Wait, don't you think she couldn't do it?
That was scary.
Ah, so frightening! That's like a ghost or something!
So scary!
- Why... when she lifted her body up
she looked like she's desperate.
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
GHOST PHOTO?
You looked like she's in pain there.
- You couldn't keep spinning?
It was the best I can do.
It was the best?
- Yup!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
A PERFECT PERFORMANCE
So this is what you can do?  - Yeah!
- Scary, she transformed when she lift her body.
Can you do Saka Agari? - I can!
- She looks confident.
Eegh!
- That's scary, scary!
UEISHOGGH
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
SUPER UNIQUE STYLE
That was dreadful.
Eh? That was not like Higuchi's character.
She said "Naghh-yat!" just now.
Scary~!
- Like "Wazzat" . - I'm done!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
EXAGGERATING
I can do "Kururinpa" too.  - I thought you have to wear hat
to do "Kururinpa" - Not that Kururinpa!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
UESHIMA RYUHEI
Just like what Ueshima-san does?
That one?
Ueshima Ryuhei = a member of Dachou Club trio
What is "Kururinpa"?
Please elaborate!
- Try to do it, this is going to be scary!
Scary, scary, what are you doing?
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
MYSTERIOUS MOVE
- That's so scary!
Hold on! That's dangerous!
Please explain it first how you do it!
Explain it first! Just one explanation!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
CONTINUES WITHOUT TALKS
No, no, why would you do it immediately?
That's scary!
- Why did you go Kururinpa just like that!
What are you doing?
Don't let your hands go!
What will she do?
- Are you okay? Can you do it?
How is it?
- Please say "Kururinpa".
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
HAZY INFORMATION
Nope, nope. Is this fine?
That's dangerous!
- She's going to do it again!  - Please be careful!
It's gonna be ok as long as you
don't let your hands go. - Yes!
Alright, here's "Kururinpa"!
Kururin...
- Eh?
AAAHH!!!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
FINALLY FELL...
For real? That's dangerous!
- How scary! Enough please!
Why...?
STOP,DON'T DO IT AS YOU WISH!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
NOT ALLOWED TO PLAY ANYMORE
Careful! It's enough!
What were you doing?
- What's a Kururinpa even?
How does one do Kururinpa correctly?
How? Oh please stop!
- From here, then to back.
Your hands here, then sit.
- That's what you did! - Yeah!
- So she did it?
So you could do it just now?
Basically it was like that?  - Yes!
Ah! Amazing!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
SUCCEED, BUT...
Is there no one here can keep spinning like that?
I can spin sideways, you know.
Scary!
- That's unquestionably dangerous! Pretty dangerous!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
LOOKED DANGEROUS
Yeah!
- No, please don't do it!
I can spin like this.
- Just one spin?
One? No, I can keep spinning!  - What a lie!
Really!  - You ready?
MATSUMURA  SAYURI
Now let us see, the infinity sideways spinning!
SIDEWAY SPINNING CHALLENGE
Side spinning technique.
- Yeah, same method.
Ah, guess I can do this.
Watch out!
What kind of technique is this? - From here...
- That?  - From there?
Alright Matsumura, just don't
release your grip.  - Yes!  - Go ahead!
No, no, no!
- Why?
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
CAN'T FIGHT THE GRAVITY
Stop, stop, stop! Please stop!
Stop!
- I wonder.
You looked like a pig being spitroasted just now!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
NAME OF THE TECHNIQUE [PIG SPITROAST]
Done~~!!!
- Was that a pig spitroast technique?
That was over the top!
You clearly couldn't do it!
- Apparently yeah!  - Why?
YOU CAN'T JUST HAVE A SHOWTIME LIKE THAT!
DON'T GO "AH, THIS SEEMS GOOD FOR TV"!
- Ah, this is interesting!
SAITO  CHIHARU
Next member who will receive a challenge,
Saito Chiharu.
NOGIZAKA CHALLENGE
IF WE'RE SERIOUS, WE CAN DO IT FOR SURE
What can you do?
- Rope jumping with my own technique.
THINGS THAT SURELY CAN BE DONE IF WE'RE SERIOUS
HER OWN ROPE JUMPING TRICK
Many members said about their own technique this time.
We saw a lot of original moves today.
- What do you mean by your own technique?
No need to jump.
This is a rope jumping without jumping.
You made this technique yourself?
- Uh huh!
Is there a name for this move?
- No.
Give it then.
Like Saito's technique...
- Okay then.
Happi...
Happi-Tan?
Happi-Tan is good! That's it then!
- Why Happi-Tan?
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
A FULL EXQUISITE NAME
Okay, Happi-Tan.
- Happi-Tan.
Simple, isn't it.
SAITO  CHIHARU
A challenge with her own
technique, Happi-Tan.
HER OWN TRICK CHALLENGE
(HAPPI-TAN)
Eh? Impressive!
That was impressive! - Hold on.
- Great!
Woah, amazing! What is this? Amazing!
What? How did she do it?
What is this? How?
- What is this Happi-Tan?
How do you do that?
- How?
Please do it slowly.
- We want to see the slow version.
- There,
this side.
Then cross, ah, aaahh!!!
- Then you cross it!
Swing the rope at back.
- Back.
I see!
- Right, it's like avoiding it.
She didn't get hit at all!
Match it with the footworks.
And if you do it quickly.
It suits the name.
Amazing!
That was amazing!
Eh? It was unpredictably incredible.
- Really?
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
CAPABILITY APPROVED
That was Happi-Tan.
- Yay!!!  - Great!
Do you think most members here can't do it?
Higuchi can do Happi-Tan too!  - Huh?!
You also can do Happi-Tan?
- This screams danger if she's the one who do it.
HIGUCHI  HINA
Unexpectedly aside from horizontal bar, Higuchi
also has the same rope jumping technique.
DOING SAITOU CHIHARU'S TRICK CHALLENGE
She's dangerous!
Not bad!!!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
OLD HABITS DIE HARD
She did it more recklessly!
- That's like...  - Amazing!
So what was that? Why could you do her technique?
Back when elementary school...
- Happi-Tan? - Did you do it?
On sport festival...
- What's the name?
Happ... something like that...
That was Happi-Tan just now!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
HAPPI-TAN TOO?
In the end, it's still Happi-Tan!
Why Happi-Tan too?
So there are many Happi-Tans.
But the moves are different a little bit.
- Kinda scary.
She was doing it more crudely.
- Perhaps that's what makes her scary!
Even her character seems calm,
but she can do it crudely!
- Yeah that's right.
After this, a tragedy guaranteed to be recorded in history.
The Weirdest Robot Dance.
WAKATSUKI  YUMI
Next, the challenger of
"If you're serious then you can do it", is Wakatsuki.
NOGIZAKA CHALLENGE
IF WE'RE SERIOUS, WE CAN DO IT FOR SURE
I've never done it but
I guess I can do this. - Yes!
- Never?
- Surely you can if you're serious.
So what's that?
- Well...
That is...Robot Dance.
THINGS THAT SURELY CAN BE DONE IF WE'RE SERIOUS
ROBOT DANCE
You seem to have a strong will, but...
Honestly this will be hurt.
Oh, so you wanna do it.
- I know the technique. - Technique?
I've never do this but my dance teacher
always says...   - What does she say?
"Many things to be remembered".
- Many?
WAKATSUKI  YUMI
And here's Robot Dance challenge
accompanied with Taiyou Knock.
ROBOT DANCE CHALLENGE
TAIYOU KNOCK
Alright, please play the music!
Robot Dance?
This?
- This?
Go ahead!
She, she, this...
Wait, wait!
- No, no!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
THERE'S THE TRAGEDY
Please stop the music! - This is embarassing!
- Why? - What?
Was the music wrong?
- The moves are more like this.
Of course since the start position
you couldn't enter properly!
Was that because of no sound? Then you can use
"Gii-gacha, gii-gacha".
- I thought so too.
- Try to say "Gii-gacha".
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
ROBOT VOICE ADVICE
That's because it's robot!
- Since it's robot, it has to be like that.
You shouldn't smile either, because you are a robot.
Please start it by sitting down. Sit down first!
Don't just stand there like a robot.
- Great!
WAKATSUKI  YUMI
The hardest challenge to be a robot
started from sitting down.
BY BECOMING A REAL ROBOT TRIES TO DO A ROBOT DANCE ONCE MORE
Sneeze?
Sneeze.
- Like a sneeze?
It's like Nanamin's sneeze.
- Yeah.
So ordinary!
- Did someone sneeze? - So cold.
Sneeze!
She's not stopping!
WHY DOES IT HAVE TO BE LIKE THIS!
You brought this upon yourself.
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
GETTING HURT ONCE AGAIN
You said you can do it!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
GETTING HURT BECAUSE OF HERSELF
Sinve you said you can.
You did say that right?
- What's that?  - What?
What's a Robot Dance Music?
Like Star Wars' music.
Okay let's make the music.
Wait a sec, that's wrong,
that seems like a wrong person!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
ANOTHER TRAGEDY YET AGAIN
That's dangerous! Like a messed up person!
Why?   - Her face from here like
a very messed up person!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
REALLY NOT CLEAR
Nooo!!!
Can the others do it too?
I can do ASIMO.  - ASIMO?
I can copy its walking manner.
- Really?
That's quite good. That too is a robot.
- Aahh~~!
Ok, ok. Please do it.
Plese you do it! Can you do it?  - Yeah!
- Try to do it!
- Do it now!
Alright, ASIMO's walking manner. Go ahead!
- Its waking manner.
Okay Ikoma, are you going to do it?
Okay she's going to do it now!
Ikoma-san, give your best!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
NOT CLEAR
Alright, Ikoma-san is going to do it!
- Okay, where do you wanna start from? There?  - This!
No, but just now...
- Ikoma-san please prepare yourself!
Please!
- So it's from there first? Go ahead!
Okay Ikoma, so now it's changed from there?
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
STILL NOT CLEAR
Where do you want to start from?
- There?  - But...
IF IT'S NOT HERE, ASIMO CAN'T SHOW ITSELF OFF!
That's enough, please have a seat.
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
ASIMO EXPLODED
Okay, please go back to your seat.
Everyone can be a robot too, right?
- Of course they can.
Himetan, for example. Can you?
- Himetan, do it.  - I can't.
Try to go "Wii-gacha".
- Do "Wii-gacha" then Himetan-Beam.
NAKAMOTO HIMEKA
That means, it's time for Himetan-Robo to make her appearance.
HERE COMES THE HIMETAN ROBOT
Wii~~Gacha~
Her legs were stepping so lightly.
- Not a human's legs?
Ah, nice, very nice.
- So cute.
HIMETAN   BE~AM
What an "amazing" robot.
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
EMBARASSING TRAGEDY
Must be awakened for sure if there's a robot like this.
Tentu sajalah,
You did it!  - I wonder why after their robot acts
are done, they just stared here?
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
THE REGRET OF AN EMBARASSED ROBOT
Why?
- Your stares are scary.
Everyone did it.
Wakatsuki was also a target!
Why?
- Hashimoto, you can be a robot too, right?
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
THE ROBOT TERROR BEGINS
Now that surely you can.
- Can you?
Nanamin can be a flexible robot.
She's good at that.  - Ah, you did this before?
For example in rehearsal.
- You've done this before!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
EXPERIENCED
Actually, you can do it!
- Yeah!
HASHIMOTO NANAMI
HASIMO, a better robot compared to
ASIMO will appear.
HERE COMES THE HASIMO
Wiii-Gacha...
Ehegh!
Gasha~
Ga~Sha!
This is a one sorrowful robot.
- She's so sad.
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
GOES TO CRYING MODE?
She's also desperate.  - This is an old school robot.
- Extra sad.
A robot in a forlorn scene.
- Her hands flexibly swings.
Oh, her hands are opened. Here we go!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
HASIMO SWINGING AROUND
Oh, good, pretty good!
Ah, neat, she's happy now!
She transformed! - Eh?
- Spinning!
Wooaaah!!!
- Very great!
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
HASIMO SPINNING AROUND
Ah, cool, cool!
She looks cool! - Great!
Say "Gasha"!
- Good!
Gasha! (swallows)
Good!
Ghasa!
- Ah, it's over! That was a good one!
That was so good!
- Don't stare, don't stare!!
Why did you stare here?
- Why are you crying?
For the last performance,
what about Hoshino?
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
THE ROBOT SHOW STILL CONTINUES
Hoshino is the last, since everyone did it.
Can you do it? Don't be in a hurry.
Take your time.
Face... her face is telling us she doesn't want to do it!
She looks more tenseful compared with
that Backflip back then.
Try to do "Wiin-Gasha", then go there,
since there's your favorite bread there.
- Then you eat it.
HOSHINO MINAMI
Next we have the bread lover robot, HOSIMO.
HERE COMES THE HOSIMO
She'll enter.
Gasha!
There's a bread in front of you.
- Gasha!
Gasha! Gasha!
Gasha!
Paku' (chewing sound effect)
m 145 -10 l -46 -10 l -46 4 l 145 4
HOSIMO ANGRY
Suddenly she stared like that!
- Sorry Minami-chan!
Hoshino stared.
After this, Senbatsu members for the 13rd single
will be chosen!
"Manatsu no Zenkoku" Tour 2015
finally enters the second phase.
Will be held in Osaka and Tokyo.
Let's see it until the end!
DVD "Nogizakatte, Doko?" Part 2 has been released.
For more information, please
visit Nogizaka46's official website.
Alright, let's close the show with robot style.  - Okay!
Go ahead.
CONVERTED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
Wii~~n~Gasha!
Wii~Gasha. Wii~~Gasha.
Good bye.
- Come one say good bye. Good bye!
Spin your hands!
Great! So great!
I'm going to announce the
Senbatsu members for the 13rd single.
And in the end,
the ONE who be the center IS...