\h\hpoji-peace.tumblr.com\h\h
DON!
And we've begun! It's been a while since I last said DON! Nogizaka Under Construction.
We're your hosts, Bananaman.
Yes, good evening!
And here are Nogizaka-chan.
Alright. With that, Himura-san, please announce today's activity.
Let's go! Today, Let's promote our movie!
Up until now, I've been running away, but maybe, I'm now able to face things more.
Coming soon. Nogizaka46's long-awaited documentary film.
"The Way to Forgetting Sadness"
...I've become able to think that...
...I think I will fight with all I have... We're still only passing through a checkpoint, so...
Showing begins on July 10.
Ah, looks good.
How is it? Will it make you cry?
I cried.
Is that so?
I cried quite a lot.
I see.
We won't cry if we go see it?
Himura-san will cry?
Himura-san will cry.
Will pull at Himura's heartstrings.
So I'll cry.
So I won't? I won't cry?
So Shitara-san will be alright?
Hmm, I'm not sure about Shitara-san...
I'll probably bite my tongue and hold it in while watching in the cinema...
So you'll cry too.
I'll probably go secretly cry alone.
So there'll be something from your mothers?
The mothers will narrate their thoughts about their daughters...
So it'll have that?
Yes.
That's strong. That will definitely make you cry.
The staff went out of their way to go film my mother in Akita.
For Ikoma.
"Even though it's a Nogizaka movie?" This did cross my mind a little.
But including that too...
But, but, but, that does sound strong.
But, but, but, but?
THAT DON'T MATTER! THAT DON'T MATTER!
It does. It does matter!
Sudden Kojima Yoshio
It does!
Why do I have to go all out like that?
So cute!
And with that, today...
we'll give the members 30 seconds each to present highlights from the movie...
using flip boards they made themselves.
First up...
Ikoma's recommended scenes.
Ikoma! Ready, start!
Yes! My recommended scene is this.
A big silhouette... Who could it be?
This is the appearance of the man Ikoma-chan is closest to in the whole world...
so please watch the movie to find out who it is.
Moving on...
I didn't just run here, this is actually...
Because of these scene, I kind of got branded as Ikoma-chan equals running away, but...
But the reason why I ended up running is...
You'll find out about the reason for that.
So, please watch the movie to see what I mean.
Next.
"My allergies..." by Hashimoto Nanami.
It wasn't just normal allergies.
It's a very touching story.
Please watch the movie to find out more about this as well!
And time's upppp!
She mentioned a lot huh.
She did. You crammed it all in.
I might've talked too fast...
Yeah, sorry, if you talk too fast what you're saying might not get across...
You've all seen the movie, so you're all going "Yes, yes" but...
I have no idea what you're going on about.
Unexpectedly you divided it all up.
What's with this running?
This is an incident that occurred after our first principal...
Ahh! That one!
The one that even got to Yahoo news!
Yeah!
You cried and ran away in the middle of an interview.
They said "Ikoma ran away".
They did say "Ikoma ran away" but I actually didn't just run away...
Behind all that, there was a reason that would really make you want to run...
So something happened.
So if you watch this, you'll find out why I ended up behaving that way at that time...
So the camera caught that too.
Yes, it did.
So we'll see that and understand.
And everything is shown here to boot.
So of course, even fans don't know the reason.
Yes. I believe there are more people who don't know the reason...
And it's not just about me, it's related to Macchun as well and she appears in the scene...
So you were there too, Matsumura?
Hm?
Wait, wait, are you saying you weren't?
So Ikoma did just run away??
She says you were there though!
Like, you'll see Ikoma-chan's strong feelings she's been holding deep inside...
It's all shown there so this is definitely a scene to look out for.
Is that so?
You won't know without watching, huh?
I hope everyone watches it.
Sounds good.
For the full version of Ikoma's recommended scene,
please watch the movie.
Next up, we have Hashimoto's recommended scenes.
Ready, start!
For me, the highlight of this movie is...
For the first time, I'll be showing something I couldn't do in Nogidoko.
You see, during winter last year, everyone went on a location shooting...
They went skiing.
And I'm from Hokkaido, but...
I wasn't able to go because I had other work.
I got told a lot by fans that they wanted to see me skiing.
So this time, we went on location shooting in Asahikawa, since I'm from Asahikawa...
For the movie?
Yes.
So there are scenes like that too.
And there...
I did...
Alright, time's up!
Lost time because of the conversation.
That's 'cuz you were talking to her.
Well, time's up.
You participated in those 30 seconds!
No, no, well...
If it was just Hashimoto she could've said more, but you were talking to her.
I thought that too.
I wanted to hear more about Asahikawa.
But I did get to say what I wanted to, so...
So you have scenes like that too.
Yes.
Not really retaking, but for the movie itself.
So you have scenes that were shot specifically for the movie.
They did it for everyone. Like Akita for Ikoma-chan.
They went to Osaka for Naachan too.
Ah, I see, I see.
So you have a ski scene.
Ski scene. You'll see me getting excited like a kid.
So beautiful!
Next, we have Shiraishi's recommended scenes.
Ready, start!
The scenes that hit me hard were... First is this.
For our first ever request hour, Ikoma-chan was really nervous and Minami softly pat her back.
request hour
So these are their backs?
Yes.
It's a light but really touching scene...
so, I hope everyone watches it.
And another is this.
Ikoma-chan also mentioned this earlier.
A full story that has something to do with Matsumura as well.
It's a really serious and tense scene...
Isn't Matsumura's face there too long?
My chin!!!
Alright, time's up!
You were too slow, Shiraishi!
Your drawings make the scene look funny instead though.
No convincing power.
This one's Matsumura, right?
Yes. I wrote their names.
Matsumura, Hashimoto, Ikoma...
and Shiraishi.
Ah, so this is Hashimoto. I thought it was...
Is that the running away scene Ikoma mentioned earlier?
It's a scene from the same time that has something to do with it.
It's quite something, they showed it without cutting at all.
That's why, it's a really serious and tense scene.
So it's a serious scene.
Yes, seriously, I think it's the biggest highlight.
But I got the positioning of the hands and all perfectly, right?
Yes, it's perfect.
That does look like Mattsun, it really does.
Yeah, always there.
Yes.
And for Nanamin too, her dress's zipper at the back was open so it's quite loose.
Wow, amazing!
We were wearing the Guruguru Curtain outfit...
That part's amazing, so it's really a scene to watch out for, huh?
It does seem so.
Yes.
It's the scene I'd like most for everyone to watch.
So what about everyone aside from you?
But everyone... Everyone else...
Don't go saying sad things like "everyone else"!
Like for Unders...
Next. Nishino's recommended scenes.
Ready, start!
Yes. After watching this movie,
my thought was... People change.
Um...
People are frogs (kaeru)?
Change (kawaru).
They change on the inside as well as on the outside.
For the outside, one of the changes were that we used to have thin eyebrows.
I think back when we auditioned, thin eyebrows were in fashion so we all had thin eyebrows.
Next is... My grandfather makes an appearance.
My grandfather made his first movie appearance!
I tried drawing my grandpa.
So good!
Grandpa's eating!
This is my grandpa.
He's eating something, he's eating something.
Alright, time's up.
Aaah, time's up.
So good!
We went to grandpa's house...
Eh? So you filmed there too?
Yes. So we went to grandpa's house and there was a scene where I, my dad, and my grandpa were eating Nabe.
This is grandpa in that scene.
So the movie has scenes like that too.
Does it have like, for example, scenes from Macau?
It did.
Oh, so it has that part where you jumped.
The video, yes.
Ohhh, that part!
This camera, the ugly face camera.
No, no, that was great.
That's included.
That was a great scene.
Please look for Nishino's grandpa in the actual movie.
Akimoto's recommended scenes from the Nogizaka movie are...
Ready, start!
Yes. First, I'll be introducing 3 big surprises in this movie.
The first is, even though this is a Nogizaka movie...
The first person who appears is someone not from Nogizaka. This is the shocking truth.
Right, next.
This here is our first photo from when we passed the auditions.
Looking at this, the shocking truth will be revealed.
Right, moving on.
The last is this.
This is the ending credits.
Before the ending credits, there are lots of points that will make you cry...
Alright, time's up.
...you'll still keep crying even then, it's a great movie like that!
Like, there's something after the credits?
Even during the ending credits, you'll be crying so much that you won't be able to read it.
So when everything finishes...
Seriously?
So that's what you meant. Not that there's some kind of trick or something.
Not that...
This one, what is it?
This is from when we passed the auditions...
We had a photo where we were all lined up and it was published in newspapers and such.
There's one there with a really big head, huh?
That is actually me.
As expected.
And with this, when I went to school the next day, my friend said...
"Manatsu, you were the only one who had kind of a bigger face, huh?"
So people will see this once again in the movie.
During that time, my friends actually quite often called me...
They called me "Flat head."
Flat head?
Wait, if they were calling you that...
They were already making fun of you huh.
What does that even mean, flat head?
Like the top of my head is really flat so you can put
anything on it, and everyone put books and stuff on it.
They did?
Yes.
Flat head? Let's try?
So, let's put that first.
Ah, she really is flat head.
Amazing!
Eh, so stable!
Flat-san!
Flat-san!!
Amazing.
Cool.
Really, that's quite something.
Yeah.
Amazing.
It seems like you could carry various stuff on your head.
Right? Maybe you could even carry water from 5 kilometers away.
Image
There are those from Southeast Asia, right?
Yeah, yeah!
Let's try doing it.
Akimoto Manatsu.
Yes.
Entry No. 17: Takayama Kazumi.
Next up. We have Wada's recommended scenes.
Here we go. Ready, start!
What I thought after watching this movie was...
A long time ago, members from other regions lived in a dormitory...
And we had a dining table on the
second floor, where we all talked until late...
Like "What do I do for my MC part in our concert?" "What do we do now?" "Delicious." and such.
Like, "I have clothes that I don't wear anymore, does anyone want it?"
So, I remembered us having those conversations before.
And the next, our vocal training teacher...
Alright, time's up!
That was really cute, but...
So it was your dorm memories? So that appears as well?
Yes. The dorm is shown.
Amazing, it has even that.
Yes.
So your vocal training teacher...
Our teacher was really scary.
Ah, I see.
But, earlier, I heard from my manager...
that this teacher is actually a very good teacher.
And that she said "I'm going to go into scary mode now" and went on to teach us.
Actually a kind teacher.
I learned that just earlier.
Well, yeah, after all, you were all beginners...
Right?
So she probably got angry to help you become people who can sing songs.
So, the lessons were always so scary, and my stomach always hurt before them.
You didn't want to go?
Yeah.
But she was REALLY scary. Right?
She was.
Really scary.
I always wondered if it was menopause.
You'll get scolded for saying that just now.
Maaya-chan! Maaya-chan...
She's probably angry now with what you just said.
Your teacher just blew a fuse at that.
Please watch the members getting scared of their teacher in the actual movie.
Next, we have Takayama's recommended scenes.
Wow, so many.
Ah, there's quite- ah.
A lot of flip boards
Can you do that all in 30 seconds?
I'm not confident that I can...
You alright?
I'll try to speak quite fast...
You will?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Ready...
Start!
This movie's highlights. First is this!
Everyone's growth check. It's been 4 years since the group was formed.
Iku-chan who was in middle school then...
...is now a university student!
She's become a wonderful lady.
Hori who used to have long hair...
...cut her hair and underwent a big transformation!
Her smile looks wonderful.
Everyone's becoming more and more beautiful, but for some reason, there's this one person...
...whose face got longer.
And next...
The scene that made Takayama laugh the most.
Hahahaha...
Alright, time's up.
Ah, too bad.
You had too many, Takayama!
But I'm curious about what made you laugh the most.
You got stopped there.
For this, I wanted... I thought I'd do something like a quiz afterwards.
This is something that happened in Naachan's house.
At my grandpa's house.
That house where her grandpa appears.
What's on TV there was really interesting.
Now I'm curious.
Right?
What do you think it was?
Eh, is that something we can guess... like...
Without any hint whatsoever?
Yes.
So it's something we can guess if we just think about it?
Ah, but it is something old people usually watch.
Old people.
Yes, yes, yes. That's a hint!
So old people usually watch it.
So it was shown there the whole time?
Alright, then let's say our guesses at the same time.
Ready, go.
Kouhaku.
Ladies 4.
Ladies 4?
At 4 o'clock on TV Tokyo.
It's now Ladies 4 YOU.
Alright. The correct answer is...
It was Hakuho wiping his body!
No way we could've guessed that!
No way.
Yeah.
Hakuho wiping his body... Really.
The sumo wrestler, right?
Yes.
Seriously, no need to go out of your way and talk about what's on grandpa's TV.
It really caught my attention.
What about promoting the movie...
So Hakuho was on TV.
Yes. It was really funny.
No, no.
Hakuho wipes his face, right?
Takaya— Takayama.
Supplementary information on Hakuho.
Takayama. Please stop talking about Hakuho already.
This is supposed to be about your movie.
Oh yeah...
Watch the movie to see the scene where Hakuho appears.
Next up. The long-awaited master artist, Ikuta.
You drew pictures?
Yes.
We're looking forward to it.
Excited to see those drawings.
Ready, start!
First thing that I want people to notice is this...
This is from the backstage when we first performed Guruguru Curtain.
It's easy to understand.
This here is the AKB group. And here is Nogizaka.
I think people who know us now will find it interesting to see just how little power we used to have 4 years ago.
Next.
This one.
This is..
Um...
Wait, everyone, calm down.
Everyone. So we had a photo shoot after our audition...
And during that photo shoot...
Alright, time's up.
Wait. Wait, this is...
Is that Hashimoto?
Yes, yes.
Is that Hashimoto? Her face looks skewed though?
No...
Why... Why did you have to draw her?
No, wait.
This is... Please listen.
My drawing isn't at fault here, Nanamin was the weird one.
No way!
A problem with the model?
No, no.
No, your drawing's at fault here.
No, that's not it.
When you say "guts pose" people usually do this, right?
That's right.
So they wanted us to pose this way, like an idol...
But Nanamin alone did a rather strange guts pose...
How so?
Like this, or like this... She was doing poses like those.
Like I was going to punch someone, right?
Not like a "I'll do my best!" kind of
guts pose but a "I'll show you!" kind.
So that's what happened.
I never experienced getting my photo taken like that...
So, I asked the cameraman what kind of pose they were going to take and they said guts pose...
So I did this pose.
It's rare to see an idol doing this pose, right?
That's true.
My face also changed.
Yeah.
My face...
Your face?
It has really changed.
Eh, so did you get it changed?
No, no.
It's okay, it's okay to do that though?
But really, I think once the movie comes out, people are going to say I had plastic surgery.
So you changed that much.
What changed?
I was all bloated.
So you were fat?
No she wasn't.
Everyone was kind of fatter then, right?
Only Hoshino got a little fatter, right?
Hey~!
How nostalgic!
So cute!!
Minami-chan, so cute!
That was a great reaction just now. Like "Hey~!"
Next. What is Noujou's recommended scene?
Start!
Yes. The member I want everyone to watch the most in this movie is this...
It's a person named Asou Ririko.
So this girl, even though she's from Shounan...
For some reason, she took the audition in Fukuoka.
She went out of her way to take an overnight bus trip to take the audition in Fukuoka.
But actually, this girl was in an idol group in Fukuoka.
She was a local idol.
And in that group, she was actually together in that group with another member, Kawago Hina.
Alright. Alright, time's up.
Wait, just wait... What... Are you on something?
It's a mystery.
Yes, um...
No she's not.
Is this a delusional story?
No, it's not like that. There's a proper punch line to this story.
Um... This person named Asou Ririko is actually me.
Huh?
Asou Ririko = Me?
It's actually me.
No, no. You're Noujou, aren't you?
Wait...
I am indeed Noujou, but...
But when they called out the names after the final judging...
The last name they call, Asou Ririko, was me.
So it's a screen name? Noujou Ami...
Yes, I had a screen name...
Ah so that's the screen name.
Yes, this is the screen name. And I used to go by this...
Ah, in Fukuoka?
Yes.
Ah, I see.
So a long time ago.
Yes.
You said earlier that Kawago was there too?
Just like me, Kawago Hina was also an idol in Fukuoka.
We were in the same agency.
Eh, that's amazing. What's with that history? So in Fukuoka...
This is the first time I've talked about it.
When Kawago passed, was she Kawago?
No, her name was just a little different.
You'll hear it when you watch the movie...
She was called Kawaai Hina.
Why use such a subtly different screen name?
Yeah, hers wasn't really that different, but...
People who watch the movie will probably wonder "Huh? Noujou Ami wasn't called..."
The long-awaited Nogizaka46 documentary film, "The Way to Forgetting Sadness"
will open in 46 theaters nationwide on July 10.
After this, a complete dissection of Nogizaka's TV drama!
The drama starring all Nogizaka46 members, "Hatsumori Bemars"
will begin at 12:12 midnight on July 10!
To protect the park they love,
girls with no experience playing softball challenge the strongest high school softball team!
If you get a better record than us...
I'll cancel this park's redevelopment plan for you.
Eh?!
With that, today we'll delve into the members' different roles.
Eh, Ikoma is...?
I play Academy.
Academy?
I'm in the theater club and then the softball club.
Ah so it's like that. Oh, cute!
Eh, so cute!
Ah, so this is your uniform.
Yes, our uniform. It's cute being pink and all.
Nanamaru.
Nanamaru... Your name isn't very...
Yes, my name alone isn't that different.
Right? So what's Nanamaru's position?
She's the pitcher.
The ace. Can you show us a little?
Can we see?
It's really beautiful.
No, no...
Well, then. Let us see Nanamaru's pitching form!
Alright.
That's quite... That looks quite for real.
Ah, really good!
Really good, really.
That's... I see. You also have lines in
the drama, but there's softball itself too.
It's hard.
Yes. Everyone practiced. We played catch.
Ikoma, you're bad at catching balls, right?
Please watch me.
Eh?
So you improved?
Yes. I'm able to do it properly now.
Before, you couldn't even catch a rubber ball and it hit you on the head.
Chopin.
Ah, I see. So you play the piano?
Yes. But, it's not just that I have the piano...
I also make use of it for my softball, like a technique.
So you're like Donoma.
It is. Donoma.
Like Donoma right? Donoma also played the piano, right?
Kote. Does this Kote come from the Kendo Kote?
Yes. I'm in the Kendo club as well.
What kind of role is Kote?
Kote is really...
Like always eating ice cream?
Eh, for real?!
Bingo?!
Wooow!!!
You got it.
But there's always that one guy in movies and all that's always eating, right?
Eh, I see.
She loves ice cream and meat buns!
That's like a Matsumura character though, but I guess it's different.
That's true, it is.
Marukyu?
So Marukyu.
My character is a sales lady at a shop called 209 in Harajuku.
Eh, a sales lady?
Isn't everyone a student?
It seems I was on a leave of absence from school.
So I work in a shop, and I have a sort of dark...
Fits you.
So at first, you're all like Hatsumori Park has nothing to do with me.
Then slowly, you change...
Bingo again?
Wait... It's usually like that, right? Right?
That role's important.
Yeah, but right?
That role's important!
So Sakurai is Bunan.
Yes, I'm Bunan.
Because you can do anything safely?
So it's that.
Not really, it's more like I only say things that are safe.
Ah so it's this.
So it's like even when everyone's all fired up, you're still like all noncommittal?
Ah, yes. That's it.
Yuuutsu.
Yuuutsu...
She's like a nervous, introverted type.
Like an otaku?
She is kind of otaku-like.
So she has that kind of image.
And Manatsu is Harvard.
Because she's intelligent?
Yes. All she does is study. For everything, even for her throwing angle and all, she computes them using formulas...
So she tries... Yes, that type.
Oh, so that type, huh?
I see. Sounds good.
Can you throw properly?
Yes, I can.
Really?
Really.
Then do it!
I'm really cool, though! Is that alright?
Alright...
Please wait. Which leg was it again?
You're confused with leg to step?
Really, which was it again?
Just try it. Just try it once first.
Wait, wait, which was it again?
Hey! Harvard!
Harvard...
I haven't been throwing lately so I've forgotten!
What are you doing, Harvard?
Harvard's throwing with her right hand yet she raises her right leg as well.
Yes. Yes.
That's weird...
Shiraishi's role is kind of amazing. Kirei...
Yes.
Cool!
I'm jealous.
Really looks good.
Like someone you'd admire.
Yeah, like compared to Kote...
There's like a huge gap between Kote and Kirei.
Yes!!
It's Kote, after all.
It's Kote. I end up wanting to say Kirei's lines...
Yes, she says that she really likes my lines.
It'll be bad if you say them though. So a little is fine?
What a lovely little story~
Lines like that. So I end up...
So, she's that type. So she's like an awful person.
She's an ojou-sama character. She's like nonchalantly cool...
I shall await you at the finals.
She's so cool!
So I practice her lines alone behind the scenes.
You practice?
Yes.
So that you can do it someday.
So for Kote it's like, Yum! Delicious! Delicious!
Yes, yes.
Like "Don't say that!"
Like, "I will protect it! I'll protect Hatsumori!"
Like that. So she's like that type of character.
Right, she's funny.
Sounds interesting.
I'm excited to see it.
This one's coming out on the 10th as well.
Wow, amazing, July 10 is pretty amazing.
Right?
For Nogizaka.
Next time... No way, a sports activity?
Oops, this line shouldn't be here
m 0 0 b -2 0 -4 0 -6 0 b -7 0 -8 0 -8 -2 b -8 -2 -8 -2 -8 -2 b -8 -3 -8 -4 -6 -4 b -4 -4 -2 -4 0 -4 b 2 -4 4 -4 6 -4 b 6 -5 6 -7 6 -8 b 6 -8 6 -8 6 -8 b 7 -10 9 -10 10 -9 b 10 -7 10 -7 10 -6 b 12 -4 13 -3 13 -2 b 13 6 13 4 13 7 b 12 8 10 8 8 8 b 7 8 6 8 5 8 b 4 8 3 8 1 7 b 0 5 0 3 0 2
Next time is their 12th single hit campaign.
The members will do a 100-knock challenge.
They keep getting up, even when they get hit by the ball and fall.
And... Master artist Ikuta presents a shocking drawing?!