\h\hpoji-peace.tumblr.com\h\h
DON!
And we've started, Nogizaka Under Construction.
Today's– Ah, hello, we're Bananaman.
Hello.
And here are the members in the studio today!
Alright, yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
So many.
Onegaishimasu!!
Yes, yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Himura-san.
Yes!
Please announce our activity for today!
Here we go!
13th Single Campaign: What should we do?
Let's all think about it! Emergency Meeting!
The traditional Hit Prayer Campaign that's held during every Nogizaka single release.
What should they do for this 13th single?
They'll be presenting the activities they've thought about, and the plans that are approved will actually be done!
Will there be some kind of prize for the plans that are selected?
Eh? What do you mean by prize, like money?
Well...
Demand for compensation?
Planning fee?
Something like that, or...
What prize?
Well... that's...
Well, just normal clo- clo-... like giving us presents...
You were definitely trying to say clothes just now, weren't you?
Caught a snippet of "clothes."
You tried to say clothes just now.
Then you stopped and changed it to "present."
Yes.
Hit Prayer Plan Presentation. First up is Akimoto.
Jan!
Skydiving AGAIN!!
Really, you just gave a good one.
Yes, it's skydiving again!
Huh? So you're going to do that again?
I did this for the 5th single.
Ah, so that was the 5th.
Yes, that was for Kimi no Na wa Kibou.
I see.
So I dove. And when I did...
Well... Actually, in the end, we decided who was going to skydive with a Pop-up Pirate.
And during that time, the remaining ones were Minami and I.
Wait... Hoshino's face...
Bad feeling.
She's making a face.
Yes.
I did my best then as you can see here.
Ah, how nostalgic!
And so...
Is this edited?
No, no, no!
Suspicion of CG.
You dove? You did? Hm.
During this time, while I was skydiving, Minami-chan was...
Well, according to rumors, she was reading a novel in the filming bus.
Alone.
And back then, it was really cold, the winds were blowing really hard.
So even while I was falling from 4000 meters, in the middle of all that...
Minami-chan had a peaceful look on her face as she read her novel and relaxed...
Huh? So then, what is this?
And what's more...
Is this going in the direction of Hoshino doing it?
What is it that you want to say?
With that, this time, we'll have
Minami-chan go skydiving alone.
A personal grudge.
There it is!
So I guess you can go sell someone else like this on a personal basis, huh?
I see... Hoshino.
I see. So this time, the point is Hoshino will jump, skydive.
Ah, sounds good.
But first of all, Manatsu's at fault for pressing on that one!
The pirate?
That.
But you know, Hoshino has a cut in her mouth today and she's having quite a tough time!
Ah I see!
Will bleed if she laughs.
I'm not smiling right now.
Is that so?
I'm holding back my laughter.
Ah, but for this single, Minami-chan is a Fukujin for the
first time... Ah, not first, but you're making a come-back.
After a while, right?
And she's one of the members who'll be shouldering the next generation,
so it would be a great hit if she skydives, right?
I see!
That's right.
That's true... Indeed. So skydiving.
For this campaign, did Kimi no Na wa Kibou sell well?
Yes.
Isn't this good? So we can just decide on this one?
If she skydives with me... Manatsu too.
No, no. I... I already did so... Here, here.
Re-diving.
Then for the next time, you can try to look cuter on the photo.
Why? So you mean she looks ugly here?
Alright, this...
NG face acccording to Hoshino.
Wait, well, I guess I do look ugly here.
Skydiving is... well... right?
I'm sure it'll be great!
Right?
For sure.
Is there anyone here who wants to do skydiving?
Ah, there's no one...
What a waste, I personally really want to do it.
Me too, I really want to try.
If I were part of Nogizaka46...
That's impossible.
An impossible delusion.
I would've definitely done that.
I want to try it a little...
You do?
A bit.
Ah but, then, Asuka and Minami, as the ones who will shoulder the next generation...
Don't involve me in this!
The next-gen 2.
Next-gen 2.
Then, maybe we could all make a circle, that seems like fun.
Oh.
Nishino, are you not very good with these things?
Well, um, it's scary.
Shiraishi, you too?
Me too, kind of...
Maybe a little okay?
Amazing, it's like the studio just suddenly went quiet!
Heavy atmosphere MAX.
What's wrong, everyone? We're talking about your campaign here!
I guess everyone doesn't want to...
What's wrong?
I guess it's like...
Why something like what the staff would think of
when the members actually get the chance to think of something for themselves this time?
Ah, so it's that?
But, since it's a campaign, it needs some harshness, right?
As expected.
Harshness is a basic.
True, that's true, isn't it?
I guess for Akimoto, if it's not harsher than before, it doesn't feel like she's done it, right?
Right?
Huh? Me?
No parachute, right?
The immortal woman.
No parachute means suicide.
It's Akimoto so she'll be fine.
Quickly.
That's impossible.
Campaign Plans. The next proposal is by Hashimoto.
My proposal is this.
Jan!
A mysterious power spot!! A phantom island that only appears a few times each month!!
I'm curious!
Up until now, when you mention campaign the first thing that comes to mind has been harshness...
These have been activities where you watch everyone's pained faces.
This time, I'd like to do something that can truly bring good fortune...
Something that can really become a plus for everyone.
Wait. When you say it like that, it's like you're saying that all past campaigns haven't been a plus.
No, that's not what I mean.
What is this? Staff criticism?
Indirect staff criticism?
Something where you can say "Ah, they look really happy!"
Eh, wait, what do you mean?
Past activities have been meaningless?
Hm? Hm? Hm?
The more you talk, the more you sound like you're complaining.
I think it would be nice if we can have an activity where everyone have fun and goes home happy.
I see.
So I researched a bit for today.
What is this?
Only appears a few times in a month...
That would be... this.
What is this?
This is an island called Yorontou.
Yorontou? Eh? So this appears only a few times in a month?
No... It's Yorontou's... Well, Yorontou is Kagoshima's southernmost island...
Yorontou
Kagoshima's southernmost island near
Okinawa's main island
Here, due to the ebb and flow of the tide...
There's a beach called Yurigahama that only appears a few times each month.
Yurigahama.
Yes, it's Yurigahama. This here is Yorontou.
Yes.
It's this one.
Yurigahama
A phantom beach that appears only a few
times a year due to the ebb and flow of the tide
It's beautiful!
What is this? It looks amazing.
I want to go!
So when the tide ebbs it looks like this.
Eh? This is... So it becomes an island, right?
This is, well, how the view looks from there.
It's this beautiful?
This is the clearness? of the sea that you can see from there.
It looks like this when viewed from above.
Amazing.
I see. So this place appears from the corals here.
There are places like these, aren't there?
It's Yurigahama.
So if you come here...
This beach has star sand...?
Star sand...
You mean star-shaped sand, right?
Yes, like corals...
Made out of corals?
Yes.
So you can find that here, and if you collect the same number of star sand grains as your age...
So you eat it?
Eating sand Setsubun-style.
Huh?
You don't?
So if you can collect them without eating them...
Without eating... If you can collect them without eating them... It's like most people end up eating them...
Won't lose to the temptation.
So if you can collect them, you will have good fortune and happiness.
It's this really beautiful island. Personally, I...
Uwa~ That looks great!
Look at the color of that sea!
This was a place I looked up when I wanted to go on a trip...
It's a beach that appears only a few times each year...
So is it known when it appears?
Yes, the periods you can see it are forecasted and are found on their homepage...
And it just so happens that you can see it from the end of September until the start of October...
Now is the time to go.
This is...!
Now... Now is the only time we have.
Since we're Nogizaka46, we'll collect 46 star sand grains...
And hopefully, that will lead to good fortune for us.
Since it's a power spot...
Yes.
To an extent... It feels like, just going there won't be enough to last the length of the show...
So, maybe you could add, I don't know...
Maybe show off your swimsuits?
Just... I feel like it lacks some sort of pull...
A special extra is needed.
Can we do swimsuits?
Ah, Nogizaka can't?
I'm sorry, but I don't have a swimsuit, but I do have my school swimsuit...
Possibility limited to a school swimsuit.
School swimsuit...?
That's...
Will you wear your school swimsuit?
It's like... I would also like to see how the tide ebbs...
Then I would like to see it flow too.
So from the start, I would like someone to stand there when the tide is still high.
Then when it ebbs...
That'd be quite a shoot, she'll get sodden.
Then it ebbs...
OMG!
Then if we can show when the tide rises again, I think it'll be just splendid.
No!
That's scary!
Everyone's busy, right?
So it's possible that not everyone will be able to go.
So then it's possible that we'll just have one of you, say Ikoma, go there from Tokyo with a digicam.
Just a possibility.
...In a school swimsuit?
Ikoma's Solo Trip in a School Swimsuit
No, no. No...
Sounds fun!
You got me there.
I have no interest in school swimsuits but I'd like to see that.
I don't know, but it could become something like that or someone else could go.
I see... I see...
This time we'll definitely choose from among your presentations.
I hope I get chosen.
Moving on, we have this hit prayer proposal from Shiraishi.
This time, this is what I'm proposing.
Ten~
A superior power spot: The island closest to heaven!
Another power spot? I think I've heard of this island that's closest to heaven?
That's... This!
This is New Caledonia.
New Caledonia
An island located to the east of Australia in the
southern Pacific that's world famous as a resort
You're going to New Caledonia?!
Yes.
I was able to go there once for my photobook shoot...
The view was really beautiful, and it seems it has lots of power spots.
Then at that time, there was this one place I wanted to visit but couldn't...
Jan!
Oh? What's this?
Top view?
Heart-shaped mangroves.
Heart Mangrove Forest
A view that can only be seen from a Cessna or a helocopter
It's said to bring fortune to those who see it
This is from above?
Yes, it can only be seen from the sky.
It's a really mysterious and beautiful power spot.
Why does it look like this shape?
So you'll go there to see this?
Yes, yes.
Eh~ That's amazing.
Then if you see this, it's said that you'll receive great happiness.
That so?
Yes, that's what they say.
This is really big, look this is a boat here.
How do you see it?
On a helicopter...
You can only see it on those.
I'd like to ride a helicopter!
New Cale– So who's going here?
Yes. Well, since it is overseas, it'll need a big budget...
So, then it'll be like ME and someone else.
So just two of you?
No, no.
Just a few.
Yes. A few.
A few?
But even though it's just a few of you, it'll still cost a lot of money, won't it?
It'll cost a lot to have a cameraman with us, so...
We'll use a handycam.
For the camera, they'll shoot themselves.
So we'll shoot ourselves...
No, no.
If you don't have at least one professional with you and you end up with no usable footage when you get back...
So contrary to that, having your manager and your make-up artist around would be...
Make-up is fine, we'll do our own make-up and our own hair!
Really?
We don't need our manager either...
No, no, if you go there without your manager, you'll just be going there for fun!
True, that'll be just a trip, wouldn't it?
Vacation?
So it'll be the director, Shiraishi, and someone else.
Yes.
I want to go~
That's something.
That sounds good.
I'll be the director.
That's impossible.
They just want to go.
Then, what, like this helicopter or Cessna or whatever, you'll have to arrange that...
Everything, the hotel and all, you'll take care of that? The places you'll eat at too, that's a lot of work, you know?
So for this, just like the power spot earlier as well...
Well, going there and having fun is all good, but like swimsuits or what, you'll need something...
You need to do something.
Then, well, we'll be going on a helicopter...
We'll bring Akimoto along and skydive together.
Oh, sounds good.
Where do we land?
Right in the middle of it.
Akimoto will wear an arrow costume and shoot right into the center of that heart...
That's great!
Real Zukkyun
Ahh, a zukkyun.
That's great, zukkyun.
You'll become zukkyun yourself.
You'll probably get severely injured though.
Yeah, cuz those are trees, right?
You'll probably go crashing through them.
No. No, don't want!
It's become a shocking video.
I kinda want to see.
I don't want to!
\hNew kinds of hit prayers proposed by the members appear one after the other!\h
poji-peace.tumblr.com
twitter: @pojipeace_yo
\hFukagawa Mai fires punsin rapid succession & uninhabited island survival?!\h
Next is front member Fukagawa's plan!
Yes, here it is!
Jajan~
Let's go pick gourmet food of good fortune!
Go pick?
What's this?
There are lots of food that bring good fortune in the world, right?
I'd like for us to go and take them.
Food of good fortune.
For example... I prepared some here...
This.
Strawberries bring good fortune?
Strawberry (Ichigo) is...
Strawberry (Ichigo) equals First (Ichiban)!
Like, it has a nice sound to it...
(Ichi = 1, Go = 5)
You'll be 15th with this, is that alright?
Well, it's Ichigo, it's one.
Going to ignore "Go."
It's one.
Then next is this.
Tanuki Udon.
So Tanuki Udon brings good fortune?
For Tanuki Udon, it means you
surpass (nuku/nuki) others (Ta).
So you surpass others.
You surpass others.
That's cool, there is that.
Tanuki Udon.
So Tanuki Udon, huh?
Then the next one is...
What is this, squash?
No, not squash, it's a melon.
Ah, melon.
This is a melon?
This... Manatsu, do you know what the reason for this is?
How does it bring good luck?
For melon...
It'll make you fall head over heels~? (meromero)
Thought she'd say that.
Heeey, come on!
The quickness of that "Thought she'd say that." is amazing.
Super assertive Kuroishi.
The look in these two's eyes and their way of speaking are unbelievable.
Yes.
That was scary just now.
Well, that's not the reason.
Oh, it's not...?
This is from "sold-out melon."
It means our CD will sell!
So any other food would do too, right?
Eh?
And...
There's more?
Wiener.
Wait. Ah, I get this.
Eh, why?
For this... Wiener, wiener, wiener, wiener, wiener, wiener... Winner!
So it means winner...
Wait... just wait. If you talk about picking, I guess you can pick strawberries...
I've been thinking that too.
Where will you go pick wieners?
A problem occured for wiener.
From the supermarket?
Like making wieners, right?
Yes, from where they make them into sausages.
Ah, I see. So from scratch?
If you go to the supermarket, you'll find all of those though.
Can be completed at the grocery store.
We'll go and get them properly.
Then the last one is... Octopus.
That's delicious.
Octopus brings good– Well, I guess it does.
For octopus, it can be written as having much (ta) happiness (kou).
Also for tests and such, we have "okutopasu."
So it's means you place (oku to) and pass (pasu) the exam, and it's considered to bring good luck.
These are just some examples,
but we'll have everyone go and pick good fortune food like these and eat them and raise their fortune levels.
This sounds good. For octopus, you'd go to the sea and all.
Yes. We can get bonito too.
That's suddenly difficult isn't it? Octopus.
Just this one is really difficult.
Serious octopus fishing.
For the rest, you'll probably get back just fine.
Next up, Takayama's proposed hit prayer activity.
Here I go. This is what I thought of.
Jan.
Do your best on your own: Daily life on her first uninhabited island experience.
Alone?
Something like this... does sound good.
It seems like an actual activity.
Great. This sounds great.
Yes. Yes.
I have a lot of confidence today.
So you'll go, Takayama?
Ah, no!
No, no. We'll have someone else go.
Not Takayama?
No, not me.
So who?
This is... The one I thought of is someone who is currently gaining popularity...
Eh... Asuka!
Fished out Asuka.
Sounds good!
Oh, Asuka-chan?
Yes. I'd like her to go.
Well... First of all, Asuka has a lot of things she can't do on her own.
Oh?
Up until recently, she couldn't buy clothes if she didn't shop with her mom.
Recently, she's been able to buy them, but she still confirms with her mom by sending a photo.
With her mom?
Yes. Even if I think it's okay, if I send a picture...
and my mom doesn't say it's cute, I won't buy it. If she says it's bad, I won't buy it.
Dependent on mother at 17 years old.
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
When I was... 17?
17.
At 17, I was already able to do internet shopping on my own.
I could do that. On the other hand...
You got cheated though.
You got cheated.
I did get cheated, yes, but I could do it. Asuka though...
A victim of fraud at 17.
You got cheated.
So you got cheated?
Well... That means I still had room to grow...
So, you'd like for her to become stronger with this.
Asuka strengthening project.
And... There's a mission.
She'll have to do this?
Eh, what?
Yes, on an uninhabited island.
The mission is this.
Escape on a raft.
This is... this is quite extreme.
Specialist Level.
Takei-san did that!
No!
Can she do this?
This is quite extreme though.
This is crazy.
This is at the Takei Sou class of work though, he tried doing this.
It's something even Takei Sou wasn't able to do, so...
Oh, I see.
If you ask why I want to do this uninhabited island survival for this single...
Well...
This single's title is "There's somebody I'd like to talk to right now."
Surely, on an inhabited island, humans would... Underneath the starry sky...
As she goes to sleep, surely, anyone would feel like there's someone they want to talk to right now.
I see. Going to an uninhabited island all alone, someone would feel that way.
Surely anyone'll think that!
So with these feelings...
I see.
Then, she'll make a raft, and while on the raft, she'll sing this song, and someone will find her...
Make?
Someone will find her?
She'll meet someone, and the moment she talks to that person...
"Ah!" She'll think of this song.
What do you think? Since she pointed you out for this.
Forced Solo Nomination.
It's not any other member.
Then, let's do this in New Caledonia!
Wonderful~
Hey...
The Caledonia Nee-san Appears.
What was that just now?
That did sound like an Onee.
Don't "Wonderful~" us.
Um, escaping from an uninhabited island in New Caledonia is just impossible.
Absolutely impossible.
It's important that it's uninhabited, right?
Yes.
But it's the same thing right? If you don't know anyone at all and you can't speak the language.
Can you make a raft in New Caledonia?
If you can, it's alright.
No, no. So she'll make a raft then what? How far will she go?
If she's going out of the country, she'll need to go through the proper procedures.
Exile idol?
I see, I see. So Japan it is.
If you're going to an uninhabited island, you're better in Japan.
Then... We'll go with Nanamin's! Nanamin's Something-tou will be fine.
Yes, so she'll make a raft at Yurigahama...
There were no trees there.
None, there were none.
It's an island that appears only for a few days.
That's bad, she'll sink.
If she's not allowed to swim...
I see.
Coming up... An unexpected sound argument from that Hoshino?
For the next hit prayer plan, the presenter is Hoshino.
Jan!
I'd like to do maintenance for my body!
What's that? Sounds like fun though!
Up until now, we've had stuff like skydiving, and I myself climbed Mt. Fuji...
Did you?
I did! I was there!
No, no, you didn't.
Ah, scary!
Seriously angry.
You've done various difficult things up until now, huh?
Yes. They were quite dangerous and also physically exhausting...
When I climbed Mt. Fuji, a fan told me "If Minami was able to climb it, it must've been a breeze, huh!"
More than seeing it as difficult, they thought it was pretty easy cuz you were able to climb it.
They say "Must've been easy!" and all, but we climbed for 13 hours!
Despite that, it would go "...2 hours after" and all that.
Of course, there's no way we could air the entire 13 hours, after all.
Yeah, can't have that.
Yes, but because of that, people get the idea that it was a really easy climb.
So you think that the difficulty doesn't get through.
Yes. So with the timing of this activity, we can all go get a massage for a smaller face, or to a therapist...
I want to go!
Massage for a smaller face?
No, no...
To make ourselves cute.
So we'll go to a therapist and become cuter and have fans like us even more...
And with that we'll be able to do our hit prayer.
I see. So even when you do extreme things, the difficulty doesn't get through anyway...
So, then it'll be more useful for the sales if you just become cuter and it's better to just do that.
Approval of Hoshino's Sound Argument.
How could I not have noticed until now?
Why indeed?
Amazing.
Takayama, you're applauding like crazy, but you tried to send someone alone to an uninhabited island.
Her way of thinking lies with variety.
No, it's fine, no need for that anymore.
So then we go to a therapist...
And if everyone gets good maintenance for their bodies, their dance will become better as well.
They'll look cute on the footage and it'll be like hitting two birds with one stone.
Oh. I see.
You thought of this well.
Yeah.
You're not going to use this one at all?
Ah! I was supposed to show this!
I went to Mt. Fuji!
No, no need for that anymore.
Mt. Fuji too late.
Too late.
We're being shown Mt. Fuji now.
I was wondering what it was.
Already late for a Mt. Fuji picture.
Well, but, Ikuta, you went there with others, right?
But because that went well, your single sold well, right?
I did get a great sense of accomplishment.
But, it's true, there were parts here and there that didn't get through. Also the way back? The way down...
Unexpectedly, it was more difficult than going up, but then the cameras weren't even rolling.
The way down was strenuous.
Seriously. There's no way we could show your way down, right?
Like after going Ah~ at the top, they'll show you taking forever again going down, I've never seen anyone show that.
Going down show?
Their way down was pretty bad though.
I do get that. I get that you were walking even when you weren't on cam and that going down was difficult as well.
Will everyone do this one?
Yes... Or after doing something that someone else thought of, we'll go do this...
You'll do that?
This, you mean you'll go to Mt. Fuji?
No, no! This one!
With Mt. Fuji Climbing.
After doing something, they'll go further and climb Mt. Fuji?
Everyone will die!
A package deal from hell.
That's hell.
Isn't it alright even if you don't get any cuter than you already are?
Do you want to become even prettier?
Everyone does... Well, we all never have the time to go do this, so...
So would some kind of interesting therapy be fine too?
What's that?
I don't know, but maybe like using what they use for construction and go like this.
Ah, ah.
Oh, like Ganbaruman?
Ah, yes, yes, yes. There's that.
Like going ow ow ow! Would that be fine too?
It'll get smaller, it will.
Eh? I want to do it.
Ah, but if it works...
If it works? You'll get jackhammer to your face like this, you know?
Real Nogizaka Under Construction.
Ouch!
Ah, but that's...
Our presentation meeting still continues.
What are the plans that will get accepted?
m 0 0 b -2 0 -4 0 -6 0 b -7 0 -8 0 -8 -2 b -8 -2 -8 -2 -8 -2 b -8 -3 -8 -4 -6 -4 b -4 -4 -2 -4 0 -4 b 2 -4 4 -4 6 -4 b 6 -5 6 -7 6 -8 b 6 -8 6 -8 6 -8 b 7 -10 9 -10 10 -9 b 10 -7 10 -7 10 -6 b 12 -4 13 -3 13 -2 b 13 6 13 4 13 7 b 12 8 10 8 8 8 b 7 8 6 8 5 8 b 4 8 3 8 1 7 b 0 5 0 3 0 2
Nogizaka46 Under Live Nippon Budokan Performance: Merry Christmas Show 2015.
Now accepting ticket reservations for mobile members.
Don't miss this chance!
More details at Nogizaka46's official website.
\hFinally the activities for the 13th single hit prayer campaign gets decided.\h
\hJust whose proposals were accepted?!\h
The 13th single campaign has finally been decided.
These two who are running as fast as they can are...?!