m 0 0 l 0 27 l 2 27 l 2 0 l 0 0 m 2 0 l -4 0 l -4 6 l 16 6 l 16 4 l -2 4 l -2 2 l 0 2 m 2 2 m 16 0 l 16 27 l 18 27 l 18 -1 l 16 -1 m 22 0 l 22 0 l 24 0 l 24 11 l 19 11 l 19 9 l 22 9 l 22 2 l 15 2 l 15 0 m 6 18 l 6 12 l 12 12 l 12 14 l 8 14 l 8 18 l 6 18 m 12 18 l 12 20 l 6 20 l 6 18 l 10 18 l 10 14 l 12 14 l 12 18 m 5 7 l 8 9 l 7 10 l 4 8 l 5 7 m 10 9 l 10 9 l 13 7 l 14 8 l 11 10 l 10 9 m 3 24 b 3 24 3 23 3 23 b 7 21 11 21 15 23 b 15 23 15 25 15 25 b 11 23 7 23 3 25
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
Wholeheartedly,
Nanamin Answers The Phone
This show had gathered 100 life complaints
from men and women of all ages and various companies.
And this is a segment where the idol
Hashimoto Nanami will directly give them solutions.
The first complaint is...
Hello...
[Hello..]
Good afternoon.
[Good afternoon... ]
May I know your name and your age?
[My name is Okano.]
- How old are you?
[20 years old]
- 20?  - [Yes]
What problem do you have today?
[I've dated this girl for one year... ]
[Now, I am really head over heels for her... ]
[I really love her
from the bottom of my heart]
[Shitara]: What's this?
[Misa]: This seems good!
[Even though we're dating, we have a fight
almost daily... ]
Eh, what are the causes of the fights?
[Maybe it's because we love each other too much]
[Perhaps that's why we fight]
[That is also what makes us even closer...]
By the way, why did
you fight yesterday?
[Yesterday she was feeling ill... ]
[...then I told her "Perhaps you're hungry,
what do you want to eat?"]
[I bought some food and then I said,
"Here, have a bite", but...]
[She said, like, "Why would you buy something like this?"
I bought her hamburger that time]   - Hamburger?
[Then I said, "There's nothing else,
just hamburger."]
Of course hamburger was not a good choice.
[So, it's wrong?]
Hamburger was a bad choice...
[Do you think Okayu is good enough?]
- Well, Okayu is a good food for digestion...
[Perhaps if it's a woman...]
Basically I recommend food like
mashed vegetables or fruits.
[Understood, radish, apple...]
- Radish, apple...
[... ginger too...]
- Yes that's right.
[When she's crying,
I will try it.]
[Hopefully this way our feelings won't fade away... ]
[Shitara]: What's this?
Eh, may I know, what do you do for living?
[Ah, my job, I'm a salaryman]
Ah I see...
[Yes!]
Amazing... eh!?...
Umm..
[Thank you very much!]
Did you think that as a praise?
[No, no, that...]
But...
... having a fight everyday for one year...
... even then, you two are still intimate...
... but surely the fight happens everyday, right?
[That's right...]
... but even then...
... both of you seem expect it...
[Really? So some time later we
just have to fight, like that?]
Since in the end you two feel happy and close everyday.
[That's quite right.]
Perhaps that habit is not a fight.
[Eh! It's not?]
So what do you think that is,
if you have to interpret it?
[Love..]
Problem Solved
I think that's the answer precisely.
[Yes!]
[Thank you very much.]
- Good bye, it was nice talking to you.
- Good bye...
[Thank you]
- You're welcome, bye bye...
[Shitara]: Wait, this is the problem?
[Shitara]: What?
Maaya, what do you think?
If he thought about it himself he must knew the answer, right?
- Guess so.
Let's continue.
- Yes..
The next complaint is...
Hello.
[Hello.]
What's your name?
[Matsutaira.]
How old are you?
[64 years old]
- Ah, 64 years old...
[Shitara]: This is more...
[Shitara]: This is a complaint
from a much older guy!
What's your problem this time?
[It's about my wife.]
[Every morning she always browses the supermarket
to look for some discounted items]
[Cooking should be her job, right?
Even then...]
[... she brought lots of discounted stuff back home]
[That's why she's always tired]
[After that, she smokes. Then the smoke from her cigar... ]
Yes?
[... she blows it to me. That's why...]
[Shitara]: What is this?
[... I said, "Can you
make me some food?"]
[But she won't do it]
- I see...
[The biggest problem now is the fridge... ]
[... it's too stacked, perhaps if a third of the fridge is filled,
don't you think that's bad thing?]
Ah, from the beginning, have you told her
to just fill third of it...
[That's difficult to do, I've told her 3 times
and she still does that... ]
[... she likes to stack]  - She's a "It could be used later" type?   [She's exactly that type]
How does she usually shop?
With car?
[No, with bicycle]
- What if you throw the bicycle away?
[If I do that, I guess she
will ride the car with me]
Isn't that a good thing? Maybe since
she rides a bicycle, she becomes tired afterward.
[Don't you think that will be troublesome for me?]
No that's not good, Matsutaira-san
doesn't have such understanding.
[If we always ride together, it will waste time
since the place isn't that far]
But if you spend some time together,
probably you can eat her cookings.
[So for that thing, maybe I have to give my best?]
Yes, perhaps your wife who's in her sixties
doesn't have a strong physical too.
[Yes, yes...]
- That's why you can go together...
... and when you two are having a meal together,
don't you think it'll taste more delicious that way?
[Ah, I see. So there are task divisions?]
Give her some support.
[Okay!]
[Thank you very much. Do your best!]
Keep supporting her. Thank you.
[Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu, thank you very much]
Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu.
That was amazing.
Some kind of Genius
Eh!?
What? Their fridge?
Because it was Reizouko (fridge),
so I wrote Reizouko (fridge)...
[ Maaya wrote kanji for Rezouko (fridge) wrong.
The sound and the spelling are the same, but there's no meaning ]
This is the right Kanji
Do you know Reizouko (fridge)?   - I know...
Next complaint...
Hello.
[Ah! Hello]
Hello, good afternoon...
[Good afternoon..]
Can you mention your name and your age?
[Sure! Yokota Jinbei, 29 years old.]
[Maiyan]: So cute!
What problem do you have now?
[Okay, I'm having a problem with the CD Debut
for a song I made myself.]
[To express my feeling, this song...]
[... there were many ideas I was getting...]
[... then I turned them into a song,
and I am very confident with this song.]
So you're confident this song will be a success?
[Yes, and...]
[... the title of the song is "Love Message"...]
Can you sing it now?
[Yes, I can. I'll try to sing it now...]
- Please.
[To save some time, I'll sing the short version...]
Suitable with TV duration?
[Wanna meet...]
[But can't...]
[There are many things...
[Akimoto]: What's happening?
... I'm thinking about~]
[Shitara]: There's no melody whatsoever
[Shitara]: His tones are all the same
[Inside...]
[... my head~]
[I'm...]
[... always...]
[... thinking about you~]
[This is...]
[...me....]
[Shitara]: They seriously listen
Is it done?
[Ah, sorry... all of...]
[... my feelings...]
[Like that, I'm sorry.]
- It's okay, I understand. Thank you.
Thank you very much for earlier
You want to do a CD debut with this?
[That's right!]
I see, this...
[Shitara]: Impossible?
... maybe, rather than CD debut,
I guess it'll be better if it's DVD.
[DVD?]
- Yes, if it's just CD, perhaps...
... Yokota-san's appeal won't be visible...
[What should I do?]
Well that depends on what Yokota-san wants...
... which artist inspires you?
[Artist?]
- Yes.
We're talking about a similar act
with said artist here...  [That...]
[... X JAPAN]
[ X Japan = Heavy metal band from Chiba, Japan ]
[X JAPAN...]
- X...
You can make a PV for
"Love Message"...
... then you can upload it to YouTube.
[That...]
[If I exactly copy another artists...]
[... I guess I shouldn't do it]
Have you made some video covers from other artists?
[Yes, I've made it...]
[... about a year ago.]
- Who were the artists?
[Well, I did...]
[... like, video cover of Matchy from Jhonny's.]
[ Matchy = an artist under Jhonny's Entertainment
management, one of big artist agency ]
[Yes, then, video cover of Maeda Atsuko-san too...]
[Shitara]: How did it end?
[About the song, what kind of feeling
emerged earlier?]
About the song?
[Yes!]
I think it's gonna be hard if it's just CD...
... but with LIVE, probably it'll be better.
That's why, started from the LIVE...
[Yes!]
- ... that way, you can get many people's attentions,
then you can do a CD debut after that.
I'm sure many people wanna see
Yokota-san's real performance...
... then, you can also perform other songs.
[Ah, but I do have other songs...]
- Ah, really?
Ah, but for now, just "Love Message" is good enough.
This song is about a desire to meet, right?
[Yeah.]
In this moment, in Japan, there are many songs with theme like this.
Yokota-san can be more aggressive here.
I want Yokota-san to make
the lyric more attracting.
[Oh... I get it...]
[Alright, I understand. Thank you very much.]
Don't lose hope! Good bye.
Nogizaka Koujichuu~
BANANAMAN
Himura Yuuki
Shitara Osamu
Alright, Nogizaka Koujichuu is starting, we're the MC
Bananaman and here are the present members today.
Okay, every episode, we always talk about one member,
this time it's Hashimoto!  - Yes!
Problem consultation?
Then members' problems here now...
... will you solve them too?
- I will take a look at them...   - Really?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Suddenly a unique problem
I am a person who never really think about it too...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Unexpectedly?
I just help those who wants to have
some consultation with me.
That means it could either help or kill?
- We don't know...
But did you do this since forever?
- It's quite famous among fans...
... back on Nogizakatte Doko, when
we had consultations with kids...
That was quite some time ago?
- Yes, when I answered those kids' questions...
... it became famous among my fans.
- I see	.
many of them want to try it like that segment...
I see. Since it's consultation so you answered it truthfully,
but if it's just the usual...
... you couldn't answer it like that?
But she had no bad intention.
Was just thinking positively.
She said, DVD or Live is better than CD,
like that...
... you didn't say, "It's impossible", did you?
He would think it's weird if I said "It's impossible".
- That's right.
Wada, why were you there too?
- Honestly I was thinking about it too...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
That's right
Nanamin herself made some memos from the phone calls...
That's why I thought, should I make some memos too?
Maaya divided one by one messages from that consultation...
... then I asked, "What do you think about this?", like that...
Looking from mature side,
I prefer it to be directly...
About the last one, that musician's dream,
what do you think?
Well, that guy really...
... it's impossible!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Straight to the point!
That was direct.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
It's finally here, what is the super ridiculous problem that Takayama having?
Also tonight, "THAT" dance of Wakatsuki will be shown!?
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
Next, the members will answer
the viewers' problems.
First, Nogitaku-san, 37 years old, male.
He's having a problem in the handshake event
regarding what should he say.
What should he say so he could be remembered?
First, Hashimoto, what should he say?
But this man, when he comes to the event...
... he should think how big is that motivation of his.
If he knows about things we like very much...
... he can preprare things he wants to say first...
... so if he meets someone he loves,
at least he can be remembered...
... not just that, he also can try to attract some attention with
his look, for example using some pins...
... this way he can leave deep impression,
isn't that good?
She's very good!
- Amazing!!!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
S U P E R B !
This is amazing!
- Impressive.
What do you mean with memorable things?
Do you remember what they were wearing?
I remember back then there was someone who came...
... that time, that man showed
his very white teeth.
He put some gum here...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Attracting attention with white teeth?
That... there was someone who did little thing like that too, huh.
He was wearing it...
- But you do remember him?  - Yes!
But my fans too, since I love Cosplay...
... I wore many, like
summer costume or sexy maid...
... when I was wearing some, there was a fan who said
"I want to wear that too"...
Then someone came wearing sexy maid costume...
... if someone did that,
I feel super...
... more stand out.
- If you say that, everyone will come
like that when they're visiting Akimoto...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Costume Parade?
... that seems like a punishment
compared to others...
It's good if he's already in your booth,
but before that, he'll...
... while he's standing with others.
Okay, next. Male, 37 years old, Robotoko.
I can't do the robot dance well.
How to do it?
Now this, I guess there's no one here who can dance like that
- There is!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Maybe there's someone here...
There is someone!
- Really? Who?
None, right? If there is, I wanna see her
comes forward while doing "Wiii~Gacha~" and do the robot dance.
Please step forward!
Wiii~Gacha~!!!
Wii....Gacha!
Wuiiing~~~Gacccha!
There she is. She's here. Oh, very nice!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
ROBOT MASTER
Finally she appears.
Ah, she did it!
- That felt bad, didn't that?
Ah, Wakatsuki...
Sucks, didn't it? Have a seat.
What do you think?
The same thing happened too
on a handshake event a while ago...
... like, "Please do robot dance?"...
... then there was, "I'll do the robot dance",
to made me dance...
... if it's not that, they would also do
BeatBox when they came.  - Ah, sounds good.
But the people who did the robot dance...
... honestly, their movements are all same.
I thought it would be cooler with sound,
but nope, no sounds, everyone were the same.
So it'll be better with sound.
- That's right.
If I can, I want to directly teach those
who come to me on handshake event.
Well open a special class then.
- I guess I should.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
She wants it that way?
If you can do that,
you can resign.
Since then, I also looked it up on Youtube...
... when I saw it on TV, the actual dance wasn't like this.  - Yeah!
Wakatsuki becomes a robot instead.
- Right, even it's a robot dance...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Ordinary Robot
Because you do "Wiii~Gacha", it's not a dance...
- Exactly, there's no dance.
No dance? So you knew that's robot?
After this, there will be a ridiculous problem
from Takayama
From here on, they'll try to solve members' problem together
First, Ikuta's
I lost my belongings very often.
For example, I lost my phone
charger quite often...   - Me too!
... I've lost it three times, then...
... I also thought my makeup was gone, but
after I bought the new one, actually it wasn't gone...
- Uwaa~ it's just there, amirite!
No, no! That sounded wrong! How could you know?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Wearing Make-Up?
Do you use makeups too?
- After we bought the new one, actually the old one is there, like that.
Like, I have 3 same items,
I really can't keep my stuff properly.
Hashimoto, this?
- What do you think?
Well this, in my personal opinion...
... people who forget or lose something easily...
... have a tendency just like rich person.
- Why? Is it because she has a lot of money?
People who worry about nothing,
and want to live freely...
... they don't wanna get bothered by bringing something, and when they go somewhere,
they're used to buy new ones.
Since she's used to be like that, then she doesn't have
a strong feelings toward her belongings...
So, the conclusion?
She has to struggle at least once.
But from here on, how should she struggle?
If it's about phone charger, she must not
lose it for one week.
Himura-san, what about you?
- For me if it's a phone charger...
... after I use it, I roll it then
I put it into my bag, then...
... in the end I forget it completely...
... like when I'm going to use it in dressing room.
That happens frequently.
- Himura's issue regarding
forgetting little things is very chronic.
Since he doesn't see this side, he only brings stuff
here, he forgets that one at all.
For example, I explained and gave him
some material for tomorrow...
... he said "Yes!", he only brought this
and forgot his bag here.
That did happen. Other story, when I was
in a convenience store too...
When I entered, I took
a newspaper and slip it in my armpit...
... then I threw many stuff into the basket,
and went to the cashier...
... I didn't give the newspaper.
After I was done, I brought them home,
and after a while...
... I just realized "Ah, the newspaper.", that happened
few times, but...
... recently, after I put
many stuff into my basket...
... I just went out like that...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Clearly a crime
I said "Ah, no, no! What's this?"...
Then, he rode a car to work once,
but he went home with taxi.
Like an illness.
- You can put it that way.
When I parked at Roppongi...
... then I took some money from bank. And since I was hungry,
I wanted to eat first, then I went on...
... after that I went home,
and didn't remember about my car at all.
I went home with taxi. And since I had a work in 3 hours,
I got some sleep...
... when I woke up and was about to go,
I just realized my car's not there.
I thought, "Ah, somebody stole it!"
I immediately thought that.
- True, it's so bad...
He got DVD Rental fines  2 or 3 times
for 200.000 Yen,...
[ 200.000 yen = about 2k USD ]
He borrowed some...
... then he put it into his cupboard.
Then I forgot...
- Usually it's not like that, right?
Then when he opened it, he went "Ah~!"
So acute.
Ah, I did that too. I went with bicycle...
... I forgot, then I walked home.
- Ah, it's the same...
- Well then, you're Mini Himura. Mini Himura!
Mini Himura
Big Ikuta! I'm Big Ikuta!
Big Ikuta
Why you too? Why do you want it too?
Big Ikuta and Mini HImura...
That's weird!
- Because I'm Big Ikuta.
Next, Takayama's problem is?
I, my back is very stiff,
I can't bend backward...
So that's a problem when you dance?
- Precisely, I'm worried...
Then try to show it now.
Start~!
Really can't bend.
Why tho?
- I don't have a clue, it feels stiff like it's going to break.
Does the same apply to your whole body?
Ah, I can bend forward,
but backward, I totally can't do it...
In Taiyou Knock, there's a dance like this.
When I do this move, I feel pain here.
This what makes me afraid
to dance Taiyou Knock...
Eh? What move?
- This one...
Ta.. ta.. ta.. like this.
- That feels hurt?
I feel a piercing pain on
the lower part of my back...
Ah, it couldn't be bent?
- Feels painful in this stiff part here.
Try to bend your knees
while lowering your back at the same time...
I guess I can do it...
But no, this looks horrible...
So you can do it if you lower your knees?
- Surprisingly yeah.
Like that, start over again.
Ready, go!
Look, bend them even more...
I still can do it.
- Okay.
Bend your knees...
See! It's easier!
Ah, you're right!
- More... do all of it while bending your knees...
- Maybe it'll be better if you keep bending your knees...
Start!
You've stepped up your game!
- Ah, very nice, you got it!
Ah, amazing!
Easier?
- Ah, it's easier!
This one, try to go more...
- Very happy!
Bend them even more?
Pretty good!
- I see.
Down more...
Down.
- Good, very good!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Solved?
Impressive!
- Is this okay?
Just do it like that.
- It's far easier, but...
That's why when you do it alone it looks weird,
but with two people next to you...
... doing the same thing...
Nooo~!
- That's true.
She'll look so poor alone.
- How's the formation?
Nanamin and Asuka.
- So, what if we see those three doing it now?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
New trouble for both who are next to her
3 members to the middle, do it with Takayama...
Nanamin try it.
- Let's see you two's positions.
Sorry, this is for Takayama's sake.
- Forgive me, thank you.
You're friends, right?~
- Friends, right?
You're all best friends, right?
- Start!
This looks terrible!
So it's like that!
Surely if you do it once...
Did you think it was difficult?
- Why?
It was difficult to bend the knees.
This looks bad, she looks like she's gonna cry...
- It's supposed to be like that.
But you can work it out with them.
Determining the 13rd single campaign!
So quick!
It was so quick!
Nogizakatte, Doko? DVD, Oshidoko!
Nogizaka46 movie that made heart beat so fast,
"Kokoro ga Sakebitagattarunda", huge success!
Please see it in theater near you.
Under LIVE perform at Nihon Budokan...
... and Merry Christmas Show 2015, members' second mobile registration,
will be started after this show!
Don't miss this too!
Emergency meeting for 13rd single campaign,
let us all think what they're going to do!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Next week, meeting to determine the 13rd single hit campaign!
The members will present many of their campaign subjects!
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
Not this one...
... but back on Mt. Fuji.
So, me?
- Without parachute.
Finally, what will 13rd single
hit campaign look like?