Brought to you by FlondrapicaSubs (http://flondrapicasubs.tumblr.com/)
Huh?
The world only Kawago knows
Hello, my name is Hironobu Komiya from Sanshiro
Behind me are some members from Nogizaka46!
Yeaaah (*^▽^*) Nice to meet you
Nice to mee~t you
I only made them laugh by greeting them...
So, our teacher for tonight is Hina Kawago
Nice to meet you!
This may be prompt but, Komiya-San, do you like Idols?
Yes, I like them.
Oh, so you like them? Who for example?
Yoko Oginome for example
Rough choice
I also really like idols from the past but..
Oh, so you really like idols in general?
Yes, I like idols but not from a simple point of view
Today, this is our subejct
Things only Kawago knows about: The world of Miss iD
Miss ID?
Oh, you don't know it yet?
I don't know it
Miss ID originally was "Miss Magazine"
Miss Magazine was started in 1982. It was a contest for beautiful girls. It was won by people like Yuki Saito, Kana Kurashina or Kie Kitano
From our members Eto won the last one of the contests
The finalists
Eto-San?
I'm not Eto-San
Eto is not here
This girl also entered the contest before joining Nogizaka46. She was one of the 15 finalists.
Since then, Miss Magazine became Miss iD
The contest has been held 3 times
It's like a usual Idol audition where it's ok if you don't dance or sing
Anyways, anythink is okay
You can be just funny and that's okay
So it's like M-1 Grand-Prix? [a famous Manzai competition]
A comedy festival?
The first time it was done in 2013.
The winner of that year was this person
Tina Tamashiro
I have seen her before..
She is extremely talented
It wasn't yet decided if it should be really called a grand prix
But because of her, it was called a Grand Prix. She is that astonishing!
Tina Tamashiro more than the other candidates made them call the contest a grand prix.
It would have been fine to call it a grand prix from the start
Fundamental issue
Now she models exclusively for ViVi magazine
She's an orthodox model
Usually, I don't really Idols that have a ordinary cuteness to them
Tonight, the idols I will present to you all have something in common.
Bad habits and darker sides
Now, we're going quiet deep into it, right?
Yeah, right now we're going deep into it
I like weird habits and darker aspects of idols
I prefer Idols who say 'I have a boyfriend'
Is there anyone who has a boyfriend now? In Nogizaka..
In Nogizaka46 it's not allowed..
Of these 5, who has a boyfriend right now?
There are no boyfriends  (*≧▽≦)
But with Miss iD, a lot of the girls have dark and weird sides to them
Today I will present my own selection of participants
Oh, sounds interesting
This is the first girl I want to show you
Rie Kaneko
First of all, here looks are cute right?
She's the winner of the 2015 Grand Prix
There are the winners but from those 2..
So it's called a 'Grand Prix' after all
Grand Prix Madness
This girl is cute in a usual way
Yeah, she's cute!
Her style is good too, but..
What's special about her is, she was 8 hours late for her final audition.
Huh, what!?
You don't do that, right?
So why was she late?
She was sleeping
That's what you call proper oversleeping
So after 8 hours she said 'I'm coming now'
She was told to wake up early the next day and come again to the audition
Even though she was late she made an impact
The evening the day before, at the place where set the alarm clock, she was acting out a play scene by herself
It was a fight about why her father didn't wake her up in time. With that act she came back to the audition
Like on the telephone or what?
She has courage like that
Now what I like most about her
A woman hated by other women
So she's like a girl who tries really hard to act cute?
Yeah, she's a girl.
Confirmed that she's a girl?
She put in the wrong words in the formular
Her face is cute but she naturally looks like she wants to flirt, you know what I mean?
We also have that among our members
For example, there's that girl called Manatsu
'That' girl Manatsu
Because Rie's face is Chihuahuah~ish, white and her eyes are round
You're pretty prejucided..
But that's what I like about her
Please show some film of her
So what did you do today?
Judge
I slept...
Even though you had this audition you only slept?
Yes
I will make a fool's blanket
Wait!
You are the worst!
Papa, why didn't you wake me up!?
That really sucks. I don't know what to do..
So, could her good qualities be conveyed?
Everybody, what do you think?
I interrupt
Change of direction
Because this show revolves around me!
Center Pride
Next up is this girl
Rei Kuroyima
She's only 14
In her final inspection she played guitar in a swimsuit
At 14, she brought a guitar and a swimsuit by herself
Asuka went to the Nogizaka46 audition when she was 13 years old
Because somebody told me "Just do it!"
Crosses?
What I really like about this girl is this:
She's awfully cheeky
She's constantly has this attitude where she's looking down at you
At 14, it's ok not to focus on the body
This was her final examination so you should be really nervous
Now let's look at a clip of her's
I'm 13 and I'm doing gravure.
My hobbies are playing the guitar, singing and drawing.
That's all
We have about a minute left.
What!?
You don't need it?
I don't need it, man!
She's tweeting stuff like 'I hate adults'
With no regard for her fans or relations, she will just say what's on her mind
But I'm also like that..
I can do that perfectly
Up next is this girl
Aonami Jun
This girl has an overwhelming aura!
I have done a lot of photo shoots with girls from Miss iD and talked to them a lot during the shoots.
I talked to them alone at events..
When I had a photo shoot with Jun-Chan, I tried to talk to her..
Her aura was overwhelming
Even though she's younger than me, I couldn't say a word
Do we have a clip?
Yes, we have one. Please have a look.
Hello, I'm Aonami Jun.
Today, the filming was very embarrassing.
My future dream is
to buy a house in Germany and to live in Germany.
She always looks like she's not motivated at all
Her voice was extremely tiny..
Try hard to breathe from your stomach!
That expressionless cuteness, it's really natural, right?
I like that about her!
Next up is this girl!
Shizu Mizuno
In 2015 she won the Grand Prix with Rie-Chan
What i like about this girl is
She reminds me of Miyuki Torii
Let's watch a clip of hers
Welcome, I'm Shizu Mizuno
This time, I will show you the Ultra Mizuno Quiz
On the back of the card, I made a mistake
I forgot to draw a hat
I wasn't able to correct my mistake...
So, first question: What is Shizu Mizuno's favorite sword in Dragon Quest?
It's the lightning sword
Did you like it?
She's completely on drugs
Yeah, she's suspicious
She's not in her right mind
She was like this when I met her one time.
We talked at this audition.
And she's always like that? - Yeah!
Was there someone who sticked out to you?
That was a lot of information to process, so I don't know yet..
Can't you just summarize them all in one book?
My goal is to become a goddess of Village/Vanguard [A gimmicky book store chain in Japan]
I want to publish a unique book
You like subcultures and so on?
Yes, I really like subcultures. That's why...
I was born in Kōenji [area of Tokyo famous for subcultures]
Isn't this freakin' exciting?
At Village/Vanguard I want to become a famous person.
That's her goal
So there is no reason for you to be here?
I'm wandering off in that direction lately..
Yuki Himura
Osamu Shitara
Bananaman
These are our members for tonight
What were you doing just now?
I couldn't come up with anything,
But there is something called a Kawago Chop
That was what I was doing
So, the member we're focusing on tonight is Kawago Chop!
You like thing's like that, right?
I love it!
You just presented to us a lot of idols, but we still have some idols left you didn't get to present in the video clip.
The people who appear in the Miss iD contest are awesome but
the judges are also really interesting
I really like them
The first person I want to recommend to you is..
Oomori Seiko. Do you know her?
Oomori Seiko
Singer-songwriter
She does a lot of really interesting things
At her concerts, she will jump into the audience
and kiss them
Her fans?
She also eats while singing
and then throw the food at her audience.
That's right, she has an unusual way of doing things.
Recently, through work I got to meet her
I got the chance to watch her live concert
This person is really something
I really understand why Hina-Chan likes her so much
Kissing? With her fans?
You can do that too, it's totally fine!
If you like it that much....
But.. That's unlike Nogizaka46..
If you like it your manager will be fine with it!
Hm... right..
Kissing is not okay, but eating rice while singing is fine!
That's crazy
She will bring a rice cooker and share the rice
That's something. I have never seen that before!
And you like stuff like that?
That's what I like
There's also an illustrator called Mel Kishida
Oh, you all know him?
Wow, awesome!
This person also was a judge on Miss iD?
Yes, he was but..
In reality he's a really perverted man.
Illustrator  Mel Kishida
That's him!?
He's a man but he likes to touch
He does hugging events
There are events where fans can touch his body
Why doesn't Nogizaka46 do it then too?
If you like it that much..
This show was brought to you by these sponsors
Nogizaka46 under Inspection!!!
We will present information that have been passed on by fans, members and staff on things about Kawago we didn't know yet
Now some information from the informant Inoue
Unbalanced diet!
She doesn't eat most food
She doesn't eat seafood!
Sea food flavour is also not good
Food from Nagazaki like Castella [Japanese sponge cake] and Chanpon is also not eatable for her
On the other side, things she can eat are Natto and rice
But fish from Nagazaki is really tasty!
That maybe.. but..
Is it gross to you? The smell for example?
Yes, it's gross.
But when I think 'Let's eat it'
I can eat it without making an awful expression
But I don't want to just pointlessly eat things
I want to spend my life eating tasty things
Everybody thinks like that, right?
That's what I only want to eat absolutely tasty things
So you only want to eat things that you yourself think are tasty
I try not to eat food from the sea
You don't eat crabs?
I don't
What do you think about Dashi? [Japanese soup stock made from fish]
So when something reminds you of fish..
I also don't like things from the shore
Are there still other things you don't like?
Red meat
Meat that has a redness to it
Things like roast beef..
That's right!
How about swine?
Swine is fine
You have a chance!
She cannot eat cream puffs as well
I thought that she'd like that
How about custard?
Things that are soft from the outside, but are not nourishing, I also cannot eat
So what can things can you really eat then?
I also cannot eat things that stick in my teeth
But that's every food!
I also don't eat snacks or candy
What about potato chips?
I can't eat that also..
Have you never eaten Kyabetsu Taro? [Japanese snack food]
I have never eaten it!
And Umai Bou?
So you can't answer the question what flavour you like?!
I cannot
What flavour do you like?
One.. Two..
Salami
Close friends
While we're at it, let's hear what kind of food the other members don't like to eat
First, what things doesn't Takayama like to eat?
You will eat anything, right?
I don't like to drink water
Wait, you have to be kidding me?!
She doesn't like to drink water!?
My teeth would hurt..
From drinking water!?
I also don't like to eat Japanese style curry
But I really like Thai style curry
But I don't really like Japanese style curry
What exactly is Japanese style curry?
Tell us about that first
For Himura, every curry served in Japan is Japanese style curry
There is Thai curry and Indian curry...
I can eat curry while putting in on Nan bread but Japanese curry..
Why don't you eat it?
When it has cooled down, doesn't it feel really rough in your mouth?
Uh, I get it!
Somehow, you don't like American food as well?
Ah, that's right, I don't like to eat it.
Because I don't like fries
I have never ordered it, since I was born
Why don't you like fries?
I don't really like things that are fried..
What about potatoes that have not been fried?
I love potatoes
My mother is a pretty good cook
Even back in the past I didn't like fried food
But my father really loves them
That's why everyday on his way home, he would buy dishes from the super market
How about Karaage? [Japanese style fried chicken]
In Boso we have a shop called 'Chicken Basket'
I can eat the Karaage from there but not from anywhere else
But it's the same everywhere
But Chicken Basket is freakin' tasty!
That Chicken Basket!
They have this thing called Nakapan, that's really delicious
You could also eat other fried stuff apart from that Nakapan
NO NO NO NO NO ∩(︶▽︶)∩
How about KFC?
I have never eaten there
But Hoshino is also similarly picky like me
For example I also don't like to drink water
I also don't like curry
But I overcame my dislike of water and curry
So, what doesn't Hoshino like to eat?
I don't like carbonated water and popcorn
Eh, but it's so tasty!
Originally, I didn't like to drink juice
So I only drank tea
The first time I drank a carbonated drink
I didn't like that it tingled my throat
I have tried some carbonated drinks but..
The only drink I haven't drank yet is Cola
Not even once since you were born!?
After this, Hoshino will drink cola for the first time in her life
That's the first cola in her life
Let's go!
This is awful. I don't know what to do
But this is just Cola!
Tasty
Did you just that it's tasty?
No, I can't drink this!
Try some again but drink it slowly
I don't like it
Have some
Is it alright?
You can drink the Cola
Ahh.. 」(￣▽￣」)
Sorry about that, please edit that out
Tasty, man!
Hoshino, it should be like that!
But it feels weird in the throat
But how do you drink your whiskey then?
Why would you think she likes to drink Highball?
Soda assumption of a drunkard
Let's hear what Fukagawa doesn't like to eat
I don't like to eat it celery
I have a trauma
When I was little, I watched a foreign TV show for children
Celery was dipped into peanut butter...
I know what you're talking about!
They were eating it and it looked delicious
So I asked my mother to make some celery with peanut butter for me
So I ate my first celery then but.
But I was shocked by how different it tasted from what I was expecting
That's why I don't eat it
So, you also cannot eat peanut butter?
I like peanut butter but
You only hated the celery?
I only hate the celery
So let's give the members who hate celery or haven't eaten it yet a taste!
Actually, we will not force you to do it but
why don't we try some of the celery with peanut butter?
I want them to eat it
First up is Shinuchi, who hates celery on its own
From the smell of the celery alone, I can't really do this..
The smell is horrible to you too?
How is it?
Huh!?
This might be tasty
Overcoming
Next up is Nagashima, who doesn't like to eat celery since her childhood
She's done it
We understand, continue
It's just a fresh vegetable
It's eatable
Peanut magic
The next challenger is Takayama, who has never eaten celery before
I'm eating it for the first time right now
Whaat iz thiz!? Σ(´д ` ﾒ)
The inner, white part is tasty
The inner white part is tasty?
Matsumura who loves celery will now try some of the celery
This is freakin' awful
The smell may be awful but try to chew it first
But she likes celery, right?
I love celery!
Doesn't make sense
This is so awful!
This is totally fine