Nogizaka Koujichu.
13rd single hit campaign
Yay........
Timer : Oca
Now four of us,
are going to do what Ikoma presented earlier.
To get to the most difficult temple to reach in Japan.
TL Jpn - Indo : Tifa-sama
In order to be a hit,
there will be a recording to promote the newest single.
TLC : Mugy
We will pick themes from members for this time's promotion.
QC : Alpecka
Previously, Hoshino and Asuka successfully
ran and ascending the hill.
Next is...
What these four members are going to do,
known as the best power spot in Japan.
They are going to pay Ohta Temple a visit
which is located in Hokkaido.
Encode&Upload : Aditya Bagus
We did a recording when we climbed Mount Fuji earlier.
- And you did a scuba...
- Skydiving.
Different kind of diving
Skydiving, climbed the Buddha statue, and bungee.
- We all have done some amazing promotions.
- We gave our best.
From the number one bungee in the world to climb the Mount Fuji,
these four have done it.
They all have done
some very difficult promotions.
And the guide who will
take them to the temple...
Guide
Morishita -taro
Onegaishimasu.
- You can see it...
- Can we see it?
Up there.
Up there you can see a hole to the left.
That's where we're going.
- There?
- Really?
This is the same as climbing a mountain.
Climbing a very difficult mountain.
Long story short,
a short yet difficult trip.
Eh...
That does seem like it.
Perhaps this will feel like climbing Mount Fuji
when we're going through a very difficult zone.
Feels like it's going on and on.
Let's start this time's promotion recording.
Okay, we're here.
The stairway looks high in a glance...
It's not normal when
there's a rope there.
They've realized it.
We still can't see the end
even if we crouch.
And the red description on that board,
"We're not responsible for any accident".
Will there be accidents?
- There's a snake warning there.
- Yeah that's a snake warning all right.
This sounds like a joke.
To get to the temple, first they will go through...
a very high stairway and narrow enough to step.
One wrong move can make them
fall and tumbling down to the bottom.
Ikuta suggests something when
they're climbing the stairway.
Counting the steps?
- Sounds good, we'll answer together when we're up there.
- Let's do it.
This looks pretty dangerous.
Finally four of them take
a first step to the temple.
Here I go.
How do we get up there?
This is scary,
if we fall then...
You'll fall if you don't
hold on to the rope.
Are you counting the steps?
19,20.
This is just the start.
All these countings make me confused.
They're using a muttering tactic
while counting the steps.
But,
since the stairs are steep,
their physical conditions
are being drained.
What's with that stairs?
- This is pretty dangerous.
- So difficult.
Makes this heartbeat...
This feels like doing an offering
to the gods.
The stairs are getting narrower above.
And getting steeper too.
It's not big enough to stand on.
If we fall here...
A sudden start with
a physical condition draining activity.
Finally they're stepping above.
What's this...
Ah they're there.
Where should we stand?
So it feels like that?
Eh...
Very dangerous.
So narrow.
Ikuchan, how many did you count?
143 steps.
Approximately 135 steps.
And the correct one is...
There are 139 steps total.
Ikuchan is 4 steps too many.
Useless countings.
I thought there were 135 steps.
Without taking a break after climbing the stairs.
Climbing a steep hill.
Yosha...
- What's this.
- Dangerous.
And then,
Wooo so dangerous.
Are you okay?
Akimoto Theater, unveiled.
Looks like she did it
on purpose.
Wait a sec.
So slippery here.
This seems harder than Mount Fuji.
Moreover,
There's a valley to your right...
Alright.
Very dangerous.
Please hold on to the rope.
- This is so frightening.
- Indeed.
There's rope everywhere
- There's only a small path.
- This isn't even a path.
Right.
And what's visible next for those four is...
Stairs used to ascend.
This is the only place
to ascend.
The first one to
ascend the stairs is Akimoto.
Wow.
Very steep.
How could this thing be here?
- Scary.
- This is awesome.
After Akimoto's done, next is...
This seems dangerous.
It's so slippery here.
It does look very slippery.
Do Fukagawa's feet
start to get tired?
Then Ikuta's turn to ascend.
What is this?
And last one is Nishino.
Hahaha...
This is fun.
But the tough field still continues.
Ikuta who looks tired,
starts doing something...
Aaa.... Aaaaa.....
What?
Waaa... Mooo....
Yoooo.... Ahhh....
Wait,
what's with her?
Yooo.... Aaa.....
I can't do this
if I don't make sound like that.
And Ikuta starts to change...
Yooo....
Yoooo.....
Ikuta Kabuki
Kabuki : one of Japan's traditional drama
One step at a time.
YOO....
She's at her limit.
Nice.
On the pathway to the temple,
this very tough road is the most difficult one.
While going on,
their energies are being drained a lot.
From here on, the path will be harder.
Be careful with landslide and rocks.
- Papanya pun jatuh
- Berbahaya sekali.
We'll be dead if we fall down there.
Does she want to fall
or something?
Just after she said,
"dead if we fall dowm there"...
- Right.
- Go on.
Ahh.... that was so shocking...
Welcome to the theater.
That looks on purpose.
Of course.
There's something there.
This is "Women Temple".
Back then women can't go
beyond here.
But now it's fine.
Back then, this was
the last place women could reach.
Temple for women
and also a place to take a break.
Here..
Akimoto P will evaluate the trip they just did.
We already have mental image about the danger.
But Naachan says she can keep going.
Up until now it's okay,
but it'll be more difficult after this.
Perhaps it will keep like that.
An experienced person is talking
"4 surviving people",
they'll use that for the narration.
True.
Just like what Akimoto said.
The road ahead is longer.
Since the pictures taken almost the same,
it will be covered with narration.
Woo...
That wasn't on purpose!
After climbing the mountain
for almost 2 hours...
Members see something...
It's been 2 hours.
There's a toori.
Toori : Shinto temple gate.
Are we there yet?
Eh...
- This is the entrance gate.
- For the hard-to-reach place.
This rocky place is a border
between the woods and the rocks.
We're going to climb
even further.
- They're there.
- It starts from here.
We're here.
Now we'll be using harness and helmet.
Is it that dangerous?
If you fall then you'll be dead.
Let us take our last picture.
That's good of you
for saying that.
Last photo?
Here I go.
3 2 1...
Then they will pray
for the success to the gods.
And now it starts to rain here.
The rain is quite hard.
Suddenly it's raining hard.
We have to be careful here.
It was raining hard too
when we were climbing Mount Fuji.
Although the situation has worsen...
With the sudden rain,
they keep continuing the trip.
Eh...
Why?
What's this?
Is this safe?
What members see is a bridge.
After passing this,
they will arrive at their destination.
But with this rain...
Since it's quite slippery here,
please don't step onto the rope.
If you do then you may slip.
And there's no handle in the middle.
Please hold the lower part.
It looks small.
Here I go.
A bad moment to step.
The first one to go is Akimoto.
Wa... Scary.
Wow this is amazing.
Dangerous, this is scary.
It's alright.
Waa... scary.
There's nothing to hold on there.
Waaa scary.
They have came this far,
they definitely can do this.
Is this place okay to visit?
Okay let's start.
Next to go is Fukagawa.
Don't look there.
Waa.. scary.
You can't move on
if it's not one step at a time.
Where's the handle?
Dangerous...
While looking there.
Please don't let that hand of yours go.
Her movements are messy.
But Fukagawa is able to move forward.
Finally arrived.
Ah !
You did it Fukagawa
It's still scary
even though you're there
Then Nishino and Ikuta calmly
pass the bridge.
Finally.
Uwa.... Awesome.
This is amazing.
That's where we did the opening earlier.
- It's been that far.
- Exactly.
We started from there.
What's this?
Wait.
We're going up with this?
This feels like a ruse.
Last place before their destination,
they have to climb a 7 meters cliff.
Can you climb with that?
If they can climb this cliff,
they can reach the temple.
But...
The irons are quite fragile.
- Which part?
- Everything.
All of the irons are fragile.
What?
So it's all fragile?
Bad weather and fragile irons.
The first one to climb is Akimoto.
- This is scary.
- Be careful.
From here,
it looks dangerous back there.
This is very scary.
Careful.
This is impossible to climb.
Very scary.
Impossible.
Better put your legs here.
Is it okay here?
Ikoma picked a good place.
Don't move too much.
This is really scary.
That looks frightening.
This place is awesome.
Don't look down.
Looks scary down there.
Seems dangerous...
After climbing for 10 minutes.
Finally.
Next person.
Next, Nishino climbs the 7 meters cliff.
Here... wait this is scary.
They can't go back, it's been this far
Strength and endurance have been drained.
Also out of energy.
Nishino battles this cliff slowly.
Finally I'm here.
That was scary.
I'm at loss of word...
This is scary.
Next to climb is Fukagawa.
Fight, fight.
Yeah this is scary.
Why it has to be this place.
You have to use the equipments smartly.
Why do we have to climb this?
Nogizaka have passed many tall walls.
There's no unpassable wall.
And four of them will show it.
Amazing.
I've arrived.
Thankfully I'm alive.
Last one to climb is Ikuta.
Ah.... Ah...
Why do we have to climb this?
Nogizaka's target is to always move forward.
And their destination this time is...
The top.
This time, these four is trying to go to the top.
They climb this with every inch of their power.
And then...
Yoo... Finally I'm here.
At long last.
Finally they've arrived at Ohta Temple.
A Power Spot that has existed for 500 years.
The hardest place to reach in Japan.
The holiest place in Japan.
And there's a miracle after they reach the top.
The rain has stopped.
- Yeah.
We can even see there.
That rain was like a joke.
What a gorgeous view.
Hopefully the 13rd single can be a hit.
Suddenly you have something on your neck.
It was a present from Ikuchan.
And usually when you descend the mountain,
the trip back won't be showed.
That's pretty bad.
So happy.
They're showing it.
Scary.
How's it now?
Descending is scary.
We're going down.
That hurts...
They're so fast.
It'll be bad if someone got left behind.
So dangerous...
If we're going down,
only the back part will get recorded.
There's the stairs!
Finally we're here.
These hands and legs have no strength anymore.
We did it.
- Ikuta can't be seen.
- Hah, 20 minutes later?
I did it.
You did your best, are you okay?
13rd single campaign,
Success!
Awesome.
Well then let's start Nogizaka Koujichu.
We're Bananaman.
Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu.
And here's Nogizaka-chan.
Okay.
So let's start this,
that was a place Ikoma showed.
That temple, was it difficult?
- Very difficult.
- We know that just by looking.
It's not really shown by that video.
Dissatisfaction?
Maybe...
- Which part was the hardest?
- The last one.
The irons are connected there.
So the irons will keep swaying around.
- Was it so difficult?
- Dangerous either.
Also about that place,
we didn't know where the irons were.
We had to touch around so we could grab it.
Felt like we had to fight hard to reach the top.
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY sekaiichisub.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
The camera always followed Ikuchan.
It never followed me.
I went up all alone.
This girl talks too much.
In the end,
there was something on your neck.
Did you prepare something before the trip?
Ah true.
I brought the flower leis from that Mount Fuji trip.
- That time I also wanted to bring them again.
- Were those the very same stuff?
Mine was.
I see.
And other members too...
... they were looking for the same leis,
but there were only Halloween stuff.
So they decided to bring them instead.
That's why their leis were sparkling.
That was spontaneous, right?
Quick image change.
What about Nishino?
I brought Doiya-san,
attached to my bag.
I saw it.
Was that a protection charm?
No I just wanted to bring it.
No reason.
Perhaps you really wanted to bring it.
- It's not like that.
Is that so?
It just attached to the bag.
Then we went up together.
Like if you faced a hardship, would you tell Doiya?
- No it's not like that.
Like, you say "let's climb together".
If we climbed together...
- So there's a reason?
"It's not like that" is the right answer here.
Since we climbed together...
The Doiya-san you made is a god, kinda, right?
A god of that white part of earpick.
So you wanted to clash the gods?
- No it's not like that.
Still no reason until the end.
Why did you bring it then?
Fukagawa.
I brought a small camera.
It could print photos immediately.
You wanna sell the pics?
Selling?
No it's for my own use.
Akimoto, what did you bring.
I brought cookies.
Heee Cookies?
I made 4 cookies with
46 please be a hit written on them.
I gave them one each,
then we climbed.
But it wasn't being shown at all.
Yeah unlike the others'.
It wasn't shown even 1mm.
- Did that take up too much time?
- There was drawing too.
She also drew Kouhaku
with read and white.
- Why was it not being shown?
- Right.
I wonder why.
Like, got the picture taken by Fukagawa's camera.
You didn't have to do that.
Shocked
No need?
That hurts my heart.
Seems like it's not needed.
To cheer the studio, let us
see the cookies for a while.
After this, there will be other stories.
After climbing the stairs last week, Hoshino...
In the beginning at the stairs part...
... the stairs looked so tall.
So you climbed it together.
I thought, "what should I do?"
Even the steps are very small.
And the safety too.
It's just the stairs look similar.
And it doesn't kill you either.
When we watched that,
you all looked like a descending bulldozer.
We wanna get massaged
too like Hoshino's presentation earlier.
But you did receive many services there, right?
Although we were in Hokkaido,
we didn't eat the specialty there.
From the airport.
to the temple just now.
it needs five hours with car.
Shocking confession.
From Chitose airport?
Five hours with car
from Chitose to that place?
Were you in the wrong airport?
Wrong airport?
How long were you there?
2 days 1 night.
It didn't feel like Hokkaido.
Didn't feel like Hokkaido?
There wa a small nabe.
This.
Eh why?
Nabe with chicken.
But you paid onsen a visit, right?
No, no.
Just in the hotel.
Was there any onsen?
Was there any onsen with chicken like that?
Onsen version of this?
No it's not like that,
it's like a big soup.
That way they could eat to their hearts' content.
- It's just a big soup.
Hitori de iru no ga ichiban rakudatta
Hi
Can these four catch a fish?