m 0 0 l 0 40.5 l 3 40.5 l 3 0 l 0 0 m 3 0 l -6 0 l -6 9 l 24.125 9 l 24.125 6 l -3 6 l -3 3 l 0 3 m 3 3 m 24.125 0 l 24.125 40.5 l 27.125 40.5 l 27.125 -1.5 l 24.125 -1.5 m 33.25 0 l 33.25 0 l 36.25 0 l 36.25 16.5 l 28.625 16.5 l 28.625 13.5 l 33.25 13.5 l 33.25 3 l 22.625 3 l 22.625 0 m 9 27 l 9 18 l 18.125 18 l 18.125 21 l 12.125 21 l 12.125 27 l 9 27 m 18.125 27 l 18.125 30 l 9 30 l 9 27 l 15.125 27 l 15.125 21 l 18.125 21 l 18.125 27 m 7.5 10.5 l 12.125 13.5 l 10.625 15 l 6 12 l 7.5 10.5 m 15.125 13.5 l 15.125 13.5 l 19.625 10.5 l 21.125 12 l 16.625 15 l 15.125 13.5 m 4.5 36 b 4.5 36 4.5 34.5 4.5 34.5 b 10.625 31.5 16.625 31.5 22.625 34.5 b 22.625 34.5 22.625 37.5 22.625 37.5 b 16.625 34.5 10.625 34.5 4.5 37.5
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
Nogizaka Koujichuu!
BANANAMAN
Himura Yuuki
Shitara Osamu
DON! Well, Nogizaka Koujichuu has started, we are the MC, Bananaman, Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu.
With them, Nogizaka-chan.
Onegaishimasu!
Today, we discuss the new song's campaign.
Who was involved?
-Who went?
-Who?
-Us, The Fishing Team
-Fishing Team?   -Yes!
Who said that she couldn't ride a boat...
Me.
- No way I could go fishing
- Couldn't go fishing?
But, after I listened to Shitara-san's advice to overcome seasickness...
- That advice to drink Brandy, right.
- No, no. Not that.
[Yujiro = Yujiro Ishihara, an actor and singer with
his famous song, Brandy Glass]
That's great. That's like Yujiro!
For the latest single release, they did some recordings to wish for success.
This time, we use three types of campaigns from the members' presentation.
Previously, Hoshino and Saitou Asuka
have run through Sakamichi.
We wish for great success!
Nishino, Fukagawa, Ikuta and Akimoto successfully wished for the single's success....
...at the most extreme temple in Japan.
Then, this time, Shiraishi, Etou, Hashimoto and Takayama,...
...following the plan from Fukagawa, wished for success by gathering food...
...to seek better luck, by attempting
Shusse-uo challenge, but...
So, you girls went to take that.
Color Code
Maiyan Kazumin Misa Nanamin
- Are you serious!?
- Why this condition?!
Campaign for the 13th single success!
Following the plan of Fukagawa Mai,
Let's gather food that brings good luck!
YAY!!!
Right now, it's five minutes to six o'clock in the morning.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Area in front of Miura City port.
- Good morning!
- Unfortunately, it's raining now.
- It's really...
- It's hard to open our eyes...
- Right, need much effort for that.
Wind and heavy rain, a weather that's almost impossible to set sail in
That day, the weather was very poor. A condition that made it almost impossible to sail.
- The weather is clearly bad!
- This is terrible!
INADA
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
Shusse-uo type fish, according to its size, the name of this fish changes from
"INADA" - "WARASA" - "BURI", analogical to change of fate into a better one
This time, the fish targeted by these four people are INADA.
[Shusse-uo : Fish whose name changes when it grows bigger]
Shusse-uo type fish, whose name changes
according to its size, is said to bring good luck
I see!
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
However, a young BURI fish type can reach
a length of 50 cm and weighing up to 1 kg!
But, even its small fish can reach
a length of 50 cm and weight 1 kg
By fishing, we will try to get some fishes...
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
Must successfully catch fishes later
Fishing Note
...for the success of this single.
We will try to get a lot of fishes...
And because this is the 13th single...
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
Everyone must be able to catch 13 fishes in total!
Success Prayer
...if possible, we have to get 13 fishes.
So, let's do our best.
TARGET
Can they fish it?
Leaving with a target of Shusse-uo "INADA" fishes
With the target of Shusse-uo fish
that brings good luck, they set sail!
Condition like this, really bad, isn't it?
While in the recording that time, Shitara-san...
...recommended sunglasses, to overcome seasickness...
...so that's why, I bought it yesterday.
Big wave made the boat shook violently!
However, as soon as they left, due to
big wave, the boat shook violently.
So like this...
We gradually feel the rain more.
This side, really heavy!
UWAAAA~
That bad?
Amazing!
This is really heavy!
This is scary!
- Are you alright?
- It's alright.
Kazumin! Are you still alive?
Fishing Shusse-uo "INADA" fish, START!
After 20 minutes, finally they reached the fishing spot.
The fishing of Shusse-uo INADA, starts!
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
Fishing rod is shaken to spread bait from the tube that is underwater
How To Fish INADA
[INADA : Japanese Amberjack that's still young
(Seriola quinqueradiata)]
I have no idea...
...is it eaten already?
Maybe it is!
There's something, right?
Is that so?
What?
Really? Seriously!
Failed, it seems...
Nothing!
Damn!
Here, something happened to Hashimoto's rod!
There's something...What's this?
Does this mean I've fished something?
But this doesn't feel heavy.
Do I only have to keep doing this way?
Clearly something was caught by Hashimoto.
Did she get INADA?
I roll it up!
What is it?
What's this?
Ordinary seaweed
What is it?
Seaweed?
I get nothing at all.
How will this turn out...
Ah, nothing at all!
In a storm like this, can it
be fished?
Difficult.
The Fisher "Etou" has her own plan!
Here, Etou the "Fisher", got an idea.
As expected from her!
Perhaps, fish also...
...perhaps in the "Fishing Interaction", I didn't lure it well enough!
"Fishing Interaction".
So, I got nothing.
Maybe that's why.
She also "Seduced" fish
I just realized it.
Hey, fish...
...hey, fish. Come here!
Etou tried to "Seduce"  fishes under the sea
Etou showed how to lure fish underwater. Then...
Feels like something is exciting!
This, serious?
Ah, there is! Feels like something is there!
What should I do? Should I roll it?
- Ah, good! Good! Good!
- Gotcha!
Big! Certainly big!
Good! Good! Good!
Really? Fished already?
- Pull up the rod! Can you?
- Yes!
With her better "Fishing Interaction", can
she successfully get Shusse-uo fish?
What is it?
Already fished?
Maybe it is fished.
Ah, it got away!
Ah! Hooray!
I did it! Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Something is caught.
I got it!
- Wah, she got it!
- Great!
ISAKI
[ISAKI : Chicken Grunt fish
(Parapristipoma trilineatum)]
First caught fish is ISAKI.
Shiromi type fish, delicious to be cooked
as Sashimi or grilled.
Then, Hashimoto also successfully caught something.
Ah, gotcha! What should I do?
Right, this is like
fishing recording.
Roll it?
We don't know what is caught.
Keep rolling! Pull it up!
I have rolled it.
Can it be pulled up already?
What is it?
Ah here it is! I got it!
Fished!
What's this?
That's perhaps the target.
Fished! Ah, no! Scary!
What? What type of fish is this?
- That's ISAKI.
- ISAKI?
This is the first time I managed to catch a fish.
Eh, but of course I'm happy.
A group of ISAKI started to be lured and  struck the bait!
Suddenly, they found a group of ISAKI
Then, these fishes immediately eat the distributed baits.
But, that's pretty good.
Next, slowly they feel disappointed
about the fishes they caught.
Everyone got it?
Takayama also got it, right?
ISAKI again!
Ah, so you again...
INADA
Shusse-uo
Then, actually where is INADA
the Shusse-uo fish?
You really wanted INADA,
right?
Then, Takayama's rod, right now
feels like catching a big fish!
What?
Is it INADA?
Even Kazumin's rod is bent that much!
For sure, she gets it for sure!
Seems like a big catch.
She gets something! For sure!
She gets INABA. That's its name right?
Kazumin, you must have caught the target!
That must be our target! I'm so sure!
Pull it up! Pull it up!
This must be INADA!
- Pull it up! Good, good!
- Kazumin, you can do it!
Why is she so calm?
Silent.
Why don't you move?
Kazumin, you certainly get it, you know!
Why not rolled it?
Kazumin, try to show some spirit too!
No reaction.
Try to roll it! roll!
You didn't get any trouble, right?
It's a bit difficult...
Really? But, that was great, you know!
Go! Go!
Try to pull it up.
What do I get?
Clearly this is heavier, not like ISAKI.
In the end, will she successfully catch it?
Ah, here it comes!
Not ISAKI.
Ah, different, right?
What is this?
It's blue!
Great!
It's SOUDAGATSUO.
Bonito?
- I got Bonito fish!
- Bonito?
- Right!
- Great!
Great!
- Big!
- Really big!
She managed to catch Bonito fish!
I got Bonito fish~
- Wah, you got Bonito?
- Yes.
SOUDAGATSUO
[SOUDAGATSUO : One kind of Bonito/Tuna fish]
What she just caught is SOUDAGATSUO.
Big!
Small Bonito fish, which is included in Tuna family.
Later, Shiraishi also seemed to catch a big fish.
Is it certain that she catches INADA?
Maybe INADA!
- Caught already?
- Perhaps this is your good luck.
- Really?
- It can be, you know!
INADA! INADA!
I have no idea about what this is.
Seen from its pull to the rod,
this is a big fish!
So, what fish has she caught?!
Big!
INADA! INADA!
Try to move it that way.
AH! Big! Big! Big!
Wah, that's so big!
- Wah, awesome!
- What's that?
This is obviously big!
Ah, I got it!
- Eh, cool!
- What is this?
What's this?
Ah, I got INADA!
- Great!
- INADA is successfully caught!!!
INADA!
Awesome!
I got INADA!
- Success!
- Yey!
As expected from her!
It's flapping its mouth.
This one is as expected!
Target done!
INADA
Successfully reaching the target
in Nogizaka is Shiraishi.
Shusse-uo INADA with a length of about 50 cm,
has been caught!
A short time later, this time Etou
also seemed to catch a big fish!
I got it! I got it, you know!
INADA! INADA!
Heavy! This feels heavy!
Eh, it's heavy!
The feeling when you get fish,
unique, right?
Okay, I pull up the rod.
Seems like INADA!
Wah, awesome!
Awesome!
This is INADA.
- I made it!
- What's that?
- Wow, it is trying to run away!
- I made it!
Is it INADA?
Is that INADA?
How's that?
There it is! There it is!
INADA!
INADA...INADAWA~
"INADAWA"!
Finally appears.
INADAWA appears!
INADA
Clearly it's Shusse-uo fish, she has caught INADA!
Wah, big!
Its length reached 51 cm, weighing about 1 kg.
It will be BURI soon.
I get no signs at all of going to catch INADA!
However, eventually Hashimoto also caught one.
It's coming! It's coming! It's coming!
She's fishing well!
Will they get INADA 3 times in a row?
Go! Go!
Must be INADA!
What did she get?
Eh, it is already caught, isn't it?
Ah, ISAKI again! This is ISAKI again.
Ah, ISAKI, right?
How come, seems like I become ISAKI Master here.
ISAKI Master.
Until now, she has caught only ISAKI.
However, Hashimoto kept fishing.
How many already?
Caught already? Ah, got it!
Always the same fish.
Hashimoto who keeps on catching ISAKI
She kept fishing until she got 17 of them.
17 fishes in a row
ISAKI
Isaki Girl
Miura Peninsula
Already going this way, she has become
like the ISAKI Girl from Miura Peninsula
It's an interesting nickname!
Why do I only get the small ones?
Ah, really small.
Ah, look at it! So cute.
- So cute!
- Look, cute.
It looks pitiful though.
So cute, this thing...
Is this SUZUMEDAI?
[SUZUMEDAI: A kind of Damselfish fish (Chromis notata)]
Kazumin, look!
- Ah, what's that?
- This is SUZUMEDAI.
So cute!
It looks pitiful...
Bye Bye...
Ah, she released it, right.
"SUZUMEDAI" is released back to the sea
Shiraishi was kind enough to release the small fish back into the sea, but...
It is so small, so I...
Are you kidding me!!!
Law of nature.
Eh! What a pity!
Are you kidding me?!
Suddenly just now!
- Unbelievable!
- Eh, this is miserable!
The small fish got bitten!
That fish...
Even though I released it out of pity...
A sad ending.
It was unlucky, I guess?
- It's such a mess.
- Looks like Maiyan is upset from catching only small fish.
That's not true!
Alongside Shiraishi who is upset,
Takayama seems to catch a big fish!
INADA, come!
Heavy! This feels heavy! Heavy!
Go! Go! Go!
- Looks like a big catch!
- Kazumin, looks like you get a big one!
Big! Big! This must be big!
- Isn't this big?
- Is that Tuna?
Wah, wah, this seems big!
Kazumin, it's Tuna, isn't it?
Was that really Tuna?
Looks like it is, Tuna!
Maybe, Tuna?
- Big!
- Great!
What did she got?
Awesome!
That's it! Wow, you just caught a big one!
- Wah, INADA!
- Finally!
Big! Wah, I like this!
Isn't it INADAWA, right, Etou!
- INADA!
- Great!    - What? What?
She fished until like that.
Eh, that's so big!
Great! Kazumin, you made it!
INADA, finally caught~!
Awesome!
Wah~ How big!
If you get that, you must
be happy, right?
Isn't that big?
INADA
Finally, Takayama also got Shusse-uo INADA.
This is the heaviest today.
Fishing Time Over
Fishing time is over here.
Everyone went back ashore then.
We're back from fishing!
Good job, all of you~
Good job, all of you!
And these are the fish that we've caught.
-Great!
- Big!
Got a lot.
We caught these earlier.
We got 3 INADAs...
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
INADA 3 Fishes - SOUDAGATSUO 2 Fishes - ISAKI 40 Fishes
Today's Fishing Result
...2 SOUDAGATSUOs, and
40 ISAKIs.
That means, in total, 45 fishes.
- Ah, almost, need one more fish.
- Ah, that's true!
Didn't reach 46.
Wah, awesome!
Only if there was one more...
Earlier I got one fish, that small one.
What fish was it...
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Suzumedai which was eaten
by a seagull
- Which immediately struck by a sea gull
- That's right!
If we put that in here, it becomes 46 fishes.
- That's right, you got that earlier.
So then, we get 46 fishes.
Awesome!
Amazing! This is a miracle!
- Awesome!
- It becomes "Fourty Six".
The fishes from fishing that we got!
Then, the fishes they caught this time,
will be given to...
...Kyouka-san, a traditional Japanese restaurant, to be cooked.
This is good! Perfect!
Grilled ISAKI With Salt
First, ISAKI which were fished a lot,
is ordinarily grilled, with some salt.
Isn't it good.
Yummy.
This has the proper seasoning, right?
- So yummy!
- Its flesh is crunchy.
INADA
SOUDAGATSUO
We will serve it as Sashimi!
Next, INADA and SOUDAGATSUO.
Please enjoy.
- Awesome!
- Here, INADA...
INADA
Then here, thinly sliced, SOUDAGATSUO.
SOUDA GATSUO
Then, this one in the middle,
the pride of this restaurant, CHUTORO.
CHUTORO
That's bonus for you.
And its kind...
- This is included...
- Wait, wait a sec!
Its kind, Premium class Tuna.
Premium class Tuna Sashimi
Well, please enjoy!
How about we also enjoy the other ones?
The main menu is still the fishes that were caught.
Right, there is also on this side.
INADA Sashimi
First, let's enjoy INADA, Shusse-uo fish.
- Let's eat.
They look like relaxing, right?
They look like enjoying it, right?
Yummy!
Really tasted when bitten.
Its oil and crunchy texture.
- So delicious~!
- Really delicious!
Not disappointing, this is delicious!
Standard class and Premium Class Tuna Bonus
Then, they enjoy the bonus,
Premium class Tuna, and...
Fish from different class.
- Ehm~!!
- Delicious?
Ehm~!!
Ehmmm~!!!
That delicious?
Showing a different reaction.
- Melts! Melts in the mouth!
- It's gone...
What's this?
The meaning of fishes that we caught today,
we win against rival, in the Katsuo fish (Katsu = win).
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Win against rival (Souda Gatsuo)
Then also success, (Shusse = success)
in the INADA fish.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Success
(Shusse-uo INADA)
Then, beginning the rise of good luck, (Saisaki = good luck)
from ISAKI fish, that we have caught earlier.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Beginning the rise of better luck (ISAKI)
I think we have done this awesome
success wishing successfully...
...so, let's keep struggling from now on.
Campaign for 13th Single's Success...
...Following the plan from Fukagawa Mai
Let's gather food that brings luck...
BIG SUCCESS!
INADA! INADA! INADA!
So delicious!
So, although they looked for INADA,...
- ...eventually they got a lot of ISAKI.
- That's right.
- Then, the condition there was pretty bad.
- Right, right.
Because this is the 13th single, they
wanted to catch 13 fishes, but...
- ...unexpectedly, they got 46 fishes.
- Wasn't that amazing?
- Amazing!
- This is "Fourty Six", right?
Awesome, there's something here!
- At least, 46 copies of this single will be sold for sure.
- Oh!
Wait, Himura-san! You too
don't say "Oh!"
If 46 copies only, that's horrible,
freakin' horrible!
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Smells like group will disband.
However, it can be said that
it's quite awesome.
Has your seasickness gone?
- Can be said that it's pretty gone.
- So no problem?
- But, you didn't feel it, did you?
- Your sunglasses, was there any effect?
Indeed, it had an effect.
Wearing sunglasses
Even though you didn't always wear it...
Because I couldn't see the fish, so...
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Couldn't see her own hands.
- Couldn't see clearly.
- Was what you did unclear?
I couldn't put the bait on the hook.
I pour the white wine.
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
Shiraishi, Etou, Takayama will make a unique cuisine from Shusse-uo!
Then, there's also a bizarre food report from Saito Asuka?
This show is brought to you by the following sponsors:
Eh! Awesome!
I made this.
It doesn't taste strange at all, right?
Although only fried, this tastes so good, right?
Did you eat all fish you caught there?
We ate it, but...
- ...because we got a lot...
- You got a lot, right?
We brought them back, then...
Today, before we started recording in the studio,
we tried to cook them.
We want Bananaman-san to eat them...
These three people tried to cook the fish
they've caught before recording.
While looking at their cooking recipe, let's see them
cooking frozen fish before the recording!
Takayama Kazumi
"Crispy Fried ISAKI"
Takayama, cooked ISAKI by frying it crispy.
Basically, my ISAKI cooking won't
change its taste too much.
Although Takayama doesn't usually cook...
...she tried to cook the ISAKI that she caught
with her own recipe.
I cover it with flour.
This is the first fried fish in my life.
The fish was covered in flour, then fried until dry.
With the scent of ginger, fried ISAKI is finished!
Takayama Kazumi Cooking
Crispy Fried ISAKI
Isn't it good!
- You made this?
- Yes, three of us cooked it.
Takayama Kazumi Cooking
Crispy Fried ISAKI
Let's eat.
Yummy!
Thank goodness, it's yummy.
So yummy!
It works.
He hides it!
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
To be shown when eating is NG.
Himura-san!
Takayama Kazumi Cooking
Crispy Fried ISAKI
Ah, so delicious! Very smooth!
- Which fish is this?
- It's ISAKI, isn't it?
- Here, ISAKI. Here INADA.
- Which Hashimoto caught a lot, right?
So, this one is Shusse-uo.
[Shusse (success) uo (fish) : Success fish
Shusse shinai (Failure) uo (fish) : Failure fish]
No, this one is failure fish.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
ISAKI is discriminated.
- This one is a failure?
- This is the one which brings good luck.
- This is ISAKI.
- Good luck, right? Good luck.
Etou Misa
"INADA Teriyaki"
Next, Etou will try the challenge
to cook INADA Teriyaki.
I will reduce the fire.
Etou who is used to making snacks
for Sake drinking companion...
...continued cooking smoothly.
Carefully she grilled both sides of
INADA that she caught.
Then, Sake, Shoyu and Mirin, is put in and cooked until the gravy thickens.
INADA Teriyaki that's also yummy
to eat with rice, finally done!
- Eh, this is awesome.
- Looks delicious!
Etou Misa Cooking
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125
INADA Teriyaki
- It's like a dish from restaurant, right?
Looks tasty   - Right, right!
Etou Misa Cooking
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125
INADA Teriyaki
Well, I will taste it.
Etou Misa Cooking
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125
INADA Teriyaki
- Sorry, he is annoying.
- Tasty, so tasty!
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Totally concealed.
- It is, right?
- Tasty!
Eh, isn't this really tasty?
- Eh, thank goodness.
- Really tasty, I want to eat it with rice.
That's right, this is yummy
to eat with rice.
- This is your INADAWA fish earlier.
- Right, INADAWA.
INADAWA~
Maybe because I was too excited that time....
No, no, that can be a popular word!
- INADAWA, right?
- INADAWA.
But, obviously it is not said
when fishing INADA!
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
A word which has no clear meaning.
Shiraishi Mai
"INADA Acqua Pazza"
Next, Shiraishi, will try to make
INADA Acqua Pazza.
[Acqua Pazza : Boiled fish dishes from Italy]
I will put this INADA in.
Shiraishi who's good at cooking,...
...follows the cooking recipe properly.
I also put in some garlic.
I also put in the scallops around the fish.
Scallops are placed around INADA,
then she also put in some white wine.
Mini tomato.
Tomato and Anchovy are added...
Then, we just need to boil it for 6 to 7 minutes.
...then covered and cooked together.
Western style stew cooking,
INADA Acqua Pazza, finished!
Eh! So luxurious!
Wah, this looks so luxurious!
Shiraishi Mai Cooking
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125
INADA Acqua Pazza
What's this? Looks delicious!
- What's this?
- Is this a foreign cooking?
This is a food from Akita, Japan.
Shiraishi Mai Cooking
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125
INADA Acqua Pazza
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Instantly become like a grandma?
Acqua Pazza? It's Acqua Pazza, right?
- He looks down at Akita.
- It's Acqua Pazza.
Thank you.
Obviously tasty!
Well, I will eat it, okay?
- What a sec!
- You are annoying!
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Don't want to be seen at all.
Pathetic! You look pathetic.
Let's eat.
He clearly doesn't wanna be seen.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Eating in secret becomes popular.
Wah, this is tasty!
Himura-san, hide!
- Isn't this really tasty?
- Don't suddenly appear like that!
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Man who doesn't want his eating way to be seen.
You use garlic.
This one is very very tasty, you know!
- However, all of them is tasty!
- Ah, thank goodness.
- Everyone also let's eat.
- Let's eat.
That means they wished for success by
eating fishes that brings good luck.
Shiraishi Mai Cooking
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125
INADA Acqua Pazza
- Even though only fried, this tastes good, right?
- So tasty!
- Tasty, right?
-  It doesn't taste strange at all, right?
Hoshino, is this tasty?
- Yes, they are all good at cooking.
- Eh, thank goodness!
- The one that's fried is so tasty.
- Have you tried Acqua Pazza?
Shiraishi Mai Cooking
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125
INADA Acqua Pazza
- Acqua Pazza is so tasty!
- Really tasty, right?
It's like a cuisine from a restaurant.
Akimoto, if you go out of here, on the side of
the road, there is a liquor store, isn't it?
Can you buy some wine now?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
White wine for fish-eating companion
I don't wanna!
I wanna eat with everyone.
Saitou Asuka, very good.
Yummy! It's yummy!
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Addicted to food.
- Asuka-chan, you in fact like to eat, right.
- That's right.
- Have you tried this?
- Not yet.
- So then we want to hear your opinion.
- Try to eat.
Great! This is brand new!
She only shows her back.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
A revolution in TV broadcasting world.
Try to say your opinion.
Sakamichi Team.
- Well, she will eat it.
- Try to eat.
She keeps eating while facing behind.
How does it taste?
Ah, so smooth!
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Facing-behind food report.
- Awesome, your reaction is not seen at all!
- Your face looks enjoying it!
The seasoning is right, no, although just a little...
[Carpaccio : Cuisine of thinly sliced raw fish,
like Sashimi, from Italy]
Carpaccio? This is the first time I eat it...
- Carpaccio? Right, this is Carpaccio!
- No! This is Acqua Pazza!
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Guessing incorrectly while still facing behind.
- This is the first time I eat this.
- Its name is Acqua Pazza.
I have only eaten fried fish...
So, other fish cooking, never?
Because I don't like raw food,
I like the cooked ones.
But, this one is tasty...
HOW LONG WILL YOU KEEP TALKING LIKE THAT!
While keep facing behind, right?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Food report revolution, Asuka style.
Alright, everyone, let's us thank for the food. Start!
Thank you for the food!
Really tasty!
Next, new unit Cinq Etoiles will
perform LIVE in the studio.
Romaji : Stage48
Otona e no Chikamichi
Lyrics : Akimoto Yasushi
Music & Song : Furukawa Takahiro
Otona e no Chikamichi
Lyrics : Akimoto Yasushi
Music & Song : Furukawa Takahiro
tsuugaku no BASU de yoku au ki ni naru hito
That boy Im interested in whom I often see on the bus to school
me ga au dake de utsumukitaku natta
When our eyes meet, I just want to look away
joshikou dakara sonna meneki nasasugite
Going to an all-girls school, Im totally affected by this
koi wo suru ni mo PUROSESU ga wakaranai
Not even knowing the process of falling in love
tomodachi wa minna kare ga iru no ni
All my friends have their own boyfriends
watashi wa doushite okubyou nan darou
But why am I so afraid?
itsuka shizen ni tsukiaeru no ka na
Will I naturally find someone someday?
otona e no chikamichi     oshiete kudasai
The shortcut to becoming an adult              Please tell me
junjou nante iranai   futsuu ni naritai
I dont need innocence               I want to be normal
kiyoraka na seifuku   itsu made mo kiteru wake ja nai
This chaste school uniform                             I wont be wearing it forever
onna no ko kara hayaku
Because Im a girl, hurry
I want to become a woman
josei ni naritai no
The campaign has finished, and both of them,
Double Center, please conclude the show today.
- 13th single will be released on October 28th
- Ima Hanashitai Dareka ga Iru...
Please Support Us!!!
See you next time.
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
In the next episode, presentation of new segment by all members!
A surprising segment from Nakamoto is instantly made!?
Wake up! Wake up!
This show is brought to you by the following sponsors:
If you do it, it becomes surprising.
Anyone...anyone please help me!
- Double Date?
- You want to have a double date?
Don't be like this again, please!
So embarrassing...
Hori, your segment this time,
seems worrisome!
Next week, the first show segment presentation!
Crying? You are crying, aren't you?
Wait, Himetan, your face...
What is the suprising thing that happened to Nakamoto?