m 0 0 l 0 40.5 l 3 40.5 l 3 0 l 0 0 m 3 0 l -6 0 l -6 9 l 24.125 9 l 24.125 6 l -3 6 l -3 3 l 0 3 m 3 3 m 24.125 0 l 24.125 40.5 l 27.125 40.5 l 27.125 -1.5 l 24.125 -1.5 m 33.25 0 l 33.25 0 l 36.25 0 l 36.25 16.5 l 28.625 16.5 l 28.625 13.5 l 33.25 13.5 l 33.25 3 l 22.625 3 l 22.625 0 m 9 27 l 9 18 l 18.125 18 l 18.125 21 l 12.125 21 l 12.125 27 l 9 27 m 18.125 27 l 18.125 30 l 9 30 l 9 27 l 15.125 27 l 15.125 21 l 18.125 21 l 18.125 27 m 7.5 10.5 l 12.125 13.5 l 10.625 15 l 6 12 l 7.5 10.5 m 15.125 13.5 l 15.125 13.5 l 19.625 10.5 l 21.125 12 l 16.625 15 l 15.125 13.5 m 4.5 36 b 4.5 36 4.5 34.5 4.5 34.5 b 10.625 31.5 16.625 31.5 22.625 34.5 b 22.625 34.5 22.625 37.5 22.625 37.5 b 16.625 34.5 10.625 34.5 4.5 37.5
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
Nogizaka Koujichuu
Don, well Nogizaka Koujichuu has started, we're the MC
Bananaman, Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu.
BANANAMAN
Himura Yuuki
Shitara Osamu
Then, here are the members in the studio today.
Here we are!
Onegaishimasu.
Well, that means go ahead, Himura-san...
...our segment today, please announce it!
Presentation of Segment That I Want To Do, First Series!!!
This time, members will do presentations of segments that they want to do.
If there's an exciting segment,
it will be realized immediately.
The first presenter is Gen2 Hori Miona.
The segment that I want to do is this!
There are still many other interesting things!
Segment to know Gen2 much deeper!!!
You know, we have already done
deeper introduction of Gen2...
...but, we haven't shown all of their strengths yet.
So, I want to do this segment.
- What face is that?
Ah, this is the face saying "Still many more!"
Still many more!
"Still many more, y'know!", right?
But, Hori is the one in charge of bringing them here when we do this segment and also when we are doing it.
That means it's all Hori's responsibility.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Isn't that your problem?
Hori tends to promote them carelessly, right?
Like telling them to do something
although they can't do it...
I think we need to work hard...
- ...so that we can surpass the Gen1.
- I see!!     - That's right!
We still can't do it well, so now,
we try anything...
- That's right, we also want to know Gen2 more.
What will you girls do?
Besides me, here are the members.
- Gen2, right?
There are still many characters
that are not known well.
- Are these already all of Gen2?
- Yes.
For instance, Suzuki Ayane-chan,
she's from Akita...
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
Suzuki Ayane
...she is a very shy girl.
So, in the presence of her senior or adults,...
...she doesn't speak at all.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
That's clearly a problem.
Wait, this can cause problems.
- Not speaking at all, that's obviously a problem.
- We get interested to do this segment.
To make her speak a little, right?
- Because she was nervous?
- Right.
If she is relaxed, she can speak just fine.
However, when she's with Gen2,
she's a funny girl.
- She also speaks well...
- If she's relaxed, she can be funny, right?
If so, in this studio, obviously impossible
to speak forever.
That's why, she has to overcome that.
Here, we will try to help her about that.
But, she's definitely able to speak fluently, right?
- Already about these two years she is still like that.
- Right, already two years...
Maybe, we have never talked
about serious matter...
Because she's very shy, can't help it.
How about the others?
Yamazaki Rena, usually called Renachi,
she has a character of often being teased.
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
Yamazaki Rena
- Ah, is that so?
- Because her hand and leg are long...
...then, also when dancing, we tease
her very funny dance, like that.
That kind of character is what we want to show.
If compared, longer?
- Ah, right, if compared to me.
Is that why her movement is funny?
Absolutely, her movement is very unique.
- Although her character is easy to tease, but
still hasn't been teased that often?    - Right.
I want to see!
Then Itou Junna, too, she's really...
- A wild-looking kid, right?
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
Itou Junna
No, she's moodmaker. She's funny.
I also have her video when in the changing room...
- ...let's take a look.
- Do you have it now?     - Yes
Sta~rt~!!!
She can do such an absurd thing...
- She obeys anything, right?
- Right!
Hori, if we do this segment,
I think it will be dangerous...
Don't worry! Don't worry!
- That means she's in action with a cap, right?
- Absolutely!
Right?
Isn't she easy to socialize!
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Forced to agree with his opinion
- She's socialable!
- Absolutely!
- She's really awesome!
- Right?
Isn't it so...
It's clearly so!
That's why, if Gen2 joins into an outdoor
recording, then we will work hard...
- Just Gen2 only, right?
Yes!
- If there's Gen1, they'll be nervous?
- That's right.
So what will Gen2 do alone?
If we only do recording alone, then...
- ...for instance, we're given a challenge...
- Wah, great!
- Bungee? You all want to do Bungee Jumping?
- Yes.
If it's Bungee, of course...
...although it's paid for,
they certainly will not want to do it.
So you all want to do it? Bungee?
- Who will do it?
- Who?
- Girls that will go Bungee jumping.
- But...
...if her body is tall, she certainly will hit the cliff...
Is there really anything like that?
I think the ones with small
body will be easier to jump.
Then, who? who?
Among these, Miria, Ranze, and Karin...
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
Watanabe Miria
Terada Ranze
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
Itou Karin
...seem easy to jump.
Those 3 girls are OK to do Bungee, right?
They are suitable to do Bungee.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Choosing members arbitrarily
-Suitable for Bungee?
- Yes!
Everyone surely agree to do it,
when chosen, right?
Anything, surely agree...
- If Hori is told to do it, surely OK, right?
- OK.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Skill of answering arbitrarily
- Wah, that's great!
- Scary.
- But, that's also scary, right...
Actually, because Gen1 has also done
extreme things like this, so you also...
But, in Gen2 there are many kids that can do it...
- Really?
- They can?
Then, maybe something unexpected happens...
- Ah, in the outdoor recording?
- Really?
If there's something unexpected in Bungee,
it can be fatal.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Accident = DEATH
That's what I know.
Extreme bungee, then what else?
Like, things that are related to
animals, then wild animals too...
- ...can meet it...
- Then eat it?
- Eat it?
- Eat wild animal?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Eating wild animal?
- Eat it?
- Like bizarre food...
- You mean, extreme food?
- So, eating extreme food.
For extreme food, who will do it?
Who seems fond of extreme food...
"Who seems fond of..."?
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
Shinuchi Mai
If Shinuchi Mai...
...she likes, shellfish.
- Right, she likes to eat shellfish.
- So shellfish is the extreme food?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Shellfish = bizarre food?
So you think that's extreme food...
- Shellfish is clearly not extreme.
- Because shellfish tastes good, you know.
- Hori surely will not do this?
- Ah, I'll do it.
- Ah, Hori will?
- I'll do it.
So, Hori will do Bungee then eat insects, too?
Ah, in the beginning, maybe I'll just watch,
if there's someone needing help, I'll go.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Role as observer?
In the beginning, you don't wanna do it?
All of Gen2, we will consider your suggestion.
The next presenter is Hoshino Minami.
Here it is!
Let's invite Minami to amusement parks!
Her plan looks cute, right?
That's really good. Really cute!
This is awesome.
- What do you mean by inviting Hoshino to amusement park?
- What does this mean?
In Nogidoko once, I...
...in "Competition of special thing presentation" segment, I talked about bread...
"Competition of special thing presentation"...
- in the "Competition of special thing presentation"...
- You talked about bread, right?
- At that time, I got Himura Present.
- Ah, you got it that time?
- But, the show eventually ended earlier.
- It couldn't be shown on TV, right.   -Right.
That's why, for the Himura Present that I got...
...I and Bananaman-san can go somewhere...
...then for the present, with Bananaman-san...
- From Himura-san?
Ah, with Bananaman, right?
...I go...
- Ah, so three of use go, like that?
- But, if it's just three of us, I feel shy...
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Feeling shy?
Shy? Why are you shy?
On the contrary, three are better.
That's why, like when we ride Roller coaster...
...we invite one more girl, and so
it'll be like Double Date.
- DOUBLE DATE!!!
- You want Double Date?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Forbidden Double Date
It only looks like that...
You want to have a partner in Double Date?
This eventually becomes Double Date, right?
Unbelievable!
If so, which is the partner for Minami?
Eh, which one? Which one?
Awesome! What's this? Why I feel shy...
- We want to know.
- Which one? Which one?
- "Which one?"!
- Because this is Double Date, right?
- Four people go, will be in pair, right?
- Of course, someone will be next to her.
-Right, that's important!
- Right! Absolutely!
- Eh, in couple?
- Yes.
In the Ferris wheel, we will be in couple.
Eh, four people are better...
Ah, now way! Must choose!
- Because we will be kissing too...
- Ah, no way!
Since this is a date, so when
riding something, that can happen.
Although not a boyfriend, but because the atmosphere is romantic.
Right, because we're already more than 40 years old, so we can kiss immediately...
No need to think about that.
We can do it while eating
ice cream together.
That's right...
We can do many activities though,
like buying something or food.
- So the goal of this Double Date is to buy you present?
- Daabee Deet...
"Daabee Deet..."
Where do you want to go to? Disneyland?
- Eh, anywhere is fine.
- Ah, anywhere, right?
If we go to Universal Studio,
that must be fun, right?
If I ride the Harry Potter ride,
maybe I'll throw up though...
Noo~
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
That's unreasonable.
In Double Date, incident like
throwing up is likely, right?
There must be...
Then, who is the one that you want to invite?
- Anyone is fine.
- So it can be anyone?
- Maybe, everyone can join.
- What does that mean?!
- Double Date must be 4 people, right?
- If everyone join...
- If we go somewhere with all of them,
maybe interesting, right?   - I want to!
If you all come up, that will be
different from her presentation.
Will we be holding hands?
Ah, so you don't wanna be touched, right?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Touching is strictly forbidden.
My manager...
- Because my manager will be there...
- Your manager is not relevant!
For a date like this, of course
your manager will not come up!
Ah, anyone, help me!
But, you yourself who want it, right?
Maybe there's anyone else
who haven't got her Himura Present?
- Me...
- Ah, this many!
- Do you remember what they got?
- No.
For me, in Mousou Christmas segment,...
...when I appeared with Ami, I
got a present from Himura-san.
At that time, what did you got?
In one of those segments,
I was promised...
...a high quality carry case.
Ah, about that...
- That's really...
- Carry case?   - Right, I myself haven't heard about it...
...but, I was promised that.
I want that too~
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Taking chance arbitrarily
Oi, don't be like that!
- Why is that?
- I want it too~
Of course you want it, because
that's a good stuff, right?
What about Hori?
In the competition of who's fastest at crying,
I cried because of Mentaiko.
Ah, long time ago, right?
At that time, what did you get?
- At that time I was promised I'd get Mentaiko.
- Isn't Mentaiko a cheap stuff?
Right, I haven't got that.
For your Himura Present, you was promised
you'd get Mentaiko, at that time?
- Right.
- So that's okay?
Yes, thanks so much.
They asked for handbag, you know.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Satisfied enough with Mentaiko.
That's not a problem though, because
she was promised to get that.
What about Hoshino?
I want an SLR camera.
SLR Camera?!
Wait a minute!
So that when we go, I bring that camera,
then I take photos for memory...
YOU WANT TOO MUCH!
Why you also want Camera?!
He's angry~
The return of Himura Present segment will be considered.
Until now, there's no such story.
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
What is the sad tragedy that fell upon Himetan?
Akimoto's segment is harshly hit by criticism
This show is brought to you by this sponsor
Isn't this Toyama?!
They really recommended it.
Himetan, your face is worrisome.
Wake up!
Ah, awake finally...
Good morning!
The next presenter is Nakamoto Himeka.
Well, the segment that I will
present this time is this.
Jyaann~
Let's erase heartache!
Revenge Onsen!
"Let's erase heartache!" what does that mean?
I, Itou Marika, and Inoue Sayuri
are good friends.
Every year, we always spend
Christmas together.
Then, in the Christmas last year,
when we're having vacation...
...we said "Let's go on a vacation!" like that.
We went on one day vacation to an Onsen that time.
- Previously you've said about that, right?
- Right. Maybe when they both were in the studio.
Then, there's this.
- This is our photo in Onsen last year.
- Three of you?
Really good! Really close, right?
That was so fun, then when
we ended the vacation...
...we said "Next time, one full day...
- You want to stay overnight, don't you?
- Right, we said "We want to stay for a night"
When Shinkansen Hokuriku* route was just opened...
[Shinkansen Hokuriku got an additional route
to Toyama in March 2015]
...there was a talk like this
"Seems fun if we go to Toyama, right?"
Therefore, I am so looking
forward to Christmas this year.
Then one day, I find something
like this in one blog.
It is an article in September on
Sayuri Inoue's blog. This is it!
Jajyan~
I want to see!
Last month, I was very grateful to have the first
summer holiday since joining Nogizaka.
Therefore, I both with Marika...
Eh, Toyama? Isn't this Toyama?!
We went to Toyama for 2 days 1 night.
- What did they do?
- I was shocked as well.
Wait, they look delightful in this photo.
Isn't this just two of them?
Carrying on. Then, we stayed in a place in Toyama that has become world heritage...
- They stayed in this place.
- Right.
After arriving in the lodge,
we then went by a bus to Onsen...
What? They went to Onsen!
We had a very long bathe in the beautiful
Rotenburo until we got too cold.
Himetan, what's this? Didn't you know it?
I've never heard the story from them.
- You knew it from her blog?
- That's right!   -Seriously!
I knew it from this blog.
Wait, from that photo you
three look so close.
They even promised next time they'll
go on vacation and stay, right?
Right, we planned to go to Toyama.
- Then why? After that...
- Eventually it became like this.
Actually I'm okay with it! I've got no problem
if they want to go to Onsen just two of them.
- But?
- BUT...
- ...I want them to tell me about it!
- That should be, right?
I don't know whether they
argued about this or not...
...but, it'd be better if after that they
told me, like "We had a vacation and that's fun!"
Until now, that kind of talk never happened.
Because today they're not here, we can't confirm it, but that kind of talk never happened, right?
It can be said that...
...I was shocked. I myself don't discuss that and just wait for them.
- They never told you?
- Right! From September, my wait has been a month.
There's no Onsen story at all!
Uwa wa wa wa wa...
You aren't in a fight, are you?
In fact, I have no problem that they went just two of them!
Is there a talk like
"I have a problem about this" ?
There's not, but maybe, this happened after Senbatsu announcement.
They must be aware of my condition that time,
because they both made it to Senbatsu.
Your schedule isn't in sync.
There's indeed such an attention,
and I don't mind it. BUT...
- ...I want them to tell me about it!
- THAT'S IT!!!
So this time, you want a segment to have a revenge
by going to Onsen just three of you?
- I want to invite them to go...
- This is dangerous!
Isn't this segment too risky?
If there's a moment like this,
probably I can hear that story.
That's the purpose of this segment.
In your opinion, why don't they tell her?
I wonder why.
I think they're concerned about me.
No, I think, this is simply...
...they both hate you.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Not friends anymore?
I think that's the most sensible reason.
If they're concerned about you,
they wouldn't write it on the blog.
Of course. That makes sense?!
What?
- She even wrote it on the blog, you know.
- Didn't they say "Let's go to Toyama!
Because if not, when they were
about to go on vacation...
...there must be a talk about Himetan.
However, in fact, they didn't talk
about that with you at all.
They could think "No need to tell her" or "That kid doesn't have to know", there must be something like that.
That could be true, from the time
they planned that vacation, right?
But, they're maybe afraid
to talk to me directly...
...so if I invite them to go to Onsen
as a part of the show...
...they will enjoy it, then
that story can show up, right?
They're maybe afraid if it's a private talk.
Among members here, there is nobody who has heard about that Onsen vacation story, right?
- Ah, I have heard about it.
- You have?
When?
Before this, I heard they talk about Onsen vacation in the summer holiday.
At that time, when we talked about summer holiday...
...I heard they both said
"That time is fun!", like that.
Don't they seem secretive about it?
Wait, wait...
Himetan, your face is worrisome.
Himetan's face...
- Eh?
- So they said something about it?!
So, they didn't hide it and told you right away?
Right, then since they're back from there, they
even recommended Toyama to me.
- They're like suggesting me to go there.
- This year that place is booming, right?
They recommended it.
Himetan, your face!
She look up so that her tears don't fall.
This is unbelievable!
But, because I know their trait, that makes me think whether we will go again this year-end.
I haven't heard that story even once.
Eh, it was perhaps like this. When Himetan heard the plan "Let's go to Toyama!",...
...actually that story was just for two of them, and Himetan just overheard it.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Not invited from the start?
Was that just a coincidence?
From the beginning, it was just Himetan who thought she's invited. Like that?
When they both planned to go, she thought "Ah, three of us will go!" Is that what you mean?
- That's wrong!
- So that's the true story!!!
Perhaps, did you misunderstood?
Were they really talking to you?
At this time, while eating...
- ...really, I really heard it.
- "Let's go, three of us!" like that?    -Right.
- So I'm wrong.
- Was it really so?
Indeed...
Here we are so doubtful about Himetan.
Why?!
- How do you think about this segment?
- Great, really great.
We really want to do this.
We really want to see the real situation.
If possible, you can go immediately after this.
- So you can hear that story?
- Right. I hope this can be realized.
It may be better, in this
erasing-heartache segment, they both...
...don't know about this. So, they who don't tell you about that vacation...
- ...feel that it's just like an ordinary vacation,
not about Onsen.     - Good idea!
Then, when the situation feels
comfortable, you say...
..."By the way...",
No! That's dangerous!
That won't feel good!
Really, it's terrific that in
Onsen such situation occurs.
Like building a comfortable situation.
For Nakamoto's sake,
we will do this segment one day!
Please wake up!
After this, criticism pours against Akimoto's segment!?
The next presenter is Akimoto Manatsu.
What I want to do is
Reaction Lesson Part 2!
Previously, I have done this
with Kano Eiko-san.
At that time, I was nicknamed ReaDol
from Kano Eiko-san.
Therefore, subsequently in this part 2...
...I want to be taught by the master,
Degawa Tetsuro-san.
I see.
Previously, I tried Wasabi Sushi...
...Gomu Pacchin and reflexology.
[Gomu Pacchin = a game where rubber is bitten,
stretched, and then let go so that it hits the lip.]
This time, because there's a pro,
I will step up the level.
So I will try reversed Bungee, then...
...Hot Water Bath...
- Hot Water Bath too?
- Do you want to try Hot Water Bath?
- Really?
- I will try it.
Do you want to try such an extreme thing?
- Because there's a pro, at least there should be something like that.    - Right, absolutely!
In Degawa-san case, when
doing reverse Bungee...
...while shot upward, his clothes got completely taken off.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Traditional naked art
That's Degawa-san's level.
That's the essence of Reverse Bungee.
- Is that really so?
- If that's not so, that's just like ordinary bungee, right?
That's what's important. Must be naked.
- Is there more? Looks like you bring a lot.
- There is! Next is this...
Jyan~
I wanna be your girlfriend~
Yey~
- Do you want to quit?
- No!
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Quitting the group?
I don't want that.
In this case, as an idol,
shouldn't we look cute?
And talking about who's the cutest in Nogizaka, that's definitely me.
Wait..wait..
I still have to explain many more.
I think fans really want
to have me as their girlfriend.
Eh, no, not yet...
They definitely want that.
Because they want it, I will face
the camera at short distance...
...and try to be fans' girlfriend.
- Like luring them?
- Right!
If so, give an example. For instance, a conversation in the morning with your boyfriend, to the camera.
I will try to wake up my boyfriend.
- You're that serious, aren't you?
- Here, it's the first time, right?
Good morning~
What? He doesn't wake up at all~
Please wake up!
Wake up!
Ah, awake finally~
Good morning!
Eh? Still sleepy?
No other way.
Here is good morning kiss
m 0 4.5 b 0 4.5 0 4.5 0 4.5 b -10.625 -3 -15.125 -7.5 -15.125 -12 b -15.125 -16.5 -12.125 -19.5 -7.5 -19.5 b -3 -19.5 0 -16.5 0 -12 b 0 -16.5 3 -19.5 7.5 -19.5 b 12.125 -19.5 15.125 -16.5 15.125 -12 b 15.125 -7.5 10.625 -3 0 4.5
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Thank you very much.
Aho~
How is it? Can we air it?
But, I want to show this, where I change my character to a new one...
- What's this?
This is when I feed a delicious cake
to my boyfriend .
Eh what's this? Where
did you took this photo?
This photo is from my blog.
What's this? Is Akimoto really lewd?
No! I'm not like that!
What actually is your goal doing this?
From the start, you do this?
I want to show my appearance that's unknown, like before sleeping...
...like, if I show my appearance
when I look sexy like this.
- Isn't that too lewd!
Idols who have this kind of skill, who use camera as her boyfriend...
...for a delusional date, like what she just presented, does really exist right?
But, she always show more than that.
That thing earlier, actually unnecessary.
Ah, so that's no good?
Didn't it make your heart pounding?
That's why, don't do it!
She just did it again.
But, really, that display can be troubling.
That was like you are imagined
by old man to live with him.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Living with old man
Then, you live with him for about
2 or 3 months as in that delusion.
If he stays for 2 or 3 months, it'd be interesting.
Then there will be a coverage of many things that happened when she come to the first old man's place.
That'd be so interesting...
Then when the New Year bell rings,
they separate.
- That's great.
- This might make old men like you.  - Absolutely!
- Is it alright to be such an Idol?
- We might be unable to do that recording.
Due to its similarity to "Ururun Taizaiki".
[Ururun Taizaiki = a show where artists try to live
with someone and help him/her working.]
I see...
How about handsome man?
- Reaction and Girlfriend segments can be done together.
- What does it mean?
For instance, when they record that video, they sit together, then the chair is broken.
That's done together with that old man, right?
- Together with old man?
- That old man will fall.
The old man is pranked?
He'd say "Since I live with you,
there are many weird things happening"
That's good! So funny!
- She will also change that old man's house interior.
- The interior?
- But, the old man becomes confused.
- That becomes a new experience for the old man.
- "It is better for you to leave!"
- "Since you came, this room somehow becomes weird!"
Ah, stop it!
By the way, members who come to studio this time might have a segment that wants to be done.
For Fukugawa, what do you want to do?
Miona once has done
a Horror make-up segment, right?
For me, I want to try Yarugawa.
Makeup? Such makeup?
- Do you want to try special effect make-up?
- Yes, Yarugawa style.
How about Ikuta?
For me, I want to go on BBQ holiday with everyone.
- You always keep an eye for that, right?!
- Ah, really?
Why do you want BBQ?
Because when we went to Macau,
not everyone can come.
So I want to go out with everyone,
to a camping ground for instance.
How about Nishino?
I have no idea...
You don't have any idea
if it's this sudden, right?
Shiraishi, how about you?
I want to be like a nurse in school...
...so we seek experience of how hard that profession is for one full day.
I see.
If there is that kind of kids,
it will be interesting, right?
Then, for instance there's an incident
where she is peed.
- Is there really an incident like that?
- Then all boys will pee like this.
Peed?!
All of them pee on Shiraishi!
That far?!
Ah, interesting! If there's a pee incident,
it must be interesting!
Next week, what is the segment
that's immediately made?
An amazing film that was played on July this year,...
..."Kanashimi no Wasurekata, Documentary of Nogizaka46"
will be released in Blu-Ray and DVD!
All viewers, don't miss it!
Onsen Vacation!!!
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
In the next episode, the segment that Nakamoto wanted is immediately made!
Nakamoto, Marika, and Inoue go on vacation to Onsen!
This show is brought to you by this sponsor
- So cute~
- Seriously!
We're going now~
We've done this before, right?
It is better that you don't make such promise!
It will be broken again.
I myself think, "What should I do?!"
This is fun!
Then, can Nakamoto erase her heartache?