Original Sub by MasToppu
ReTranslate by Yuuki
QC by TechiNeru46
Nogizaka Koujichuu.
Let me do it! 2nd Presentation of a new segment series!!!
m 0 0 l 0 20.25 l 1.5 20.25 l 1.5 0 l 0 0 m 1.5 0 l -3 0 l -3 4.5 l 12.25 4.5 l 12.25 3 l -1.5 3 l -1.5 1.5 l 0 1.5 m 1.5 1.5 m 12.25 0 l 12.25 20.25 l 13.75 20.25 l 13.75 -0.75 l 12.25 -0.75 m 16.75 0 l 16.75 0 l 18.25 0 l 18.25 8.25 l 14.5 8.25 l 14.5 6.75 l 16.75 6.75 l 16.75 1.5 l 11.5 1.5 l 11.5 0 m 4.5 13.5 l 4.5 9 l 9.125 9 l 9.125 10.5 l 6 10.5 l 6 13.5 l 4.5 13.5 m 9.125 13.5 l 9.125 15 l 4.5 15 l 4.5 13.5 l 7.5 13.5 l 7.5 10.5 l 9.125 10.5 l 9.125 13.5 m 3.75 5.25 l 6 6.75 l 5.25 7.5 l 3 6 l 3.75 5.25 m 7.5 6.75 l 7.5 6.75 l 9.875 5.25 l 10.75 6 l 8.25 7.5 l 7.5 6.75 m 2.25 18 b 2.25 18 2.25 17.25 2.25 17.25 b 5.25 15.75 8.25 15.75 11.5 17.25 b 11.5 17.25 11.5 18.75 11.5 18.75 b 8.25 17.25 5.25 17.25 2.25 18.75
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
Continuing from last week, this time members also will present about segment they want to do
If the topic is interesting,
the segment will be made in this show.
First, presentation segment from
Matsumura Sayuri.
Right, the segment I want to do is this.
Ja~jyan~!!
Let's show our real character!
Aroma Competition!
- There it is. - Aroma Competition?
Everyone has their favorite smell ...
Of course, everyone is different. Many variation, I think.
,, But, from the smell that they like,
I can figure this out.
What is it?
This is it!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Basic Mistake
This is definitely a mess!
Ahh !! No, no!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
"It's over" Signal
- Well, It's over! - Please return to your seat.
Please return to your seat
It's already over!
What do you know?
This is it!
The character of a person!
Based on their preferred smell, the real character of the person ...
... can we see,
perhaps we'll  also know about their life.
Their life?
Of course, everyone here have certain characteristics ...
... from there, they probably will found new characters ...
... so each of them,
will be requested to say the smell that they like.
Is that so?
Is this interesting?
I think, basically, if we just look at the TV,
we don't know what the real smell is, right?
Because it's only talking about smell.
Then, what if, for example, someone say they like the smell of Steak, it's not interesting right?
For example a person who likes Steak , the characteristic of ...
...an American.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Meat Loving American
- Is it like that? - If, for example, I like Mabo Tofu .
- I love the smell from Mabo Tofu , so what am I? - If you like that ...
... the characteristic of  ...
...a fat person.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Nothing to do with the Mabo Tofu?
- My characteristic and my real character turned out ...
- Wait a minute!
Wait a minute! What is this?
- In my future, too, huh?
It wasn't from the smell of Mabo Tofu , but you're just now seeing Himura-san!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Dislike Himura from the beginning?
She said I'm fat
If Steak was Americans,
then I think if it was Mabo Tofu then it will be Chinese.
So, the answer is always fat, right?
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Fat in previous life.
Only your fat that stand out.
- So cruel~! Is this okay?
- What? Wait,this is interesting, isn't it?.
- This is clearly an insult.
She's clearly just mocking me.
So later, is it Matsumura who will explain this?
Previously, Hashimoto Nanami , also good at detecting smell ...
Hashimoto may even know someone from the clothes smell.
- She is very sensitive to smell.
- That's right!
- But, actually I am a smell specialist.
- Really?!
- Then what smell do you like?
- I love the smell of this.
Ah, you brought it, huh?
Toilet paper!
Hee, So you like the smell of poop?
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Idol World Revolution?
Obviously it's not like that!
- It's not like that.
- If it's that smell, we certainly don't want to know.
What does this mean?
- This is the center part of the toilet paper.
- Ah, so the middle part?
- I love the smell of this center part.
- If its the middle part...
- Eh?!
- How?
It's not clear.
But, Takayama said, "Ah ~" as if she knew.
- It may be like the smell of paper.
- Right.
- So you like this?
- Yes, right.
Why?
If its this, what characteristic is it?
Is there a characteristic for this?
Probably, because I'm from city faction...
Unfair! Yours looks cool.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Fat vs City Faction
Why do you say I'm fat before?
Why I'm not a city faction too?
Isn't this paper, made of wood?
Of course, because I'm from city, and live in the city,
so not too often come across with trees ...
... that's why,I miss some trees, perhaps.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Special requests from City Faction.
You miss some trees?
Then, there is another one. This is it.
- Ah, so it's a paper bag, huh.
- Paper bags from Tsutaya.
There are some people who like the smell of bags like this.
- I know this.
- You know how it smells?
So, you like the smell of that section?
The smell is really good!
Please try it.
This is basically the same as the paper smell like this.
This is bad!
Ah, where's the front?
Wait, wait a minute ...
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Panic Old Man
Himura-san! Himura-san!
You surely know your front, right!
Part before you here, right?
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Although can't see, surely know.
"Where is the front ?!"
You obviously know.
I didn't understand why she liked the smell of paper like this.
You guys also like this?
- Maybe, because Himura-san is a country boy.
- What is that ?!
Because I'm a country boy, so you say I'm fat, before ?!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
2 times suffer.
There is nothing good she said for you.
Ah, the front ...
... I know!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Adding peephole.
- Here!
- This is bad, huh!
A pervert appeared!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Voyeur Man.
He wants to commit a crime!
No! No!
Wait, you ...
... hit the lights here!
Lighting staff, i'm sorry.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Humble Voyeur Man
Ah, this is nice.
So, will we play like this?
No, not really.
- But, is quite rousy!
- That's right, Matsumura.
- Why do you love the smell of paper?
- I don't understand this.
Probably, because you love books
and when you visit the bookstore ...
Ah, I really like Manga.
There it is!
Of course, as I took Manga,
the paper smell that I like came out.
- I understand that.
- You understand?
Although I'm a country kid, I know it!
Because she told me she was a city kid ...
... looks like she underestimate me.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Country kid also like it
Country kids also love the smell of paper!
Because it's the smell of paper, right?
For those who like to read books,
this is reasonable, isn't it?
- The smell of freshly printed books, right?
- Then, the smell of the ink, and the wrapper also ...
...... like a thin wrapper used on Wagashi.
[Wagashi = Japanese traditional cake]
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Smells like a paper wrapper.
I know it!
- Smells like that, right?
- It smell good.
I also like the smell of a sink filter.
Eh? The smell of kitchen waste?
- Everyday, there is a distinct smell there ...
- It was a foul smell, isn't it!
What the person ate yesterday,
the smell will come out from there the day after.
So everyone's sink filter?
No, no! The one in my house.
Isn't that bad?
If you like the smell of kitchen waste,
Aren't there something wrong with you?
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
No sympathy
- It's waste, right? Why?
- It's bad.
That means, people who like
the smell of kitchen waste is a neat person.
- Said a kid from city!
It's absolutely absurd!
It was obviously the wrong conclusion!
But, on the other hand, there is also someone like that
For the winner of the Aroma Competition,
How to determine this?
Member with her favorite smell that
get good response from the other members ...
... get Himura Prize!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Without the permission of the person.
What is that !?
How to determine the champion
from the response of the member?
How?
Is it if other members understand
why she like that smell?
Therefore, for example, perfume ...
- Ah, so it was not like that.
- The smell that was good according to other members ...
... otherwise it would be easy for them
to understand, if it's good.
Then, is it going to be an interesting segment?
We're going to do a simulation in the studio!
- Yes, that's right.
- Shinuchi!
There's a smell that you like?
Maybe this would not be understandable to anyone.
I really like the smell in the elevator.
Elevator ?!
Not the smell of perfume, so even if people are going in
and wear some perfume, it smells different.
How the smell of the lift?
How, huh? There was the smell of ...
.. people, the smell of the building,
and all of them in the elevator was mixed together.
Like the smell of engine oil?
I particularly like the smell of metal.
It started when ...
... I take the elevator in a large supermarket in the area
where I come from.
When I know the smell in there, ...
... I immediately "What is this nice smell?"
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Sense of Smell Awaken.
If you say it like that,
I want to know how it really smell!
What was it? I thought there was no smell there, right?
- I don't know.
If you go up the elevator, try to feel the smell in there.
Smell of elevator, huh?
- Ah, but there could be some sort of smell there, huh?
- That's right.
Matsumura you know smell of elevator ?
If it's me Erebe..tum...Elevator smell, I didn't like it..
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Remain in paper group
Ebe..be..ta..no...
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Strain tongue group
It makes this even confusing
It's not elevator then.
Inoue?
If it's me...
...I like the smell of premium Tissue.
Aaahh~!
Sweet, right?
Not normal tissue. But, premium type,
which feels softer ...
- Is there any smell?
- There is.
A little sweet, too.
- It was sweet?
- That's right.
It taste pretty good when eaten.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Snack flavor?
Wait, what the hell is that?
So you eat it?
To know more about this, if you can ...
... I want you to eat the tissue too!
Wait a minute ...
So, to find out about the premium tissue smell ...
.... they'll try it that way.
I'll try it too.
- It smells not too strong! I don't know.
- Me too.
- Try to eat it.
- Maybe it feels stronger...
If you eat it, you would know.
If it's eaten, it's not the smell,
but we can know the sweetness.
Ah, it's true ! Sweet!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Really sweet.
So premium tissue taste sweet, huh?
Himura-san eat it ...
m 126.875 31.5 l 0 31.5 l 0 0 l 126.875 0
※"Hana-Seleb" Tissue Doesn't Have Aroma
You guys also give it a try.
Amazing!
But doesn't the smell was a bit weak?
- It smells like the sweet taste of sugar there ...
- Ah, just a little, right ....
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Meeting of tissue smelling.
Of course, there is a slight smell
as sweet smell of sugar, huh?
Sweet! Sweet!
Sweet! I know it smells so sweet!
- But, if that's it, the smell was not there.
- The aroma is difficult to be perceived.
It smells like Odougubako.
Ah, that's true!
Why would anyone know!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Mysterious Response.
You said casually when you know that smell!
What is Odougubako?
- What kind of thing is it?
- If it smells Odougubako  means cute, huh?
What is Odougubako?
- What is it?
- There are a lot of things there!
Odougubako is what?
So you don't know  Odougubako?
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
ODOUGUBAKO Generation?
What is it?
Odougubako!
m 126.875 31.5 l 0 31.5 l 0 0 l 126.875 0
Box to store equipment in the elementary school.
Due to purchased together, a lot of students used the same box.
- One with flowers motive on it?
- For scissors. - For glue as well.
Ah, stationery box?
We don't use Odougubako.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Not ODOUGUBAKO Generation.
Maybe I didn't know at all?
How's the smell?
Maybe it's a special thing for a girl.
So, Odougubako is a girl things.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Much More Mysterious
Eh, Odougubako, huh.
So this is like the smell of Odougubako?
We certainly don't know it. But, I like this.
- There are many things that appear, right.
- Nakada?
Nakada what's your favorite smell?
I ...
... like the smell of Reika's back
Of course there is something like this, huh
What does that mean?
She was wearing perfume, but not only that ...
... there is a natural scent deeper in her
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Like Sakurai's scent
- So, Reika's scent as ...
- I love the natural scent of Reika as a human being.
Her human scent?
- Reika's like inviting...
- No! No! No!
From here, even though I wanted to scent her
still couldn't because of her clothes ...
... so I had to try it from the neck part.
- That part? - Try to do it.
Try to smell it!
- How is it?
- She's like a pervert.
Ah! It smells good!
- It calms me down.
- What makes it different?
It's like....
... the warm feeling from her body.
Hinoki! smells like Hinoki, huh?!
[Hinoki = Japanese cypress (Chamaecyparis obtusa).]
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Sakurai = wood from tree?
Because Reika's back smell like Hinoki.
That's great.
The warm feeling, right?
Nishino, try to smell the scent.
What to do, huh? I don't understand
The meaning of that good scent ...
Scary! Scary! It's a little scary.
There is a scent?
- It's not her perfume? -
It's not. Smell deeper.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Behind her perfume!
Because this is the natural scent of Sakurai!
Smell deeper to sense the natural scent of Sakurai.
Try it again! Nishino dug up in!
Naa-chan looks so cute!
Sakurai,can you take off all your clothes?
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
For Segment Sake.
- I like this!
- You don't know?
This is bad!
- Although it was practically there, that part ...
.. maybe the most senseable.
- Her scent as a human being?
True, human scent.
Although Reika wear perfume,
the scent persists.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Uncoverable Scent
So, the smell of another member, you don't like it?
Other members aroma couldn't calm me down.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Some kind of sedative?
Is it like that, huh?
Matsumura, try to sense Sakurai's back!
- Matsumura like the smell too, right.
How is it?
You can smell it?
Try to pat her back, probably
the scent will come out from the collar.
- Ah, there seems to be indeed!
- It came out?! How it smells?
Aaahhh~!!!
How is it?
- The smell of nature.
- Smell of nature ?!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Natural smell.
Like a forest, like that?
You get it, right?
- The fresh smell of soap, like that?
- Not it's not.
- Is it like baby scent?
- Well, almost. It smelled like a baby scent.
Baby, huh?
If it's baby scent, Ikoma also like that
Marika also has a scent like a baby
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Still a baby
You guys are still like a baby, huh.
Himura-san also smelled like a baby, right.
Kyaa!!!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Monster appeared!
Here comes Big Baby.
Like the smell of a newborn baby.
Since everyone has a different scent, right?
Anyone else, is there another scent that you like?
Ah, what is it?
- The scent from Saito Asuka's hair is very nice
- Ah, that's right!
Isn't that the smell of the shampoo that she use?
Different, huh?
So, it's not the shampoo?
- Can I try to smell it?
- Go ahead.
May I enjoy the scent of your head?
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Spooky request
What does that mean? What is that ?!
Her request is so dangerous!
You feel ashamed because your head smells bad, right.
Even though she's shampooing, but
there is the smell of sweat, right? - Yes.
But it smells really good!
- If It's me ...
- Grand piano.
m 126.875 31.5 l 0 31.5 l 0 0 l 126.875 0
Members favorite secret aroma finally unveiled!
Takayama Kazumi try hard to realize her favorite segments.
Like the smell of the mother earth.
The smell of the mother earth !!!
Is it really like that ?!
Can i request something crazy,then?
If it's a bit crazy...
Rotti? What's your favorite smell?
I like the smell of a cab
The smell of the engine fuel, right?
If it like that, I understand.
It's not the smell of gasoline.
- It's that, right?
- Right, it's that right? - Correct.
When refueling ...
... a good smell came out. I know it...
Takayama?
The smell that I like?
Ah, I like the smell of a new car.
Aahh...
There are some people,
that like the smell of a new car, right?
- The smell is so good!
- Right ?
But it's not just our imagination?
For example, previously ...
...when she likes reading, she also like the smell of books.
The same is true in this new car.
That's what makes it so
they like that smell.
So, it's true, from there, we can know about someone's life
- Ah, that's right.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Scent is Life.
Therefore, she likes the smell of the lift,
because she likes to be in the big supermarkets.
Maybe it's the reason.
Ikuta, Is there a scent that you like?
Surely piano scent, right.
It's not that. What is it?
Piano scent!
- It's not that.
- Let her talk first
What's that smell? The smell of Pi ... Pi ... Pi ...
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Curse of PI.
So, Pi from Piano?
Don't force her.
The smell, the smell of Piano, right!
No, not the smell of the piano.
If It's me ...
Grand Piano!
No,it's not that!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Piano Loving Old Man.
Oi, let her talk to you first!
- I love the smell of new paper or cardboard.
- Ah, the same group with members who like the smell of paper.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Paper loving group
I understand, if you like the smell of paper,
perhaps because of the smell of the ink.
You like to read in your spare time, right?
Fukagawa?
I love the smell of oil paint, and also ...
... the smell of dog paws.
What? The smell of dog paws?
It's so rare that people like that smell
How does that smell like?
It might just, a dog owner that knows it,
but the smell is soothing ...
- That was the dirtiest part, you know!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Dog paws = Lower leg part
Look, Uncle Himura said,
"That was the dirtiest part!"
That was the part that affected by dirt right?
Isn't that dirty?
People who keep dogs certainly understand this.
Direct sense it like this?
- When I smell it,"Ah, it's a good smell."
- Like the scent of Senbei!
[Senbei = Some kind of Japanese rice cracker.]
Senbei?!
What kind of Senbei did you eat?
So, the smell is like Senbei?
Nishino, you agree with this?
I think, it's not like Senbei. But
it's like the scent of wild animals.
It's like the scent of THE SUN WARMTH
SCENT OF THE SUN WARMTH?!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
A poet appears
What does that mean?
- Right.
- It's amazing. - What is that?!
It's a warm and soothing aroma.
Like where?
If person, perhaps there is no one like it.
It is the scent of Mother Earth.
SCENT OF MOTHER EARTH !!?
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Another poet appears!
- Is it really like that?!
- Really!
Scent of Mother Earth.
Of course, maybe the scent of the soil or grass,
you can say that the aroma of nature...
Maybe the scent from where the dog was wandering.
Could it be the smell of the soil?
No ...
Isn't that the smell of the soil?
I just keep my dog at my house and
not too often bath my dog with shampoo...
- ... so maybe it was the smell of the dog itself.
- Dogs scent, right.
It's not the smell of "Odougubako", huh?
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Completely unrelated.
That's not it
Surely, some special smells like this ...
... for example, the smell of the gas station,
the smell of exhaust fumes ...
...smell of Thinner, some people like it, right?
- It's definitely not Thinner!
[Thinner = a solvent used to clean oil-based paint.]
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Thinner obviously not allowed
- Indeed there are some, but ...
- Like those who like to paint ...
Ah, do you like it?
- I love the smell of a gas station. - Ah, I know it.
- You understand?
- Yes I know.
Uh, wait a minute.
The aroma segment turned out quite interesting, right !!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Simulation success.
Really interesting!
We seem to be able to do this segment!
But, you could say we've been doing
this aroma segment, right ?!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Already done.
The simulation is fun,
so we finish up here first.
For the sake of realizing that famous segment, Takayama present them all out!
The next member is Takayama Kazumi.
Segments that I want to present is this.
This year, Let's do it again!
Christmas Delusions 2015.
Ah, so it's this segment, huh.
This segment is popular, right.
A lot of members also want to do this segment.
Often I heard ...
- We have always done this in NogiDoko, isn't it?
- That's right.
and, one of NogiDoko is this.
- Ah, it's when Noujou playing the male role
- That's right
In the questionnaire, I write this in detail!
Takayama is indeed like this segment.
It was difficult though, because
there are a lot of ideas that I have ...
Everyday I was up all night because of this.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Delusion until morning.
- Takayama really loves segment like this!
- She proposed 4th series.
That's right
It would indeed be troublesome, but this year ...
... our Halloween regular segment didn't exist.
That's right, huh. Why did it happen?
Since we changed to "Nogichuu", many segments of "NogiDoko" that we forget.
But when you say it like this, of course
we are happy, especially the staff.
So they know, that there are great segments like this.
So, we have to create something new,
for a segment like this.
Of course, if I want to do this Halloween.
Is that so, right. Even Himura-san
seriously doing Cosplay !
I did it often!
- If it's Himura-san of course it's Oden series, right.
- That's right...
[Oden = Japanese soup with a lot of different ingredients.]
This year, you're wearing Gobomaki costume.
[Gobomaki = one of the ingredients of Oden.]
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Oden Style Cosplay
He's using brown Futon.
[Futon = Japanese traditional bedding.]
- So you use Futon?
- Right.
There are many opinions from the fans, who say they
want to see some NogiDoko segment in Nogichuu.
- Many, huh?
- Yes. Then...
Since last November ...
...fans were asking, "Is there going to be Christmas
Delusion segment this year?" is running rampant.
Rampant?
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
1 line of support.
Is it until like that?
Right, running rampant recently...
Scream of the fans, right ...
So, because they want that segment
until to the point of rampant?
- Right.
- They asked " Why isn't it made?
- So, a lot of them?
- Right.
Then, maybe we all have forgotten, but in fact ...
... I was the winner last year.
Takayama's the winner, huh?
Is there a winner?
There is, and the winner receive Himura Prize..
- But you haven't received it yet, huh?
- Yes. - Wait, if this Himura Prize ...
... should we change, so there is a new prize.
- That is true.
Could be developed further, right.
But I've been thinking about a suitable prize for this.
This time, of course, we also decide who's the winner ...
... and for the winner of this year ...
... joint with winner of last year ...
- It's you right? last year winner?
Yes, it was me.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Winner of last year = Me.
Even though it's yourself, but you don't realize it.
Me who win before, and the winner
this time will receive Himura Prize
...Location shooting.
So, it's like the bill paid at once, huh?
Right, so this year is the last Himura Prize.
For once ...
... so we end it, because Himura Prize looks like a fake.
So, for this one, the prize must be the greatest!
So, with this, everyone can strive
to get the prize this year.
Christmas Delusion...there is more?
Right, then, now "Myself" already ...
And now, "Me"?
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
In a hurry because too enthusiastic.
"Myself here in after also .. .."
What's wrong with that "Me"?!
What was "Me" thinking?
- Now, I've been thinking about the idea for delusions.
- Uh, you've made it?
So your idea feasible to do?
I think this is the best that can be tried.
So, there's something you've prepared?
- This is the best idea that available
- Please begin.
Unrequited love for 3 years with classmates ...
- Wait! Calm down.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Messy.
- You step on the gas just now!
- She's in a hurry.
- Well, you might have an accident!
- Just now, " Love that isn't..  ..." what is it?
- The way she read it also a bit messy.
- We didn't understand. Please read it slowly.
She just accelerate!
Because it's been a while since
I do this, I'm a bit nervous
- Why are you even nervous, there's only your friends here!
You're a veteran, you know!
Because a lot of people will see this..
You're a mess just now!
- Continue.
- Furthermore, this ...
Unrequited love for 3 years with my classmate
I'm giving him a surprise at the last Christmas
during my high school
I think, everyone agree that this is better.
Next up is this.
A friend who had a fever at Christmas
When you came to visit,
love lightning strike at a sunny day.
What was that? What? What?
- I know this, He appears suddenly, right.
- Correct.
This story, before this, she didn't have any feelings ...
... and then, when some friends came to visit ...
...she then meet with the boy,
like some kind of approach.
If he came to visit at Christmas,
she must have known that he was in love!
Ah, that's true, that was right too!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Assuming lightly.
Don't flip the pages as you says,
" Of course, that's right! "
That's right.
In order to realize
the Ideal Christmas Delusions segment ...
... appear some surprising idea for confession of love ?!
The last one is this.
Secret love between me and my celebrity classmate.
- This is.. the reverse version of Nogizaka, huh?
- So true.
- This looks like Nogizaka were in a weak position ...
- Right
- You're making a lot, huh?
- Right, and this is the last.
As it looks, Takayama looks so passionate,
what about the other members?
- Do you really want to do this?
- Yes. How is it?
Do you also want to do this
Ideal Christmas Delusions?
Here, we won't only decide
our role and setting, by ourselves...
... but, the girlfriend role as well, right?
We understand.
You want to play with Sakurai, right?
It's not like that!
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Abusing director position?
Absolutely not!
So, you once again, huh?
Then, at NogiDoko,only
Senbatsu members that appeared but ...
... in Nogichuu there are many members who can perform ...
... so 2nd Gen too, can perform!
- I want to see!
- We want to see it.
Is it okay? Later she will throwing a Shougi pawn.
m 354.25 -131.25 l -356.5 -131.25 l -356.5 14.25 l 354.25 14.25
Romance between "Pawns" and "King" type?
At the scene, she even throws a Shougi pawn.
That's definitely fine. That's her character.
I'll take Ryou role then.
Itotani Tetsuro
Ryou (Dragon King)
That Ryuo!
- Director, I'm right for the role, right?
- You are that Ryou, yes.
With Takayama's burning passion , Ideal Christmas
scenario registration has been opened!
The first set of Nogizaka MV,
"All MV Collection - Ano Toki no Kanojotachi"...
... finally released on December 23!
Please check the cover of the album too!
Then, ticket sales for Under LIVE
at Nippon Budokan concert, has been opened!
Don't miss it!
m 126.875 31.5 l 0 31.5 l 0 0 l 126.875 0
Wakatsuki Yumi taking humor classes for the sake of eliminating her serious side! So why all the members laughed at Wakatsuki reborn?
- Look, Fuku-chan standing with his head ...
- Ah, thank you!
Ah, thank you.
Until like this, huh...
Wait, that's the same with mocking him.
Just washing your hair ...
Who is that Ikima woman who
was with you a couple of days ago?
I'll take it out! Everyone ready ?!
Wakatsuki will unveil new character
that will be remembered in history!