Warning: since this my first time subbing and its a one man team. Please understand if i made some mistakes and kindly please tell if there are.
DON! now starting Nogizaka Kojichuu. We're your hosts, Bananaman. Please take care of us
Now, here's Nogizaka-chan...
ok.. ok..
-oohh.. oh..
ok.. ok.. ok.. ok..
uuuwwwuu
HAHAHAHAHAHA
-That was good
right, they are the present members in the studio
-mmhh
Today, what are we doing?
-Yes
Eh Himura-san, please announce it..
Let's get started. Today, The 1st...
Nogizaka46
PRIVATE MATTER MONOMANE TOURNAMENT
Members in the group are often good at imitations...
Today, Nogizaka will detail private matters of members in a Monomane tournament
However, as a private matter they have to single out the important points.
uhm.. since its a private matter
Everyone, will bark at excitement! People watching TV will say "What the hell is this?"
Amusement required
-so.. so..
Japan, Absolutely promised...
...then, this guy and everyone, accepted power.
In a sense it's a team competition
-That is
-That's important.. That's important
That, in no way may not last barely
It's important.. It's important
First up these four what kind of monomane will they show us
The first monomane, is this!
-ah, Shiraishi
Example of Takayama Kazumi's hands when she's noisy.
-hahaha
-ah her legs are wide open
ah wait so listen...
before this Jo-san and I ate together right...
so
I asked for Lunch "A"
I wonder if it's quite okay?
When the clerk said "This... is good"
and at the end Lunch "E" came out.
-that was great
-amazing
everyone wants to see more
-ok I get it
-Let's keep going
-Lets's keep going
So let's keep going. Next monomane is this!
The action that she gives when she surely feels trouble or embarrassment by Akimoto Manatsu
I do not plan through more 20 minutes of Akimoto.
EEEHHH!!
Looks Good
-it's the same
Ahhh looks the same
ah I see, thats what it is
-I was surprised my own voice came out and heard it
-right? that was good...
Ok let's continue.. Next!
Kawago Hina's not so much girl pose
The truth is.. honestly this year has gone by fast.
...Let me take a picture
i'm a model now so i'll go
see ya
BYEPICHI
Next monomane please!
Under Live "Senpuuki" Performance, faci...
...facial expression while dancing by Nakamto Himeka
-It's heeeeer!!
DOG?
First of Shiraishi
-Oh she was good
Shiraishi-Takayama
Firstly your legs where too wide open...
-you really did it
You're normally good at monomane... like talking
-truly good
-She was, right? it was really amazing
It's like watching the real me
-"Watching the real you"???
You who?
no, that was just great
so that thing??
It's like her hands is following her voice
-I do.... yeah
-you really do
-I really do...
honestly.. this.. but.. of co..
I'm staring at myself again...
but I didn't know I was doing it
you're doing it right now
Right of Freedom
"It was staring again"
Now Wakatsuki
yes
GOOD!
she always..
maybe
Your head... your head is big right?
maybe it wants freedom?
Prevention of head fall
I saw..
on a photo, that a hand to the face lend a rough small face effect?
are you aiming for microcephaly effect?
(T/N: Microcephaly is a abnormal smallness of the head, a congenital condition associated with incomplete brain development.)
Comb the illusion
-Ahhhhh
Ohhhh
-Ahhhh
this is just a private matter of imitation, we're just getting started right Wada
Yes
yes.. this.. the fans absolutely don't know yet
-right
these days
her appeal is too great
The last part..
at the last part you said?
"BYEPICHI"
this is really... a lot hard
BYEPICHI what?
Bye bye and...? what do you think Himura-san?
Ehh.. Bye from "Bye-Bye" right?
you don't know what "PICHI" means right
So while walking...
She runs on a Pinch of crisis
Narrow stride
-thats fast
-Bye-Pichi..
-Bye
-Bye-Bye.. while in a pinch?
Why BYEPICHI?
"BYEPICHI" was when I was actually in Primary School
an old magazine called "Pichiremoso"
by taking the "PICHI"
i'm saying "BYEPICHI"
Why is it only Kawago's fault
Sometime I will come out to the members full throttle
so... Nakada, Himetan
-likely right?
-uhm..
-yeah likely
-there was that everyone went "Aaaaa"
that's right everyone went "Aaaa"
it's the intro for "Senpuuki"
first of her eyes as i thought its impossible
So i tried to look like it
Ah I understand
what do you think?
Ehh.. I think I just watched myself
A serious Problem
I didn't think it was like that
right?
maybe because you came in and out unconscious?
not unconscious, nothing like that
Himetan's tongue was a little sticking out
Himetan's case
-I know
-I know.. I know
Can you demonstrate it for us just a bit
Do it.. do it
Understood.. understood
-I want to see the exact way
Ah it came out
-So thats what  you mean
-Ahhhhhh
-Ah
that's why, because she's laughing
-right right
-AHHHHHH!!!!
It's out right?
-Ahh, because she was smiling too much
yes, like this
-I see! I see!
-Ahhhhhh
so that sort of face
ah so that's it
Your tongue was really out
It was
why not make it more exaggerated?
Nogizaka46.
Indeed.. Thank you very much.
Ok thank you very much.
Next monomane are these three entries
Takayam Kazumi mumbling to fans during handshake events.
Ohhh Kazumin do your best okay
Bye-bye.. bye-bye
Kazumin good luck okay...
POJI-PEACE!
AMAZING!
-Ahhh I see...
-Ahhh
-Understood........
Alright next monomane, is this!
Hoshino Minami's "Promise" not to say the same thing over and over at an handshake event
Ah Minami please visit tokyo. Do your best okay
Thank you
Minami do your best in senbatsu okay
Yup
Thank you
Minami
Good luck on your next single
Minami! what's your favorite food?
Thank you
Ah! Pan!
Pan!
Last minute Pan
so that's how you are in handshake events
Okay now next monomane, Go ahead
Alright
Nakamoto Himeka's "Ha line" beginning to sound like a shop during handshake event
Welcome
Ahhh
Hmmmmm
Himetan will do her best okay
Okaaaay!
Special "Ha" line
I see
Saito Chiharu went for Takayama
Yes
So whenever fans go to her she jumbles her words
Yes thats right
they're so fast they can't shake their hands properly
Baby hands Takayama
Amazing it looked like me..
aaaaamazing it was like me
Honestly it felt like me till the end..
nevertheless
time and time
We often practice hand swinging for handshake events
-Ahhh
then lately
it's like it shifted to doing something
Busy hands schedule
So that your handshaking you can do your "AMAZING!"
-yah yah yah yah yah
-that's great
Yah it's really great.. and fun
Uhm.. that's right she was amazing
Fast hands
and then Saito Yuri with Hoshino Minami
Yes
Hoshino's "hm.. hm.. thank you" is a little interval
feels something like that
while at it she also fixes her hair
-How about that food that she likes
ah that time "uh.. uh.. thank you. Ah! Pan! Pan!"
Time lag Pan
Not once but two pans
about this, do you know
I do say pan alot
Japanese Pan issues
-pan, your favorite is pan
But sometimes I worry
something like meat
It's like meat is inside my head
Clear the meat inside
They ask
"Did you have bread this morning?" something like that and I was like "Yeah! Bread!"
Wants to hear bread
So it want's to know if you had bread
and your voice was so little again
hm.. p..pan.. pan
correct correct
but lately my voice has been loud
right
so then your pan is loud?
-certainly
Lately it's been loud
Can you say "Pan" one more time?
PAN
-No no
Minimum Pan
-So little
-louder
-Ehh?!
like that Pan
PAN! like that. you let it out
ready.. go
PAN!
Limit of Hoshino
-so tiny so tiny
-right so tiny
-why?
Oh someone came out again, Himetan
Inoue went for Himetan
Himetan's targeted a lot..
so Himetan's shop
Maybe beacuse she's always like this
Welcome!
cause it feels like a shop right...
She really does that?
She does face to face
welcome
-Hello
Ah first "Nice to meet you" then "Welcome!"
-Ehhhhhhh....
welcome huh
uhm at the handshake event
When she's alone... no not alone but when theirs 3 or 2 of us paired.
When a small child came she also went...
AH WELCOME!!!
the best in everyone
when I reply "Hee" or "Haa"
everyone want's to listen to the conversation and hear "Hee" or "Haa"
Correspondence to "Haa" line
Ahh so theirs unity
Maybe it has alleged breath leak
Out of Order?
I understand, I see
Himetan's hanging out tongue and leaking breath is making her look like a fool
-we don't really know that yet
I'm not an idiot, I only look like one
there's something like that?
Lot's more of monomane are coming. Next up are these three entries
so so let's keep going next up is this!
13th single "Ima, Hanashitai Dareka Ga Iru" second verse Ikuta Erika's robotic like dance moves
-There's something like that?
-Wait, this one I wanna see
This one we don't know
I wanna see the real one
Next monomane please!
Takayama Kazumi's "Shi" during the unit song "Sakanatachi no LOVE SONG"
-Haha Takayam again
fukai kurayami ga
soko ni arimashita
Ahh they really did it
I saw myself
they really done it
Alright, next monomane is this!
Nakamoto Himeka responding to the fans even when the live show is finished
-Haha
-Himetan again haha
Re-appeared
Alright Akimoto
the second verse of "Ima, Hanashitai Dareka Ga Iru"
Yes, the second verse doesn't really get shown in Shows
so in that on the extent of difficulty Iku-chan
other than that, it looks like she's trying to shake something off
the other members know all about this though
but it's still a little weird
Iku-chan, just drags her left leg
Broken over
you're suppose to move both your legs
I wonder why put the left leg behind
I wonder too
Honestly I think Manatsu did well
Ikuta, what comes to your senses
That's right
My apologies I can't anymore I give up
Gracious decision
You can't do that
We will now see Akimoto's exaggerated monomane dance
No way. You've got to be kidding me
for real? for real?
Ikuta, that just now was that for real?
it's different from the others
Same song?
Ikuta's the odd one
You're lying
That now was serious?!
that's how i do it
Seriously?!
it's real
This is bad it's like a horror movie
Ritual curse?
Furthermore I'm not even the most good in that position
wait a minute
wait
Eh why what's wrong?
wait a minute now, Hashimoto sorry but can you show us seriously this time
It's very different
It's kinda difficult
But this part was correct
wait Ikuta can you..
Ikuta your real you okay
Ready.... go
Scary.. scary... That's just scary
Demon advent dance
Why do this? why move like this?
why why
terrific
that was hilarious
you must do more...
I don't really know the second verse when not much done in live's
uhmm
so I'm not afraid to do at live's
So now to be honest you can do it in live's?
-you rehears that right?
Yes we do
-So you really do the second verse
We do, but not that much
-not that much
not that much
-ah that's a relief
-Do it....
Super dance.
we did it our handshake event
ah right we did
-ah so at the handshake event
you do the second verse at handshake events
-We do
Next Wada
Again with Takayama
Takayama is really popular
When ever she says the word "Shi"
it's Like a person without teeth at all...
Dentures feeling
that's the comparative strength to it?
it all went out in one breath
just like a grandma right
I first cannot say "sashisuse-so"
line of natural enemies.
you where just fast now
"sashisuse-so"
When I say "sashisuse-so"
I'll loose the sharpness of my breath
now, try for a little while
I can but...
the "sashisuse-so" ?
sashi... so..
that was real
one more
just relax
i'll relax
sashi... so
you're kidding me?!
where's "Su"
it's "Sashisuseso" you know
try to say it from "AEIOU"
"AEIOU"..."KAKIKUKEKO"..."SASHI... SO"
"SU&SE" are missing.
"Shhhh" I can but "ShiShi to" I can't
-Eh?
"ShiShi to"
shishi to?!
Hates the word "ShiShi to"
i thought you just said die
What are you going to do about eating Green pepper (shishito)
ehhh.. no.. uhm.. when you put "toka"
Shishito pose.
Kawago
As i thought Himetan again
-why this also?
Himetan's something like...
Who's face did she saw down the stage and was like "AHH"
So there isn't... uhm a towel with everyone's name on it huh? that's why she saw it and went "AHH"
Well me, I think I'll probably try doing it to everyone
The best in everyone.
Try haha... so you'll try it to whomever
with some staring eye's
with staring eye's
I'll come closer and say "I found you" that kind of feeling is amazing
but doesn't everyone do that "found you"
but it's like your pulling someone
-I see i see i see
Let's talk about for a while
I wanna hear about this.....
did you do it?
because i can't see them all
-ah cause their is a big scale of people
because you saw them raising your towel that's why..
Yes, that's why I said "Ahhh" "Thank you" "Haaaa" "Heee"
-Mechanical service
-right right right right
But there is a tendency that a person's characteristic is mimicked
it's true
everyone one has to watch their origanal self
right.
everyone has exaggerated characteristics
everyone here is a bit exaggerated except for Ikuta because she showed us her true self.
Woman beyond mimicry.
Up next, the monomane with life impact is found?
Next three monomane entries will be done by Wakatsuki alone.
Next monomane is this!
Matsumura Sayuri's embarrassed at full power when given a compliment
thank you very much for your time we'd like to start the interview
onegaishimasu~
YAAAA~ I'm really happy, actually my oshimen is Matsumura-san
EHHH!! I'm glad, what do i do? HEHEHEHE~~~
Alright next monomane please!
The mysterious movements inside the dressing room by Matsumura Sayuri.
Suun!
te te te te
Tekori hmmhehehe~~~
There's something like that
yiiiyaa I wanna hear this
So let's continue next please!
Matsumurua Sayuri eating Eggsandwich with sound because of onomatopeia.
-Sayurin again
hmmhehehe~~ ham ham ham ham
Onomatopeia queen
Amazing, Wakatsuki you alone
3 consecutive.
on Matsumura
-Wakatsuki 3 consecutive copied Matsumura
you know Matsumura well
you two watch monomane right?
ah right
She really puts out the sound that much?
she... does
During recording... when were about to begin.. "Suun!"
-she went "Suun!"
teko teko teko... tekori
isn't that bad
Mysterious onomatopeia festival.
Eh I don't say such things
but you said it yourself
when she eats food properly...
"mogu-mogu" "ham-ham"
with egg sandwich right... "ham-ham"
-egg sandwich
It's not ham.. It's egg.
it's like... huhuhuuu~~
That
That too right.. that "hehehe"
huhuhehehehe
because i like manga's... manga and anime... I heard "gyoon" and i thought I should use it
uhm.. ge.. eh it's so embarrassing... what should I do I look stupid
Do you make sounds like that everytime you work?
-no no you don't have to do that
Mystery pose
This is bad.. because when you're on a occasion and you have to go to the toilet you'll make sounds will you be okay?
GACHAN (slam) PEKOPEKOPEKO BURIBURI (poop)
Guess what sound effects.
you don't know... but someday it might  happen when you're all together
some say when you get angry you PUN-PUN (fart)
ahhh when you're angry it's called "OKO"
-do you really get angry?
truly angry
When I'm really angry
how?
I might say "Mu~u"
Rage "Mu~u"
she really said that
-Really?
"I'm angry mu~u" like that?
-you're definitely not angry
-That's no anger