Original sub by MasToppu
ReTranslate by Yuuki
QC by TechiNeru46
Nogizaka Koujichuu.
m 0 0 l 0 15.25 l 1.125 15.25 l 1.125 0 l 0 0 m 1.125 0 l -2.25 0 l -2.25 3.375 l 9.125 3.375 l 9.125 2.25 l -1.125 2.25 l -1.125 1.125 l 0 1.125 m 1.125 1.125 m 9.125 0 l 9.125 15.25 l 10.25 15.25 l 10.25 -0.625 l 9.125 -0.625 m 12.5 0 l 12.5 0 l 13.625 0 l 13.625 6.25 l 10.875 6.25 l 10.875 5.125 l 12.5 5.125 l 12.5 1.125 l 8.625 1.125 l 8.625 0 m 3.375 10.125 l 3.375 6.75 l 6.75 6.75 l 6.75 7.875 l 4.5 7.875 l 4.5 10.125 l 3.375 10.125 m 6.75 10.125 l 6.75 11.25 l 3.375 11.25 l 3.375 10.125 l 5.625 10.125 l 5.625 7.875 l 6.75 7.875 l 6.75 10.125 m 2.875 4 l 4.5 5.125 l 4 5.625 l 2.25 4.5 l 2.875 4 m 5.625 5.125 l 5.625 5.125 l 7.375 4 l 8 4.5 l 6.25 5.625 l 5.625 5.125 m 1.75 13.5 b 1.75 13.5 1.75 13 1.75 13 b 4 11.875 6.25 11.875 8.625 13 b 8.625 13 8.625 14.125 8.625 14.125 b 6.25 13 4 13 1.75 14.125
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
DON!
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
We are your hosts Bananaman Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu.
So, this is Nogizaka members for today
BANANAMAN
Shitara Osamu
Himura Yuuki
Huh?
There's so many members today.
- So many
Then, Himura-san, please announce what we're doing today
Okay, this is our segment for today
Hori Miona presentation segment.
I want to know more about the uniqueness of 2nd Gen !!
There are still many interesting things! Let's find out more about the 2nd Gen Segment !!
This time, we will use the segment ...
... presented by Hori some time ago.
Hori, Itou Karin and Shinuchi have thought of ...
.... a segment where members of 2nd Gen will be able ...
.... to show their uniqueness with a challenge for each member.
What about..
...your relationship, Is there any problem?
m 265.5 -98.5 l -267.125 -98.5 l -267.125 10.75 l 265.5 10.75
Want to go to Onsen?
There's a good Onsen available
A nice Onsen is ready for you
If you guys together like this, do you still feel nervous towards 1st Gen?
- Not really...
- No?
Really? You're not lying?
- Eh???
- Are you okay?
Obviously it is difficult to say, huh?
So today, we leave it all on Hori.
- Ah, well, leave it to me.
But if we do that, It would be weird.
m 265.5 -98.5 l -267.125 -98.5 l -267.125 10.75 l 265.5 10.75
A little bit worrying
It's okay. I'm going to do it right.
- Well, please begin.
- Yes.
Can I stand there?
- May I stand there?
- What is it? You like to sell us something?
m 265.5 -98.5 l -267.125 -98.5 l -267.125 10.75 l 265.5 10.75
Business Segment?
No, That's not it!
It's not that kind of program
We want to know more about the uniqueness of Gen2!
Yamazaki Rena
We want to know more about
the uniqueness of 2nd Gen !!
The first member is Yamazaki Rena.
Yamazaki Rena is good at drawing face!
- So you're good at drawing face?
- Yes.
- You can draw pictures of people ....
- In addition I draw with a pencil.
- So you draw using pencil?
- Yes, right.
She's also good at drawing face of the members, and ...
... she also drew members face in the studio this time.
Oh, very good!
Shiarishi Mai
Ikuta Erika
Wakatsuki Yumi
Hoshino Minami
It's more than I had imagined ...
... really similar.
- Everything is similar.
- Easy to recognize them, huh?
- The other members who were not present, as well.
- Good.
How long it takes for you to draw this?
For example, Shiraishi.
For Shiraishi-san, about 30 minutes.
Shiraishi Mai
- So, Shiraishi takes 30 minutes?
- Yes. - Ikuta?
Ikuta-san, about 45 minutes.
Ikuta Erika
Ikuta 15 minutes longer!
Why? Why is that?
From the beginning, you really like to draw?
I like to draw, but never draw a face before.
Is that so?
- So, you like to draw a face, when you enter Nogizaka?
- That's right.
This style, without a nose, huh?
Shiarishi Mai
Ikuta Erika
Wakatsuki Yumi
Hoshino Minami
That's true, but more recently, I draw my first nose for Wakatsuki-san.
That's right, there's Wakatsuki nose.
- Actually, there are some more drawings of other members.
- There is? - Yes, please watch it.
- Wow!
- Ah, this is wonderful!
Etou Misa
Matsumura Sayuri
Noujou Ami
Saitou Chiharu
- So similar, right - Right, so similar.
The one on the bottom left, Noujou-san.
Ah, so it was Noujou, huh?
Noujou Ami
- I think it was Takayama.
- I thought so.
I thought so, too.
This drawing is Noujou when in good condition.
Right.
My drawing becomes sweeter than it was.
Of course, this makes us worried,
what if it turns out weird, right?
Noujou, isn't it better like this?
Noujou Ami
Why is that? Why?
She also took the original image of the members in this studio.
Original drawing?
Ah, it's that small, huh?
First, Kazumi-san
Here's Takayama Kazumi-san.
Takayama Kazumi
This is what I want to see.
- This is when she smiled.
- Ah, that's right!
- So you drew it this small, huh. - Yes.
I absolutely love it. Are you going to give it to me?
No, it will not be given.
- So it was not given, huh?
- Because there is only this.
- Takayama are there any unique parts of her?
- Kazumi-san ...
... she has a tiny mouth, so.
- Right. This part also ...
- Cute lips.
- That part is so cute! - It's good, right
- This part is really cute!
- So she's cute, right?
m 265.5 -98.5 l -267.125 -98.5 l -267.125 10.75 l 265.5 10.75
Nogi-Ota.
- You're a Nogizaka fans, right?
- Right.
This part I think is cute.
Takayama this part is amazing, huh. That will appear when she smiling.
- Right.
- Is it really black as it was?
You do something in that part, huh?
m 265.5 -98.5 l -267.125 -98.5 l -267.125 10.75 l 265.5 10.75
Plastic surgery?
- What's wrong?
- Because this part is so cute.
- Here's Akimoto-san.
- Ah, similar!
Akimoto Manatsu
Her head should have been bigger, right?
No. My head is not that big.
m 265.5 -98.5 l -267.125 -98.5 l -267.125 10.75 l 265.5 10.75
For sure
- Not that big.
- It makes the difference, right?
- This time, Bananaman-san also ...
- This is it!
- For us, too? - Thank you very much.
- My newest work ...
If anyone draw us, it always turns out strange.
- I haven't show this in my blog yet. - Really?
- This is really new.
- The first time you show this?
If you can make it to be a more sweet drawing, huh!
Because many say we are sweet!
So the correct picture!
- I'm looking forward to this!
- OH!
- It's really good!
- Really similar!
- Ah, very good!
- Wow, this is so great!
Ah, very good!
Wah, the quality is so high!
The drawing of Shitara-san, very nice, huh?
- Right!
- Good!
Like in a photo ...
- In a photo ...
- Its like this, right?
- Great!
- Yes, like that!
This is great!
Really similar!
- Conversely, This actually similar with photos, huh?
- That's right.
- Uh, who's this aunt there beside me?
- That's me!
m 265.5 -98.5 l -267.125 -98.5 l -267.125 10.75 l 265.5 10.75
Mysterious aunt
I'm an old man
This?
That's definitely an old man
Why didn't you know, even though we've been together for 20 years.
This is awesome, huh?
- I'll give this to you.
You'll give it to us? - Yes.
- Really?
- I'll give it.
- Eh?
- Well ... this ...
But there's only this one.
Right ...
m 126 31.5 l 0 31.5 l 0 0 l 126 0
Kitano Hinako has excessive reactions? !!
2nd Gen physical tests, the results will be!?
WAH!!!
Did Maiko-san also play hula hoop?
- Obviously we didn't know!
Ha..ha..ha..ha..ha..ha..
She laughs
That's scary!
Well, let's go on, huh? Hori, please.
Well then, six members of 2nd Gen will perform a physical diagnosis* on them.
- Physical Diagnosis?
- Physical Diagnosis, huh?
- I mean physical condition tests.
- Tests of physical condition, huh?
Who are those 6 members?
- Me!
- Why is it just ...
Only these 6 members that fit with the schedule.
Hori, it shouldn't be said.
This time, six members will take
three challenges, those are ...
... high jump, hula hoop and bridge.
First challenge, high jump
Suzuki Ayane
Oh, amazing!
Success~
Ah, so cute!
Kitano Hinako
Looks like all of them can do it, huh
Shinuchi Mai
- OL.
- Maichun!
Slow, so slow.
She's really slow.
Wait!
Sasaki Kotoko
Looks like she can't do it
- How can this happen?
- She didn't even jump over that.
Terada Ranze
Looks like she can do it.
No, no , what is she doing!
Ah! Cramps!
Wait a minute.
Please, don't, this is embarrassing.
What a shame.
She's still young but she cramps already?
Hori Miona
Hori looks like she can do it.
BELLY ROLL?!
Isn't that Belly Roll?
And this is the result of the high jump.
First, Kitano Hinako
who managed to jump as high as 105 cm.
Second challenge, hulahoop!
What challenge is this?
Terada Ranze
Earlier you said you can do it, right? - Her waist is so slender!
Actually it's quite easy.
I usually do it.
Shinuchi Mai
Terada so thin!
She looks so slow right?
She's like Kabajou.
[Kabajou = Cabaret club girls]
Maichun so sexy!
Don't make me laugh.
Kitano Hinako
- She's so thin!
- Wah, so fast!
Ah, she can do it!
All of them seems they can do this
Sasaki Kotoko
Ah, it turns out I can do this.
I can do it.
I can do it. I'm glad.
Sasaki...
Suzuki Ayane
...looks like Maiko-san, right?
So serious!
She looks like a doll.
Ayane looks like enjoying the rhythm of the rotation!
- Her looks!
- Her girls aura didn't come out, huh?
They are good at this.
Hori Miona
No, no, ...
How many is that? How many times?
Why does she still continue?
Why do you continue?
Look, the hula hoop fall down!
Hori is indeed something else.
Hulahoop Extra
Shinuchi Mai "Neck Spin"
This! This!
Shinuchi Mai
What are you doing? What?
Third challenge is....
... while doing bridge,
they will bring their hands and feet closer.....
... then measured how close the distance that can be made.
Terada Ranze
Ah!
- No, it's ... -
- [staff]: Already?
Uh, please measure it!
No, I really can't do this!!!
She's still young
※ Measuring distance between hands and feet
[staff]: 63 cm.
She lifted her chin ...
Uh, exhausted.
Measured the flexibility of the back.
Suzuki Ayane
- Hands and feet are approximated. - Ah, so that ?!
Ah, so the distance?
Please measure it.
Zenjou! It's Zenjou!
[Zenjou = Meditation position.]
- [staff]: 34 cm.
- Alright!
You pretend to be bad in the challenge before, right?
It looks beautiful if they could do it, right.
Shinuchi Mai
Everyone so good, right
,, But, if the body is tall, it's difficult, isn't it?
Eh, I can't do more!
Measure it, please.
[staff]: Distance: 60 cm.
"Measure it, please!"
Kitano Hinako
Ah, so low.
Her back is so stiff.
DONE!!!
So stiff.
[staff]: 66 cm.
Ah, she's tired.
Hori Miona
Hori.
Great, great, great!
Ha...ha...ha...ha...ha...ha...ha...ha...ha...
Her hands and feet approaching.
She laughs. So scary!
Please measure it!
[staff]: 40 cm.
HA
That's all for 2nd Gen physical test.
Ah, very interesting!
- Wait a minute, what was that?
- What is that?
- Why it should these 3 challenges? - What do you want to measure?
- We also do many other things.
- Approximately 10 challenge.
You guys do up to 10 challenges?
- So, among all of that, only those 3 which could be considered attractive?
- Yes, like that.
- Everyone, seems good at sports. - Me too?
- You look a little weird.
- But, we can see what you mean.
You look like a middle-aged woman.
How about that physical condition test before?
Me and her, you could say not good at sports, so it was a bit ...
... i'm sorry, as this may sound bad, because we think Ayane-chan couldn't do sports either.
and when she could, we thought it was so great.
- We were surprised.
- Yes, quite shocked.
You like to eat Kiritanpo Nabe*, right?
[Kiritanpo Nabe = traditional soup from Akita,
where Ayane dan Ikoma come from.]
Although people from Akita looks like they often eat Kiritanpo , but in fact we rarely eat it.
Oh, is that so? - I rarely eat it even though it was from my hometown.
- If it's me, I can eat it up to 3 times a month. - So you did eat it!
- She ate it, right! She often ate it! So you must be eat it too from time to time.
She really like it, huh?
We also want to try again
some physical condition test like this, huh?
Right, we want to try it, right.
If it's now, that can turns out to be really bad.
For me, because I get some hard practice for LIVE, so ...
... now may be better than before.
- No, no.
- So good she presented herself.
It's just pretending, right?
If I thought, this is also the same as the Hori's Belly Roll , isn't it?
That's right
No, that's because I don't know how to jump over that so...
How she play hula hoop too,
unbelieveable!
Scary, how you play that hula hoop
Sasaki also terrific, her hair tied above ...
...like Maiko-san* who is on vacation.
[Maiko-san = traditional dancer from Kyoto.]
We obviously don't know about Maiko-san.
Just a guess,
maybe that's how they looks.
- She looks deft in her home. - Right, like a lady.
- Did Maiko-san also play hula hoop?
- We certainly don't know.
On the other hand, we also want to know
Did she play (hula hoop)?
- It wasn't Maiko-san, right? - Right.
- You only talk like her. - Ah right, thanks.
- Terada so slender, right
That's true
- I'm shocked. - She was like a pole.
Ranze never played in the park.
Eh, what is it? You're not good at sports?
She never felt it. She also didn't play out in the park.
Why? Are you locked up?
That's not it...
- But, certainly you play once when you were a child.
I like it, I like it!
Even if i go there, there's insects everywhere
Is there any merit for going there?
Well you can have fun doesn't it?
So you never go to a park?
I don't remember going.
- Then what are you doing?
- Right, what are you doing?
Instead of going to the park, I prefer,
such as shopping ...
... or eat some sweets, it's more fun.
So, you prefer it like that.
We want to know more about the uniqueness of 2nd Gen !!
We want to know more
about the uniqueness of 2nd Gen !!
Kitano Hinako
Next is Kitano Hinako.
Segment for Kitano Hinako is this..
Kitano Hinako is very suitable for dokkiri.
What does this mean?
- Her voice was loud, and then the reaction is too excessive.
- Good reaction? - Right.
- WAW !!!
- Ah, that surprised me!
Amazing!
Good, good!
WAW!!!
Wait a minute,~
I could die there~
He's getting there ...
Wait, what? What's wrong?
When I was doing this before, my back strained ...
While we wait to record this 2nd Gen segment ...
Me, Hori and Shinuchi, did some dokkiri on Kitano.
- So you guys who did the dokkiri?
- That's right.
So, please watch it.
This time, Kitano will be tricked
3 times in a row.
Normal Macaron
Super Spicy Macaron
First, between these 8 macarons,
there are 5 pieces of Super Spicy Macaron.
And, the perpetrators must be able to make her eat one of these 5 Macarons, to see her reaction.
Super Spicy Macaron
And soon after, she would be given sour lemon vinegar, and ...
Lemon Vinegar
Senburi Tea
...followed by bitter Senburi tea.
Strategy to get some good reactions!
Operation Start
- It's a little scary.
- Scary, huh?
Hinako definitely wants the one with Pistachio flavor.
- Which one is Pistachio?
- The green one.
It's Green Tea, right?
It's called Pistachio.
- What is Pistachio?
- Here there are Pistachio, Vanilla and Strawberry.
First, 3 of them, will take normal Macaron before Kitano.
- It smells good
- It smells good.
- Maybe this one is caramel flavor.
How about you try it?
Super Spicy
- Maybe it tastes like milk.
- There is a bit taste of salt.
Super Spicy
Ah, salty, huh?
NICE REACTION!
Oh, nice one!
It appears.
It's good, nice reaction!
You want some water?
Very sour lemon vinegar has been prepared
Are you alright? Are you okay?
The taste, is something wrong?
What? What's wrong?
Very sour lemon vinegar has been prepared
- Here, drink this!
- Nothing's wrong.
- You're unlucky.
- True, she was unlucky.
Lemon Vinegar
- Uh, drink it first.
- Drink it.
Lemon Vinegar
It tastes bad, huh?
Ah, this is nice!
SUFFERING
Nice! This is good!
This is so good!
- Are you okay? - Hinako,are you okay?
Her reaction is so excessive.
What happened? Is there something wrong?
The perpetrator is so...
What's the matter?
The perpetrators is so relaxed.
Why, huh? Perhaps because of the taste from Macaron before is bad,
so the water too also taste bad.
- Why is that?
- Then, try to drink some tea.
Very bitter tea has been prepared.
After that, Senburi tea that taste very bitter has been prepared
It's because of this Macaron!
Is there anything wrong?
Senburi Tea
Eh, this one is also doubtful to drink
- She hesitated. - Ah, she's scared, right.
Senburi Tea
Uwaaa~
Watch out, you'll spill it everywhere!
The drink ...
She knows?
Use a tissue first, here.
The perpetrators keep attacking
Maichun, the way you pour it makes
it taste unpleasant!
Until now, Kitano is still not aware that she was being tricked
- It's my fault that this happens ...
- The way Maichun pour that tea isn't right!
Hey, hey ...
- Why does it become like that?
- But, this is just water.
Heh?!
- She's not aware of this yet?
- Amazing.
What happened to you?
Why did you speak so carelessly?
Here, we'll tell her about the dokkiri!
Wah, wait!!!
- [staff]: Thank you very much!
- Thank you very much for your cooperation!
[staff]: The recording was over..
Yey, thanks for your cooperation.
Because Hinako has the most excessive reactions among 2nd Gen, so ...
... there are no culinary program.
So, we just playing dokkiri on you with
many of these things, and it's already over.
Because it's so spicy, my tongue came out.
Great Job!
SO FRUSTATING!!!
DOKKIRI BIG SUCCESS!
So cute!
Nice. Nice reaction!
- It could be considered successful.
- Ah, thank goodness.
Isn't this nice? Because it can be said ...
... there are such segments in
several programs.
- You aren't aware of it, huh? - I'm really not aware of it.
,, Don't you think, if something was weird, with that spicy taste?
Because the fillings is red, and I think it was a fruit, Cranberry ,are popular today, so...
... maybe it used that fruit, but after I ate it,
it was spicy, ...
- So, I think there are some Macaron with taste like that.
- Ah, so you think there are really some like that, huh?
Then about Lemon Vinegar and Senburi Tea ...
Because my tongue was surprised with that spicy taste, so ...
... I think, because of that, all of it tastes bad.
Nice reaction, and she is easily tricked, huh?
,, - Yes, she is easily tricked. - Nice, huh!
- She is innocent, huh?
- It's a good thing from her.
- She could be trapped by anything.
- If the reaction is so excessive, isn't it nice,right?
- Obviously, it is!
Don't worry, we won't surprise you right now.
Ah, so you're worried about the "WAH!" from before?
So she could be easily tricked, huh?
Then any other?
- Because she is still innocent.
Is there someone like her?
But, most of the 2nd gen has normal reaction...
Shinuchi, for example, her reaction is like a old-stinky-woman.
- Like old-stinky-woman?
- It's a bit exaggerated, ...
What does that reaction mean?
Her action is actually looks older than her age.
- What is that?
- Shinuchi, that's what they said.
- Maybe she's right.
After this, Itou Junna will do crazy challenge !!
We want to know more about
the uniqueness of 2nd Gen !!
Itou Junna
We want to know more about the uniqueness of 2nd Gen !!
Last one is Itou Junna.
Itou Junna, the Mood-maker, will undertake any challenge given to her.
- Is that so?
- That's right.
- She doesn't look that way, right? - She looks different.
If there is a camera, or an adult ...
... she always doesn't want to
show the crazy stuff that she did in dressing room.
So, usually she's excited, huh?
She's a comedian in the dressing room?
So, this VTR , we recorded it in secret.
- Hidden Camera? In the dressing room?
- That's right.
This time, to show her real character ...
.... Itou Junna will be challenged to do karaoke,
until she was able to score 95 points. ..
...with all of her skill,or she can't go home!
That is the challenge she needed to do.
This is a hidden recording about
things she did while waiting.
If we're doing karaoke, it's okay to dance, right?
For example, we dance according to the movement in Nogizaka songs that we sing.
We have to sing a Nogizaka song?
No, anything is fine.
We can just look for songs usually sung at karaoke.
Songs on my phone, like "Ai no Uta", "Sakuranbo" ...
KARAOKE Motivation MAXIMUM!
"Rao" ...
- Try "Sakuranbo"! - True, that must be fun.
"Sakuranbo" looks like impossible ...
- I want to say  "Mou ikkai! (Once more)"
- Ah, that one.
[Mou ikkai! (Once more) = a part of Sakuranbo lyric.]
- I want to see!
- I want to do it.
Eh, but if you know, we can try it once,
then we can immediately play at that show.
What if you try it first.
First, the perpetrators trying to make her sing to lift her spirit
Songs which you can sing.
For now, try it first.
No, I don't want to sing ...
... I want to sing when it's time for recording later.
For Junna whose not excited, Hori make her move!
For Junna whose spirit is missing ...
.. here, Hori began to move!
Didn't bother to sing ...
This could be ...
It seems to be used
in several segments in the program, huh?
Tennis racket is likely to be used too.
Afro Wig
Uh, you know, it's like that ...
This...
Afro Wig
- The hair ... - Very funny, right!
Can we bring this to karaoke?
I want to bring it!
This certainly can make things rousy, right!
If Junna wear this, when you meet the staff,that would have been nice!
Try to use it once.
This can ruin my hair.
Ah, it's okay. You can fix it later.
Hang on. Isn't that Inoue Yosui?
Are you Inoue Yosui-san?
So you're Inoue Yosui-san?
- I'd better get my bangs in first.
- She put it in!
Seeing a chance here, 3 of them is doing something...
So, Inoue Yosui-san song, right.
Seeing a chance here,
3 of them is doing something here...
Inoue Yosui "Shounen Jidai"
Eh, but you can sing this!
You can exercise your voice.
- Try to sing. - What song?
"Natsu ga sugi..."
Standing?
Romaji lyric: project-imas.com
Natsu ga sugi kaze azami
Dare no akogare ni samayou
- Record it! Record it! - Ah, yes!
Hachigatsu wa yume hanabi
It's definitely 95 points. You can do this!
watashi no kokoro wa natsu moyou
Amazing!
- You did it.
- Your voice is strong?
My voice is strong.
Want to make her do more,these 3 will ...
Then,these 3 try some other things.
It looks like there's another Afro wig, right?
Isn't this like Sukima Switch?
Sukima Switch
What is it?
Jun aura already existed!
Sukima Switch - "Kanade"
Here.
Let's hear it.
Kanade by Itou Junna.
Romaji lyric: animelyrics.com
Kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
itsumo no zawameki, atarashii kaze
Don't use the mic, it's okay!
Completely unnecessary.
It looks like this, from here.
Piano
Akaruku miokuru hazu datta no ni
Stereo voice.
Her mic over here, perhaps?
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
- Here? - But, look, look.
It's there, right? In the video.
Her voice is so good.
Saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
"Sayonara" ni kawaru kotoba wo
boku wa sagashiteta
Wow, amazing!
Here, we'll tell her about the dokkiri!
[staff]: Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Eh?
Eh? What is this?
[staff]: Recording is over.
- This...
- EH?!
- This time ...
- SERIOUSLY ?!
because Junna real character
only appears in the dressing room, so ...
... we did some hidden recording in the dressing room!
Great Job!
Is it finished?
- [staff]: No karaoke program.
- Really?
But Jun already search for it
Pity me. Eh?
Name of the new segment will appear?!
Let Me Do It ! 2nd Presentation Segment
Next episode,
Nogizaka Koujichuu will hold a presentation segment!
Members will present
segment that they want to do!
Then, which segment from members that will be made?
- So that is Ami?
- It's bad, there is a short-legged horse like that?
m 126 31.5 l 0 31.5 l 0 0 l 126 0
Next episode, Let Me Do It ! 2nd Presentation Segment
Some new segment will appear?!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
What are you doing? What is this?
Then, only robot will left, huh.
That's seems fun!
Why is it like that?
You said Lesbian Robot, just now!
Lesbian Robot!
Ah, who is that? Sunplaza Nakano-san?
Then what is the segments that presented
with passion by Noujou?