m 0 0 l 0 40.5 l 3 40.5 l 3 0 l 0 0 m 3 0 l -6 0 l -6 9 l 24.125 9 l 24.125 6 l -3 6 l -3 3 l 0 3 m 3 3 m 24.125 0 l 24.125 40.5 l 27.125 40.5 l 27.125 -1.5 l 24.125 -1.5 m 33.25 0 l 33.25 0 l 36.25 0 l 36.25 16.5 l 28.625 16.5 l 28.625 13.5 l 33.25 13.5 l 33.25 3 l 22.625 3 l 22.625 0 m 9 27 l 9 18 l 18.125 18 l 18.125 21 l 12.125 21 l 12.125 27 l 9 27 m 18.125 27 l 18.125 30 l 9 30 l 9 27 l 15.125 27 l 15.125 21 l 18.125 21 l 18.125 27 m 7.5 10.5 l 12.125 13.5 l 10.625 15 l 6 12 l 7.5 10.5 m 15.125 13.5 l 15.125 13.5 l 19.625 10.5 l 21.125 12 l 16.625 15 l 15.125 13.5 m 4.5 36 b 4.5 36 4.5 34.5 4.5 34.5 b 10.625 31.5 16.625 31.5 22.625 34.5 b 22.625 34.5 22.625 37.5 22.625 37.5 b 16.625 34.5 10.625 34.5 4.5 37.5
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
NOGIZAKA KOUJICHUU
First, let's watch Nakamoto's presentation last week.
Here it is, Jyaan~~
Erasing heartache with "Revenge Onsen".
- Woaah, that's great!
An onsen is a Japanese hot spring.
Nakamoto who's good friend with Inoue and Ito Marika, last year planned to go on Onsen vacation.
They said "Next year let's go to Onsen in Toyama, three of us!"
However,...
And, there was a day, I found something on the blog.
This is an article in September on Inoue Sayuri's blog.
Here it is, Ja~jyan~~!
Last month, I was very grateful to have the first
summer holiday since joining Nogizaka.
Therefore, both Marika and I...
- Eh, Toyama? Isn't this Toyama?!
They went to Toyama!
- What? - What did they do?
Wait, they look delightful in this photo.
That's right!
- Isn't this just two of them?
Next is this.
- They stayed in this place.       - Right.
After arriving at the lodge, we then went by a bus to Onsen.
- What? They went to Onsen!
We had a very long bathe in the beautiful Rotenburo until we got too cold. That was fun.
Rotenburo are hot spring baths that are situated outdoors.
Usually surrounded by beautiful natural view.
Himetan, what's this? Didn't you know it?
I've never heard the story from them.
- Eeehh?!
- You knew it from her blog?
- That's right!   -Seriously!
Wait, from that photo you three look so close, even going out together.
They even promised next time they would go on vacation and stay together, right?
LAST YEAR VACATION PHOTO
We indeed said "Let's go together to Toyama!".
- What's wrong?
Actually I'm okay with it! I've got no problem if they want to go to Onsen just two of them.    - But...
But at least I want them to tell me about it!
- That should be, right?
Among members here, nobody has heard
about that Onsen vacation story, right?
- Ah, I've heard about it.
- Really?
- WHAT?
When we went together, and I said that
I want to go to Onsen, they heard it.
After that, they started telling how fun their Onsen vacation was.
Don't they seem secretive about it?
Himetan, sorry!
- No, no, Himetan, your face is scary.
Then, when we're going home, they said "Toyama is the best choice", like they have been there.
- This year that place is booming, right?
- They're like suggesting me to go there.
Himetan, your face looks sad. Looking up won't hold up your tears.
- Sorry.
ALMOST CRYING
- This is awesome.
This perhaps is interesting enough to be done.
- Hai!
That's good idea.
- If possible, you can go immediately after this.
And, finally,...
Private Onsen Vacation with Onsen Trio!!!
[Himura]: Why do you say Yeee!
Color code:
MARIKA   HIMETAN   SAYURI
As you know, three of us are good friends.
[Shiraishi]: Kawaiii!!!
[Shitara]: Is that true?
We always say, when can we go to Onsen together, right?
Today, it's finally realized through this show!!!
[Shitara]: They both don't know the truth.
Today, we're totally doing a private vacation.
So, we can talk like we casually do.
As we usually do, let's make this trip fun.
That is it, the plan to be carried out.
Through this, will the two friends, who don't understand Nakamoto's heartache, tell their Toyama vacation story?
But, suddenly...
[Manatsu]: What a pity!
This is so fun, because I do want to go THREE OF US.
- Yes, we really do want to go THREE OF US.
We do want to go THREE OF US
Want to go THREE OF US
After that, they visit Service Area before going to Onsen.
TOMEI TOLL ROAD
EBINA SERVICE AREA
[Shitara]: Maybe her friendship with them will end.
Suddenly, they find something in a corner of a shop.
It's Maiyan!
- Maiyan!
Maiyan! Himetan too!
Look at this! Can you try doing that here?
HIGH-SPIRITED INOUE.
Clearly you don't look like Maiyan.
[Shitara]: Maybe they're so excited
for having vacation together.
Good.
- Ah, so pretty~~(Himetan photo)
This is so good, right.
- Really?
Let's put Maiyan in the front.
SHIRAISHI
[Shiraishi]: How can it be bought, if laid out like that?
That's weird.
And, here...
By the way, do you want to buy something?
- Ah, how about buying something matching?
Eventually, they choose...
[Himura]: They are lined up like that...
So ugly~~!
So cute!
Really?!
They are really interested in these luck dolls.
With many options of luck color,
they then choose their favorite color.
St~art~~!
Red
Green
What did you say? What? What? What did you say?
Green.
- Green.
Eh, only Himetan who's different.
- Yes, right.
Clearly this vacation will just feel ordinary without bravery.
- That's right
RED : BLESSED WITH BRAVERY (BRAVE)
But, Nakamoto has a reason why she chose red.
It's because she needs bravery to ask the reason why they both went to Toyama.
We're the same, aren't we? - You two are the same.
Why? Why?
GREEN :  CHANCE TO MEET NEW THING (MEETING)
Wanting to find new things...
- Wanting to find new things, right.
Somehow, their choice both are the same.
Is this a bad omen that they want to separate from Nakamoto, seen from the color they chose?
[Shitara]: Eh, is that so?
However, they three still put up those luck dolls.
With full of spirit and happiness,
they forget that problem and start the vacation.
[Shitara]: Dangerous, her doll is still different.
This time they will visit Onsen Nanasawa in Kanagawa prefecture.
[Member & Shitara]: Very nice!!!
Of course, first they will enjoy the tourist attractions in this region.
[Himura]: In holiday season,
it's surely crowded!
The first chosen destination.
CHOKOKU SHRINE, IIYAMA KANON
A shrine famous for uniting couples frequently, Chokoku Shrine.
They want to get Omikuji with the best luck.
O-mikuji are random fortunes written on strips of paper at
Shinto shrines and Buddhist temples in Japan.
[Shitara]: It's impossible to get three luck, right?
Nakamoto surely wanted to get the best prediction for this vacation with her two friends this time, but...
[Himetan]: No, not like that...
What is it?
- Fairly lucky.
Luckier
- Fairly lucky
It is a travel luck,
"Lucky with your travel companion".
So, I'm lucky for having companions.
[Shitara]: That kind of prediction came up?
For me, good travel
- What does it say?
This, a good travel
- Ah, right!
Love prediction, no need to think about your love fate.
- That's,...
That's a bad prediction.
- Right, such a love prediction.
Beside that, Nakamoto's Omikuji also says...
Someone you're waiting for isn't coming due to obstacle.
Quarrel won't end if you stay quiet.
[Shitara]: Won't end if staying quiet?
[Shitara]: Eh, isn't that bad?
Next place is the favorite destination in this region, Atsugi Ham.
ATSUGI HAM
[Shitara]: Atsugi Ham.
One of the world's biggest sausage processing place, where visitors can enjoy the sausage with German original recipe.
This is fun, because it's been a long time since THREE OF US  went together. - That's right.
It's been a long time.
- Clearly.
Why should it be Ham? Is pork really popular?
Suddenly after this, shocking words come out from Inoue.
[Takayama]: What?!
Do you know which region consumes the most pork?
Eehhm...
Hai, Nagoya!
Wrong, it is Toyama
- Heeeehh~~~
[Shitara]: Eh? Toyama?!
It is Toyama
- Heeeehh~~~
TOYAMA!
- HEEEHHH~~~~
[Shitara]: Eh, Toyama?
Really? - Yes
Toyama?
[Himura]: This is scary.
I know it, when we went there at that time.
So what did you do in Toyama?
[Shitara]: When they went before?
In Toyama, what did we do?
But, at that time, we didn't eat Ham, right?
- Eh, yummy!
[Himura]: Wuuaah, she's lonely if left alone like that.
We didn't find anything, right?
- Yes
After that, we just ate fish and meat, right?
[Asuka]: No, no...
[Manatsu]: Awesome!
It seems, there are many other yummy food.
- Yes, right.
[Shitara]: Eh, did they say it?
Slowly, the talk is directed to the Toyama topic.
Now, it's the matter of how Nakamoto will steer the conversation to their Toyama Onsen vacation.
[Shitara]: seems like that prediction really came true.
Eeehh, I see.
By the way, in my hometown, Saitama,
there's a bread with square-shaped wrapping.
Because that's indeed the best bread.
Oooh..
- How can you know that?
DOES NOT MATTER
You're amazing that you know such things.
With such a good explanation,
when we go together, you can be the best guide.
If so, how about we go to Kyoto?
Let's go to Kyoto!
I want to go to Kyoto!
If so, we go to Kyoto!
Let's go to Kyoto!
I want to go to Kyoto!
[Shitara]: Then they both will go alone again.
By inviting her to go to Kyoto,
Can that story of Toyama show up?
Wah, this is so complicated.
Dangerous! This is like their farewell vacation, right?
I also want some day off, maybe?
I also want to be a person who can do that.
In my case, I can't be that kind of person at all.
- You certainly can't. - That's right.
Although you don't do that,
you still can go out if you are invited to go on vacation.
Surely.
- Right.
[Himura]: They really said it.
TOYAMA AGAIN...
That is possible, right.
- The process is like that.
[Himura]: Wah, critical hit for Himetan.
For Hime, is there any place you want to visit?
Perhaps because I'm an indoor person, so I don't really...
Himeka is always unavailable if invited to go, right?
No, if invited, I'll certainly accept it.
Maybe that's just your feeling that I'm unavailable.
- You're always unavailable.
Maybe that invitation never comes.
- All of them...
You also previously refused when invited, so I'm not sure to invite you.
[Manatsu]: That's a heavy pressure for the heart.
You can't compare it to the past.
After this job, if you say "Let's go eating",
I surely come, and I also want to invite you two.
So, don't hesitate to invite me.
REACTION, SO SO....
What's this?
- She seems desperate.
The next visited place is a beautiful park.
IIYAA HAKUSAN SHINRIN PARK
And,...
[Shiraishi & Takayama]: Kawaii!!
HIGH-SPIRITED INOUE (2).
So happy!!!
[Shitara]: She is recording while running.
After that, Ito's artistic soul appears.
A photo session with Inoue as the model is started.
[Shiraishi]: So happy.
ALONE.
[Himura]: A little time ago they looked like good friends.
[Shitara]: Himetan, Himetan is going to cry.
Then, eagerly, both of them...
[Shitara]: Dangerous, she's hard to blend in.
[Shitara]: This is really painful.
This is fun, just like in primary school.
[Himura]: This must be painful.
Riding a swing like this is fun, right?
- Fun!
PHOTOGRAPHER
[Shitara]: No, no. She looks really sad.
You're like  young again, right...
[Maaya]: Young again?!
Next, the market of freshly-picked groceries in Atsugi, Yumemichi.
JA.ATSUGI FARM MARKET, YUMEMICHI
And suddenly...
[MisaMisa]: What? [Shitara]: Eh, more?
I want to buy flowers. - Really?
- This is for the greenhouse.
Previously, when we went to Toyama,
I also bought a plant.
- Yes?
Yes, you bought it!
[Himura]: Awesome, Toyama comes up again
[Shiraishi]: Ah, that photo again!
Previously, when we went to Toyama,
I also bought a plant.     - Yes, you bought it!
All of the sudden, Toyama topic shows up.
Nakamoto, what will you do?
Tulip is quite popular in Toyama.
[Shitara]: They look just like tourists, right.
Marika couldn't choose white Tulip,
[Shitara]: Here, they don't seem secretive about it, right?
She immediately just put it in and brought it.
- Great.
Shocked by their conversation, Nakamoto couldn't say a word.
[MisaMisa]: What a pity... [Himetan]: No, not like that
Next, they both decides to buy fresh vegetables.
Ah, there are tomatoes here!
- I like tomatoes!
I want tomato...
- Looks tasty...
You don't like tomato, do you?
- Yes, I don't like!
Ehm..you two just buy it...
Really?
Are those three really good friends?
[Himura]: Didn't buy it?
[Shitara]: That's not good, because she didn't buy.
[Himura]: Are these three people really together?
Where will this thing go on?
[Shitara]: Unlike them, she didn't buy it.
Meanwhile, they take a rest while enjoying the food they just bought.
[Himura]: Should we stop this?
[Himura]: Why do they still look together?
[Shitara]: What a pity...
After that, they arrive at Onsen.
NANASAWA-SO
This time, they stay in Nanasawa Inn.
[Himura]: So beautiful...
[Himura]: Oh, really good...
Famous for its beauty, an Inn with Onsen that we can be proud of.
And they three immediately go to...
Now, we're going in to Onsen.
[Himura]: This is interesting!
[Himura]: Here it is!
[Shitara]: Watching 3 people in Onsen, right.
[Himura]: Here it is.
From here, let's listen to their conversation in the Onsen.
Let's go in!
- Let's go
Waaah!
[Himura]: So beautiful.
So beautiful....
So beautiful, right...
- Really beautiful...
[Shitara]: Looks beautiful from below. [Himura]: Right
It's all Rotenburo, right?
[Himura]: Eh, one by one.
I'm going in.
Aahh, feels good! Warm!
- So warm
[Himura]: Ah, their feet are white.
So warm!
[Shitara]: Many men surely like this.
I'm naked you know.
We are naked again, right.
It's nostalgic, right.
- Just like in the past, right?
Christmas last year, we also went to a place like this.
[Shitara]: They really bathed.
We did do it.
- Yes, right. We also went to Rotenburo at that time.
[Himura]: How can they be invisible?
But, the chance to do this
for the three of us is rare.
[Himura]: How did they do it?
We can only be together at that time only, right?
- In the radio, right?
At Christmas, we can be naked together like this, it's like...
[Shitara]: Story from last year sounds interesting!
That's right, maybe because I don't really like going to Onsen,...
- Himetan doesn't really go (with other people), right...
She only goes with us, right.
- That's right.
Really kind, right.
No need to worry about that actually.
As long as I can be with you two, that's enough.
- So happy.
BATHING FINISHED
We're done bathing in Onsen.
- Already done.
[Shitara]: Considering the purpose of this show, she looks miserable.
So tasty!
- Really?
COMPLETE MENU [AUTUMN LEAF]
[Shiraishi]: Chirashi-Sushi!
So pretty.
~Itadakimasu~
You know, if we three didn't go to Onsen like this,
We couldn't enjoy tasty food like this.
I do want to do this.
- Right?
I want to do this since long time ago.
- Me too. I like things like this.
They must have done such things.
- That's obvious.
When they three get more enthusiastic enjoying the food...
[Shitara]: Obviously! [Himura]: How will this go on?
This is Nakamoto's last chance to gather bravery to ask them.
But, because of her anxiety,
not even a word comes out from her mouth.
[Shitara]: Ah, it's heavy.
[Shitara]: Here it is, the plan to erase heartache.
[Himura]: Keep up the spirit!
COMPLETE SILENCE
[Himura]: Why you become afraid?  [Shitara]: Good move.
[Himura]: This is really bad. [Manatsu]: Go for it!
Eventually, Nakamoto doesn't say a word.
[Shitara]: Eh, can not speak?
To relieve her anxiety, she goes out of the room.
Eating time is almost up.
Nakamoto who has calmed down, will soon start her big battle.
[Shitara]: Will she speak?
[Shitara]: Speak!
[Shitara]; Let's speak up!
By the way...
I...
[Shitara]: Here it is!
May I say something
Yes, it's okay, go ahead.
Unexpectedly, she suddenly wanted to start talking...
[Himura]: Scary!
Just like the suggestion, by using
"By the way", can she do it?
[Himura]: Scary!
[Shitara]: Quarrel won't end if you stay quiet.
May I say something
Yes, it's okay, go ahead.
I also want to hear it if something needs to be discussed together.
- Really? - Yes.
May I?
What?
What should I do...
What's wrong?
Alright, I will talk.
By the way, this time,
When I said "I want to do this vacation trip",
Actually this trip has another purpose.
[Shitara]: This is great!
You two weren't told about that.
Eh?
No need to worry for not knowing that.
Last September, you both went to Toyama, right?
Yes, we went.
Yes, and,...
That story, I have never heard about it before, right?
After you had gone back,
I've never heard a story like "I've just been there" from you.
I think I want to hear that story...
[Shitara]: You said it.
At Christmas last year, when we were bathing in Onsen,
just after Shinkansen Hokuriku route was opened,
Shinkansen Hokuriku is a high-speed railway line
connecting Tokyo-Toyama-Kanazawa.
I remember, at that time there was a story like
"Riding Shinkansen Hokuriku three of us then go somewhere".
At that time, we wondered where we wanted to go...
Then, both of you already rode Shinkansen Hokuriku, right?
Yes, you did, right?
Yes, we rode
Although I'm okay with it, I think "Ah! So that was it...."
[Shitara]: Wah, this is dangerous!
Not like that!
I think they deliberately did that.
But, maybe that's just me worrying too much. Just like that...
But, that's not true, right?
I am sorry...
but that's not true at all...
We completely forgot.
[Shitara]: Terrible! This is so terrible!
Does that mean you both didn't remember me at all?
- No, not like that.
Talking about Onsen,
I definitely want to go to Gokayama,
Gokayama is a region in Toyama,
where Onsen that was visited by Inoue and Marika is situated.
I have also made a plan for that,
Because at that time we got a summer holiday,
I thought I must go there immediately.
But, at that time we were still in tour (Zenkoku).
- Still in tour, right.
Marika coincidentally came to my hotel room,
Then we talked "This summer holiday where do we want to go?",
I explained to Marika that I've already
had a plan "Going to Gokayama",
Then Marika said "Let's go!", like that.
Then we tried to find out.
We found a hotel, then we thought
"If this is not booked now, it can be bad,"
We thought, "How?" "Book, book now?"
like that. - Because you both wanted to go, right?
Eventually we booked it.
Maybe due to excitement in tour,
I see.
Just because Marika came and said that...
[Shitara]: That must be painful.
[Shitara]: A painful gathering.
That was also just a coincidence that Marika said so...
- You both became eager to do Sayuri-chan's plan
because Marika came, like that...
[Himura]: Because of Marika...
[Shitara]: Coincidentally there was Marika
I'm sorry because I didn't think long enough at that time.
- No, it's alright.
I see! If that's true then it's alright
although you haven't told me the story.
I see...
Sorry...
Eh, it's okay. I myself don't really mind it, really.
Really, it's okay.
DEEP REGRET
[Takayama]: Ah, Marika is also sad...
It's alright, you know.
Because of that, even though you said "There was no such plan",
as long as I've heard it, I'm satisfied enough.
But, honestly, today I feel relieved for this one full day.
Spending time together with you two truly makes me relaxed.
Because of course, I think having a conversation
by three of us like this is the best.
Sorry...
It's alright.
Through this, Nakamoto's heartache has gone by itself.
ONSEN VACATION
TO ERASE HEARTACHE
THE END
Well, Nogizaka Koujichuu has started and we are
Bananaman, Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu.
And here is, Nogizaka-chan!
Well, this time we do the segment
that was presented by Himetan. - Yes!
We do "Revenge Onsen",
Inoue and Ito Marika are also here,
- Thank you very much.
After that show, you three are enemies, like that?
NOT FRIENDS ANYMORE?
No, no. We're still friends.
Still friends?
- Of course, why not?
Has your heartache gone?
Of course, it's already gone.
- Ah, I see.
For Christmas later, we also have talked about
"Let's go to Kyoto".
But, it would be better, if you didn't make
that kind of promise.
WON'T INVITE TO GO ANYMORE.
But, she looked miserable,
- Himetan's reaction was so miserable...
Saito Asuka, you also saw that
she looked really painful, right?
Painful, right?
- Really interesting...
Interesting?
- Interesting?
Not like that. I'm also an indoor person, like Himetan,
and I have many similarities, like favorite or disliked food.
But, they two should have a similarity like hobby or favorite food.
But, I think it's completely different.
Because of that, after watching you think
why they are not the same, like that?
That's a mocking laugh!
MOCKING NAKAMOTO.
This show is brought to you by this sponsor.
So, it's done. Your heartache has gone, right?
- It's already gone.
Already gone?
- Already gone!
But, from what I see, it seems like it hasn't gone yet.
Looks like they two and you alone, right?
-Right!
Like when in the swing,...
- That swing is really dangerous!
That's a problem!
No, that's different!
- That's not different!
That's a huge problem!
Not different, right?
- Absolutely!
That's because we want to have a relaxed journey, isn't it?
Because from the start, they like playing swing, and
I'm not the type who likes to interfere.
That's the real situation.
- So it's no problem?         - Yes!
But your face looked so lonely at that time.
DOESN'T THIS LOOK LONELY?
That's not true, right?
- Her face was so serious!
But, Inoue said "Coincidentally Marika was in my hotel room",
At that time, you said "Let's go". Did you think that usually there are three of us here with Himetan?
Inoue, Inoue-san, try to answer...
Inoue-san, it's your turn, you know.
- Her expression...
When in the hotel for example, when you two are staying,
it's usually three of you, then you remember "Ah!", like that.
- Saying "Ah!", ever?
Inoue-san, please answer...
PLEASE ANSWER.
Her true trait isn't coming out.
That day, maybe we were too excited to book.
- Therefore you forgot?     - Right
But despite being excited, when booking for 2 people, you should have seen 3 people choice, right?
HOPING TO BOOK FOR 3 PEOPLE.
One people, two people,...
When you scrolled the choice of number of people,
"Eh, Himetan too," like that.    - There is such service, right?
But, it was said that "We three will gather at Christmas"...
Ah, because that was not Christmas, but summer, right?
- Is it so?
We have talked. Christmas this year we will go together.
- So Himetan's position is like Santa Claus?
FICTIONAL CHARACTER?
No, no, not like that.
So from the start, her position is like that?
So, from the start, it's alright without her, isn't it?
I see. When other than Christmas,
it's okay, if Himetan isn't there?
If it's not Christmas,
it's alright without Santa, like that?
MEETING ONCE A YEAR?
That's good, that way is also good.
That was good, after that, she will give
a rattlesnake as a present.
SURELY WILL BE SHUNNED IF SO...
That's a good idea, right?
- That can be made into a food, right?
After this, a surprising truth will be revealed!
Himetan, in the recording this time, did you ever think "This feels strange" or "What's this?", like that?
Eh? I didn't feel that way.
- Really?    - Ah, I see.
In fact, they both, Inoue and Ito Marika,...
...have known beforehand about this vacation of yours.
- Eh?
- No way! - They already knew.
And, all things that they talked about in the trip
are the scenario that had been prepared by staff.
Thank goodness if so.
- Absolutely.
So, the vacation this time is a reversed Dokkiri for Nakamoto.
Dokkiri means to do prank on someone.
Both of them are also the instigator.
They talked about Toyama a lot to make
Nakamoto awkward. Additionally,...
Do you know "Ham Quiz" from Inoue?
- Yes.
That's also in scenario.
Great!    - So natural!
- She did it well, right?
You were acting that time, right?
That was like a stage to show my acting skill.
TAKING ADVANTAGE FROM FRIEND.
There?
- That's great.
But, the tomato incident was not in scenario at all.
I truly didn't know if she doesn't like tomato.
So, I forgot and what came out was my real expression that time.
OUT OF SCENARIO.
After that, the last one, when you talked about that topic.
Both of them apologized while showing "Ah, sorry" reaction.
- Lie!!!
However,...
In the morning after that recording,
Although I said "After sleeping tightly, today will be fun"
Actually, I was so stressed out,
My true feeling, I think, really...
This is bad, a new heartache appears.
IMMEDIATELY NEW EPISODE?
This indeed can't be forgiven...
even until today I haven't apologized.
- This is like drama, right?
This all is because of going to Toyama.
To make everything alright,...
REGRETTING FOR GOING TO TOYAMA.
With such feeling of Inoue,
how about you do Dogeza?
Dogeza is kneeling and bowing until your head
touches the ground, as a deep apology.
WORST ORDER
DVD and Blue-ray of "Kanashimi no Wasurekata"
has been released this week.
Ticket for Under LIVE Merry Christmas Show can already be bought.
At Christmas this year you will also go, right?
- Yes me too,...
This show is brought to you by the following sponsor.
Inoue will possibly go to a place with different member again.
Do not do it again!
Aahh, that's great.
She is laughing!
What will Hori do again?