m 0 0 l 0 27 l 2 27 l 2 0 l 0 0 m 2 0 l -4 0 l -4 6 l 16 6 l 16 4 l -2 4 l -2 2 l 0 2 m 2 2 m 16 0 l 16 27 l 18 27 l 18 -1 l 16 -1 m 22 0 l 22 0 l 24 0 l 24 11 l 19 11 l 19 9 l 22 9 l 22 2 l 15 2 l 15 0 m 6 18 l 6 12 l 12 12 l 12 14 l 8 14 l 8 18 l 6 18 m 12 18 l 12 20 l 6 20 l 6 18 l 10 18 l 10 14 l 12 14 l 12 18 m 5 7 l 8 9 l 7 10 l 4 8 l 5 7 m 10 9 l 10 9 l 13 7 l 14 8 l 11 10 l 10 9 m 3 24 b 3 24 3 23 3 23 b 7 21 11 21 15 23 b 15 23 15 25 15 25 b 11 23 7 23 3 25
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
Nogizaka Koujichuu
BANANAMAN
Himura Yuuki
Shitara Osamu
DON! Okay Nogizaka Koujichuu is starting,
we're the MC Bananaman, Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu...
And here's Nogizaka-chan~
What? There's a lot of members here today.
- Yeah that's right.
Kawamura, long time no see.
Ro... Rotti.
I wanna see HimuRotti act~
- What are you talking about~
You're good at dancing~
I'm good at dancing~
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Favorite word.
That's a striking resemblance!
- Just like the real one!
What are we going to do today? Himura-san!
- Yes!  - Please announce it.  - Here I go!!!
Something I Want To Do Presentation, the second!
There you go!
This like, just as announced before,
the second presentation for...
... segments that members want to do in this show.
If the topic is interesting,
the segment will be made in this show.
The one that got made was Himetan's
"A Travel to Erase The Heartache."
Yeah we did that, then there's also Hori's
" Deeper Investigation of Gen-2".
Today if there's something good too,
we will make it into reality immediately.
The second important meeting,
the first challenger from Gen-2, Itou Karin.
This time I pick the theme about something
I can only do, here it is...
This.
- Ah, Shougi.
Everyone knows she will go with Shougi.
Have you told this in other show?  - Yes, that's right!
Since she likes Shougi,
she got a job related to this...
... and here's the segment
that Itou Karin wants to do.
She wants to teach everyone
everything about Shougi world!
First, this topic...
Shougi players are great people.
In Japan, there are only about
500 professional Shougi players.
Just 500?
- Yes.
Those chosen ones are great people...
... and I want to introduce them.
First, this man...
... Itotani, The Dragon Emperor.
- Dragon Emperor?  - That's very cool!
He also got "The Expert" nickname, and many more,
but he's widely knows as The Dragon Emperor...
Did he win this nickname?
- Ah, true.
He's still young, still 27 years old.
The Dragon Emperor, actually he has won
42 million Yen prize.
[ 42 million Yen = about 411 thousand US$ ]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Super Special.
Eh! He got it from Shougi?
- He won that much?
He didn't get it from just one match,
but the accumulated prize is 42 million Yen.
You totally like it if it's money we're talking about.
It's out, huh?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Suddenly this topic.
All of you have such dream.  - Yes, this is everyone's dream.
- You have to put some faith in that.
Next, here we go...
This is Satou Shinya-san.
Everyone please watch closely.
Those are the same guy?
- Yes!
Which one with wig?
- What's with his hair?
Usually when he's on TV or
he has a match to do...
... he puts his wig on.
- So there's something like this?  - Yes.
Then he makes the place cheerful...
But this one, this is he looks normally
and no wig on?
He also wears the wig as a joke material.
And he also brings many wigs with him.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Various head looks.
He's quite funny.
Next, I'll introduce the female Shougi players.
Actually, there are many
beautiful female Shougi player. Like them...
Eh! Young, so young!
Yes, this is Muroya-san,
Fujita-san, and Takemata-san.
Is Takemata-san still in school?
- Yes, Takemata-san is still in senior year of high school.
They're really beautiful.
It's not strange at all if she joined Nogizaka, right?
- Very true.
They're very beautiful...
- Yes, they are...
... but there are ugly ones too, right?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Wanna know about the uglies.
No, no, no!
Since she said every female players is beautiful...
But they are beautiful.
They have this refreshing image, but...
- You do think they're beautiful!
Those two are beautiful.
- Alright, next...
This! Characters based on Shougi pieces.
Woah, you're so maniac!
So it's based on these pieces?
- Yes.
The characters?   - There are many pieces here...
- Is this okay?   - Yes.
Next, Nogizaka members' characters
will be compared based on Shougi pieces.
This is it, the first one
is the ones in the first row.
These are "Fu"s,
you can see lots of them here...
[ Fu = pawn ]
The ones that form a line?
- Yes. If they don't move, then the game won't start.
In Shougi, it's like a war.
The King's...
They're like soldiers, the ones that become the wall.
If the King here gets defeated, the game is over.
"Fu" here has many friends in this position,
and it will be hard to penetrate the barricade...
Did you know that there are many variations
to change the formation?
- Mister, that's too detailed!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Secretly a shougi fan.
That's not too important!
Today you talk too much because you like this, huh?
- No, I played this back in junior high years.
Who's this "Fu" might be?
This "Fu" is Iko-chan... Ikoma-san.
- So Ikoma is "Fu"?  - Yup.
Why, it seems that you're not important.
- Ah, I see now.  - No...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Easy to forget?
First, this "Fu"
always wants to move forward!
Then, they go into enemy's line of defense,
just like she entered AKB...
... and learned many stuff from there...
Thank you!
Karin-chan thank you!
What an awesome explanation~!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Master class explanation.
Next is "Kyousha".
- Do you know "Kyousha"?
[ Kyousha = lance ]
"Kyousha" is...
- Do you know which one is "Kyousha"?
Yeah, they can move forward wherever you want.
But they can't move backward,
so they're like only looking forward...
This piece is represented by
Noujou-san and Rarin-san.
I think they suit this well.
For example in variety, they always stick out...
... they can always attract some attention.
- Like "Gyuuun!!!"
They're just, like, "Pyoon!!!"...
They often pull some extreme move,
and that's their weapon to attack the enemies.
So there's something like that...
That's how you will be known.
Next...
- "Keima"!  - Ah, I know this one.
[ Keima = knight ]
... "Keima"!
- Many of you here knows this?  - Yes.
Basically they jump forward and backward...
... you can say they're unique pieces...
- Jumping around?  - Yes.
They jump in weird ways...
- Because they're unpredictable.
For this different kind of piece,
they are Kazumin-san and Iku-chan.
Different?
- Yeah.
So that means you're weirdos?
- Are we that weird?
Since she thinks you two are "Keimas"...
They're also sitting in a same position.
- They did some weird movements.
Next is "Gin".
[ Gin = silver general / silver ]
"Gins" are pieces that move stiffly,
they are offensive pieces.  - Offensive pieces?  - Yes.
The representing members, when attacking...
... they are the one who start the attack.
- Those two in the back?  - Precisely.
These pieces are on the same positions here,
and these two are Wakatsuki-san and Reika-san.
Right. Like in some art exhibition,
they show it a lot...
It's understandable since they're lesbian...
- No! We're just close!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Officially Lesbian.
If we have something in common,
and let me emphasize this, there's nothing going on.
Her image...
- Wakatsuki seems very sensitive regarding this matter...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A truth that can't be laughed off?
I've been trying to lose this character slowly lately...
If you do that,
all you have is the robot character.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Wakatsuki - Lesbian = Robot
Just that...
- Why?
Very interesting,
there's no difference between lesbian and Robot...
Eh, you said "Lesbian Robot"!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Birth of A New Robot.
Lesbian Robot?
- No!
LezRobo!
Next, "Kin"!
- They're pretty important.
[ Kin = gold general / gold ]
They can't move backward diagonally?
- They can't. Basically, we make the piece moves forward...
... if we do that,
it changes into this "Kin".
Ah, so everyone becomes "Kin"?
- Since they're strong pieces, they're like guardians...
... in the end, there will be a "checkmate", right?
These pieces are usually used to attack
to achieve that checkmate.  - Ah, got it.
For these "Kins" who stay next to the King,
are Shiraishi-san and Hashimoto-san.
Eh, so they're "Kins"?
They guard?
- Yes, they're tough and if they're not there...
They're like the final defending wall.
Next...
- This "Hisha" or "Kakkou" is pretty cool.
[ Kakou = bishop ]
Indeed.
- This piece is big in size, right?  - Yes.
Good players can't shake the
"Hisha" and "Kakkou" off from them.
That's what makes this piece so important.
How does "Kakkou" move?
- "Kakkou" may freely move in diagonal manner...
So it can move to wherever you wants
- Yes.
That's why this is a strong piece.
- Like, "byuun"...
This piece is Minami.
- Eh!?
Are you listening?
- I am.
Minami looks like she has no clue...
... she talks about interesting topic
while she seems think nothing.
Her moves changes a lot...
- You can say that she's very expert in this.
She can just "gyuun!",
just suddenly attacking from unexpected direction.
Next is "Hisha".
[ Hisha = rook ]
This... this is a very good piece.
- "Hisha" is indeed a good piece.
The shape is also different, and it can move freely
in vertical and horizontal manner.
For this "Hisha", it's Asuka.
That makes sense, huh...
The kanji character of her name is same, right?
- So that's why?
Besides, I like the position,
right here together with "Kakkou".
This is a strong piece.
- Agree! They also...
... are inside this area right here!
They're the most played pieces.
What a cool piece.
- Yes!  - Great!
And, last one! This one is definitely needed.
- "Ou-sama"! There it is!
[ Ou-sama = king ]
"Ou-sama".
Basically "Ou-sama" doesn't move much.
But if there's no "Ou-sama",
then the player is lose.
That's why this is Nishino-san.
- Nishino?
I thought you were going to say
"It's me!"...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Purposely mention herself.
I would say "Eh! You!"...
That might be interesting!
Since you've yet to make an appearance,
I thought your name would be the last.
Just suddenly "This one is me."
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Waiting for the chance.
That was very interesting.
Nishino?  - Yes, she looks like
she need to be protected...   - That's not wrong.
Yes, that's Nishino-san.
- Don't attack Nishino!
It's amazing that this kind of blunt statement appears.
You're the King, you know!
Awesome~
- What do you think?
I'm very thankful .
- No, no, the King doesn't need to feel that way...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
The commoners are here.
So that's that.
It was interesting. Everyone here wants
to know more after hearing your explanation.
I wanna try it.
But just now, do you think it
can make a lively atmosphere here?
No, no, not yet...
- But I want to play human shougi.
You wanna try human shougi?
- We do!
No, no, everyone wears the costumes
and just stay like this...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Boring.
Shot from a high place, and the players say
"That one, move here", and they move...
Amazing~
Now Nishino...   - Not interesting at all.
All a King does is this...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Waiting for the command.
That's interesting, though!
Since there's some worry it can't make the studio lively,
this segment is put on halt.
Next, the second presenter,
the one with many friends, Noujou!
I want to do a segment where there are battles
with swords and horse ridings.
Battles with swords and horse ridings?
- That's why, I think I'll use this way...
I want to try a colossal history drama!
This sounds like a very serious segment!
I thought about the title very hard,
and it's...
In the end, the title is TERRIBLE!
What's this?   - Sorry, sorry...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Showa atmosphere can be felt.
[ Showa = between 1926 - 1989 ]
Sorry, my writing is bad...  - It's not about the writing,
but you being so confident about the title.  - Sorry~
Tomo to Katana
(Friend and Sword)
This sounds like a dumb title!
What's going on?
And I also have selected the casts.
Please let us know.
- You can say they're the most ideal casts...
Alright, so who'll have roles in "Tomo to Katana"?
Okay...
- What? The main character?
Why? Ah, this is your
personal presentation, huh.
Doesn't Ami sound too sweet?   - Ami as the main character?
I think she should be "side character A"!
She has a close childhood friend, Kaede,
portrayed by Takayama.
Since she's good at kendou?
I think she can do this.
There will be fights between girls?
- I think this will play out like Azumi...
[ Azumi = a tale of a female assassin with sword ]
Then there are three henchmen,
they're going to get killed later...
Your role is to get killed! A killed role!
From the start you've been chosen to die.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
No dialogue.
- I want to slash with sword.
I want those three to get sliced
in a cool way, then...
... for the role of rich merchant's wife is...
- Awesome, but that one is not needed.
This is an ideal role for her.
- That's impossible.  - Sorry.
And for the rich merchant, Himura-san.
- Thank you very much, I'll do my best!
No, no, why are you so fired up for this?
Himura-san is here too?
- Yes.   - Thank you very much.
Next, explanation about the script
with her own illustrations.
Is this alright?    - Sorry, but please
don't pay too much attention to the pictures.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Worrying illustration.
Ami and Kaede are orphans.
Which is who?
- Ah, this...
The one that looks like a garbage bag?
- Ah, this is Ami.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Something sticks out.
And who's the other one?
Sunplaza Nakano-san?
[ Sunplaza Nakano = a Japanese musician and writer,
famous for his bald head ]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
The Baldie.
This is Kaede.
- Ah, Kaede.
So that's Kaede?
- Right.
For role as Kaede,
can you completely shave your head off?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Later appearance = BALD
Do I have to?
- Well yeah, according to this.
Noujou only has to shave it off
up until this part!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
No wigs allowed.
But it has to be the same with this one
right here, right?
No wigs allowed!
- You have to be like this...
You have to shave just like this!
Then, these two siblingless girls
are gathered and get nursed in a...
... school of swordsmanship in that town
and they're like blood sisters.
Back then, "Ami" got left on the side of a road...
... carrying a sword with a beautiful engraving,
the crest of her clan.
She and her sword?
- Yes.
From that on, "Ami" always has the sword with her...
... she thinks
"This sword is a way for me to meet my parents".
And those two always look after the sword.
And then they lived happily ever after...
- Ah, it's not like that!  - I've yet to make any appearance!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Show cancelled.
Kuroki-san and I don't have any appearance.
Also those killed three!
Kuroki Hitomi-san and I have to be there.
- You're just standing by here.
[ Kuroki Hitomi = a famous Japanese actress
and ex-member of Takarazuka. ]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Big shot actress in vain.
All we do is waiting.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Noujou's presentation is heating up! Will the historical drama [Tomo to Katana] be made?
Himura who has casted as the rich merchant got surprised with the movie production...
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
Next, Ami and Kaede take a walk in town as usual...
- Who are those?
Ah sorry, the one that's kinda hidden here is me.
- That's Ami?
Who's that?
- This is Kaede. I forgot to draw her hair in the beginning.
So Kaede has to shave her head
just up until this part...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Noujou the Knight messes up again.
Only this part remaining?
- She's like an old man...
Then on this announcement board, they see an information
about a missing person.  - Ah, that board.
"Someone is looking for his daughter
with sword like this!" is what the board says.
So both of them see it together?
- That's right.
The one who wrote that on the board is a
rich merchant, an owner of some shop...
... a ruler and also the country's richest person,
"The Business Magnate of Echigo".
[ Echigo = a name of Niigata back then. ]
And the sword picture there
is the same one as the one that "Ami" always carries!
I...
- So she comes from a rich family?  - Yes.
Suddenly after she knows about this, "Ami" is very happy,
since she will meet her parents.
Then those flowers grow around her?
- No they don't...
Why then?
- The illustration...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
There are flowers, though.
Ah, it's redundant...
So he's the Business Magnate of Echigo.
- Yes!
Yes, and she becomes very jealous of this...
- Who?   - Kaede.
What?
- Why though? This...
They were always together before.
- Right, her heart becomes corrupted...
So she's the antagonist?
- Correct.
"Kaede" who's being envious,
takes the sword away...
... to the Business Magnate of Echigo, and says
"I'm your long lost daughter".
She steals the sword?!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Best friend's betrayal.
Next, an important scene while chasing "Kaede"
by horse, but...
Then she...
- Who? Who? Who was that?
This is me.
- That's Ami?
This is bad, can we prepare
a short-legged horse like that?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Fantasy creature?
Who... What is that?
That's some WEIRD horse right there!
Is this okay?
- This...
Are you riding a real horse there?
- Yes, I want to ride a horse, and here...
... I want to insert this riding scene.
- Ami heads to the merchant's manor?  - Yes.
Then she says, "Kaede! Give me my sword back!"
Then, Kaede...
... says "That woman wants to steal my sword".
Eh!? After this whole time, they've been going through
a lot of things together, and she suddenly becomes like that?
Something like "Why do you do this?"
Correct, after that she still won't change...
... then her henchmen attack Ami.
They're ganging up Noujou?
- Yes, then they fight...
- Who are those baldies?
They can be Maaya or anyone, they're going to
get sliced by my sword later anyway...
Wada Maaya
Saitou Chiharu
Kawamura Mahiro
Kawamura, too?  - Yes!  - You too, Kawamura!
Perhaps you have to shave your head later.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Wigs are not ALLOWED.
Shave it all!
- I've thought about the moves too...
Then lastly, Ami will battle Kaede.
We fight for real here...
Her condition...
She looks different...
- Judging from her expression, she gets mortally wounded.
And here, finally I'm trying to say these words!
IN THE END, THEY LIVED HAPPILY EVER AFTER.
HOLD ON~!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Himura doesn't appear.
May I continue?
"A sword is not only a tool to cut human down... but..."
To cut konnyaku too.
- No!
[ Konnyaku = some kind of jelly made from tuber. ]
It's not like that!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
By Lupin the 3rd.
What then?
- The conclusion, right?
So the conclusion, it's used to cut Konnyaku...
- "but... also a friend..."  - Ah, so that's the "friend"...
Friend, huh.
- Yes, it's like that.
I see...
- What a good story.
THE END!
- Eh, the end? Then Himura-san...
WHEN WILL I MAKE AN APPEARANCE!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Miscast?
He doesn't make any appearance yet...
I'm okay with that,
but there's also Kuroki Hitomi-san!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
An unrecognized big shot.
She'll definitely say "I...
when will I make an appearance?"  - She's not there?
In the end, Himura-san puts his hand
on Kuroki Hitomi's shoulder.
Just suddenly?
At the last moment?
In the most last moment, Kuroki Hitomi-san makes an appearance
and I put my hand on her shoulder...
What's the point of this scene?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A mysterious ending.
She might think,
"Who's this guy?"
Then finally Noujou lives happily in that manor?
- Yes, but lastly...
... they live together with Kaede.
- Ah, Kaede lives there too?
Yup.
- But she's evil...
But of course she thinks that friendship
is the most important thing, so they live together.
That's very nice of her.
First, if we cast Kuroki-san, that's kinda...
- Yes, sorry, but she is the most ideal one...
Budget-wise... perhaps if it's that interesting,
we want to do it, but...
... if it's a big scale drama, then...
- Maybe a trailer style will do.
So it's really short.
Maybe it can be summarized into a PV.
- Yes, I want to do it.
Maybe it's possible budget-wise,
but it will be considered.
If it's interesting,
it will be used immediately?
A debate to choose the new segment!
Does anyone else have some idea?
I guess I wanna do this...
Is there someone like that?
Ah, there is!  - What?
- Well I...
... work at a company, right? I want a segment about
many companies' special meals around us.
Companies' special meals, not bad...
That sounds like a perfect segment.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
That was too much.
Perfect?
- Others?
Me!
Perhaps the quite-known gen-2 are only
Karin-chan with her shougi and Kii-chan with her strength...
... we saw characters like that,
but there's still something else...
... the unseen character of each individual.
A gen-1 member and a gen-2 member,
doing a recording together somewhere...
In pair?
That way, some new character may be seen.
- Ah, understood.
Is that alright? All gen-1 can do is eat a lot, right?
- Ah, no, no.
About that, we can hold it...
- Hold it!
You hold it so you can eat even more.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Variety queen's special privilege.
No, the purpose is so it won't disturb us much,
and with gen-2 I will talk about many things...
Clearly we also want to know more about gen-2.
- You're curious, right?
Then, anything else?
With a 20 years old group...  - 20 years old group?
- We have a recording with 20 years old group in Nogizaka.
Soon enough, Marika, Rotti and I will have
a Seijinshiki ceremony.
[ Seijinshiki = coming of age ceremony,
held for 20 years olds. ]
You're 20 already?
I want to make a plan for the age of 20.
- Hey, that's mildly adequate.
What do you think? Bungee?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Suddenly a bungee request.
Why does that sound like a tribal ceremony?
Since this is a ritual to adulthood!
- Adulthood jump!
You look for the bungee rope yourself...
- You use it to jump down there.
Also tie your own legs too.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Her face got hit.
And then you jump just with that, "crashh"...
What else we have next,
it might be a rarely-known stuff.
Ah, go ahead. What is it?
I want to make something trendy.
We have Nogizaka jersey...
... gen-1 has been wearing that for 4 years.
- Ah, the purple one?
That's quite old...
- Yes, that's why I want to make new jerseys.
Why? That jersey has been together with you,
the proof of the sweats and tears of your hard work...
That leaves a deep impression.
The purple has faded away!
Make jerseys on this show?
You need 15 thousand Yen for one person...
- That's expensive!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Material cost.
But as a university student, everyone has
their own money, right?   - I want to make that.
Then a winning member may
choose the material or the style herself...
I wanna try that...
- Then...
... we use America-style retro logo like
"NOGIZAKA" written there, then there's the 46 below...
We make something like that.
- Yeah, let's make it that way.
Like under the "Underman"
there's "Yomiuri GIANTS" written.
[ Yomiuri GIANTS = a professional baseball team from Tokyo. ]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
GIANTS style.
Why? Clearly this is not Yomiuri GIANTS.
This is interesting!
- Yomiuri GIANTS!
This indeed is interesting.
- Then we'll make jerseys for Yomiuri GIANTS instead!
The development of Nogizaka46's new segment,
presents some unexpected ideas!?
Continuing previous program,
I want to make accessories again...
You've made it previously, right?
- Yes, we made our own characters...
There's Doiya-san, then...
Tin-chan?
- Ten-chan!   - Yeah, that...
... we can make our own original characters.
In the end, we offered the products at Kiddyland,
right?  - Yeah, we did that.
It'll be nice if we do that too.
- Like Fuchiko-san.
[ Fuchiko-san = a small toy put on the edge of the cup.
Pretty popular in Japan and the design is cute. ]
Ah, if we make a Nogizaka version of Fuchiko-san,
it will become very popular, huh.
I wanna do that.
- Seems like everyone want to try it.
Eh Ikuta, you don't know Fuchiko-san?
I don't know.
- She's like that...
Puchiko-san?
- Fu... Fu... Fuchiko-san.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Minimizing as she wants.
Puchiko-san must be very small in size.
Well then Ikuta should be Puchiko-san.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Milimeter-sized figurine.
That's not Fuchiko-san!
- She's just standing and getting pinched like this.
Fuchiko-san is that thing on your cup.
You don't know that one? Usually it's put
atop of cup's edge.  - First time I'm hearing that.
So you really don't know Fuchiko-san.
You can also put it on the piano keys.
- Yeah.
It gets in the way.
True that.
- It does get in the way.
Yeah, it sure does.
It will just like this there...
Yes.
- Cute.
The smell here.
It smells so good!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Last part of segment presentation! Smell maniacs of Nogizaka46 are emerging one by one!?
Lots of stuff will get sniffed!! So, what kind of smell do members like!?
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
I love the smell inside an elevator.
Ah, it smells so good!!!
You've said it!
Not bad...
Jyan~ Let's do it this year too!
Dream Christmas 2015.  - I'm involved yet again...
Next week, the last part of New Segment Presentation!
Matsumura's presented segment makes studio go crazy!
Smells that Nogizaka members like
are going to appear!