NOGIZAKA KOUJICHUU
DON! Alright Nogizaka Koujichuu is starting,
we're Bananaman, Onegaishimasu.
And here's Nogizaka-chan!
Hai, Onegaishimasu!
Okay first what are we going to do
today, Himura-san...
Erasing Wakatsuki Yumi's
Seriousness Project.
Alright now let us
welcome Wakatsuki.
Wakatsuki...
- Wakatsuki...
Eh? Wakatsuki...
- Waka~Waka~
So Wakatsuki isn't present.
- What's so serious then?
NOT SERIOUS?
No, it's not like that!
Wakatsuki herself said that she's
worried with her own seriousness. - Eh?
Why? It's good to have some seriousness.
But...
But since she's too serious...
- I see.
She felt like she's invisible.
TRANSPARENT?
But on this show, she got many
chances to talk.
That's true, but this time she wants to
reduce her seriousness, so...
After this, we will be having the Wakatsuki reborn
- Eeeeh!!!
I wanna see!
- What??
But she was great when she became a robot.
She looked like a pro.
But do you think it wasn't good enough?
THIS ONE?
That because she was being too serious.
- I see.
Even she wanted to do robot dance,
she became a real robot. - Too serious, huh.
BECAME A ROBOT IMMEDIATELY
Alright then, before Wakatsuki's here...
First let's hear some informations from members
about how serious she is.
Wada will tell us how Wakatsuki
really follow the lyric when she dances.
Wada have talked about this before, right?
When there's a lyric about "in pain"
or "sound of a ball got hit".
She's doing it for real like hitting the ball.
Then she gazes to the direction. Lately she even
tried to hear it.
HER REACTION EVOLVED
She does that?
Next, a report from Nishino.
When I saw Wakatsuki's muscle, this part.
The shape was very good. I said "Isn't that cool?"
I wanted to know how could she shape it.
She said "I didn't shape it at all."
"But just with washing your hair, it became like this."
- Nishino!
Hold on, it sounds like you were mocking her.
- It's not like that, but...
WAKATSUKI IS SERIOUS TOO WHEN SHE'S SHAMPOOING
It means she washes her hair strongly.
- Is that so?
So serious.
- She really washes her hair like that, huh.
Next, information regarding Wakatsuki's
seriousness is...
She also did it on a survey.
- So we have more.
It's from some show, the question was
"Is there any object that makes you worried
if you don't have it with you?"
The others answered too
- Yes.
For example, Ikoma, Manga and Anime,
I can't live without Naruto.
- That's Ikoma's character.
Wakatsuki answered here...
Water and air!
SURPRISING CHOICE
What an amazing answer!
Why?
Really?
- Why did she answer that?
What kind of conclusion was that?
- That's not what it meant...
Of course!
So there was answer like that too.
But water and air?
- Water and air?
She also wrote something she worried about.
I asked, "What are you worrying about?"
She said "My heart."
Of course, heart is also important.
Too serious!
- Too serious!
That Wakatsuki we were talking earlier,
what is she going to do now?
[Shitara]: This is interesting!
Erasing Wakatsuki Yumi's
Seriousness Project.
On this show, I, Wakatsuki Yumi, want to
change people's opinions about "She's too serious."
I'm also worried and I thought, "Am I
a boring person?"
Here, I want to try one way
to heal this problem of mine.
This time, I'm going to attend a humor class.
After I attend that class,
I won't be serious anymore in the end...
Won't be serious anymore, like...
[Shitara&Himura]: Too serious!
I guess, Wakatsuki Yumi will be better
with her humor later. I'll give my best!
[Himura]: It won't be that serious with humor
And the humor class has been started.
HUMOR CLASS
START
[Himura]: Who's the teacher?
The consultan who'll be the speaker
in the class is a Humor Specialist.
[Ikoma]: This seems very serious!
[Shiraishi]: Indeed!
[Ikoma]: What is this?
Humor Speech Consultant,
Wakabayashi Isei Sensei.
[Shitara]: Eeh, so it's like this
Everyone, good afternoon.
- Good afternoon.
The problem here is a too serious Wakatsuki-san
- Yes.
To make someone laugh, we can use various methods.
Today we will try to use
some things to do that.
And this is the most basic technique.
[Himura]: Really?
WAKABAYASHI
METHOD
USING OBJECTS
TO BRING OUT THE LAUGHS
[Himura]: What will he show?
[Himura]: It looked funny when he
was looking for something
The easiest method is by using chopsticks.
- Eehh~~
[Shitara]: Making a humor with chopsticks?
You only need to make some dialogue
between these chopsticks.
Make an interesting story and that's good enough.
And it will make them laugh.
SO CONFIDENT
Okay let's try it.
- Hai!
You show this to everyone.
Then you pull the chopsticks out.
That bird on the bridge,
what bird is that?
WORD PLAY: [Hashi] can also mean
chopstick or bridge
Ah, that bird, it's an owl.
WORD PLAY: [Fukuro] and [Fukurou] have similar
sounds. [Fukuro] means chopsticks' sleeve,
[Fukurou] means owl
Aaa~~~
FASCINATED
Like that.
- Amazing...
[Ikoma]: Eh, amazing!
Because you only say the [Fukuro] earlier as [Fukurou].
[Shitara]: Did he say Fukurou?
That doesn't mean you can use it for
every jokes.
[Shitara]: Word play of Fukuro?
That bird on the bridge,
what bird is that?
[Shitara]: Once more?
Ah, that bird, it's an owl.
[Shiraishi]: Twice?
UNEXPECTEDLY TWICE...
It looks easy to do, but...
[Shitara]: So that's because of the sleeve?
[Himura]: What? It doesn't make any sense at all
If you don't do it yourself,
it'll be difficult to surprise or make
people laugh.
FOR REAL
[Himura]: Perhaps in the "on the bridge" part?
That's why, you go try it.
[Shitara]: This looks bad!
Me?
[Shitara]: Will she do this?
WAKATSUKI'S
SHOW
[Ikoma]: Stop! Stop!
Try to think about how would you pull them out.
- Hai!
[Takayama]: Maybe this is okay
[Shitara]: But probably she's been training
First, show it to everyone.
[Shiraishi]: Maybe she could since she's serious
[Minami]: My heart is pounding!
Ah! Ah! Yes, yes, that...
SEEMS
DIFFERENT...
[Shiraishi]: Why?
That bird,
- that bird on the bridge, what bird is that?
[Shiraishi]: No!
Ehm, yes, yes, yes...
Ah, that?
That's an owl!
[Himura]: So stiff! [Shitara]: Yeah!
Yes...
YES...
Look, everyone's laughing.
[Shitara]: Because of that, everyone are waiting
for this when we're having a meal with her
Clearly they're not.
[Himura]: That is so wrong! [Shitara]: I'm quite surprised!
[Ikoma]: Sensei is too kind
But if you spend some little time with this method,
you can do it.
[Shiraishi]: Really? [Shitara]: This is awesome!
Most people will laugh with this.
WITH THIS MOST PEOPLE WILL...?
This is quite difficult.
[Himura]: What "Eee"?
Let's try the second story.
- Second story?
[Ikoma]: There's a second story
THERE'S A [SECOND STORY]
Let's see...
[Matsumura]: Ah, no!
It's like this too, you do this...
[Shitara]: She starts again?
[Shirashi]: For real?
Then pull the chopsticks out.
[Shitara]: Another chopsticks?
Hashi-kun, Hashi-kun,
[Shitara]: Eh, Hashi-kun.
Who was that elegant woman with you just now?
Eh? There was no woman like that!
There was! A middle aged woman.
Ah that, that's my mother.
- Ehmm.
WORD PLAY: [Ofukuro] is how to formally say [Fukuro/bungkus]
[Ofukuro] can also mean someone's mother
Since this is [Fukuro].
BECAUSE THIS IS FUKURO
[Shitara]: This is dangerous!
[Himura]: She can do more
Okay! Now it's time to study.
You do it again.
[Ikoma]: Studied?
[Shitara]: In the end she tried it too
WAKATSUKI'S
SHOW
[Shitara]: Who was she talking to?
[Himura]: Hashi-kun, Hashi-kun.
Hashi-kun, Hashi-kun,
Who was that elegant woman with you
some day ago?
No, no! There's no woman like that.
Yes! That middle aged woman!
[Shitara]: She's doing it seriously!
Ahh! That middle aged woman is...
My mother!
- Yes...
[Shitara]: Ehm!
HELL
That was quite good.
- Hai!
[Shitara]: Hell?
You made everyone laugh just now
- Yay!
[Ikoma]: They are not laughing!
Judging from the result, you can use this
on end of the year's party.
[Himura]: So bad!
[Ikoma]: End of the year party?
You can do it there.
- I see.
[Himura]: There?
SHOW FOR
END OF YEAR PARTY
[Himura]: Sounds interesting, stuff
like this in end of the year party!
That was the basic level.
- Basic level?
[Himura]: Indeed
Now, the advanced level.
- Hai!
SERIOUSLY...
In this level we will add spoon.
[Ikoma]: Really?
THERE ARE ALREADY [CHOPSTICKS]
[Ikoma]: Why could he be so prepared?
[Shitara]: Why did he have everything?
It's a conversation between
two young ladies.
Hey you know what, my mom is so noisy.
When we were eating, she's always praising me
if I use the chopsticks.
Because she wouldn't shut up, I swapped it
with a spoon.
[Shitara]: What's this?
Suddenly she's snapped, took my spoon,
and hurled it at me.
[Shitara]: Hurled the spoon?
Then you move here.
Your mom shouldn't
care about some little thing like that.
- Ehm...
WORD PLAY: [Saji] means spoon or redundant things
[Sagi o nagette] means hurling spoon
or not paying attention to redundant things
Do you understand, "care about some little thing"?
- I do...
[Himura]: He cares about little things himself
UNDERSTOOD...
Once again, you try it.
[Shitara]: Oh man!
WAKATSUKI'S
SHOW
[Shitara]: We feel like we just want to get out
if we have to watch this
You know, when I was eating using chopsticks...
[Ikoma]: Waka~
My mom kept praising me for that.
She just kept talking.
Since she's too noisy,
I used spoon to eat
the rice for the first time.
Suddenly she's snapped.
Then she hurled the spoon at me.
Ah, she shouldn't care about
some little thing like that.
SATISFIED
[Shiraishi]: Satisfied? [Akimoto]: No!
Wasn't that interesting?
PRAISING HIMSELF
[Himura]: What's with the praise?
Now we'll talk about
the speaking method.
Wakatsuki can use some humor in
introduction or speech on the stage.
First the introduction, try to introduce
yourself normally here.
[Himura]: This seems good. Finally!
WAKATSUKI'S
SELF INTRODUCTION
[Shitara]: This? [Himura]: This must be different!
Member of Nogizaka46, Wakatsuki Yumi,
My nicknames are Wakatsuki,
Waka and Wakasama.
I'm from Shizuoka, this year I'll be 21 years old.
I like to watch art exhibitions and movies.
My dream is to be an actress.
Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu.
[Shitara]: That normal introduction is good
[Himura]: This is good
Of course we can start from the bottom
so we can get used to it.
Like what you just said, you talked and acted too seriously...
[Himura]: That wasn't bad
[Shitara]: I want this to be funny
That's why, you can change your name or hobby
with something funnier.
[Shitara]: But changing name... [Himura]: Can she?
WAKABAYASHI'S
METHOD
TECHNIQUES NEEDED TO
MAKE SOME LAUGHS
First, you can talk excessively.
Use hyperbole.
You can use anything you see
to make it excessive.
[Ikoma]: She's writing it!
NOTES
[Shitara]: How dilligent
Using that method, it will be funnier.
For example, about your hobby.
I like to watch movies, in a month
I can at least watch them 500 times.
DEADLY TECHNIQUE,
WITH OVER THE TOP EXPRESSION
That's an example to hyperbole one little detail from one thing.
[Himura]: Not bad!
Then, word play!
WORD PLAY?
[Shiraishi]: Word play?
Word play is the best way to make Japanese people laugh.
Because word play flows through Japanese people's vein.
Japanese people = Word play.
You said you're from Shizuoka?
You can add something there.
Add something there,
and that part will sound funny.
Shizuoka prefecture, famous for its eel, then I'll say
"I'll give my best to promote it"!
WORD PLAY: [Unagi] means eel
[Unagi nobori] means promoting something
START GETTING IDEAS...
You can say it from that viewpoint.
- Hai!
[Ikoma]: Amazing!
WAKABAYASHI'S
METHOD
MAKE SOME LAUGHS
FROM EXPLANATION
Also you can tell some backstory
in the beginning of your story.
You can start it by explaining something
before you talk about some funny stuff.
Autumn, for example.
Autumn is fun,
there are lots of interesting stuff like
Autumn food, autumn sports,
reading in autumn, autumn arts,
Yashiro Aki is an Enka singer from Japan
Yashiro Aki too, right?
- Eehmm..
FINALLY IT'S HERE
That last part will make people laugh.
Really?
Everyone, lift your face
and watch closely!
WATCH CLOSELY
But I guess you can pull it off already.
- Ah, that's good to hear!
From all people I've seen,
you're great.
CONFESSION FROM WAKABAYASHI ISEI
That's why I'm waiting for your performance.
- Hai!
[Himura]: Let's see now
What will Wakatsuki show us
after she studied humor?
Wow~~
I see. - Interesting!
CONVERTED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
Finally, the Wakatsuki reborn is coming.
- At long last.
Wakatsuki, please enter!
She looks usual.
What a good project, huh?
- That's right.
Have you studied? - Yes.
Good.
Today we will see the new Wakatsuki.
From here on let's see how will you introduce yourself.
INTRODUCTION WITH WAKABAYASHI'S METHOD
I need to look at this...
- I'm taking this!
Wait, wait, wait!
I worked hard to make this!
She wrote it like she's
accepting the graduation certificate. - Impressive!!!
MADE A SPEECH TEXT
Okay I understand, go ahead.
Let's see Wakatsuki's introduction
in the style of Wakabayashi that she made herself.
Nishino and Fukagawa will introduce themselves
too like they usually do.
First Nishino, Fukagawa, then Wakabayashi.
- Understood!
Ah, Wakabayashi!
HEIR OF [WAKABAYASHI]'S NAME?
Shitara-san, you can't decide the name for her.
Aren't you Wakabayashi this time?
How's Wakatasuki's introduction?
Let's see Nishino's first.
I'm Nishino Nanase from dari Osaka, I'm 21 years old.
I like Udon, Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu!
- Onegaishimasu~
I'm from Shizuoka, MaiMai, MaiNichi, MyPace
Fukagawa Mai, Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu.
Alright, this means it's time for my introduction.
SOMETHING'S WRONG
Recently, I did something on this show
I thought I could do for sure.
Like everybody's been talking about,
I did a robot dance.
That time,
The atmosphere in the studio became terrible.
WORD PLAY: [Jiko] can mean accident/misfortune
or own self, like in [Jiko Shoukai/ self introduction]
Ah, sorry, why did I talk about that,
I have to introduce myself instead.
WAKABAYASHI'S METHOD
TALKING ABOUT [MISFORTUNE]
Let's fix it a little bit.
I gues it's time to introduce myself.
Okay, my name is Wakatsuki Yumi.
I've been called Wakasama often too.
Everyday I thought, can I go through
the changes from young age to old age well.
WORD PLAY: [Wakasama] can mean young master
[Tonosama] can mean great master. I use
old and young so it's easier
WAKABAYASHI'S METHOD [NAME HUMOR]
But let me think about that myself,
you all may call me Wakasama.
But do you know that I was a kid
who always scored 5, be it on
math, science, and social science.
5 in Japanese student report card
is the highest. Kinda like ABCDE
I always scored 5!
But actually the maximum score was 10,
I guess I'll have to remember this more.
WAKABAYASHI'S METHOD [SCORE HUMOR]
Okay, actually I,
The last one, I'm from Shizuoka and
some words that suit Shizuoka are...
We must have heart as tall as the tallest mount in Japan,
Mount Fuji.
About tea products, we have to befriend many people
just like the tea leaves inside the glass.
[Unagi nobori] again!
Next, we also have to work hard
to promote this group so we can always be known.
That's all from Nogizaka46's humor specialist,
Wakatsuki Yumi.
VERY EMBARASSED
Amazing!
That was great, you did your best!
If you did that, the others won't have their chances.
DURATION EATER
That was like one introduction for everyone.
- It looked like that.
How do I say this. It felt lame.
Like, you know?
- Really?
Maybe that was not like your style?
Perhaps they didn't show it in the VTR earlier, but...
I did something with the 10.000 Yen paper money.
Does anybody have it? - Fukuzawa Yukichi-san
Ah, that!
There you go!
-  The first reveal?
You shouldn't explain it beforehand.
Everyone please try to have a normal expectation.
Try not to think this will be bad.
Just be normal so Wakatsuki
feels it's her first time doing this.
Can you please sit down when I'm talking?
Now let's see Wakatsuki's
struggle to change.
But even though everyone say she's serious,
that's not a bad thing either.
Right?
That's why you need a balance,
like when you're giving a welcome speech. - I see!
- Yeah!
But, talking about welcome speech...
What is it, Wakatsuki?
- That...
I can make all of you here laugh,
with my welcome speech.
Ehh, show it! Show it!
I, wait a sec, brought
a 10.000 Yen paper money.
Do you know who is this?
This is Fukuzawa Yukichi-san.
Usually people call him "Fuku-chan".
Nope! He's never been called that way.
SCENARIO DESTROYER
He has, in my area.
Is that true in Shizuoka?
- No.
Usually that's his nickname in west and east area.
- Really? - Yeah!
I don't think so!
This won't get anywhere...
Oh yeah. - Do you call him that?
Yes I do.
SCENARIO IS BACK ON TRACK
He actually does.
Fuku-chan here always says he wants to get out from my pocket.
He always asks this to me.
That's why I advise this
Fuku-chan from time to time.
Fuku-chan, you may get out...
But if you're going home, don't come alone,
bring your friends too.
Like that.
- I see.
DON'T LAUGH YET, BECAUSE THIS ISN'T DONE
Then this Fuku-chan here once
asked for a permission to go out.
In order to look for him and bring him home,
I made a circle right here. Then he finally came out.
Somehow, half a year later...
Fuku-chan came home.
He's so lucky to have this circle.
That means Fuku could go home because of luck.
WORD PLAY: [Fuku] here means luck
and also Fuku-chan's name
Thank you, thank you!
Of course when we're giving a welcome,
it has to be deeply thought before.
HOPING ON TAKE 2.
Right?
- That's right!
Now look.
- What? What is it Wakatsuki?
I have a game.
THERE'S ANOTHER HUMOR
A game?
- Something like specialty.
I want to introduce my friend first.
- A friend? - Yes!
He's this 10.000 Yen paper money.
He's been called Fuku-chan.
FUKU-CHAN AGAIN
Have you knew him? - Fuku-chan?
Yes! And this Fuku-chan here...
His specialty is he can stand with his head.
Don't you know that?
Let's see how will he do it.
First you fold Fuku-chan
in half like this.
After that, fold him in half again.
And again.
Then we open this.
Look, Fuku-chan is standing with his head!!!
His head...
- Thanks, that's good. That's good.
Not bad, that was a decent
humor for everyone.
Maybe she did it with her own style just now.
- Right, and that's not easy!
Actually...
- What is it, Wakatsuki?
STUBBORN
I only had 10.000 Yen in my pocket, but...
Well...
- Do we have something else?
If there's a pair of chopsticks, maybe I can do it.
- Eh, chopsticks, chopsticks.
Ah, really?
Here you go.
- These are ordinary chopsticks, but...
What?
- Look, there are ordinary chopsticks here.
Yes.
I pull them out.
Hashi-kun, Hashi-kun,
Who was that elegant woman
with you that day?
No, no. There's no such woman with me.
There was. That middle aged woman.
Ah that, she's my mother.
OK, please... thank you.
Members thought that was pretty lame.
FELT LAME
Yeah that was exactly the same, I guess it'll be nice if
she added something like weird face.
- I thought so too!
That's a great advice!
- Right, right.
Young people will be more interested that way.
- Ah I see.
What you did was just copying.
- Yes!
BECAUSE SHE'S TOO SERIOUS
That's why try my advice and do it
with some weird face now.
Try to do it with the weird face
in the middle of that joke.
With the weird face method,
what kind of face she will show?
WAKABAYASHI'S METHOD
[TALKING ABOUT CHOPSTICKS]
WEIRD
FACE VERSION
Okay, here I go.
These are chopsticks, right?
- Yes.
Hashi-kun, Hashi-kun
Look, everyone reacted, they all laughed.
That was great!
- Once again from here!
Everyone, please look here!
- Go ahead.
These are chopsticks, right?
- Yes chopsticks. Everyone, watch it seriously!
Watch this one!
Hashi-kun, Hashi-kun, who was that elegant woman
with you some days ago?
There was no such woman with me.
There was! A middle aged woman!
Aahh~~
Well...
that's my mom!
Last, the closing.
Aahh, so good!
THAT'S IT?
The atmosphere is different.
- See?
Clearly different.
But next...
Himura Sensei will give an example too.
A VERY DANGEROUS MASTER
Alright.
Hashi-kun, Hashi-kun, who was that woman
with you on that day?
Eh, there was no such woman.
HASHI-KUN HAS COME
Wah, pretty good!
- There was no such woman.
You can also keep making
the weird face like that.
The middle aged woman.
Now this is good.
Was my mom!
WRONG FACE
That was a great weird face. - What?
That was good...
You wanna try?
- Ah, nope, nope, nope. No way!
CHOPSTICKS OF BAD LUCK
Now the studio has become
the hell of weird faces.
It's because Matsumura is also too serious.
The forbidden collaboration between Wakabayashi Sensei and Himura.
Can it be done?
WAKABAYASHI'S METHOD
[TALKING ABOUT CHOPSTICKS]
HIMURA'S METHOD
[WEIRD FACE]
Hashi-kun, Hashi-kun, who was that elegant lady
with you that day?
Eh, there was no such woman!
Ah, that was amazing!
Do it up to "my mother" part.
Eh, there was! That middle aged woman!
Eh, that woman was my mother!
Great.
Surely they all laughed so hard.
Alright, now Hori!
Next, Hori will feel this hell too.
WAKABAYASHI'S METHOD
[TALKING ABOUT CHOPSTICKS]
HIMURA'S METHOD
[WEIRD FACE]
Here we go.
Hashi-kun, Hashi-kun,
The one with you that time...
The one with you then went, that time...
The one went with you that time?
HOW SHOULD I KNOW
That sentence didn't make any sense!
The one with you that time, eh?
The one who went with you that time?
How should I know!
There was an unexpected mistake.
TAKE 2!
WAKABAYASHI'S METHOD
[TALKING ABOUT CHOPSTICKS]
HIMURA'S METHOD
[WEIRD FACE]
Hashi-kun, Hashi-kun, who was that Ikima woman
who went out with you that day?
WHO!
What's wrong with you?
The elegant woman who went out with you.
Please do it up to the weird face part.
- Hai!
Now she has to work hard
to reach the weird face part!
WAKABAYASHI'S METHOD
[TALKING ABOUT CHOPSTICKS]
HIMURA'S METHOD
[WEIRD FACE]
Hashi-kun, Hashi-kun, who was that elegant woman who
went out with you that day?
Eee....
That was different! How was it again?
DIFFERENT FACE CAME OUT
Eeh, that woman... What?
She's still making the weird face!
Do the weird face!
There was no such woman.
There was! A middle aged woman.
Maintain the weird face!
Eh, that's my mother.
WHERE'S THE SLEEVE
The sleeve!
Ah, so interesting!
Music Video "Kanashimi no Wasurekata"
is finally here.
Released together with Music Clip collection,
"All MV Collection" on 23 December 2015!
Get it ASAP!
CONVERTED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
Wonderful.
- Look, everyone...
That was so good!
Which one will be the best?