m 0 0 l 0 27 l 2 27 l 2 0 l 0 0 m 2 0 l -4 0 l -4 6 l 16 6 l 16 4 l -2 4 l -2 2 l 0 2 m 2 2 m 16 0 l 16 27 l 18 27 l 18 -1 l 16 -1 m 22 0 l 22 0 l 24 0 l 24 11 l 19 11 l 19 9 l 22 9 l 22 2 l 15 2 l 15 0 m 6 18 l 6 12 l 12 12 l 12 14 l 8 14 l 8 18 l 6 18 m 12 18 l 12 20 l 6 20 l 6 18 l 10 18 l 10 14 l 12 14 l 12 18 m 5 7 l 8 9 l 7 10 l 4 8 l 5 7 m 10 9 l 10 9 l 13 7 l 14 8 l 11 10 l 10 9 m 3 24 b 3 24 3 23 3 23 b 7 21 11 21 15 23 b 15 23 15 25 15 25 b 11 23 7 23 3 25
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
NOGIZAKA KOUJICHUU
DON! Okay, Nogizaka Koujichuu is now starting, and
we're the MC, Bananaman, Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu.
BANANAMAN
SHITARA OSAMU
HIMURA YUKI
And here's Nogizaka-chan...
Alright, what will we do today?
Himura-san!   -Yes!  -Please...
A two dimensional boyfriend contest
number one!!!
Idoling is an entertainment world where
love relationship is forbidden.
But if it's just an imagination
character from a fantasy world, then it's allowed.
And this time, members who love mangas and animes
will present a character they love.
A boyfriend from two dimensional world will be chosen!
And the one who will choose are Himura, who
never watches animes and reads mangas, also...
Ikuta!
- Oh, okay!
Ikuta, you've never see it right?
- Not even once.  - Ah, is that so!?
So, because you've never watched anime,
your drawings are always weird, huh.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
UNCAPABLE.
IKOMA RINA
The first contestant, Ikoma Rina who
loves anime very much.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
AN ANIME ABOUT SWIMMING CLUB IN A HIGH SCHOOL,
TO FACE THE UPCOMING SWIMMING CONTESTS.
The ideal boyfriend she will present...
...comes from an anime about men's swimming club
at a high school, [FREE!]...
IKOMA'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
TACHIBANA MAKOTO
HIGH SCHOOL SOPHOMORE
Tachibana Makoto is the childhood friend of the main character in this anime
Nanase Haruka who joined the very same swimming club
An anime about swimming?
- That's right
I joined swimming club too, once.   - He did.
Yeah!
He got a nickname THE TORPEDO.
- That's not true!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
HIMU-ROCKET.
Since when did I have that nickname?
Start!
- Okay!
Guy I like is Tachibana Makoto-kun
[FREE!] TACHIBANA MAKOTO
IKOMA'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
In the swimming club he belongs,
Mako-chan is the kindest one
And Mako-chan is a guy who
like a big tree, 183 cm,   - He's tall!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
SOFT AND KIND
But he has a very soft look
Soft look?
- Yeah, like this
[FREE!] TACHIBANA MAKOTO
IKOMA'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
USUALLY HIS FACIAL EXPRESSION
IS VERY KIND
APPEALS
Although he looks pity, but...
...when he wears the swimming outfit, he looks different
When he wears it, he looks pretty cool
[FREE!] TACHIBANA MAKOTO
IKOMA'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
This face, really looks like a true man
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
WHEN HE SWIMS, HIS FACE
SUDDENLY BECOMES WILD
APPEALS
From the soft one before?   - Yes!
Although he's kind, but once he gets into the water
his character changes!
- Ahh, so that's Mako-chan?
Mako-chan also has very good muscles!
[FREE!] TACHIBANA MAKOTO
IKOMA'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A VERY MACHO BODY
APPEALS
That's because he swims, yeah?
The most interesting thing of this anime, FREE! is...
...the upper body muscles of the male characters
there, very cool!
Ikoma, do you like stuff like those?
Parts like those, I love it very much! Yes!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
STUFF SHE LIKES IS MUSCLES.
I really love it!
Besides, if we look at those guys' looks,
they're...
IKOMA'S SPECIAL POSTER
Cool, aren't they.
- You can say that they're perfect!
Try to introduce them all
This one in the corner is Tachibana Makoto, Nanase Haruka,
Matsuoka Rin...
And,...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
HER PRECIOUS THING IS BROKEN.
Ripped, her poster is ripped!
You ripped it? Ahh...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
VERY SURPRISED.
Is this yours?
You ripped your own poster...
Aahh...hold on, she's still in shock
Shocked huh? Of course
Ikoma, there's no time. Ikoma, because there's
no time, start again from the one before
- There's no time.
Mako-chan, really looks like
a true man, and he's also kind, so...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
SPIRIT DECREASED DRASTICALLY.
...please choose him!
Ah, Ikoma~~
IKOMA'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
TACHIBANA MAKOTO
We also don't know their faces
if it's ripped like that - Don't know~
But I think if we look at
Ikoma's spirit...
...when she explained it earlier, maybe
Mako-chan will be happy!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
FOR MAKO-CHAN'S HAPPINESS.
But...
HASHIMOTO NANAMI
Our next contestant is Hashimoto Nanami.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
FULL METAL ALCHEMIST
A STORY ABOUT THE ADVENTURE
OF BROTHERS EXPLORING A WORLD WHERE
MIRACLE OF THE ART OF ALCHEMY CAN BE FOUND.
In a world where the art of alchemy
can be found...
...a story of brothers who raised from
the death using some magic stone...
...a famous fantasy work,
Full Metal Alchemist.
HASHIMOTO'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
JEAN HAVOC
NOTES
A SECOND LIEUTENANT SOLDIER
MAIN CHARACTER, BUT HAS SMALL ROLE
The one who will be the ideal boyfriend is
a supporting character...
...a friend of the brothers and often smokes,
Jean Havoc.
Ready, start!
- Alright!
The one I want to introduce this time
is Jean Havoc
HASHIMOTO'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
[FULL METAL ALCHEMIST] JEAN HAVOC
And what I want to show you now is
how he's having a bad luck with women
Women never care about him
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
CONFIDENT
ALTHOUGH UNPOPULAR
But this guy finally succeeded
in getting a girlfriend. And he's very happy
Sadly, that woman was actually...
...setting him up!
That woman only wanted to
steal some secret information
But Havoc is always having a great resolution
He always separates his personal business
and his works...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
HE ALWAYS SEPARATES THINGS BETWEEM HIS JOB AND HIS PERSONAL BUSINESS
...and there was not a single information he gave.
After that, a fight happened...
...and he got impaled by the very woman
he loved
Eeeh~!!!
And after that fight, Havoc's lower body
got paralyzed
He couldn't move it at all
But he never gave up to keep
fighting in his force
That time even if he wanted to cry, he
had a debate with his commander!
"You can't leave me here!
I'm still coming!"
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
HE CARES SO MUCH FOR HIS FRIENDS
He said he has a very important
place in the force
He also doesn't want to be pitied
Then the commander said,
"Alright, you're in!"
He said "Because you
want to do this, you better catch up real quick!"
HOSHIMOTO'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
JEAN HAVOC
Judging from his appearance, he looks like
a kind man, pretty cool
But wait, his chin looks protruding.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NOT A COOL GUY.
Does he always smoke?
- He does
Is that okay? Always smokes...
- Ah, I hate smokes
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
HATES BEING A PASSIVE SMOKER.
Are you going to tell him to stop smoking
when you guys are dating?   - That's right
If we're dating, maybe I will
tell him to stop
"If it's just like this, please
don't tell me to stop"
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
THE SMOKER WITH A PROTRUDING CHIN APPEARS.
"It's all I have..."
The cigar..."I...please don't
tell me to stop"
He might be saying that
After that he will have nothing anymore
AKIMOTO MANATSU
Next, Akimoto Manatsu
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
OTOKO NO ISSHOU
A STORY ABOUT A LOVE STORY
BETWEEN A 51 Y.O. PHILOSOPHY PROFESSOR AND
31 Y.O. OL WHO LIVE TOGETHER.
The main character in Otoko no Isshou,...
...a manga about an unusual
love story...
...between a man and a woman with 20 years old difference
who live together
HASHIMOTO'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
KAIEDA JUN
NOTES
A SINGLE PHILOSOPHY PROFESSORSEORANG
AT AN ALL-WOMEN UNIV
FROM KANSAI AND 51 YEARS OLD
A 51 years old man, known as
a professor and philosophy prince at a university
The boyfriend, Kaieda Jun
Okay, start!
I love how Kaeda Jun-san
affectTsugumi-san's heart like that...
AKIMOTO'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
[OTOKO NO ISSHOU]
KAIEDA JUN (51)
DOUZONO TSUGUMI
Because this guy is 51 y.o...
..also he's very experienced as
a professor at a university
He's also very intelligent...
Plus, he also has the calmness
of a middle aged man
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
HIS CALMNESS IN UTILIZING HIS
CLEVERNESS ELEGANTLY
IS VERY AMAZING.
His calmness is much more
than the young people have
He also has more life experiences
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
HAS A MATURE MAN'S CHARM
THAT YOUNG PEOPLE DON'T HAVE
Because he's intelligent...
...when he talks, it's very straightforward
but it's very logical
Also, sometimes....(Jyan~)
...he also looks like this
He can be uncool sometimes
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
OFTEN SHOWS CUTE CHARACTER
OF OJIISAN
- Very thin?
This also what makes me interested in him
But, thing I like from him the most is
this...
When he said "There's no way
to not love you,"
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
LOVE
QUOTES
"THERE'S NO WAY TO NOT
LOVE YOU"
After he said that, Tsugami asked Kaieda-san for his explanation...
...about all this stuff
Tsugami-san said "What about our
age gap. Please think about it again" like that,...
But becase he's already fell in love
He answered "What if we're being honest
with our feelings..."
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
HE DIRECTLY CONFESSED
HIS FEELING
I think... Yes,
I like this part when he said this
- Like a true man
AKIMOTO'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
KAIEDA JUN (51)
You like a middle aged man like this?
I like middle aged men very much
You really like....
- I like the way of their thinking
There are people who have the calmness  - Yeah!
I think middle aged men have that
So, you do like thin middle aged men?
He's very thin and only wearing boxer
If it's like that then Tanaka from Ungirls is fine?
- Well...
AKIMOTO'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
KAIEDA JUN (51)
UNGIRLS TANAKA
About that thin
WAKATSUKI YUMI
Next, Wakatsuki's two dimensional boyfriend
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
TOKYO GHOUL
A STORY ABOUT
A SPECIAL FORCE IN BATTLE
AGAINST HUMAN-EATING MONSTER [GHOUL]
Fantasy manga about battles between...
...human and Ghouls, human-eating creatures,
Tokyo Ghoul
WAKATSUKI'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
KANEKI KEN
NOTES
HALF GHOUL WITH
SUPERPOWERS LIKE THE GHOULS
The main character of the manga, half human
half Ghoul with superpower
...Wakatsuki's ideal boyfriend, Kaneki Ken.
Okay, start!
Alright, he's the one I want to introduce,
Kaneki Kun
WAKATSUKI'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
[TOKYO GHOUL] KANEKI KEN
Kaneki-kun was a normal human, but
he transplanted a dead ghoul's organ to himself
That's really wrong
- Why would he do that?
WAKATSUKI'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
[TOKYO GHOUL] KANEKI KEN
After that, Kaneki-kun's been called as
half Ghoul
Although he was a human,
now he's a half ghoul
Kaneki-kun too...
- He cries?
Right, he cried alot
because he felt pressured
Even he was a real human,
but now he's a human-eating monster
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
THE VAGUENESS
OF HIS CONDITION BETWEEN HUMAN AND GHOUL
IS VERY INTERESTING
He also had to disconnect himself
with his friends
Because his friends are normal humans,
He also worried that someday he will look
his friends as food
Because human's food tastes disgusting for him,
this thing made him a man eater
- Ah, so that's it
But even if he couldn't eat human's food,
he also couldn't eat humans because he was human himself
- He realized that!
This "Uwaa...." when he's in pain
is very amazing
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
AMAZING?
Amazing?  - Amazing, isn't it?
- It is!
WAKATSUKI'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
KANEKI KEN
But if he becomes your boyfriend
could you get eaten?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
RISK OF GETTING EATEN.
It's better to be alone then
- Even if you love him?
Because he's half ghoul, there will be times
when he's hungry and need to eat humans
- That's right!
But he's also fighting the ghouls
- Exactly!
So, what is Kaneki-kun?
- Kaneki-kun is...
...he's between human and ghoul
He's not really a friend or foe
of humans
Uwaaaaaaaaaaa.a..a...a~~~~~
TERADA RANZE
Next, Terada Ranze's presentation
of her ideal boyfriend
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
OOKAMI SHOUJOU TO KURO OUJI
A LOVE STORY ABOUT A QUITE WEIRD
RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS
THAT STARTED FROM A LIE
A couple that started from a lie...
...with a unique relationship,
Ookami Shoujou to Kuro Ouji,
RANZE'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
SATA KYOUYA
NOTES
LOOKS LIKE
A PRINCE, BUT HIS TRUE COLOR,
IS CRUEL, SADIST, AND STRANGE
The main character has a
real sadist character...
...Terada's ideal boyfriend, Sata Kyouya.
Start!
- Okay!
As this picture shows, Sata-kun's described
as a cool guy and prince-like
- His face is definitely handsome
RANZE'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
[OOKAMI SHOUJO TO KURO OUJI]
SATA KYOUYA
With Erika, who looks like your
everyday normal girl, he treats her well
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
HE LOOKS LIKE A PRINCE
But he has this bad attittude?
He's very sadistic
- He's a sadist?
For example, like this...
Wow, so he's like that!
"If you wanna date me, be my dog
and make me laugh!"
I can't contain myself if I'm in this situation
You love things like this?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
HE TREATS WOMEN LIKE DOGS
I really love it. I myself
really love a sadist like him
Really really...
I... I'd love to be his dog
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
HAPPY TO BE HIS DOG.
This is actually pretty interesting!
I really do, I want to be his dog
So there are girls like this too
- Right, I'm a human like that.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
DOG CHARACTER.
Terada, you're awesome
She suddenly said something like that.
But he's not always like that
RANZE'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
[OOKAMI SHOUJO TO KURO OUJI]
SATA KYOUYA
After "cruel, cruel, cruel, cruel, cruel"
then "kind" appears.
- But does he "care"sometimes?
When his "love" shows,
that's what make me madly in love with him
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
ALTHOUGH RARELY, WHEN HE SHOWS
HIS AFFECTION, IT'S VERY WONDERFUL
Like when he said "I too will be angry
if someone hurts you",
"Because you're my girl, all you have to do is stay still
and I will protect you,"
Ain't this charming?
Stuff like this makes him a real man
- Precisely, that's why...
Just like earlier, when he doesn't care but then he does,
it makes me madly in love!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
9 IGNORANCES : 1 CARE
This is the only thing that can make me...
Really...
- What? He kisses her?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
ROMANTIC
SCENE
SAYS "YOU'RE NOISY!"
THEN KISSES HER.
He does?
- That's right!
That's why, when his sweet side appears,
I love it very much!  - Why is that?
Like when we're arguing, suddenly he says "You're noisy",
- You're noisy?
I love stuff like that very much!
Love? You love this?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
HIS SADISTIC CHARACTER IS VERY CHARMING
I really do!
- Aaahh, I really do~
It seems the others are like that too
honestly I like a weird person like this
Is it okay for you
to say that?
But I actually like weird person like this!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
UNMOVABLE.
Well, I said this once
When someone asked me, "what kind of person
do you like?", I said...
"A really really ugly person" and also
loves to trashtalk me
RANZE'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
SATA KYOUYA
But Sata-kun is actually a kind person
like a friendly guy, right?
- That's right, he actually is
He too looks weak
- I love him not because of that
Although his real color is like that, he could
make me love him, it's very...
- I see.
Ikuta, do you understand someone like this?
- So?
I really understand
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
UNDERSTANDS THE SADIST'S CHARM.
Is that right?
Women are weak against things like this
- Seriously?
RANZE'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
SATA KYOUYA
When I heard the story,
my heart skipped a beat.
Ah, thank you.
- Skipped a beat?
- For real?
CONVERTED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
INOUE SAYURI
Next contestant, Inoue Sayuri
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
TENSOU SENTAI GOSEIGER
A DRAMA ABOUT BATTLES BETWEEN
GUARDIAN KNIGHTS GOSEIGER AGAINST
EVIL TROOPS OF WARSTAR
Inoue's ideal boyfriend is one of the heroes
who appear in Tensou Sentai Goseiger, Gosei Knight.
INOUE'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
GOSEI KNIGHT
NOTES
AT FIRST, HE'S AN ENEMY.
BUT AFTER FEW FIGHTS,
SLOWLY HE OPENED HIS HEART
AND BECAME AN ALLY.
He's like a helping god
...who got involved in many battles and became
a true friend, the mysterious knight, Inoue's ideal boyfriend
Start!
- Okay! Character I love is...
INOUE'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
[TENSOU SENTAI GOSEIGER]
GOSEI KNIGHT
...this, Gosei Knight-sama.
Actually, Gosei Knight-sama
was not a human
Eh?!
- From birth, he became a Gosei Knight immediately
He's very powerful
- He does look like it!
Besides...
- This man is very strong, huh?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
HE CAN FIGHT ALL ALONE
BECAUSE HE'S VERY STRONG
In history, he is the strongest.
He's very strong, like at the start
when he was the humanity's enemy, he's pretty cool
- I see
Although he received many attacks and got wounded,
he won't fall to his knee
He's always like that
- So, he's that strong?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
THERE'S NO ATTACK THAT CAN
MAKE HIM FALL TO HIS KNEE
For example, "Bang, bang, bang" someone shoots
Then he goes, "Wuaah" like this,
- He will kneel!
"Aaagh"...
Eehh!!! Awesome!
Pretty great huh?  - Very powerful!
- He is
But this super strong Gosei Knight
in the end became an ally of five Goseiger heroes
INOUE'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
[TENSOU SENTAI GOSEIGER]
GOSEI KNIGHT
They fought together
- They're friends?
And his quote is...
"Now it's my turn!", when he appears
And slowly the Goseigers' heart finally
opened and welcomed him
Then they said "Now it's our turn!"
(Goseiger + Gosei Knight)
Lastly he said "Now it's you guys' turn!"
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
IRRESPONSIBLE.
Well that's...
Because he didn't wanna do it?
Really?
He has...um...soft character, so
people said "Ah, that man is actually kind"
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
KIND ALTHOUGH
HE'S STRONG AND A LONE WOLF
Aaaaaaa..oooo..~~~
INOUE'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
GOSEI KNIGHT
This one is really different than the others
- Exactly!
When he born, did he come
in a shape like that?
Yes, also,
- I see. How did he cry if he look like that?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
PROBLEM WHEN BORN.
The tears will be all over his face
- Really?
But isn't he cool?
- Absolutely
Compared to what we got showed
by Ranze earlier...
...he's not cruel at all.
He's silent. He doesn't like to talk at all.
So you think he's not noisy
- Yup!
If he's like that...
- Clearly
"Hey, please listen...
...I got wounded here, today!"
INOUE'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
GOSEI KNIGHT
"It hurts so much, I thought I was gonna die",
There's no complaint like that, right?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
SUPERHERO CHARACTER.
No, nope...
- So he's that type
HIGUCHI HINA
Next, we have Higuchi Hina
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
HIGH TEEN BOOGIE
MANGA SERIES STARTED IN 1977,
ABOUT A TRUE LOVE BETWEEN
HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT AND BIKE GANG MEMBER
WITH AN ORDINARY HIGH SCHOOL GIRL
A story written 40 years ago...
Love story between a bike gang Yankee
with an ordinary high school girl, High Teen Boogie.
Yankee = delinquents / "badasses" in Japan, more info check Google
HIGUCHI'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
FUJIMARU SHO
NOTES
HE'S A BIKE GANG LEADER,
ALTHOUGH HE COMES FROM A RICH FAMILY,
BECAUSE HE'S FORCED BY HIS PARENTS
TO BE ENGAGED
And the main character is...
Bike gang leader who actually
came from a wealthy family
The two dimensional ideal boyfriend, Fujimaro Sho.
HIGH TEEN BOOGIE
SERIALIZATON STARTED IN 1977
Manga from 1977...
It's been so long, back then we were still...
kids.
- Kids.
Back then when my mom was still in high school,
she read this manga
When she was still young,
she lived in Nagano
I found it in her house there,
and brought it back to my house
Immediately, I like his style in this cover
the first time I saw it  - With his style?  - Yeah!
This manga too, when my mom was dating my dad in high school back then...
She didn't tell this to my dad...
Before dated my dad...
She had a boyfriend back in high school
similar to this character.  - Is this okay?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
DIGGING MOM'S SECRET.
You said it just now.
- Ah! What should I do? Dad... Maybe it's alright.
But dad too...
- Then your dad be like "HEY, I'VE HEARD NOTHING ABOUT THIS!"
What if he suddenly rides a bike?
- It's ok, maybe...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
DEBUT AS A GANG.
But why do you like him?  - Yeah, why?
Okay, please present it to us. Start!
Okay, character I like is...
...Fujimaru Sho, the main character in this manga
HIGUCHI'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
[HIGH TEEN BOOGIE]
FUJIMARU SHO
He's a bike gang leader
On the other side, Momoko-chan is just an ordinary girl
who's very serious. Because he loves her...
MIYASHITA MOMOKO
...he stopped from the bike gang. He even lose his Pompadour.
He even got laughed at because he tried
to not look like the other bike gang members
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
HE'S READY TO DISCARD EVERYTHING
FOR THIS GIRL
Actually, his Pompadour hairstyle
is his real hair style
Since Momo-chan saw that, she asked him
to go back to his she like that better
His actions and willing to do anything for Momo-chan
, girl he loves, is very cool for me
HIGUCHI'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
[HIGH TEEN BOOGIE]
FUJIMARU SHO
Besides, he's very good in fighting
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
PROFICIENT IN FIGHTING
Also, his hairstyle,
leather jacket, and bike
Aren't those symbols of a man?
- That's right
HIGUCHI'S
IDEAL
BOYFRIEND
[HIGH TEEN BOOGIE]
FUJIMARU SHO
I like this character
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
APPEALS
LIKES BIKES VERY MUCH
AND HIS POMPADOUR HAIRSTYLE
Lately I'm looking for mangas like this,
and searching something like this one
But I didn't find young guys
like this.  Yes!
- This one?
I think they don't have the spirit
and passion like this character
Hey!, I too...
- Why did you say [Hey] just now?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
SUDDENLY "HEY".
That's...the thing I like the most...
- Hey!
Maybe she's into it too much?
- What's with the "Hey"?
There's this one scene I like very much...
When Momo-chan thought where will this relationship of theirs
will go, and sat in the park bench...
He said "Would you ride with me?"  - Eh?!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
ROMANTIC
SCENE
Says to Momoko
"Would you ride with me?"
"Would you ride with me?", huh?
- From this onward, where will he bring her to?
He thought about her future
- Yes!
If there's a guy who said that to me,
certainly I would say "Sure, let's go!",
Would you ride with me?
- Yeah!
True man and open-minded, also mature,
those two things I like the most
HIGUCHI'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
FUJIMARU SHO
I see
- This is unpredictable too
That's right, because this didn't use
the modern theme like now
- Yeah
Now this, you can really feel the two dimensional impressions.
- Ah, I agree
- Understood, understood.
I really want it, in school, there's a voice
"Brrm, brrm", sounds like a calling
He does it from the school gate
then everyone be like "Eh, who, who's that?"
Then I come out, go to the gate, then "Ah...!"
- I knew it!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
WANTS TO BE A YANKEE.
That's cute! Cute!
Ah, so that's what you really want to do?
After this, the imaginary dates will cause some problems!
And now, it's question time
to choose the most ideal two dimensional boyfriend!
For example, when you guys are going out...
...then suddenly you meet bad guys...
...how would he help you?
Now Hashimoto, he's a soldier, right?
WHAT IF THERE'S A BAD GUY WHEN YOU'RE DATING?
That's right. Even though he's a soldier, he
would prioritize his woman
HASHIMOTO's IDEAL BOYFRIEND
JEAN HAVOC
Like if that happens,
he'd observe the situation first
He would hide his woman
After she can't see what's going on,
he will kick the baddies' asses
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
LOVES TO FIGHT.
Ah, I see!
About him, isn't he dangerous?
- He is
No, it's not like that...
- He may be your nightmare  - Well him...
WAKATSUKI'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
KANEKI KEN
Could he talk it out?
No but actually there was this scene
where he helped a girl  - There was?
Yes, when he helped his friend, Touka-chan
The enemy is his own brother, who later
will be his enemy. That's because he forgot many things about him...
When they clashed, and he beat him...
He said, "You're my brother and the most important person
for me, so I won't kill you"
But he beat him to the point of near death...
- That's scary
Half of his bones are destroyed...
Humans alone have 206 bones, so...
THAT'S TOO MUCH!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
OVERFLOWING REVENGE.
When he was being asked, "When we're out and there's a bad guy,
how can he help you?"
Then he said, "I'll smash half of his bones",
lthen he smashed all of them
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
WORST DATE.
Clearly that's not good!
That's scary!  - Yeah!
- But that's because he's extraordinarily strong...
But he doesn't have to go that far!
What about Fujimaru?
Well clearly he's good, right?
- He's good at fighting, he also rides a bike
HIGUCHI'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
FUJIMARU SHO
Then he's like, "Hop on!",
then we bailed out of there
Kaieda-san, can he fight?
AKIMOTO'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
KAIEDA JUN (51)
He's also not young anymore
Kaieda is weak, he's the weakest
Wait, don't underestimate him!
Even I can win against Kaieda
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
CONFIDENT.
He's strong!
- 51 years old man who that thin is easy to beat!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
HIMURA READY FOR WAR.
That thin...
- Surely easy to defeat
Himura-san, why are you getting so worked up?
- With words...
Because he's genius and teaches in university,
he can win with arguments
He beat his opponents with
philosophical quotes
No no, it has nothing to do with words.
Himura-san will just "smack" like that
- It has nothing to do at all!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
HIMURA YANKEE.
He could die...
- I'm a pretty straightforward guy like this
That's because Himura-san is impatient
Because I need no arguments!
"You talk too much, Kaieda!", like that
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
THE FIRST WIN.
That's because he won't punch!
You, is there something you want to ask?
If you're going out, where will you take him?
- Oh, dating spot, huh?
What about Kaieda-san?
WHERE WILL YOU GUYS DATE?
AKIMOTO'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
KAIEDA JUN (51)
Onsen Atami. - Ah, that's good!
- It suits him!
Onsen Atami = Hot springs located in Shizuoka that
near the sea. Visitors could soak
while watcing the scenery of the sea
We reserve a room that has a Rotenburo
Rotenburo = Outdoor onsen.
We eat a whole complete menu there, and just chilling
What about Jean Havoc, where will you two go?
HASHIMOTO'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
JEAN HAVOC
There's this one scene when he was in a restaurant
He brought flowers while he waited
Will he smoke all the time? Recently in restaurants
there's no smoking allowed
No, maybe because he always prioritize a lady,
he won't smoke
But if he's always smoke like that
- That's true
"If it's restaurant, I can't smoke anymore,"
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
MR.PROTRUDING CHIN APPEARS.
He'll say that
- That guy certainly will!
Okay now, this Gosei Knight.
Where will you bring him?
I'll take Gosei Knight to the amusement park
INOUE'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
GOSEI KNIGHT
If Gosei Knight goes there
then it'll be dangerous
He'll be "Gacha-gacha" like that,
- Yeah, he can't go to amusement park then
Gacha-Gacha = sound a robot makes when it moves
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
CLEARLY A SUSPICIOUS PERSON.
Besides, the kids will come near him
- That's right
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
SUPERHERO SHOW.
Your fault for picking the amusement park
What food does he eat?
- Food...
Well...
Food won't go inside
In restaurant for example
But since she's dating Gosei Knight,
even if she helps her eat, it will bump into his mouth
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
PROBLEM WHEN EATING.
It will be all over his mouth...
Then it's no good...
- Well..
You can say this part here is his mouth
- If he eats from those holes, then...
He has to eat liquid food?
- He eats liquid food?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
LIQUID FOOD FROM MOUTHGAP.
Does Sata-kun not like to go out?
- He doesn't...
TERADA'S IDEAL BOYFRIEND
SATA KYOUYA
To persuade him, I have so keep saying
"I beg you, I beg you please", but in the end he still won't go
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN DOG AND ITS OWNER.
Do you have to do that when you're dating?
- What's with that dude?
Like for example, where would he go?
Probably a normal amusement park
But if you go there, you'd meet Gosei Knight
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
AFRAID TO MEET.
Well?
After this one, the ideal two dimensional boyfriend, finally get chosen!
So, who'll be the ideal two dimensional boyfriend
that got chosen by Ikuta and Himura?
The most ideal two dimensional boyfriend is...
The boyfriend that introduced by Higuchi,
Fujimaru Sho from High Teen Boogie!
I see. It's chosen then.
What made him get chosen clearly, because slowly
he looks more dominant with his true male character, very cool
In the end, is there anyone else that deserved to be picked?
- Of course, there's a good enough character
CONVERTED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
The human ones, right?
Humans are more calming!
- Even then, since he's a monster...
I too don't know where should I take
a robot like that
Under LIVE "Zenkoku Tour" Touhouku Series,
Ticket reservation by phone will be served first!
Audition seminar of third generation members
will be held nationally on seven places
Registration still open!