Tonight's episode is still about for Nogizaka46's
14th Single Campaign in Guam.
Different prices are given to each member that have won the game.
On the other hand, the members that lost the game will end up challenging the 4200m skydive.
Previously there were 15 losers during the Beach Flag Race. Who will win this time?
Beach Tube Battle Royal Sumo!
What is it? I've never heard of it...
Kindly look at the sumo arena floating near the beach.
Each member will compete in a sumo match while wearing a life jacket..
The members that won the challenge
will immediately get the prize but...
Since this is a Battle Royale, instead of 1 vs. 1. There shall be 4 members competing.
- So four people will fight from the start.
No!
This is bad!
Within the 4 participants, the last one survive wins.
Since there are 4 people playing, both players can team up and eliminate the other two, which is an advantage.
Intelligence is also needed.
- That's a great idea.
- But there's also this idea...
Since Fukugawa-chan is the center, shouldn't she win this match?
That kind of thinking isn't allowed.
Anyone who fell out of the stage is considered out, but if someone fell over inside the ring, she's still safe.
- You can also do this at the start of the match.
- Kicking?
Kicking is allowed.
Each participant is randomly selected.
Are you all ready?
- They look too tense!
- You guys should relax a bit.
All are waiting.
- Ready?
- Yes!
Hakkeyoi....Nokotta!!!
Go ahead! Huh? They're not starting.
Wait, huh? Oh, the atmosphere... atmosphere...
- The atmosphere is heating up!
- Hori versus Asuka-chan.
She's not moving! Sakurai is not moving!
How will this end? How?
- This is bad! Hori is getting ganged up!
- Hori you are getting teamed up!
3 vs. 1?
- Hori is alone!
- You're right!
Well, this is it!
- How will this end?
Oh! Hori... Hori attacked! Hori...
- Oh! Hori finally falls in!
- Hori, you're out!
Before, these three are like giving a signal to
each other "Let's do Hori" like that.
Great, now only 3 are left.
- Ready, start!
- Oh, they've clashed! What will happen?
Who? Who'll win?
Oh? Sakurai... Sakurai... Sakurai is in danger!
Oh, she's pushing her! You should stop doing that.
- Oh, Hashimoto?
- Hashimoto is still going strong!
- Hashimoto is tough.
- Isn't she?
- No~!
- Asuka-chan, is tough too!
Oohh!!! What will happen? Who will win?
What will happen?
Both of them are getting tired.
- Why? Eh? What the heck is this?
- They're taking a break...
Taking a break.
- Both of them are tired! Come on!
- Start!
- No~!
- Oh, which one?
- Which way? Hashimoto is pushing her!
- Which direction?
Hashimoto wins!
Oh, Sakurai? You're still wearing them?
Sakurai is stuck.
- What are you looking at?
- Sakurai...
Can someone help me get out?
It's like your stranded.
Unnecessary Spinning!
Sakurai! Sakurai!
Look, you are finally out! Sakurai, you're free.
You're free.
Did you just do something? - Just now, Shitara-san?
- No, it's the waves.
Though, you kinda look nice. Like posing for a Gravure shoot.
- Like a scene in the rain?
- That's right.
- Very nice!
- Asuka-chan! You're stuck too?
- How about I help you?
Please stop.
You need my help, right?
- No, please! Stop!
Separation success. See? You're out too!
Asuka is born.
- Ah...! Wait, wait a minute.
- Stop.
- Why do you look so happy?
From what you did, it does made me feel somewhat very happy.
She's having fun.
- What's with the cheerful atmosphere?
- Maybe it's the effect of the island.
- Hashimoto wins the prize.
- Hashimoto congratulations!
- Congratulations on your win!
- You can now relax.
The next participants are the nonathletic members.
Hoshino, Ikoma and Akimoto...
- Yatta!
- Please come here.
- Is something wrong?
- We want to participate!
- You want to join this group?
Why do you want to particpate? Is it because they're all weak?
- Yes! Definitely!
- If we made it like that, then these 3 will definitely be the target.
- That's right!
One of you will need to resist the attack from these three you know.
The one chosen for the last position for this group is Kawamura Mahiro.
Hoshino, who will you attack first?
- Well, I want to attack Rotti!
- "I want Rotti..."
Kawamura goes first
So, all of you are targeting Rotti?
Without further ado, the match for the second round starts now!
Well, it looks like everyone is already
facing and ready to attack Rotti.
Battle Ready.
- Mahiro, good luck!
- You can do it, Rotti!
- This is scary
- Wait!
Hakkeyoi~!!!
- Nokotta!!!
- Go!
- Oh, they're starting!
- Will she fall?
- No! She didn't!
- That's good.
- She survived!
- Rotti fell down too!
- Oh, this is bad!
- Mahiro, good luck!
- That's dangerous!
- Akimoto slipped
- Huh? They're ignoring Akimoto?
Ikoma-chan, come over here!
Panic.
Huh? Both of them are fighting? Oh!?
- Ikoma!
- Ikoma Safe, Safe! Ikoma didn't fall out!
- What?
- Oh, she's out! She's still not out!
Ikoma lost her suit.
- She's out of the tube, but not the ring!
- Oh, Ikoma finally falls in too!
- Oh, Akimoto's out too!
- Oh, she's strong!
- Hoshino's strong!
- Who will win? It's amazing how Rotti survived the attack from these three.
- You're right.
- Roll her over, roll her!
- Woah, she's pushing her!
- No~! Wait!
- Wow, Rotti's still pushing her
Rotti! Wow! Woah!
- No~!
- She's close!
Rotti, Rotti, Rotti!
Rotti! You're amazing!
Sasuga - "As one would have expect! / Great (As we all know) / Indeed, you definitely are amazing
Woah! Sasuga!
- That was amazing!
- Rotti wins the match!
Slipping by herself.
- I lost!
- Wow, she managed to beat them all.
- Well, here we go.
- Akimoto, let me help you out, okay?
Already a process.
Akimoto out.
Woah! You're a mess.
- Hoshino, how about I help you too?
- No, no~!
Sacrifice to Satan.
Wait~!
- Oh, how cute!
- Cute!
I don't want to
- Hoshino, he'll help you take it off.
- Yes, I'll take it off.
Ah! I hate this!
Oh, sexy! Now, you look sexy!
- It's already 3 versus 1, but they still lost~
- How frustrating!
Lame~!
- You guys are lame~
- No way!
- Damn
- This sucks~!
Rotti wins!
The winner for the 2nd round, is Kawamura! She can now relax herself!
The 3rd match includes the new center, Fukugawa together with these three members.
Wouldn't it be nice if the Center herself does the skydive, right?
- Right, right. You guys can actually do her in right from the start.
- You have a point.
Oh, her face suddenly changed~
The Holy Mother is angry.
Well, before we actually start the next game,
...it looks like the winners are already enjoying themselves.
- They really are, aren't they?
- Ah! You're right!
- Nanamin~
- Well, if you look at it, Hoshino, it was rather fun, right?
- Yes, it was fun until after Rotti dropped me out of the ring.
- Ah, I see.
- Rotti really did go for it.
- Oh, they're ready, they're starting.
Well, it looks like everything is set up and ready. So...
Hakkeyoi~
- Nokotta!
- Go!
- Woah!!!
- That's dangerous!
Ikuta bouncing off.
- Ikuta became the target!
- No wait, Ikuta still hasn't fall out!
- Ikuta fell out. Oh, Nishino's the one that attacked her!
- Nishino, you're amazing!
Nishino attacks like a cannon!
Mai Mai! Mai Mai's the new target!
- Maybe this is happening because of what I told earlier...
- Oh, no!
- "If Fukugawa wins, wouldn't it be nice?,"
- Like that.
- They're teaming and forcing Fukugawa out of the ring!
- You're right.
- Mai Mai~
- 1 versus 2? It looks like the reds are eliminating the green one.
Pinch!
- Mai Mai, don't lose!
- This is bad.
- Mai Mai don't give up!
- Oh, there it is! Noujo is finally using her hand!
And, and look, Nishino too!
Nishino also attacks Noujo.
Nishino is now focusing Noujou!
No one is still out. No one has fallen in yet!
- Stand up!
- Oh, all of them are back on their feet!
Fierce Battle.
Okay, let's start again! Nokotta~!
- Good luck!
- Go!
- Mai Mai, that's dangerous
- Good luck!
- Ah! Ah!
- Oh, Noujo, Noujo is using her hand again!
- Ah, Ami!
- And Nishino uses her too!
- Ah! She fell!
- Ah! Which one? Who will fall first?
- Oh, this is bad!
Oh, she... almost fell!
Nana survives.
Oh, she... survived!
She almost fell!
But still, she really almost fell out!
- Oh, she's grabbing her hand!
- Oh that's great! Noujo wins the match! Noujou you win!
Well, Noujo is really strong, right?
- Oh... oh... oh...
- Sasuga!
Note: Kiai da! - "Used in martial arts for short yell
when performing an attack move!"
Kiai da! Kiai da! Kiai da! Kiai da!
Kiai da!
Kyoko! Kyoko! Kyoko! Kyoko! Kyoko!
Note: Kyoko - "Japanese female free-style wrestler"
Kyoko!
- Oh, she's finally here.
- Let me help you out.
Not waiting for answers.
- Oh, leave it. Let's leave her like that.
- How cute!
- She looks cute!
- Now, you're finally out. She's out!
Fukugawa saved.
Oh, how sexy! Sexy!
Well, Ikuta actually fell out after these three ganged up on her.
- That's right.
- Then both of them, Noujo and Nishino started to focus on Fukugawa.
- That's right! That's exactly it.
That's right, I actually thought maybe I can finish them.
Doing her best to win.
- This was so unexpected coming from Nishino.
- Ikuta, you became a victim too, right?
- It's really interesting!
- Earlier, when you almost fell, you even reached your hands out.
- It looked like you really don't want to get wet.
- But you know, I really enjoyed it! It's fun!
-  Huh, it's fun?
- Yes!
A very fun battle.
- Well, that's good then. There are only 3 people left.
- Yes.
- Since there are 3 people participating, this could be the same like earlier 2 versus 1.
- That's for sure.
Looking at your figure, it looks like you can easily drop all of them on this match.
- You're under training right?
- Yes, I am.
Sayuri is macho.
Well as you see, 3 people will face each other for the final round of the Beach Tube Sumo Game.
How will this end? Who will win?
- This is really like a real battle for all 3 sides, right?
- You're right.
Well, if they actually run away from each other, all of them will be out at the same time.
Hoping for a miracle.
- They need to fight.
- They don't really have a choice anyway...
- They really need to fight.
Okay, let's start. Ready...
Hakkeyoi... Nokotta!
- Just now, it looks like Inoue is the target!
- Inoue! Oh!
- Oh, this is bad! Matsumura... Matsumura...
- Ah! Matsumura fell, she fell!
- This is unexpected, Inoue is strong, she's really strong!
- Oh, her feet! She's using her feet!
- She's using her legs as her weapon!
- This is shocking, this is great!
Inoue wins the match!
- She's really amazing!
- That was unexpected!
- That was great!
- Earlier, she...
- You guys deserved it!
- Enough!
- Oh, you didn't remove the tube, that's great.
- Alright, thank you very much!
Welcome.
You're suppose to take it off here.
A mess.
Alright, please come here. Quickly.
- It's alright, it's alright.
- Wait, my head!
Merciless spinning.
No~!
Okay, that's pretty!
I'm sorry, that was rather difficult to take off compared to earlier.
- But, I think it did worked out well.
- Well.
- This is really unexpected.
- You're right. That was unexpected.
Somehow, right after both of you attacked Inoue...
- she just started doing...
- What is that?
- That's really scary!
Macho Inoue
She was just like a guy in a fight.
You really want to finish them all, right?
- Well, they did underestimated me, so yes.
- We're so sorry!
Pretending to be weak.
Handshake Survival in Guam!
A handshake event?
In order to make, Nogizaka46 known around the world, the members will also need to gather fans from Guam.
From this onward, each member will need to introduce themselves in "English" under the presence of these foreigners.
The most interesting member will receive the handshake from the foreigner and will become his Oshimen and shall win the game.
- Well, would you look at the table next to us.
- They are completely relaxed.
- Kazumin!
- They're really enjoying it, right?
Relaxed.
Takayama with Wakatsuki, huh.
- How nice~
- We're going shopping after this!
- How mean.
- Shopping, huh? Well, that's nice.
Full vacation.
The first member is Akimoto. Will she be able to introduce herself in English?
My name is, Manatsu. Manatsu, say?
- Manatsu.
- Ah, thank you, thank you.
- Oh, nice.
I'm the most beautiful girl.
They're laughing.
- How about you try showing them your "Zukkyun"?
- Uhm, how do I do this...
- She's really showing it, huh...
- Sniper...
- I'm a sniper!
- I'm a sniper? What was that?
- Oh, that's good. Great!
Your heart...
Zukkyun!
Oh? Wasn't that great? Right?
- Thank you! Thank you!
Following up with another English introduction, is Ikuta.
Hello, my name is Erika Ikuta. I'm 19 years old.
And, I like singing! (ahhh)
Yay!!!
- Why don't you perform that song?
- Yeah, that you should try that song.
I like songs from Finland.
- Finnish Songs.
- Songs from Finland, yes.
~Finland Song - Ievan Polka~
Isn't this nice?
- Wouldn't this leave a very good impression?
- This is good.
Coming next is Ikoma Rina's English Introduction.
My name is RIna Ikoma.
I have a baby face, but...
I'm 20 years old.
- She told them she's 20, huh?
- I'm a girl, okay?
- Well, uhm. Here's a gag.
- Oh, she's doing a gag. Wouldn't this be great?
- I'll make you guys smile, big smile, okay?
3, 2, 1...
Komanechi!
Note: Komanechi - "Famous gag created by comedian Beat Takeshi"
Why?
- Oh my!
- Thank you very much!
- Wow, look at their reactions. Well done.
- That was dangerous!
Next up doing her English Introduction is Eto.
- Since they are many, I'll approach them.
- Oh, how nice! Doing it very close, huh.
- My name is, Misa Eto.
- I'm 23 years old.
- Wh-what?
- Oh..?
- She wants them to be familiar with her.
- She's doing handshake events for them.
Political Campaign?
Things should be going well, since this is a handshake event, right?
- She's really trying to get close with them...
- This really seems that this is your specialty.
I, uhm... I like you~
Target found.
- I like you!?
- Wait a minute! Why are you only focusing on one of them?
- That's great though.
- She's cheating! Definitely! Oh...!?
- Oh? She's really fishing him now.
Seducing as her tactic.
- Alright, time's up! Finish!
Wasn't that pretty good?
Can Saito Asuka introduce herself in English?
Okay. start!
Hello.
My name is, Asuka Saito.
- Asuka... Saito
- Thank you~
I'm very dark.
"I'm a very bad person"
Very dark!?
Huh? Dark? What do you mean by, dark?
I like... uhm, I like...
- I like crazy!
- "I like crazy"? I love crazy~!
I like insane people.
- What do you mean by that?
- I'm finished!
- Why did you say you like weird people?
- Was it because you are dark?
Coming up with her English Introduction, Sakurai Reika.
My name is, Sakurai Reika.
I'm, I'm... the Captain...
And?
...but,
But?
...I'm very, "Ponkotsu~"
Note: Ponkotsu - Slang term for "airhead"
- What's "Ponkotsu"?
- Can you explain "Ponkotsu" in English?
Uhm...
My inside head~
"My"...huh? My...?
My head is, Popcorn!
The inside of my head is made of popcorn.
- What was that statement all about?
- Why did she said that?
Saying "My head is popcorn", how do you think they will understand that?
- I like popcorn!
- Well, he's...
You're mistaken, he just like the popcorn.
Next up is Nishino's Appeal Time.
My name is Nanase.
Nanase...
Seven is...
Nana, is Seven.
- Lucky Seven!
- Isn't "Nana" in Japanese?
Seven in Japanese is "Nana"
Oh, I see.
- You should tell them your favorites.
- Ah, I love animals.
- "I love Animal."
- Somehow, it does look like she really like it.
Note: Shitara is still referring the "Animal" to the former Japanese wrestler Hamaguchi.
Acting like an animal?
- What animals do you like?
- I love snakes!
She said, she love snakes.
- We have got a lot of snakes on Guam.
He said, there's a lot of snakes here.
It looks like it became a hot topic here.
Finally, the center, Fukugawa. Will she succeed introducing herself in English?
Hello~
- Hello.
My name is Mai.
My hobby is drawing.
I can draw faces.
- "Face Picture"?
- Face Picture
- Okay, good.
She mistook "seconds" as "minutes"
10 Minutes
10 Minutes.
- I can...
- "Juu!?"
A huge difference.
10 minutes! I...
I can draw within 10 minutes.
- I can do it in 10 minutes.
This will take 10 minutes?
So, this will take 10 minutes?
- Right, start!
Unaware.
- Eh? 10 seconds... right?
- It's 10 seconds!
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1,...
Okay, time's up!
- Is it complete?
- Is it? Oh, how nice.
- Yes, it is.
- Who did she draw?
- Oh?
Alright, that was good, she did it.
This time, it's Hoshino. What kind of appeal will she go for?
- Hi~
- Hi.
- My name is, Minami.
- Minami.
Smile~ Love~!
- Ah, how cute!
- Oh, that's nice.
- That's really nice.
- Looks like it's working.
- They're smiling.
- Okay, let's go on.
Why don't you tell them your favorite food?
I love, bread~!
- You are bread~?
- "You are bread"!?
Are you guys, bread?
- What was that?
- Uhm, I'm sorry~
Let's go bread~!
Let's go to the bread!
- You're inviting the bread?
- That was interesting.
Next up is Hori's English Introduction Appeal Time.
- Hello~
- Hello.
- How are you~?
- Good.
- Good, good, you?
I'm fine. My name is, Miona Hori.
I'm from Japan.
My favorite foods are Steak and Sushi~
Do you know Sushi?
I love "Uni". Do you know Uni?
Never ending questions.
This is great, she tells them what she likes then
she asks them if they like it too.
Eh... I have no more.
Quick Situation.
- You have that special skill where you blink your eyes fast, right?
- Ah, look at me.
3, 2, 1...
Oh, nice! Nice!
The last one is Matsumura, what kind of appeal will she do?
- My name is, Mattsun.
- Mattsun.
I, I'm an artist under Sony Music.
- Without a doubt, she just said she's working at Sony.
- Sony, yes.
My job is, My job is acting, singing and modeling.
- What about your nickname?
- Huh? My nickname?
Why did you do "What's my nickname?" to Himura-san?
My nickname is, "Sayuringo".
- Sayu-Apple?
- "Sayu-Apple"!?
- It's not related right?
- Sayu-Apple?
You should choose me, because I'm very very pretty~!
Ah, that's a good one. That last one was very good.
- This isn't like your usual event, right?
- It's like your doing again your first handshake event.
Okay, let's start.
So, who will he choose?
It's now the foreigners turn. Which member did appeal to him most?
Ah, so..? so..? so...? Oh?
This is scary~
- He chose her!
- I did it!
You've already fallen for her in the beginning right?
- No.
- No, really? That isn't the case?
Strategy Worked.
Next up, whose member managed to get a fan in Guam?
Okay, please proceed.
He's not even looking at me at all.
- He's not even seeing Akimoto.
Invisible?
- He's not looking.
His eyes are not even staring at me.
So, who'll he choose?
He's already chosen!
- Oh!?
- Why!? How come!?
- I always have popcorn in my head...
- Ah, the popcorn.
- Was it because he really likes Popcorn?
- That's the reason!?
And the last member that won the heart of the foreigners is...?
Akimoto...? Oh?
- Somehow, he's moving into the middle. Oh?
- Is it me?
- Huh? Hoshino!?
- Wait! Isn't this strange!?
- I chose her because of her smile.
- Oh, her smile huh.
He says your smile is beautiful.
- Smile~
- Ahaha.
Smile~
SasugaPosts - Where all cool stuff can be found.
Your dream haven for 48 & 46G stuff.