SasugaPosts
Continuing last weeks episode, is the 14th Single Campaign in Guam!
Each member has to participate on a challenge and if they win, they'll be awarded with prizes.
And the final member that lost the challenge will be chosen as the final participant for the 4200m skydive!
Previously, the members that lost the match on the Beach Tube Sumo Battle Royal Contest and...
... Handshake Survival Contest.
With these 8 members, what kind of challenge awaits for them?
BANANAMAN
SHITARA OSAMU
HIMURA YUKI
Okay, Himura-san. Please announce the next game!
- Okay, here we go!
Guam Point Competition!
Survive the streets of Guam!
- What's this?
- What? What?
- Starting now, all 8 of you need to explore the city.
- Sounds good! Let's go!
- The last time we're on Macau, it's called Macau Points.
- Since now, we're on Guam, we're calling it Guam Points, you get it, right?
- That's right. It's like that.
- During that time, what's the purpose of those points again?
- Ikuta, can you remember?
Nogizakatte, Doko!? Episodes 124 - 126
Ah! It's for, making Bananaman-san happy...
- That was nice! Here's 1 Guam Point for you.
- Eh!? Too fast! That was too fast!
The member that can make things interesting while they're walking will be awarded with Guam Points.
After they've reached the final destination, the two people with the highest point wins!
- Before we start, everyone should be happy, okay?
- Don't be too quiet when we're walking at the destination, okay?
- Do your best, okay?!
- Let's enjoy this trip!
- It looks like Matsumura's not even listening at the situation, minus 5 Guam points for you.
- No! That's not it!
- That costs you 5 points you know.
- Naa-chan...
- There's also this kind of pattern, right?
- What?
- I just want to protect Naa-chan from the bugs.
- Even if there are insects, it has nothing to do with the camera, right?
- That's right!
Grabbing every chance.
I'll give Nishino 1 Point, while Matsumura -1 point.
Nishino's the worst, she basically doesn't care!
- Ah, how pretty.
- Ouch, the thorns...
- Oh, I got caught in the bush...
- Are you okay?
- What should I do?
- Oh! 1 point for you.
Wait a minute, if you include those things, then no one would really know how to get the points.
- Minus 10 Guam Points!
- I'm involved too!? Why are you making me do this?
- Everyone must be very thirsty and wanted to drink beverages and eat Ice Cream, right?
- We want to!
- Oh! What's this! Seriously! Shitara,
what will you guys do?
That was really dangerous! Everyone, be careful!
Situations like this will appear often, you guys should be alert. It's because he really likes doing it.
Favorite thing.
You guys should get everything ready.
- What's that place? It somehow looks like an amusement park.
- It's an amusement park, right?
- Oh, so that's the one that flies huh?
- That's what I'm talking about everyone.
Presenting one of Guam's popular attractions, "The Slingshot".
SLINGSHOT GUAM
Speed:160 km/h Elevation:70m Cost:20$
A reverse bungee with an elevation of 70 m under speeds around 160 km/h!
Who do you think will be interested in doing this challenge?
- What about Asuka? Asuka?
- Eh, really?
I think Asuka really wants to do it.
Forced Nomination.
- She's always quiet and we never really see her shout, I think everyone will be interested.
- Oh, I see. Good point.
- If the fans saw her unexpected reaction, I think that would be really good.
- We understand, that's a good point.
- 5 Guam Points for you.
- Oh, I did it!
- Want to go for it?
- What do you think, Asuka?
- Why~?
- It looks like your doing it alone, yeah, right. Since no one volunteers.
- Eh!?
- Okay, that's settled, one more!
- One more person needs to go.
She's really doing her best these days, I think if Miona jumps...
...she'll be able to bring more fans for Nogizaka46.
-That's right. Very Nice. Plus 5 Guam points for you.
Abusing her senior status.
- Okay Hori, go!
- Eehh!!!?
- Both of you go!
- Well, then.
- Both of you are selected!
- Saito Asuka and Hori let's go!
Well, that's how it is! Both of these selected
members shall challenge the ride!
- It looks like they'll start soon enough!
- Good luck! - Okay, let's start!
The Next Generation Aces.
- The Next Generation Aces, huh?
- Next Generation Aces! Good Luck! You guys can do it!
- Because of her...
- That was nice.
As you see, this time, we're actually given a special permission to operate this button that will let you jump.
- Eh..?
- That's really awesome!
CCD Camera - "Charged Coupled Device Camera"
Video from CCD Camera.
- Alright!
- No~! Stop~!!!
- Both of you, get ready!
- Woah! Good luck! You guys can do it!
- Hori!
- Why don't you say something?
- I'm fine!
- "I'm fine"? Plus 1 point for you!
- Asuka-chan, what about you?
- Say something!
- I- I'll do my best~
- 3... 2.. Oh, they've already started.
- It already started.
- He pushed it too fast!!!
- How is it up there?
- 3... 2.. Oh, they've already started.
- It already started.
- He pushed it too fast!!!
- How is it up there?
- 3... 2.. Oh, they've already started.
- It already started.
- He pushed it too fast!!!
- How is it up there?
- How does it look like up there?
- What's happening up there?
- How is it?
- Hori?
- Hori, why don't you say something!
- This looks really amazing.
Is Hori under meditation?
- Asuka-chan, what about you?
- How is it?
- Is it scary? How?
- They're not giving any comments.
- This is bad, should we try this one more time?
- It's because Shitara-san made a mistake in the countdown.
- I'm sorry. How is it?
Hey, how is it?
They haven't really said anything about it.
- Since both of them have tried their best riding it,
I'll give them 15 Guam Points.
- What do you think?
- Isn't this great?
- It's great!
- How nice, both of them got 15 Guam Points.
- They really deserve 15 Guam Points.
- 15 Guam plus it's summer overall.
- Oh, they're finally here!
- How does this look?
- What happened here?
- They're not moving at all.        - How are they?
- Eh? Isn't this really bad?
- This looks really bad.
- What's going on here? Huh!?
- Oh no! This is bad!
Miona... Miona is...
Fainted.
- So that's why they have no reaction.
- Are they really okay?
Hori... Hori and Asuka-chan, are..
- You guys did it!
- Are you guys alright?
- Was it scary? Is it really scary?
- Which part is the scariest, the launch?
- Somehow, the moment it explodes...
- Explodes?
- Oh?
- Somehow...
- I never imagined that I'll be doing this in Guam...
- Oh, really?
- You didn't like it at all?
- Asuka-chan too?
- I-It was f-fun...~
- It was "fun"!?
Quite an unexpected reaction.
- Eh? What do you mean?
- Why does she say she enjoyed it?
- Okay, +5 Macau, no, I mean...
- +5 Guam for you, alright?
- Actually, the time you guys were thrown up there, I gave both of you guys +15 Guam.
Given points as a reward.
- Ah!
- Those points were very big, you know!
- Yes, those are large points, indeed.
- Well, right now, you've got 20 Guam Points.
- How about this?
- Fukugawa and Himura-san, doing it?
- Me!?
Unexpected Proposal
- Wait a minute...!
- How about both of you this time?
- Why am I suddenly involved in this?
- Well, it does seem you really want to do it...
- It's alright for Fukugawa though...
- Why should I!?
- Your even staring at me!
They've given, OK! Let's start then, Fukugawa.
- Me, Why, me...?
- Himura-san, Himura-san...
- I'll give you +5 Guam, alright?
Fukagawa, let's go! Fukagawa!
- How the heck did I get involve in this situation?
- Are you sure? Eh?
- Yes, yes. It looks like you want to try it anyway.
With that, Himura and Fukugawa will challenge!
Fukagawa, your face looks bad.
- Are you going to cry?
- I-I'm fine...
Are you alright?
- This restraint is really small, you know!
Himura-san...Himura-san...
Face won't fit?
- It's locked? - Himura-san... Himura-san... your face!
- Yes?
- +1 Guam, for you!
- Wait a minute, is this really okay?
- He looks like a child.
- His face, his face...
- Himura-san, your face!
Seriously?
- Eh...? Is this how it should be?
-That's definitely how it should be!
Starting from here, a problem occurred!
The CCD Camera that was suppose to film them is broken!
We would like to apologize for this incident, please watch them without the CCD Cameras.
- Fukugawa!
- Yes?
- Please give out a few words!
I LOVE GUAM!
- "I love Guam"
- You also want the 14th Single to be a success, right?
- Yes, I want that too...
Then, why don't you ask everyone for support?
- Please support "Harujion ga Saku Koro"!
- Oh, that's good. Himura-san!
- Yes!?
- Eh?!
- Your face is still stuck?
Is your face, still stuck?
- Ah...! He started it too fast, again!
- This is not good!
When I was still asking "Is your face, still stuck?"
he pressed the button!
- This is bad!      - Himura-san's face!
- This is not good!
- It's really high, isn't it?
- It's high...
How is it? How is it there?
- How is it up there?
- It looks like, Himura-san's really scared, right?
- He does look like it.
- Oh my, this isn't good.
- MaiMai's crying!     - Himura-san...
Himura-san, Himura-san...
Himura-san... I'll give you, +10 Guam, okay?
- It's because his face looks really funny!
- Himura-san's really bad.
Did I just do this!? You're scary! This is scary!
Do you guys want to try again? One more?
- Wait! Wait! Wait! I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
- Huh? What?
- I'm really sorry!
- One more.
- Wait, wait, wait!
- Shitara-san!
No! No! You're lying!
You did say, you want do one more.
So I told him.
- Scary!
- No! No! No! No! No!
MaiMai, hang in there!
- MaiMai, FIGHT-O~!!!
- Fukagawa, you want to stop?
- Do you want to stop, Fukagawa?
- W-what should I do, for you to stop?
- Oh, woah woah woah~
Oh no...  It looks like I accidentally pressed the button.
- You did!
There was suppose to be a warning if it's about to start.
But, you see that I accidentally pressed the button.
- That didn't happen!
- You're clearly lying!
- We clearly see you press the button.
- You didn't accidentally pressed it.
This... is really bad!
MaiMai hang in there!
- Since it's already like this, I'll give them +20 Guam each.
- You really should!
- You're right.
MaiMai...!
Himura-sa... Himura-san... Himura-san... Himura-san...!
Himura-san! Since your face is really funny,
I'll give you another 5 Guam points!
- Poor MaiMai!
- No more! This is really impossible, I can't do this anymore!
- Eh? What do you mean?
- I'm really serious! Please stop this already!
- Fukugawa, do you really want no more?
- Do you want to go for one more?
- No! No! This is really impossible!
- Please stop this.
Okay, please get ready!
WHY ARE YOU DOING IT AGAIN!?
- But you said you want to do it again...
Going for the 3rd time?
Why!?
I'm really sorry, Shitara-san!
- Stop! Stop!
- This is impossible!
- I told you this is impossible!
- I already told him to stop.   -  Eh?
- Okay, please come here.
- MaiMai~
- MaiMai!
- You know, this is...
- She's angry!
- H-huh...? You're really scary, Fukugawa. This is the first time I've seen you so angry.
- She was really angry, you know!
- How is it? Is it really scary?
- Devil...
- You two?
- He's a devil, right?
- Evil!
- You two?
- You're evil!
- "You two?"
- Evil!
- Evil....!
- What are we talking about again?
- But seriously, that was really scary!
- Really?     - Yes!
- Is it much more intense the 2nd time?
- It was terrifying! I thought you were still lying when you told him to stop.
- Right? Seriously!   - Really.
- Well, since you guys did it twice, I'll give you 1 Guam points each.
- That's too little!
That's too small!
SasugaPosts - Where all cool stuff can be found
Your dream haven for 48 & 46 Group, content!
Right here, is a very famous place in Guam where one can enjoy several shops, restaurants and other stuff, San Vitores Road!
San Vitores Road
- This is Guam's Main Street, right?
- This road, right?
- Right here!
- A lot of good things can be found here.
- Ah, how nice.
Since you guys are here now, you can buy different souvenirs, such as bags and other stuff...
- We want too!
- Isn't that a great idea?
- Himura-san will pay for it...
- Oh!!! Alright!
Wait a minute, wait a minute!
- He'll give a maximum of 80k yen per person!
- Alright!   - Don't say "Alright", like you mean it!
What? Huh? What? Oh?
- Aren't those ice creams?
Winners from the previous challenge.
- Eh!? That looks delicious! It's really good!
- Where did you buy that?
- Right, there~!
Oh, that ice cream shop, huh?
- Oh, do you guys want to eat ice cream?        - Yes!
- Well, then. Let's go!
- It's good that you guys are having fun.
- You know our group, everyone's been crying and stuff.
- These three people are the ones that cried earlier.
- It's because, us three are popular, right?
Chosen as the most popular by the locals.
- Ah, that's right! The three of them did win the contest, right?
- It's only because they're not really good with the foreigners.
- Oh, really?
- Okay, I'll give you guys 1 Guam point each!
- They don't need that!    - Yay!
- Okay, let's go buy the ice cream.
- Alright, let's go!
Right here, is Dolce Frutti Gelateria.
DOLCE FRUTTI GELATERIA
All their products uses ingredients to make Gelato
which originated from Italy.
A store that uses imported ingredients which came from Italy in order to bring the taste of the real Gelato.
- That looks good!
- It looks really delicious!
- How nice!
- Oh my!
- Ah, it looks delicious!
- How nice!
- Mango and Raspberries!
Okay, you can wait there. We'll be eating all together.
- Oh, thank you. Yay!
- What's that?
- Well, this is, Watermelon and Coconut flavor.  - Oh, Watermelon?
- Ice Cream!
Oh, isn't that nice.
Yum! It's delicious! Like, American!
- Minus 10 Guam!
- Eh!? Why did you..!?
- I just said that we would eat all together.
- Ah, that's the worst.    - No way!    - Please wait outside.
It's already over for you. You're already losing.
- Matsumura, you're really waiting for it, right?
- Yeah~!
- You're eating on a cone?
- Yes, I am.
- Looks delicious.
- What's that? There are 3 flavors?
- It's 3 flavors!
- W-What are the flavors?
- Raspberry, Cookie and Coconuts.
- That's nice. They keep telling the coconut is really good.
- I think it really is tasty.
Is coconut flavor really that delicious?
- How is it?
- Yum! It's really tasty!    - Really?
- Minus 10 Guam for you, okay?
- Eh, why?
I just said we'll eat together.
- He's the worst, right?
- Please wait outside.
- No no no.
Really...
- Well, you know I, did told them..
- Oh, Asuka-chan...
- Thank you~!
- I mean, Nishino.
- This is Raspberry and Peanut flavor.
Peanuts? It's the first time I've heard peanuts.
You like eating peanuts?
- Yes, I like eating them.   - Is it good?
- Yes!
Raspberry sounds tasty too.
- Can you tell us the taste?
- No, I want to eat it together with everyone.
Alright, I'll give you, uh, plus, +2 Guam points, okay?
- How come she's so sensitive?
- She's very attentive, isn't she?. She's really great.
Itadakimasu~!
- This is very nice!
- It's delicious!
- Woah, it's good!
- It's tasty!
- I think mine's the best!   - What flavor is that?
- Eh?  - What's the taste like?
I'm not telling!
- Himura-san, what are you doing?
what is that? You're really funny.
- I'll give you +1 Guam, okay?
- Alright!
- This place is really nice isn't it?
- I agree.  - Oh, it looks great.
- Those branded clothes...
- How nice!
Ikuta, do you also love branded items, like that?
- Well, I don't think I can wear them yet, but I'm willing to.
- I think you can wear them!
- I think you can!   - No, I can't...
- But it's possible for you to buy it, right?
She wanted to try, but she don't want to buy it.
- I can't buy it. Ah, Why did I said it like that.
- We had one like this in Shizuoka, right?
- Eh!? Ah, that place!    - It's the same in Shizuoka.
- I believe both were build at the same time.
- Really?
UNDERWATER WORLD
- You girls, love dolphins, right?
-They're cute aren't they?
You guys know "Todo", right?
Todo - Name of a Sea Lion Mascot
- Oh here it is! I'll give you +10 Guam, then.
- Alright, I did it!
- Shitara-san! You keep giving points to Himura-san!
- Himura-san's not fair...
- Don't give him more points.
- It's because he imitated "Todo".
- Well, I'll give you too but no one wants to do "Todo", right? Todo!
This is a chance, you know. Todo!
- It looks like, Nishino wants to do it, right now.
- Alright, Todo!
She's thinking, "Hey, why should I!?"
"Why do I need to do that?"
- The wind here is really fresh, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Alright, everyone should enjoy the wind.
- That's right, everyone should try Guam's Wind.
- Let's all enjoy this wind.
- This is Guam's Wind.
- Puu~!!!
- Oh, here he goes again!
There he goes!
- He's doing Miki... Miki-san.
- That's right!
How does the "Air Game Pressure" look like again?
Pu~!!!
Alright, +10 Guam for you.
- Well, how about you try it?
- Yeah, try it.
Okay, here I go.
Buuu~~!    - Oh, that's great! +10 Guam, for you.
- She did great. She can do it.
Coming up next, a game of death!?
TAGADA AMUSEMENT PARK
The next place they've visited is a place filled with excitement that's gaining a lot of attraction which cannot be found in Japan.
Tagada Amusement Park.
- Alright, everyone. Take a look at this, "Tagada Disco", they said this is really interesting.
- Oh, what's this?
- They said, this is their special attraction here.
- Oh, I see.
- Wait, do you guys want to try?
- Yeah, we want to!   - Yeah, we do! We do!
The first ones to challenge Guam's "Tagada Disco" are Akimoto, Ikuta, Ikoma and Fukugawa.
TAGADA DISCO Cost: 12$
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
"Welcome!"
DJ & Machine Operator
"Hello!"
- Hello~!
"Are you guys ready?"
Ah, so he's the one operating it.
"Can you guys speak in English?"
- No!
-"No?"
"Okay then"
"If that's the case, then I'm really sorry about it"
- What's happening?
- What's this?
Oh, it's very fast! It's really fast!
"Okay, let's go!"
It's spinning really fast too!
Are they crying!?
Woah, this is incredible!
Isn't it... spinning too fast!?
Woah, woah! Aki... Akimoto looks amazing!
Akimoto, Akimoto! I'll give you +10 Guam, okay?
- Very nice!
- She's really swinging like that.
IKUTA
Huh? Ikuta, Ikuta, I'll also give you +10 Guam, okay?
- Iku-chan's in danger!
- Ikuta looks really bad! Ikuta, looks really in danger!
IKUTA
Ah! Ikuta will fall, Ikuta is falling!
- Hang in there!
- Iku-chan, hang in there!
You can do this!
"Hang in there!"
- Ikuta looks really bad.
What is this?
"Okay, I'm sorry. I'll be serious now, One!"
Ah, they fell! Ikuta fell!
All of them really fell out!
What is this?
"Slower?"
- "Do you guys want to do it slowly?"
- Woah, amazing!
"Here it goes! Wooo~"
He's making fun of them.
- They also need it enjoy it.
- Oh, Ikoma that's very good! Nice!
Ikoma, I'll give you +10 Guam!
Ikuta face, Ikuta's face looks really bad. It looks really bad.
- Ikuta~!
- Iku-chan!
Ikuta, hang in there!
Ikuta...
"Hang in there everyone! Why aren't you guys falling?"
Ikuta fell! Ikuta...you deserve +10 Guam points for that!
Ah, they decided to help her.
CAMERAMAN
Seriously, what is this?
Oh, over there! The cameraman...
CAMERAMAN
Camera-san, I'll give you +10 Guam too!
Camera-san, take care of yourself!
CAMERAMAN
- Are you guys okay?    - Iku-chan's face...
- Her face...
- Her face... she looks like a kid who lost in a fight.
- What's up with that?
Angry?
Is she being reborn-ed or what?
- Seriously, what's up with your face?
- You guys are amazing!
- Are you okay?
- This, isn't this great?
- That was interesting.
- Interesting?
- You guys are drenched in sweat.
- Yeah, we really are.
- So that's why it has a protective fence! I didn't realize it would shake like that!
- It's really scary, right?
As a matter of fact,  while we're watching, we can clearly see that you guys are getting thrown out.
Yes, it did also happen.
What's with you making those faces?
- What's wrong?
- Why are you...?
- Are you angry?
- You're angry aren't you?
- I'm not angry.
- "I'm not angry"?
- This is nice, since you don't hate it, +10 Guam for you.
- Very nice, Ikuta.
The next challengers are these 4.
Oh! Here it is! It's starting!
- Hang in there~
- Wow! Amazing!
Wow! Wow! This is amazing!
Isn't this bad?
Nishino is in danger!
Nishino's not holding the handle!
Wow! This is really bad!
Okay, since you guys look really bad, Nishino, Matsumura! I'll give both of you +5 Guam Points!
Ah, great! Asuka, Asuka also receives +5 points.
Hori! Hori looks amazing!
How is everyone?
"Please look here!"
"Eh...? How cute!"
"What's this? Why did you guys fall?"
Oh Nice! Oh, everyone fell off the seat!
"Seriously, you guys shouldn't have fall down"
Matsumura and Nishino are rolling...
To everyone who fell just now, they'll receive +3 Guam points each.
I think this is going to be interesting...
- Oh, Mannequin!
- Oh, Nogizaka46's 4th single, right?
Woah! Isn't this too fast? This is really fast you know, right?
Hey!
It's too fast! This is dangerous! Oh..? Oh!?
They'll get thrown out!
They'll get thrown out! Oh... look out! look out!
This is dangerous!
Woah, this is scary!
You guys need to hold it tighter! Tighter!
Watch out! Watch out! This is really dangerous!
Asuka! Asuka looks really small!
They look really desperate! Ah, this looks bad!
"You guys are still not falling?"
Oh!? That's definitely dangerous! Didn't she fall?
Right now, just now, she just fell with her head, right?
Oh, this is amazing, they are all rolling.
Are you okay?
She's definitely in pain, right now.
Ah, watch out! Watch out!
Ah, very nice! Hori! Hori looks interesting!
- Headbang!
- Hori's doing a head-bang, isn't she?
- Okay, come here.
- Great job, everyone.
Everyone was amazing...
- Wow, you guys really sweated a lot, aren't you?
- Sweat...
Wow, Nishino's drenched in sweat.
- That was amazing! How is it, Nishino? You're sweating a lot.
- She's drenched.
Somehow, I don't really understand what just happened.
- You clearly have no idea what will happen up there right?    - I don't.
- Is that so?
The match for Guam Point Survival
Competition is finally finished!
And the two people who collected the highest Guam Points are...
I'll announce the 2nd place, out of the two people that will be elected
- For getting 28 points...
- Oh? Who's that?
Ikoma!
- Yeah!!!
- You made it!
Ikoma!
- You really gained a lot here.     - Here?
- In this, Tagada.
And finally, the member with the most points are...
- Akimoto!
- Alright!!!
- I did it!    - You also gained a lot here.    - Really?
- Yeah, you too!
The positions here have dramatically changed.
Which means, that the remaining members here will still need to do another challenge.
So, who will be the final member that will be elected for the 4200m Skydive...?
SasugaPosts - Where all cool stuff can be found
Your dream haven for 48 & 46 Group, content!
SoftBank's Special Unit, GIGA 200, has finally made their debut performance!
Featuring their debut song with the title of "200 Giga Age-chau"