Tonight show! Nogizaka camping - Part 2!
In previous episode, 4 teams Ikoma - Shiraishi - Sakurai - Matsumura
have prepared ingredients for dinner
Tonight challenge is cooking dinner
Unique food, break all normal rules
how will it tasted?
Teams will grab their ingredients to their area and start cooking
All ingredients have been prepared
Each team can have their own discussion, selecting favourite ingredients
But there is one important rule
You must use the things that you have collected
Each team can use given ingredients here for the dinner
According to the rule, you must use the ingredients that you have collected.
Moreover, you have to make fire by yourself.
At this time, Nishino has joined us
and she goes to Ikoma team
No more, we will start cooking now!
Please!
Come on all of you !
It will be divided into Firelighting division and Cooking division
Cause I don't know how to cook
How much should I put ?
Maybe some of this gag?
It is up to Reika
Despite of confusion in firelightning
But the team has started with a solidarity.
Have you washed your hands?
I have done it
I haven't
You said that you have not wash your hands?
Nope
All teams have been struggled in cooking
But there is one team has started smoothly, it is...
This side seems to be good
Oh! Ikoma!
The fire has been lightening ?
There is some small signs of fire here
Ikoma is so good in camping activities
Nature is the friend of human
Thanks to Ikoma's firelighting techniques
The cooking process of Team Yellow goes smoothly
So what do you cook team Yellow ?
houtou noodle and curry
Oh! When you go camping you must have curry.
Ikoma will cook regular dish in camping, curry.
Furthermore, there are houtou noodle too.
What are you cooking?
Curry
This side also cooks curry.
Have been show their high-level cooking skills
Shiraishi and Takayama led the Blue team make the curry dish.
After that, rice is washed to be cooked. But...
There is no fire here.
Cause they don't have any experience,
Many teams have been struggled with firelighting.
What is this ?
It is the thing to lighten fire.
It is not curry powder ?
Basic mistake?
How can you mistake curry powder with wood ?
But it looks like curry powder.
Let me smell it
Time has passed but there is no progression
When there are 3 teams struggling, Ikoma team
Wow, the fire is big here.
Big fire
Houtou consists of:  pork, onion, carrot, Green onion, pumpkin
Full of fresh vegetables.
At the other side
It is not lighten up ? Is it OK ?
The fire is so weak so no heating.
[Should we have uncle Ikoma to help us]
Should we call the Uncle?
He will make fire for us
No need?
No need !
Despite of strong words, there is no sign of fire.
At this moment
I see that you are having trouble in firelighting
So we have do it for you
Gift from so-kind TKO !
Three team leaders have show up, but
Of course it won't be easy
Some deals
We have done lots of work.
If you show us some interesting things...
Mimicking... anything is acceptable
If we feel good we will give you fire
It is muchaburi, no kindness here.
But, what should 3 members do ?
I need some discussion
Feel free to do it
No discussion?
Oh, you have something ?
There is an idea there.
Blue team captain Sakurai will sacrifice
I will act now
Dancing and $%^%&^#$%^&*
Bizarre
Dancing and bashing
Got fire
Acceptable?
Is it OK ?
So brave
Understood.
I thinks that's enough
After that
impersonate Sakurai Reika
This is Sakurai Reika
Please give us some fire !
Whole team
After the muchaburi, all teams now have fire.
We can start cooking now
Seasoning soup with miso
adding houtou that the team has done
adding fried tofu
The process for making houtou of Ikoma team goes smoothly
After we have fire, immediately go to cooking
We will make stew dishes
She's numerous time making incredible dishes on TV shows
Red team captain - Cooking monster Matsumura
What will this dish become?
Let put pork, beef, chicken into it
You say it for real?
Yes, for real
- Don't put the salmon
- But I like salmon
- So put it in
- Really? Love Marika so much!
Thanks to Matsumura's innovative ideas, team now having troubles.
What can we do with the salmon ?
Things get worse when no one in the team knows how to cook
A disaster is going to appear
Do you know how to process it?
The fish is already processed.
Already
Have no idea with salmon
Beef, pork, chicken, sausaged - all will be mixed together
How can this stew dish be cooked?
Something popped out. It looks dirty
At this time in Shiraishi's team, apart from curry, there is one other dish
Yamane will be baked with salt
Would this rarely made dish bring any good result?
You baked it by yourself?
Kazumi, you know how to use skewer ?
I do not know too
Just do it from the mouth, like arranging flowers
Do it this way
No way, it can't be like arranging flowers
Despite of some trouble in the beginning, baked fish is now completed.
What is the taste ?
- It's good!
- Good?
Success!
Baked yamane with salt is done perfectly
This side, Sakurai team progress goes smoothly after they have fire.
Thanks to Wakatsuki superior cooking skills.
Wow! Looks good!
It must be delicious!
I want to eat this!
Whoa! It looks so good!
It's a little bit overcooked.
Self-harvesting strawberry
Add some self-made jam to the surface of French toast
it becomes a very elegant dish
Rice cooked beautifully
Adding tomato sauce and we have omurice.
Stunning dishes continue to come out.
It can be trusted
At the other side, (Matsumura team) is in turmoil.
Sayurine definitely can't cook
She cooks it in an innovative way
The thing makes Kinoshita worry about Matsumura is...
Little by little
Put milk and butter into the cook
It should be cream stew but
Just mix it together
We can't see what it is.
Milk, butter, meat, all are mixed together
But it looks good, Kazumin?
Looks so yummy.
After that, ignoring the stew on fire
This thing turning into a disaster in later part exactly.
At this time
Houtou of Ikoma team is going to complete
It's tasty
It's similar to my mother cooking
Your mother cooks this often ?
Yes, in the dinner time the smell spreads.
This smell exactly.
You have some tears in your eyes
You missed her?
Yes, so much !
You want to meet mom?
I really want to!
ears from Ikoma adding some country souls to the houtou
MHand-made houtou is completed
Curry from Shiraishi team is going to complete
Adding bean sauce and pepper
What is the result?
Delicious!
It is good!
Put some soy sauce into
Well done
Absolutely pleasing
Each team completes dishes
Only Matsumura left
Can it be completed?
Making French toast using this, adding butter and it's delicious
What about the stew?
Apart from stew food, we have baked food too
French toast and other things from Matsumura team made people worried.
And it's the time for the Cooking Monster
I want to do something
What do you want?
Ohm... just cook it with milk
Once in a lifetime, yakisoba with milk
What will the taste be ?
All in?
Why do you make yakisoba too?
Milk, what the hell is that?
Milk poured
What are you cooking ?
Are you nuts?
Who cooks yakisoba with milk?
After that, adding mayonnaise and salt freely.
- Maybe those things go well together
- Hope they are
It's like Carbonara
It ain't jambon (ham)?
It can be anything
Skipping petty things
You want to become a genius or a dummy girl ?
Miso with milk, an unique dish has been invented.
Continuation
Cooking monster defeated TKO !
It's time to judge Yellow team and Blue team
Starting with Yellow Team
Please introduce your dish
We made houtou from the noodle before.
It's there
The quality seems to be good
Main ingredient is houtou noodle
Ikoma team has done 4 yummy dishes
What the taste would be?
Yummy!
Yummy... let's eat
It's really similar to the restaurant
Praises!
Up to the green team
The fruit you harvest is
Strawberry
Using strawberry, we made jam, French toast
Those dishes show your feminism
It's different from baking using kitchen foil
Implying 3 people
Sakurai team with strawberries as the main component has cooked 6 high-level dishes
What is this white thing?
It's yaourt
- Yaourt?
- Yes
Success!
So delicious
Really, really good.
There is so much yaourt left, just try it
Make the most out of main ingredients, Sakurai team achieved great success
The next is
Teams have trouble in cooking process
Along with many good dish
I smell something really terrible
Which dish
It really is
What smell is this?
It's worth waiting
First try it with baked fish from Shiraishi team
Starting with this
Delicious
- So good!
- Thanks so much!
Time for the curry
Wonderful!
Really love it!
Eating this and we will be full.
It's inevitable
Scary dinner by Matsumura
This side does not have any specular smell
It means？
This smell still punching into my face
Just start eating!
Looks like you are preparing to play roller coaster
It's became donburi (rice and foods mixed together)
It really is!
Take a look!
It's better to eat with rice.
The very new stew don
What is the taste?
Is it delicious?
The source of the strange smell is here
How can it be?
What is this smell?
It smells like some new building.
Why?
Please don't say that.
Really is it.
It came from the stew
It comes from the stew that the team left it on huge fire
Just drink some overheated milk
It stuck in to my mouth
One more
Yakisoba with milk and miso
TKO has been defeated with the unique milky-yakisoba
Are you alright?
Terrible!
It can't be
The ingredients did not go well
Miso and..........
Dish left people become breathless
What are the reactions from the chefs?
The miso is so bold
It's not important for us to judge it now
You leave me breathless
How is it? Say something
Scary!
We tried our best
Thank you ! We knew that but
it's not enough to make a good dish.
The legend of Cooking Monster Matsumura still continues
Matsumura is a cooking monster, isn't she?
I'm tired with Sayurin
Firstly she said we cook stew dishes.
And then she baked sweet potatoes
Marika , you also do not know how to cook too.
Yuttan so...
What is this?
Lost solidarity
It's really considering when Mattsun didn't wash her hands before cooking
Wait a second, this time is to enhance the solidarity, isn't it?