Nogami46subs
DON!
Now starting Nogizaka Kojichuu and we're Bananaman. Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu
Here is Nogizaka-chan~!
Okay~~ Onegaishimasu~~
Okay here it comes...
TSUN!
Ahhh...
Just like Matsumura
Members held an inside joke monomane convention of
other members within the group
First, let's see some Monomane from last week.
An example of Takayama Kazumi's hands when she's noisy
Ah she widened her legs
Ah please listen. Before this, Jo-san and I ate together right...
So
I asked for Lunch Set A
I wonder if it's okay?
When I decided, the clerk said "That.. is fine"
and at the end Lunch Set E came out instead
Next is Wakatsuki
The reaction given
The reaction that Akimoto Manatsu gives when she feels trouble or embarrassment
when truly feeling troubled or embarrassed by Akimoto Manatsu
I didn't expect to see 20 minutes of Akimoto
Ehhh~~!
Looks similar.
Last is Akimoto
13th single "Ima, Hanashitai Dareka Ga Iru" verse 2
"Ima, Hanashitai Dareka Ga Iru" 2nd verse. Robotic like movements by Ikuta Erika
Ikuta Erika's quite like robotic dance moves
"Ima, Hanashitai Dareka Ga Iru"
She moves like that?
I kinda want to see the real deal
So let us now continue
to start things up, we have these four
So let's start immediately. Here you go
Takayama Kazumi carefully
pronounces each word clearly in the unit song "Dekopin"
buta no shippo nante
right right just like that
Let's continue to the next monomane. Here you go.
When Sakurai Reika's
tension is uncontrollably too high
Waah~!
So let's move on, next monomane
11th single "Inochi Wa Utsukushii"
Ikuta Erika's fox like hand movements.
So that's how it is
Let's go with the next monomane, here it is!
Nakamoto Himeka's
high tension self introduction
Hello~! Nogizaka's number one spoiled brat, Nakamoto Himeka
but you can also call me Himetan~!
Takayama you're very popular, everybody wants to imitate you
What was that line again
Her line is "buta no shippo nante"
She sings it very well...
but somehow the way she
Takayama Kazumi carefully
pronounces each word clearly in the unit song "Dekopin"
sings it, it's very clear and carefully pronounced
Did you notice that?
Yes I do, it sounded like me
Is that so
Yes
You were singing it very clearly
Some days I'm doing it... and I very much know that. And sometimes I've been getting into
recordings a little lately
This is Sakurai's first right?
When Sakurai Reika's
tension is uncontrollably too high
What's this?
When her tension is high
She's a little crazy right?
Awesome
When she sees a member she'll go
Kana-tan~ Kana-tan~
Ah she does. She does
I can't help it cause they're so cute
I like to add "tan" to it
What about that "wah!"?
How does she do it?
Sometimes Reika comes even closer when we're doing nothing
wah~ wah~
Ah just like that
Try it on Himura-san for a second
Practice with Himutan.
I'm not that dangerous you know
Himu-tan~! Himu-tan~!    Himu-tan~ Himu-tan~! WAH~!
WAH~! Himu-tan...
WAH~!
That was so cute
That was cute!
So cute~    So cute~
I thought it was kinda cute too
That's not the case
Try not doing that again...
Wada again... Again with the dance moves
11th single "Inochi Wa Utsukushii"
Ikuta Erika's fox like hand movements.
She was good
This is her second time right?
Her hand gestures are amazing and girly like
Hand gesture?
The way it moves... is like...
Something... like this...? does anyone do the same thing
Everyone does it normally like this sa-sa-sa
Right the real thing
but the girly way is like sa-sa-sa~!
Ikuta, try doing it "sa-sa-sa"
I do it like I'm touching something hot
Himetan again
Amazing
Do you still do that often?
Uhm... probably
Nakamoto Himeka's high tension self introduction
She probably moves her shoulder about 6 times... by doing this
You don't do it now?
Now I don't do it that much
Can you show us?
What about now? Can you show us?
Current self introduction
Hello, From Nogizaka46  I'm Nakamoto Himeka, please to meet you
It's way different
Her voice was very soft, can you do the old one?
I'll do the old one
The loud one, do the loud one... with more energy, energetic!
Old self introduction
Go
Hello~! Nogizaka's number one spoiled brat, Nakamoto Himeka but you can also call me Himetan~! Please to meet you
Full throttle idol!
That was good, that now was better
Next monomane contestants
are these four entry
Next let's go, please!
Takayama Kazumi feeling sorry for Wada Maaya
"when Maaya acts like an elementary school student"
You know Maaya really loves ginkgo, but...
After a leaf fell from the the ginkgo tree
It was so smelly, it smelled like poop
Ma~aya Ma~aya
That's no good Ma~aya
Ah... I see~ I see!!
Okay. Next. Please
When a camera is showing her during a music program
Takayama Kazumi skillfully draws attention with her hand action
Takayama Kazumi's hand action
when the camera is on her during a music program
I do... I do...
So that was her technique
Okay let's continue the next monomane! Here it is!
Nishino Nanase singing with her nose
during her solo song
Hitori Yogari
Is this real?
That was interesting
You're in a bad spot
So let's continue with the next monomane. Here it is!
Matsumura Sayuri singing Karaage Sisters "Expressionless"
Aa~ doushite mendou kusaindarou?
nandemo shiritagaru
That was horrible
That's scary
Saito Chiharu, well I still don't know what it means but...
Well she was with Maaya
Takayama Kazumi feeling sorry for Wada Maaya
"when Maaya acts like an elementary school student"
I've seen this in my imagination before
Incredible, I never done it before but, probably
That was your Imagination?
Probably my Imagination
Ah so this never happened before?
So that's all based on your image?
If I were to do it for real
Ahh...
Ma... Maay...
Ahh~
like that
What the hell was that?
Fukagawa imitate Takayama as well
Kazumin does this thing quite often
I do, I do
Takayama Kazumi's hand action
when the camera is on her during a Music Program
That's when it's properly faced at her
Yes, when it's properly faced at her
When its pointed at her
I've always been doing that
So you do that, deliberately?
Ah... Ay... Uhh... I wonder... I thought...
Since the camera is just on you, I thought I might as well, rather that just continue singing normally.
Nishino... Wada
Naachan really sings well... but
Nishino Nanase singing with her nose during her solo song
Her mic is carefully placed here
You've been really mean recently, mean but interesting
Is this true Nishino?
I really dislike this part right here
when I practiced I found a way to cover it
that's why I place it here so it gets covered
Even though the mic is placed here I still sing with mouth
It's natural.
Of course you'll still be singing with your mouth
It'll be weird if you sing with your nose
At the end she incredibly raised the mic even more
Thats mean
Maaya that's mean
Also the one who imitate Matsumura
Your kinda bad too, Nakada
You two
are apparently badasses
Prank?
It's out of respect
You imitated Matsumura
Matsumura Sayuri singing Karaage Sisters "Expressionless"
Yes
That part was roughly sang by Sayurin
I kinda wanted to do it
But...
My voice is a little... ahh~! haha~
What's wrong?
Let us hear the real singing voice
Aa~ doushite mendou kusaindarou?
nandemo shiritagaru
The same.
It sounds the same
nandemo shiritagaru~
Somehow it... it has a weird feeling to it
Yeah...
We still have more monomanes from these four for our next entries
So let's continue and see what's next, go ahead!
Making sure that she finished her make up on her own face by Hashimoto Nanami
Hashimoto Nanami making sure
that she finished her make up on her own face
It's alike~
Cute~!
Next monomane please!
The way an Idol acts when
she has an daifuku by Akimoto Manatsu
AH!
IT'S SO CUTE~!
TSUN TSUN TSUN TSUN
CHU♥
This is bad
Okay let's continue. Next one is this!
Nakamoto Himeka's mysterious sexy appeal when eating delicious food
She does that?
You've done it now
So the next monomane is this!
Praised during an interview, Noujo Ami suddenly put on airs
Ah I understand
Noujo-san's face is so cute
I think ever since your elementary school days you've been this way
Eh? For real?
First is Fukagawa by Hashimoto
Right
So all of you
know about this?
Hashimoto Nanami making sure
that her make up is perfect after applying it
When she's using her compact for makeup she does it normally... but then
She does this thing with her lips
What kind of face do you make
What is that?
I think maybe my chin is distorted
It's not distorted at all
Cause my chin just bends to the left
so I consciously try to fix it by doing this when I look in the mirror,
and because my chin is bent, I kinda get worried about my laugh lines.
This part... I want to fi... Here i fixed it
So you try to fix it?
Somehow...
I look like crying
That's what you mean
and then the next one was Wakatsuki
imitated for Akimoto
If she sees something cute like a daifuku or marshmallow
*note: Daifuku or Daifukumochi is a japanese confection consisting of a small round mochi stuffed with sweet filing, most commonly anko, sweetened red bean paste made from azuki beans.
The way an Idol acts when
she has a daifuku by Akimoto Manatsu
She'd always go "It's so cute~~!"
that "Chu~" is probably the worst
I don't do that at all
No... No... No... No...
She always does
Has anyone... seen you do it before?
Probably at home, I was trying to talk to a Persimmon before
Kakitoku?
What do you mean?
Because it's that time of the season so it came out
Then what did you do?
I ate it
Why... Why do you do that?
After i pick it up and put it in my hands, I pet it like I pet a kitten
For real... even though you're truly innocent...
Your thinking is weird
Paper thin.
But it's good
So it's good
She doesn't only do it to daifuku but also to humans
Really? the "Tsun~ Tsun~"?
She did it in the morning and said "Good morning~ Tsun~Tsun~!" and was told to stop it
The closest to looking like a daifuku here is...
Don't look at me! you punk
Just try it
You're the only one who looks like a daifuku here
Ah Good Morning! Tsun Tsun
Ah morning...
What the hell are you doing
I'm your senior, idiot.
Sinking
Disappointing isn't it
You don't even know the old man and still did it
That's right it's gonna be weird
Saying it to an old man that you don't even know
Even though I don't know them I still do it
The "Tsun Tsun"?
Even on members... Chut~ and Pachut~
Ahh exactly
Ikuta doesn't know what to do
What now
Just like that
Of course you don't know what to do next
Kawago imitated Himetan again
Yes Himetan again
Again with Himetan
First off, when she has pudding or any kind of food then when she eats it
Nakamoto Himeka's mysterious sexy appeal
when eating delicious food
Then whatever is left on her lips
she licks it all, then does this flick thing at the end
Then goes Mmmm~
Like this
She does, she does
You've done it now
Now Takayama
imiated for Noujo
I had a feeling that you were going to imitate Noujo
Praised during an interview,
Noujo Ami suddenly put on airs
She's been doing that hair flip when she was little
I don't know why but every time she gets praised
Noujo aren't you getting kinda cute?
More shocking monomane one after the other!!
We are now on the last block, these three are the final entries
So let's move on, go ahead!
"Sekai de Ichiban Kodoku na Lover"
Wakatsuki Yumi's exaggerated hip movement
For this I'll do separate versions
"Sekai de Ichiban Kodoku na Lover" Normal version
Alright
Next I'll do Wakatsuki's version
"Sekai de Ichiban Kodoku na Lover" Wakatsuki version
It's a like
Let's go next monomane, Please!
At Manatsu Zenkoku tour during the 12th single "Taiyou Knock" performance
Wakatsuki Yumi switches hand with the mic weirdly
Taiyou Knock
So this will be the last...
Let's go, the last monomane go ahead!
In "Sekai de Ichiban Kodoku na Lover"
Wakatsuki Yumi's
arranged skating style move
I'll do separate versions
"Sekai de Ichiban Kodoku na Lover" Normal version
Eh? That's all?
Next is Wakatasuki Yumi's version
"Sekai de Ichiban Kodoku na Lover" Wakatsuki version
The final block was all Wakatsuki
All of them imitated Wakatsuki... It's like a Wakatsuki special
Thank you very much
First off, Akimoto
Her hip movement was very exaggerated
Yeah, I wonder why she's the only one moving like that
"Sekai de Ichiban Kodoku na Lover"
Wakatsuki Yumi's exaggerated hip movement
She's doing it sexily kinda...
Everyone uses their feet to move, but I move with my hips
Ahh I get it
Takayama, what about yours?
Wakatsuki Yumi switches hand with the mic weirdly
At the Zenkoku Tour, Wakatsuki is always on my left side
We're a little close to each other... then when it starts...
"yagate natsu wa sugisatte iku" then...
We are like this, and the mic is right here while we dance
Wakatsuki's head is always right here! Right in front of me!
Wakatsuki Yumi switches hand with the mic weirdly
Right here, imagine this is me
"yagate natsu wa sugisatte iku" then!
Ah right right right...
Then she'll sing right away
So that's what you mean
And if you look carefully, you switched hands with the microphone.
Probably
What is it?
To be honest... for this...
Another member
and I pretended to be one
Ah is that so
The teacher didn't say anything
about the timing to hold it (microphone)
That's why I don't know my own timing
That's why...
I thought I was too fast but...
For some reason everyone is stopping already...
So that's it
Furthermore, everyone just moves from here...
But Wakatsuki positions her self like this
Ahh I see...
Unaware of the mistake...
And the last one is Wada
I think Wakatsuki is really exploring her style and showmanship when she gets out front.
And what she came up with is this movement.
Wakatsuki Yumi's
skate-like movement
Wada you meany
So when you get out front, then, each of you is allowed to do something like that?  Like show off a bit?
Do you do it normally?
Everyone does it normally like this, but...
Right
The way wakatsuki-chan does it...
But... I understand... uhm... wait
When Wakatsuki walks, if there's anything special going on, it's like, isn't it?
I totally get it... That movement.
Now let us see the real dance
It's totally different
Who will shine on the laurels of victory?
Himura-san
Yeah
Shall we decide the number 1?
Lets see the number 1
HIMURA AWARD
Oh ah wait still?
First Himura Award of the New Year
It hasn't even been long since the last one and you want to bring it back alre-
It's okay if you don't want to do Himura Award, we can do anything else.
Well, we did this whole thing, so we should have a winner.
But we are still together
Then let's do the Himura Award
Oh Himura Award
Inside joke Monomane competition grand prize winner?
Wada Maaya-san!
Well she deserves it
even though she was a little mean
For real. Congratulations
Congratulations!
Last, let's hear some words from Wada
You can choose any monomane that you did earlier
So let's see Wada's winning monomane
Nishino Nanase singing with her nose during her solo song
Tokyo metro has chosen a departure melody for Nogizaka station
and it will be Nogizaka46's Ikuta Erika playing piano on "Kimi no na wa Kibo"
Nogizaka station on the line up from the spring timetable revision