m 0 0 m 0 0 m 0 10 l 49 59 l 37 71 l 90 71 l 90 44 l 65 19 l 78 6 l 90 18 l 90 0 l 18 0 l 63 45 l 59 49 l 50 58 l 38 46 l 48 36 l 12 0 l 0 0 m 90 24 l 78 12 l 71 19 l 90 38 m 0 17 l 42 59 l 36 65 l 0 29 m 0 36 l 24 60 l 11 73 l 29 90 l 27 90 l 0 65 m 0 72 l 0 90 l 20 90 m 36 90 l 21 76 l 90 76 l 90 90 m 35 71 l 27 63 l 19 71 m 64 26 l 58 32 l 64 38 l 70 32 m 44 46 l 50 52 l 57 45 l 51 39 l 44 46 m 52 32 l 64 20 l 76 32 l 64 44
Nogami46subs
Nogizaka46 14th single Campaign in Guam!
We are in Guam!
Guam Tumon Beach
This is awesome, right?
- We came here.
- Look at this beautiful sea!
Isn't this good?
Attack Sakurai
I thought about plunging Sakurai into the water for the opening, but I decided to stop because it will happen by itself later anyway.
I see.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Not everyone has recorded oversea programs.
I feel after 4 years, we can finally do something like this.
On the top feels
Yeah, I think so.
You can feel that you've already come to the top.
- That's right.
Ah, Shiraishi is not here? It seems her condition is not good.
※ Due to her bad condition Shiraishi is absent from this shooting.
- Is that so?
Yeah.
That's why, shall we pay her a visit?
Visit her from this location shot.
We want to, but...
The Guam location shoot this time is not a vacation project, but a campaign for their 14th single hit.
And the campaign is?
Skydiving from a 4200m altitude!
This time's project is skydiving from a 4200m altitude that is even higher than what Akimoto did in the past!
Now they will play some kinds of games in Guam.
The members who win the games can have a vacation right away.
But the members who are remaining until the very end won't be able to enjoy the Guam vacation, but will be chosen to do the fearsome skydiving.
Therefore, on my right are the senbatsu members.
But not only the senbatsu members who came here. Please take a look over here.
Under members came as well.
- Yes, this time they all came.
Under came as well!
Himetan!
- Yes!
Under members look enthusiastic, coming with the swimming float.
- Yes we are!
We received this one year worth of a holiday because we did our best,
But we came here for vacation. So please do your best for the recording everyone!
Completely carefree
So they won't be participating?
I was wondering, at the right end, there's a hostess.
Beach night Queen
Ah, Shinuchi?
- She is Shinuchi.
I thought she was a hostess on vacation.
- No, she is not.
What should we do? Because they're here, shall we recruit some members,
from over there?
Eh? We don't want to!
If we recruit all of them it will be too many. In that case we will choose 4 people.
And the selection method for recruiting is?
"Answer the question correctly then you may go on vacation right away!" Under members selection quiz!
- "Answer the ques.....
I'm excited because we're in Guam, I almost said the title myself.
They will be given some easy Guam-related questions.
If they answer it correctly, they will have the vacation right away.
And the 4 remaining members will be participating in the campaign.
You are really have no schedule for today, am I right?
- Yes.
So, if you overcome this, you can really have fun.
That's nice.
- What a treat.
Forced Participation
You better do the bonfire here.
Trivia thing in Guam
You have to do that at least.
Isn't that fun Rotty?
It is fun!
What are you talking about, really?
Himurotty in southern country
Isn't dance a good thing?
- Dance is the best!
We are in Guam, but...
What is the direction of this place from Japan? Please write in English.
Okay, Please write it!
They are writing.
You know the globe, right?
The hostess is so noisy over here.
Fussy hostess
She is very noisy.
I don't know but I feel so excited.
Are you done? Everyone is done.
Therefore, show your answers!
South, south... Light?
Ridiculously wrong
It's the right side.
T/N : She meant to write "right"
You saw it from where?
It's right from Japan.
- If you point right from Japan, there is Korea and China.
Bad orientation of direction
Besides you wrote "light"
It should be south.
- Terada Ranze!
She wrote "Minami" (Jap: south)
Full Hiragana
Didn't we tell you to write it in English? You don't know what the English for that is, right?
There's someone who wrote "left" too
- Yeah.
Ah, there it is.
I didn't see it coming. she matched it with "right"
Idiot's 2 answers
Will "center" come?
Shall we try the 2nd time?
Okay, I will announce the correct answer!
The correct answer is "South"
The correct spelling is S.O.U.T.H
12 among 19 members answered correctly.
Their work is done here, and they can go have fun!
The members over there get their vacation.
Vacation group
But please bear with us for a while. It will be over soon.
Unexpectedly some of you can't write it.
Seeing their faces, I could see their elimination!
Stupid group
You mean that they are kinda stupid?
- They are totally stupid.
Where are we now?
- Guam!
Please write Guam using the alphabet!
This is extremely easy!
You've already seen the word everywhere!
You can see it on the ticket as well.
Let's go, 1, 2, 3 open your answer.
Guam... they are fairly write "Guam."
- Which one is correct?
Huh? Some of them seem weird.
Terada Ranze, how many characters did you write? Show us.
Show it to the camera.
Guarmu~
It's foreigner-ish.
Wrote too many
Huh? Rotty?
Guame?
"E" Added
The correct one is
G
U
A
M
You did it Terada! You already lost.
Rotty too.
Why are you happy? Of course you are out as well.
Come here now Kawamura!
And here Kawamura and Terada are joining the recording.
And we have to chose another 2 from the remaining 5.
The place which we are visiting now. Which country does this place belong to? Please write the official name.
In Kanji?
What?
- In Kanji?
Write it now!
- Write it now!
Useless Question
Write it quickly!
Hurry up
- They are afraid of getting sunburned.
I don't even have a clue!
Stop writing!
Show your answers together.
United States of America.. United States of America.
Overseas!?
- I don't even know!
America... and Guam!?
I never thought you would get it wrong with this question!
Guam belongs to the United States of America!
Because I asked you to write the official name, the correct answer is United States of America.
Those who wrote "Guam" and "Overseas" are pretty bad.
- You thought that the "guam" answers would come in a row?
I was hesitating with Eurasia continent.
United States or Continent
How good of you.
You are talking global here, right?
Kawago and Kitano who answered correctly are getting their vacation!
Because they seem unable to answer the quiz, the 2 losers will be decided by rock-paper-scissors.
Noujo-senpai, come here, you are chosen.
As expected from Noujo-senpai.
You make sure to remain here, Noujo-senpai.
Let's proceed for the last one!
- It's not over yet!
Come here!
- Come here Miria-chan.
With that, these 4 are chosen from the under.
Ganbatte kudasai!
Himetan, please say something for these 4.
We will enjoy the vacation while thinking about you!
Farewell vacation
16 senbatsu members plus 4 under members will be fighting here!
Please take a look over there.
Look at that! If we talk about a southern island, we should do something like this.
Enjoying Guam
Congratulation!
- Congratulation! Are you having fun?
Are you having fun?
- Yes we are!
What are you drinking over there?
Melon juice!
That's nice!
Relaxing on the beach
Therefore, if you can win the game, you will go to have fun like that, right away.
I hope you can give your best.
Himura-san, what is the first game?
Spinning beach flag!
This is a 4 man race.
After spinning 10 times, they will run for the flag. For those who get the flag, the vacation is waiting for them.
They will be divided into 5 groups so their will be 5 winners since only 1 person is the winner from each group.
We have cards with your names here.
Over there is number 1, 2, 3, and 4.
- Starting from the sea.
Who will be on the edge of the sea?
Fukagawa-san
- There it goes.
That's good.
For the 14th single, Fukagawa's name is called in this game.
- You're right!
The members who will race in this round are the following.
Who will get the vacation?
Fukagawa, do you think you can win?
I'll do my best!
Are you okay Miria-chan? If you can win here you will go on vacation right away!
Because I'm the youngest here, I will do my best!
Huh? It's already going bad. She almost went into the sea.
Fukagawa almost went into the sea.
You have to spin quickly!
It's bad! Kawamura is in bad shape!
Are you kidding? Are you kidding?
Quickly! Spin fast!
Spin quickly!
- Spin 10 times!
Are you kidding?
- Spin quickly!
Etou you are funny, that's nice!
Nice Etou!
Fell into water again
That's good Etou!
Etou is already drenched!
Miria?
They're coming!
Do your best Miria!
Granny!
Drenched old lady
I didn't expect you would go into the water like that.
Unexpectedly Fun
This is good. You can get into the water like that with this game.
You got into the water because your eyes were spinning.
I thought I wouldn't go into the water.
The two places nearest to the sea are dangerous places.
Dangerous seaside
Number 1 and 2 are the worst places.
That's right! Please be careful.
Advice from the experienced
With that, Watanabe Miria is winner in this group!
Timer : nogidoki, Martin Calden | Translator : Martin Calden
Typesetter : Veliem, Nogami | Kara : NiL
QC : Cris6z, boots27 | Encoder, Uploader : boots27
The program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
First, let's decide who will get the seaside place.
And the one who gets that is,
Matsumura-san.
The seaside position is the most critical place in this race.
Who will get the vacation rights?
Let's start the race!
Ready!
Ganbatte!
- The second round is starting.
Akimoto, you're a nuisance for those around you.
Akimoto, your surroundings... Oh wait Matsumura.
Matsumura, you almost...
You almost got drenched with just a couple of turns.
Matsumura, ah there she goes.
In the Pacific Ocean
Matsumura got drenched already.
That's good! That's good! That's good!
Matsumura, aren't you already soaked enough?
Sakurai!?
Sakurai also goes for it!
For real? Are you for real?
Is that really that bad?
Here she comes, Ranze!
Ranze! Ranze! Ranze!
Why was everyone gone like that?
Horrible Losers
What are they doing?
It's already over!
What are you doing?
Why are they crawling on the coast?
Newborn Foal?
That is... Matsumura!
You were really going for it!
For real!
When I tried to see where I was going, before I knew it, I was already in the water but I couldn't get out at all.
We were like pulled to the water.
Seriously?
What is that?
Until the end both of you couldn't get up and just stay there.
I like that.
- Really.
Let's play this game every time.
Spinning bat special program?
This is fun. Let's have an extra time.
Let's play it until the sunsets.
- I agree.
After the lunch break we will play this game again.
And the winner for the 2nd group is Terada Ranze.
Who will get the seaside place?
I'm afraid.
The one who gets the seaside is,
Nishino.
I want to see Nishino plunge into the water.
I don't want to!
Nishino-san
- Ganbatte!
Until now, the seaside position always goes into the water.
And what will happen with this 3rd group?
You have to spin properly!
Ready!
One, two...
Wakatsuki is so fast!
Ah, Nishino.
- You need to be faster.
Wakatsuki is so fast!
- Ah Hashimoto!
Hashimoto...
- It's bad.
You haven't spun 10 times yet!
- Wakatsuki's too fast!
You haven't spun 10 times yet! Put your forehead on the bat properly!
On your forehead! Ah there she goes!
Watch it Wakatsuki!
There she goes!
Nice job, well done!
That's bad! Nishino is...
Nishino is bad!
It's over! It's over!
It's already over!
She's cool!
- Her final pose is kinda...
Jojo's pose
It's already over!
Nishino almost got into the water, didn't you?
It was impossible for me to spin 10 times.
You got wet a little bit, right?
Yes.
I could control it somehow.
Hashimoto seems like she couldn't do it as well.
How should I say it?
It seemed impossible to maintain my sense of balance on this beach sand.
It'll make a deviation?
- Will it?
Balance Fault
In this 3rd group, Wakatsuki who didn't fall over, got the vacation.
After this, the tragedies will continue!?
The wet beach flag!
Vacation team!
Yes?
Do you think this game is fun?
It's interesting!
- It's funny!
Enjoying Vacation
Shut up!
They're really pissing me off. What the hell is that?
We're doing our best to be funny out here, please watch us with enthusiasm.
Noble family vacation
Seeing them like that even get on my nerves.
Let's proceed with 4th group.
The one who gets the seaside place.
The seaside place belongs to,
Noujo-san!
As expected you have good luck.
Based on the ballot, the 4th group is as follows.
Who will win in this always-get-wet race?
Noujo is spinning already.
Isn't that a minus point?
Image Training Begins
She will get dizzy. Her eyes will start spinning already.
Asuka-chan
Asuka-chan, do you think you will go into the water?
No I won't
Strong Denial
Hori!
Yes!
Your position is far from the water but please be careful nevertheless.
I will.
Ready!
Ah, they're fast!
Ah, they're so fast!
Takayama is so fast!
Noujo is fast too!
You have to touch your forehead with the bat!
Touch your forehead with the bat!
She's coming! Ah, not yet!
Be careful!
Hori! Hori!
I got it!
Where are you going Hori! Where are you going Hori!
Running in the opposite direction
Where are you going Hori!
Where are you going Hori! Ah, she fell.
Asuka-chan almost went into the water too!
You went in, that's nice.
Wait a moment, Hori why did you go the opposite direction?
Hori, in the end why did you go to...
- Why did you go in the opposite direction?
My head became weird and I just thought about running as hard as I could.
You sprinted in the opposite direction.
Asuka-chan, you went into the water a couple of times.
I hate it!
- You got wet!
Asuka-chan, you said that you wouldn't go into the water.
No way, this is weird!
I went into the water!
That's Ikko-san.
That's what Ikko-san would say.
You naturally went in.
- It was hard?
I don't want them to think that I went into the water because of variety's sake.
This is not what variety would do.
Now that's variety
"You said you wouldn't go into the water but you went in"?
Yes, Noujo.
Yes.
- Noujo, you didn't even go into the water...
What the hell were you doing?
But, seriously..
Even when I went in this direction,
somehow, someone pulled me.
A strange power was pulling you somehow.
Getting pulled to the sea
A strange power, like...
Why are you showing your butt to the camera?
The camera is over there.
Don't play around!
Yes, seriously.
Asuka-chan, is your head head hurt?
No, I was annoyed.
She said something dull, right?
She's annoyed.
- "What is she saying?"
No, I was just annoyed with my hair.
- Ah your hair.
That's a relief, I thought you were annoyed with the whole thing.
Thank God!
Aversion to filming?
The uncles wanted to see you smile, after all.
Takayama got the vacation in this 4th group.
Final race!
Who hasn't participated?
Ah those four, but I'm still drawing the cards to decide your position.
That's right.
- Everyone is fine with them.
Hoshino, you don't have the image of going into the water, right?
For sure, but...
there's nobody in charge of something like that among the four of us.
Absence of the dirty role
So you have someone in charge of something all along?
In charge of being drenched
You're in charge of something?
- You're not in charge of this, right? But you will go in nevertheless.
- Right.
You were the one who was supposed to get plunged but you didn't, don't you feel bad?
What should I do?
Quite far from the sea
That's not the case.
Somethings happened, right?
The seaside position belongs to?
- I will draw.
This person.
Ikuta!
Iku-chan!
The final groups positions are as follows.
Ikuta whoever is on the seaside has the biggest disadvantage, and then?
Ikuta you will bump into the others, so please take a step to the left.
Like this, you most likely will get plunged.
I'm already in the water!
Barely on the sea
That's not our problem.
That's not our problem!
- You should spin clockwise!
Ready!
They're starting!
Ikuta quite... Ah Ikuta you want to go in already?
Ikuta! Ikuta! Ikuta!
Spins 3 times then kerplunk
Ikuta! Ikuta!
Awesome! Didn't you get plunged too early?
You just spun 3 times!
Ah, she's going in!
Ah Hoshino got plunged too!
Is she drowning?
Marika-sensei!
- Marika! Marika! Marika!
- She's going on her senses!
You can get it! You can get it!
You can get it!
- Whoa Hoshino!
Hoshino!
She got it!
She said she didn't want to go into the water.
Ikuta is in bad shape! She spun 3 times only!
Struggling in 15cm depth
What are you doing Ikuta?
Ikoma just take it slow...
- Ikoma
Please come here everyone!
- What's wrong with her?
This group's members are rough!
She's soaking wet!
You got this soaked?
- That's nice.
Ikuta, you just spun 3 times, didn't you?
You got plunged immediately.
I didn't think that would happen.
You couldn't help it?
I was spinning in the water already, after all!
It's sea before she knows it
It was too sudden.
And Hoshino as well.
Hoshino was not good either.
I was surprised.
You didn't think you would go into the water like that?
- Yes.
You didn't think you would go into the water by yourself?
- I did not! I didn't want to.
I didn't think that, that's why I came today with a cute hairstyle.
Going into the sea was an accident
Ikoma was too far from the sea, right?
I didn't go into the water, but...
Your eyes didn't spin?
- Just..
I'm just a good-for-nothing person.
But when you were spinning it was beautiful, just like a rainbow.
Shadow of the rainbow
Itou Marika is the winner in the final group!
15 members remain.
Who will do the skydiving from 4200m altitude campaign?
14th single is going on sale in 23 march.
Harujion ga Sakukoro.
The first publication of the MV!
HARUJION ga michi ni saitara kimi no koto wo bokura wa omoidasu darou
When the harujion blooms on the street, I’m sure we'll think of you
Itsumo soba de hohoendeta hinata no you na sonzai
Always smiling by our side. A presence like a sun.
Kokoro iyashite kureta shiroi hana no karensa
Soothing our hearts, the sweetness of a white flower
Hoka no iro ni magirenagara hanashikakeru kikkake mo nai mama
Among the other colors, there was no reason to call out to you
Nani mo kawaranu SUTANSU nakamatachi wa jiyuu no imi wo shitta
An attitude where nothing will change. Our friends found the meaning of freedom.
Kimi wa doushite sonna ni yasashii me de mitsumeru no?
Why is it that you look at us with such kind eyes?
Kanashimi ya ikari yuuutsu na koto wa nai no?
Don't you ever feel sadness, anger or depression?
Kaze ni fukaretemo sugasugashii hyoujou de
Even when stricken by wind, you are standing holding a refreshing expression
Subete wo yurusu you ni tatazunderu
you showed us that you'll forgive everything.
HARUJION ga ame ni utarete sore demo mada aozora miageru you ni
When the harujion is hit by the rain, it seems like even then it's looking up at a clear sky
Tsurai toki mo kawaranu mama  Kimi wa kimi no shisei de
Even in rough times, you never change with your attitude.
Unmei ukeireteta  Chi ni ne wo haru tsuyosa de...
You accepted your fortune with the strength of roots spreading.
14th single is going on sale on 23 march.
Harujion ga Sakukoro's nation-wide handshake events are decided!
For further details, please check Nogizaka46's official website.
Timer : nogidoki, Martin Calden | Translator : Martin Calden
Typesetter : Veliem, Nogami | Kara : NiL
QC : Cris6z, boots27 | Encoder, Uploader : boots27
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
The seminar for the 3rd generation audition will be held in seven regions.
We will wait for everyone's application!
And then.
Under Live Nationwide tour Tohoku series.
The tickets are on sale.
You can get them earlier!