m 0 0 l 0 27 l 2 27 l 2 0 l 0 0 m 2 0 l -4 0 l -4 6 l 16 6 l 16 4 l -2 4 l -2 2 l 0 2 m 2 2 m 16 0 l 16 27 l 18 27 l 18 -1 l 16 -1 m 22 0 l 22 0 l 24 0 l 24 11 l 19 11 l 19 9 l 22 9 l 22 2 l 15 2 l 15 0 m 6 18 l 6 12 l 12 12 l 12 14 l 8 14 l 8 18 l 6 18 m 12 18 l 12 20 l 6 20 l 6 18 l 10 18 l 10 14 l 12 14 l 12 18 m 5 7 l 8 9 l 7 10 l 4 8 l 5 7 m 10 9 l 10 9 l 13 7 l 14 8 l 11 10 l 10 9 m 3 24 b 3 24 3 23 3 23 b 7 21 11 21 15 23 b 15 23 15 25 15 25 b 11 23 7 23 3 25
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
NOGIZAKA KOUJICHUU
DON! Okay, Nogizaka Koujichuu is starting,
we're the MC Bananaman.   - Good evening everyone!
BANANAMAN
HIMURA YUKI
SHITARA OSAMU
And here's Nogizaka-chan...
This feels like a school.   - Yes.
Himura-san...  - Yes!
Please announce our segment for today.  - Here I go...
Congratulations for Nogizaka's Fourth Birthday!
Important advices for the members
to face the fifth year!
Discussions?
- Yes.
It means, it's been four years since the debut
back on February 22nd. Everyone congratulations!
- 4 years, everyone. Congrats!
It's been that long, huh?
That means everyone are grannies now!
- No, no!
Not yet!
- I too... Ah, no, no!
It's grandpa for me.
Many things happened until now.
Of course since it's been 4 years0,
there are lots of things they have done.
Now there are unusual things
they don't do anymore.
And surely there are good things
they still do.
Today they will explain them all
and we're going to talk about them.
First, advice from
Shiraishi, is...
Okay, let's start! For Gomunu...
Ah sorry, let's do it again.
- Oh, she started!
Okay, the topic is Gomunu!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
GOMUNU?
Ah, sorry!  - Gomunu?
Alright!
To face the fifth year, we all want to...
- Ah, that?
- So that became Gomunu?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
TAHUN KE-5  GOMUNU
To face the fifth year...
- Everyone had to face Gomunu just now.
To face the fifth year, I want to
talk about this.  - What's that?
Create a character that makes sense!
Everyone, do you remember
how I introduced myself?
Who?
- Ah, I know, I know. - Okay Takayama.
Alright please show it, Shiraishi's introduction
back then.
- Can you do it?
I came from the fourth dimension, a citizen of Mayora,
19 years old, Shiraishi Mai, Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu!
Mayora = Mayonnaise Lover
Aaah, that!
Right!  - It was like that.
Yes!
Like that?
- Yes, but...
... now, I won't use that ever!
Yeah, that doesn't make any sense.
- That's right, and...
- Zero sense!
Actually even in the first year, I was in doubt,
should I use it still or not.
But then I decided to stop using it
because it looks so bad.
The question is why did I
use it back then? The reason is...
... here, because I was forced to.
I understand that.
- It's all forced.
Of course to be an idol, I thought
I have to leave an impression.
Everyone know that.
- Yes, yes, we do!
At first I really liked mayonnaise,
and used Mayora.
From there on I thought
if it's just that then it's too weak, so...
That's it? Weak?
- Yes!
Maybe with "Seijin" it will sound stronger!
Seijin = citizen of planet....
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
JUST ADD [SEIJIN]
That's what I thought.
- Because you were only using Mayora? - Yeah!
Moreover, I thought if it's just that then surely
it's not enough.
Mayora Seijin was not enough?
- It's weird if it's just that.   - Right!
After that I thought, what else should I add?
And I picked that fourth dimension.
Wakatsuki helped me to think about it back then.
So Wakatsuki made that?
- No, it's not like that.
Thing Wakatsuki taught me
when I was desperate...
This, an explanation about the concept of dimensions.
Why this topic?
- What's this?
I didn't understand about 1st dimension,
2nd dimension etc, and...
Wakatsuki gave me an explanation
with drawings.
1st dimension is just a dot, she drew it
and she said "This is the 1st Dimension".
2nd Dimension is line, while 3rd dimension is
our plane of existence or this physical world.
And she kindly said,
"4th dimension exists inside Doraemon's magical pocket".
She taught me patiently.
Until you understand?
- I explained it.
After hearing that, I really wanted to use it.
I said "4th Dimension sounds good!", like that...
4th dimension sounds good?
- And that's why...
I added the fourth dimension into my self-introduction.
You really used, "Came from the fourth dimension".
- Yes.
Then the first time I showed it
on Nogidoko, I thought it's very interesting.
But back then we asked "What's that?"
- Yes, I thought something's wrong too.
It's... this
"What's a citizen of Planet Mayora?"
Firstly, this.
- I see!
This feels like you came to earth by accident.
- Her place of origin?
You made it yourself,
but after that...
That's right!  - Did you feel it?
Yup!
I thought something's wrong,
"what is a citizen of Planet Mayora?"
I see, even you said you like Mayonnaise.
I thought I like to add
more Mayonnaise compared to others...
But that won't make me
a citizen of planet Mayora automatically.
- So you thought that?
Perhaps just a little bit more than everyone else?
- Yes!
Fans also asked about this.
- Oh really?
They said, "Mayora Seijin, it does not match."
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
FANS DID REALIZE.
Besides, there's no base of science for
the fourth dimension even until now.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
RAW CONCEPT.
Since it came from Doraemon.
- Yes!
That's why my advice in creating a character
so you won't make a mistake like that is...
This, create a character that makes sense,
just like reality and not unusual.
Of course stuff like normal human,
not like what I was talking about.
Let's think about it carefully.
I want everyone to watch this out.
That's the lesson from Shiraishi Mai
for everyone. Thank you very much.
That means you're not a Mayora?
Well it's not like that...
- You're not a citizen of that planet.  - Yes.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NOT A CITIZEN OF THAT PLANET.
But from the beginning, I thought you realized
that you're not from there.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
STILL AN EARTHLING.
The more important thing here is
she said she liked mayonnaise.
I wanted to leave an impact
like that.  - Yes, I know.
Like that.
- So you want to lose it all,
except the liking for mayonnaise?  - Yes!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
ONLY USE MAYORA.
How much do you use mayo?
Like for broccoli.
Broccoli?   - Do you use it on that?
Yes!   - On what part?
The top green part.
- That soft part.
This part...   - Yes.
How much?
Assume this is a broccoli.
How much?  - This is Himuccoli.
Himuccoli!
I poured it like three times.
- Three?!  - That's a lot!
About this much?
Yes.
So you're a Mayora?
That's quite a lot!
Really?
-  Until that part can't be seen...
It means you're a citizen of Planet Mayora!
No! No!
Clearly you are a citizen of Planet Mayora!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
RECOGNIZED AS A CITIZEN OF PLANET MAYORA.
They said it!
A citizen of Planet Mayora!
- But that's the combination I want to lose!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
FIRMLY REJECT
But how's it compared with your self-introduction now?
It's very simple now.
- How simple?
Shiraishi Mai, 23 years old.
No, no! Why?
- That's it? Just like that?
It's boring.
- Not interesting at all!  - Yeah.
Try "a citizen of Planet Shiraishi."
- That sounds good!
23 years old, a citizen of Planet Shiraishi...
You have to be like that!
- Try saying that. We want to see it just once. Ready?
Go!
23 years old, a citizen of Planet Shiraishi,
yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Now that was very interesting!
Like we said in the beginning, we will
lose the bad things and keep
the good things.
- It's easy to remember.
- Don't lose it!
It's not interesting if we lose them all.
- You shouldn't lose things you've made!
Even so, have you like new things
such as food in these four years?
A citizen of what planet are you now?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
DANGEROUS QUESTION.
What planet?
A citizen of what planet? Eh...
- We're not forcing you.    -  Anything's fine.
Eh? I like lacey stuff.
- What?
Well then, a citizen of Planet Lacey Stuff.
- Yeah.
Try saying that!
- No!
Do it, try to think this as a practice.
Do it seriously, don't laugh. Ready?
Make yourself comfortable!   - This is important!
The real version. Ready, Go!
23 years old, a citizen of Planet Lacey Stuff,
yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NAME CHANGE.
Very good!
- Now I feel like a ghost.
No, no.
CONVERTED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
Is there any other member here who've made weird character
and never use it anymore?
Please answer!
- Surely there are.
There she goes, Asuka-chan.
She again!
- A~suka-chan, what did you do this time?
I said I love strawberry milk.
Is that, like, on top of strawberry...
Like strawberry milk candy.
- Ah, there's one with Ume flavor too right?  - Yes!
Ume = Japanese apricot
Candy like that, basically
I love candies.
But I chose the strawberry milk one.
That's delicious, everybody likes that!
- Yes, me too.
When I first entered Nogizaka, I was
13 years old.
- Eh? That young?
I entered when I was a first grader of junior high school,
and that time...
I had the same problem like Maiyan.
- You didn't know what to show?
I thought, in order to be cute
idol has to like sweet things.
Then I chose to love strawberry, but...
- But do you like it?  - Yes, I do!
But if it's just strawberry then it won't stand out.
I thought it won't stand out.
That's why I chose strawberry milk.
- So it's weak?
But back then, this sounded like if you were given a
stawberry milk candy, you could be attracted to that person.
Aa~hh!! That's right!
That kind of character is kinda new!
This is dangerous!
Being attracted just with a candy!
Did you really say that?
- Yes.
Then...
Here, here, stawberry milk candy~
Like that?
Character like that?
- Kawaiii~~!!!
Did you put it into your self introduction?   - Yes.
How did it look like?   - Eh! No, I don't wanna.
- But it was there, right?
We're this far, so please show it.
- Do it.
I wanna see! - Was it that bad?
- Come on!
This might be different.
- You shouldn't say that.
We're eager to see now.
- Since after this, you'll never do it again.
Ready? Can you start? Here we... go!
- Do it!
Okay, first year in junior high school, I'm 13 years old,
my name is Saito Asuka.
Since I like strawberry milk very much, if you give me some
I might get very energetic. So, be careful!
There it is!
She said "very energetic"...   - But wasn't her
style so cute when she did it?
Kawaii~~  - It's good.
- What about now?
You have it too now?
- Please introduce yourself.
Member of Nogizaka46, Saito Asuka,
Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu!
Why?
- Her voice was low! What was that?
What do you like recently?
- Food?
Anything.
Okayu.
Okayu = Japanese style porridge, similar
to chicken porridge without toppings
So it's Okayu.
- You like Okayu?
Yeah. I like watery food.
- Watery!?
Wait, Okayu and watery food
are different.
Actually I like soupy food too, but...
Well, Okayu... everyone knows Okayu has no soup!
You can say he's a watery food too then!
Did anyone else here have
food in your introduction?  - Is there anyone else?
Oh, Itou Junna.
- Junna-chan.
Did you have it too?
- This one is bad!
My name is Itou Junna, rigjt?
- Yes, I know.
I used "Liking Konpeitou" theme,
- Konpeitou?
Konpeito = Small sized traditional Japanese candies
(5-10 mm), come with many cOlors and melt in your mouth
I said it with Konpe and Itou,
I thought that's interesting.
I entered when I was in second year of junior high.
Back then, I made it myself.
But did you like Konpeitou?
I only liked it for about 2 weeks.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
SHORT RELATIONSHIP.
So you didn't like it from the beginning?
I guess I only wanted to like it.
So that you could use Konpe Itou?
- Yes.
Konpe? Doesn't Konpe Itou
sound not cool at all?
Why did you want to use Konpeitou?
- I'm KonpeItou!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
KONPE ITOU?
I want to see you do that!
- Nope!   - But that's cute!
That's good!
- Try saying "I'm KonpeItou!". Go!
I'm KonpeItou~!
- Ah, nice, very nice!
Are you gonna shout "Charan!" too?
Charan = Konpei Hayashiya's shout,
Japanese actor, comedian, and Rakugo performer
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
KONPEI?
That sounds disturbing.
- Yeah.
But when Gen 2 appeared on Nogidoko, when I showed
my introduction to Shiraishi-san.
She told me to stop using it.
- She did?
She said, if you see my
introduction, you'll understand.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
MINE WAS BAD, SO STOP
She told me to get a new one.
- Did you understand that?
Conversely, anyone here still use
the introduction from back then?   - Yes.
There it is!   - Among all,
the one we thought together?  - Exactly!
The one made by Shitara-san?
- Yes, I always use it.  -  Ah, good!
The same sounding name if you read it from above and below?
- Yes!
There were seven people who got their introduction made.
- That many?
I'm sure there were seven.
- So the other six never use it anymore?  - Yes!
So what do you use?
Who are those six?
- Confess!
Ikoma's wrong, actually Shitara made this nickname (Nogidoko ep2).
Ikoma?  - How was Ikoma's self introduction?
- I got it from Himura-san...
I said, "Ikoma Rina, Ikoma Rina, Ikoma Rina...
Ika Marinate (spiced squid)"
- Me?
Now this is interesting!
That's pretty funny!
- Why won't you use it anymore?
Why Ika (squid) ?
Since Ikoma Rina and Ika Marinate are similar...
- So you never use Ika Marinate?
Never, except for that Nogidoko.
- What about now?
Well, since my name changed...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
I AM SPICED SQUID.
That's right. There's even no Ikoma Rina
in the last one there.
After this, there are still many interesting things!
Next, an advice from Hori
for the members is...
Why was your running so weird just now, like...
Hori-san, that's pretty bad!
- What a weird running style!
It's not like that!   - Was it like that, Shitara-san?
Alright let's start, Hori please!
- Okay, the topic I want to talk about is...
This! Je~JeN~
Be careful with your specialty!
So it's about specialty.
- Yes!
For an Idol, a specialty may
gives her many problems.
- I see!
When I just entered Nogizaka,
I wanted to be like Gen 1.
You may say that Gen 2's characters were so bad at that time. That made us to work extra hard.
After I thought harder, I visited one place in particular.
That place is...
A sushi shop!
Yes!    - Why? Did you go there to
look for some specialty?  - Yes!
From the... from the very start, sushi is...
~Gross!~
Who was that? I heard someone said gross.
- Because of the pictures?
Oi?
- Itou Junna, was it?
Are those Sushi?
- Yeah!
Isn't this Himura-san?
- Hold on!
Himura family, huh?
- Why?
I drew many...
- Young family.  - Yes!
Even I went there...
- Eh? To look for some specialty?    - Precisely!
At first I had this character.
Eating without chewing.
Character?
- Clearly that's not a character. That's a way of eating!  - Yes!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NO CHEWING CHARACTER?
Since without chewing, I could eat quickly.
- Why was that a character?
- No chewing character?
Sorry, sorry...
Because without chewing, I thought maybe I
could eat faster.
- Go ahead!
- Like, gulping it? Awesome!
Right!
- Quick eating, huh?
When the other members were slowly eating,
I was eating so quickly.
So I always finished first.
So you chose that specialty
to challenge yourself?  - Yes!
The other members were also looking for their own specialty,
like Hulahoop.
Hulahoop? It's boring to see an idol
who's good at hulahoop.
There are too many.
- Yes.
But they too couldn't do it like the others.
It'll be very interesting if you show us here.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
MIGHT BE INTERESTING
In the end we didn't do it. But
there's something I did in the end.
It was...
- I wonder...
DRY EYE.
I have dry eyes problem,
so I blink alot.
Many of my friends know about
this skill of mine.
I thought if I do it seriously,
I can blink very fast.
I remember that, you did it, right?
- Yes I did!
Back then I thought, it's the perfect choice!
Then when I appeared the first time in Nogidoko,
I showed it like this...
You can blink quickly? Well
let's check it out then. Start!
MAY 2013
- I wanna see!
- Please do it!
That was quick!
- How quick~!
Yeah!
- When I saw her, her face suddenly changed!
[Shitara]: Himura-san was slimmer!
[Himura]What do you mean?
That?
- Yes!
But I have a problem with this
blinking skill.    - What?
And the problem is this...
I can't maintain the quality!
- What?
Lately I'm thankful for getting many jobs.
But because of that, my eyes become tired.
No, what does it have to do with anything?
Before, I spent a lot of time in Gifu.
Gifu = a town in Japan where there are
Kinka Mount in the middle of the town and Nagara River
When I lived in Gifu, where there are
mountains and rivers...
The environment is still natural...
- Ah, the influence for the eyes...
I remember, my eyes were
still in top shape, but...
... when I arrived in the city, I got my eyes infected...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
GOT INFECTED IN THE CITY?
Infected?!
Why? Why did you get an infection in city?
That really happened!
- Really?  - Yeah!
Slowly, the speed isn't like it used to be.
- Your blinking skill?   - Really?
How fast is it now?
Alright, I'll try it.
- Let's see the quality now.
Here I go!
Eh?! So fast!
- That was fast!
Wasn't that fast?  - Really?
- That was good!
No, but...
- So you could do better?
That's not me...
- I wasn't like that...?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
I'M NOT LIKE THIS.
No, that's fast!
- I know, right?
But when we're having a handshake event, fan said
"Hori-chan, please blink quickly!"
So there would be many requests like that?
- Yes!
When I did it, they gave no reaction,
they just went "Ah....", like that.
I guess I can't do it anymore...
- How was the reaction?
"...Ah....", like that    - Were there
people like that when you did it?  - Yes!
Eh?!
- Like, for example...
He's the fan...   - Yes!
Let's do it. I'm the Hagashi!
Hagashi = A guard on the handshake event near the member's chamber.
They count the time in handshake too
Ah, sorry, can you do the quick blink?
"AH...."
That's so bad!!!
What's that?
- What's that? Please don't come again!
There are people like that?
- Yes! Lately...
Lately I thought about a rule
that maybe can be used for this specialty.
-  That's interesting, the "Ah..."
According to that, this is my advice for everyone.
When you're eating sushi, you have to enjoy it!
- What does it have to do with anything just now?
Where will this lead to?
-  What a unique presentation...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
ADVICE DIFFERS SO MUCH FROM THE EXPLANATION.
We're back here?  - Yes!
Clearly you've surprised everyone!
An advice from Inoue is...
I thought, it's been four years,
maybe it's okay.
This will...
- A surprising announcement?   - Yes!
What?
- Scary!
This time, I want to tell you about this...
I don't like my cute appearance.
- EEHHH!!??
What do you mean?
- You don't like your cute appearance?
Judging from my current appearance, I guess
many people will say "Ah, so Idoly!", but...
But isn't that good?
Back then since I looked like a boy,
people often mistook me for my brother.
And honestly, I don't really like girly things.
So you mean, even until now you don't like
cute stuff like that?   - Yes!  - Huh?!
Scary!
- Heehh!!?
So you're pretending all this time?
- Give us an example.
Like when on Nogidoko, when we had
a clothing style check.
Ah, we did that didn't we?
That time, I wore clothing that's
already prepared beforehand!  - EH!
NOVEMBER 2011
Here...
Cute... You really looked like a girl here.
Were that your clothes?
Actually my mom bought all these clothes.
I was forced to wear those.
Eh, so actually you don't like it?
- I hate it very much!
Oooohhh~!!!
That's pretty embarassing!
- So honestly you didn't want to?
- That...
Why?
Perhaps because of my brother.
Since I grew up with my brother,
I wore his clothes often.
Actually there was a photo back then when I was still in junior high.
This!
- With uniform?
BROTHER
MOTHER
CLOTHES INOUE USUALLY WEARS
Which one are you?
- Which one?
The middle one?
This one...
The right one?
- Yes!
That's me.
- That's Inoue?
The one with jeans and t-shirt?
- Yeah!
That's Sayunyan?
Next to me are my brother and my mom.
Did you wear his clothes often?
- Yes, I did.
Judging by this, we wouldn't imagine if she's
going to wear that one piece before.   - Right!
So usually you wear pants?
I don't want my body to be seen.
Oh, is that true?
- I'm pretty embarassed if that happens.
That's why I think it's very amazing if
someone dresses like Manatsu.
If there's a contest like, who's the most
"girl" between all members, you can win it if you want it!
UWEEEIII~~!!!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
VOMIT.
Uweeeiii~~~
I see.
- What's with that "Uweeii" ?
So you really hate it.
I see.
There's also something else...
- This sounds bad.
Oh she seems hate this too!
Let's see...
Sayunyan!
- Ah, this too?
If we look here, maybe I really
look like an idol.
Right, we think so.
- Yeah.
Like doing that "Nyan".
You have to do that,
- Yeah.   - Sayunyan has to do this.
It's really embarassing when I do it.
- Why?
I was confused back then,
should I get some nickname or no.
Did you think about this nickname by yourself?
- Seirarin made it up for me.
Nagashima Seira..
- Ah, Nagashima...
She said "It sounds like a cat".
But this is quite a good nickname.
- Sayunyan.
When we're doing a LIVE,
there are fans who call my name.
They all be like Saa~~Yunyan,
- I see....
Uwee, Sayunyan, Uwee
- Not like that...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
CALL & VOMIT.
What's with Sayunyan?
I am Sayunyan, not Uwee!
There's also one more thing I don't like.
- Another one?  - Really!?
This one is quite problematic for me.
This, Jyan~
Idol face?
- Idol face!  - What does this mean?
Actually I want...
A cool gaze....
Sparking from my face...
- Which part was that?
Where?  - What?
- What's with your face just now?
This... pshoo (some gibberish)...
Face with a gaze like that.
Like my face from I was born.  - I see.
I really had to make a soft face.
But now...
What do you mean face from you were born?
Like thick eyebrows?  - Yes!
Like Kato Ryo-kun?
- Well, he's...
Kato Ryo = A Japanese actor, famous for his super thick eyebrows
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
IDEAL?
That's pretty cool!
- I really want to look cool...
That's why I exercised so my body
can be stronger!
Stronger?
- Yeah.
And today I brought something I usually use
to train at home.
- Alright!
- Do you usually use this at home? - Yes!
INOUE SAYURI'S MUSCLE EXERCISE
And Inoue's muscle training
who doesn't like the cute character is...
You have to open your legs like this.
- Is that okay?
Legs wide open and bent.
Maintain a leaning forward body form.
That looks like Animal Hamaguchi-san,
Animal Hamaguchi = an ex free style wrestler
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
PRIMARY TARGET?
And then?
- Then pull the rubber back...
Like this...  - Ooh!
- That's quite...
What muscle is that for?
- For this muscle.
So you trained that part?
- Yes! This part doesn't look like girl's muscle.
This area for example,...
So you want to look more macho?
- Actually...
SayuMacho?
- SayuMacho sounds good!
Perhaps you want to be SayuMacho!
- SayuMacho??
That's pretty good!
- Then when you're being cheered in LIVE "SayuMa-Cho", like that?
SayuMa~Cho, SayuMa-Cho
-  Then probably you can...
The problem is this...
Okay here, Jyan~
I like that!
Look, she likes it!
Alright, are you kidding now?
Now you can get information regarding "UnderLIVE Zenkoku Tour"!
You can check Nagashima Seira's graduation message too!
The title of the next 14th single has been announced,
"Harujion ga Saku Koro".
This single will be released on 23 March.