m 0 0 l 0 27 l 2 27 l 2 0 l 0 0 m 2 0 l -4 0 l -4 6 l 16 6 l 16 4 l -2 4 l -2 2 l 0 2 m 2 2 m 16 0 l 16 27 l 18 27 l 18 -1 l 16 -1 m 22 0 l 22 0 l 24 0 l 24 11 l 19 11 l 19 9 l 22 9 l 22 2 l 15 2 l 15 0 m 6 18 l 6 12 l 12 12 l 12 14 l 8 14 l 8 18 l 6 18 m 12 18 l 12 20 l 6 20 l 6 18 l 10 18 l 10 14 l 12 14 l 12 18 m 5 7 l 8 9 l 7 10 l 4 8 l 5 7 m 10 9 l 10 9 l 13 7 l 14 8 l 11 10 l 10 9 m 3 24 b 3 24 3 23 3 23 b 7 21 11 21 15 23 b 15 23 15 25 15 25 b 11 23 7 23 3 25
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
NOGIZAKA KOUJICHUU
DON! Okay Nogizaka Koujichuu is starting,
we're the MC Bananaman, yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
BANANAMAN
Shitara Osamu
Himura Yuki
And here's Nogizaka-chan....
- Yoooo~~!!!
Alright!
We'll continue from the last week's episode...
It's been four years, huh?
- Yes.
It's been right after four years of Nogizaka's debut until now,
and they'll discuss many things that have happened.
Okay then!
First, an advice Kawago wants
to tell everyone about.
This time, the advice I want to tell you all is...
Don't aim too high!
Every members here certainly have felt that idols have to act
according to their targets, but...
In my case, my targets are
too high to aim.
Too high?
- Yes!
Basically, what kind of Idol did I aim for?
This...
Jyan~... Mayuyu!
Yeah!
When I passed Nogizaka's audition back then...
KAWAGO'S IDOL TARGET
AKB48  WATANABE  MAYU
"I wanna be like Mayuyu!",
that's what I thought.
That's good.
If we're talking about Mayuyu,
I think she's a Super Idol.
With her black hair, double twintail, and what's that...
Her introduction? Really suits her character.
Now you're not like her?
- Indeed!
Like, your hair isn't black.
Yes but I had straight black hair
and also half twintail...
... like a witch character.
- Ahh?!
Yeah!
- Did you really use that witch character?
I also had my own self-introduction like this...
[I'LL CAPTURE EVERYONE'S HEARTS
WITH MY MAGIC], like that.
You said that?
- Yes!
Surely now not anymore?
- Yeah since I have no magic no more.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
LANGSUNG MENGAKUINYA.
Really...
- Her nerve was amazing.
I see.
Aside from copying Mayuyu's character
to be like her...
To became like Mayuyu, I thought
I'm going to need this too, Ja~jyan~
Liking Anime!    - Ah, Mayuyu likes anime too.
Yes, with this, I...
Plus I wanted to be an idol
with anime lover character.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
IDOL  =  ANIME
Idol who loves two dimensional character.
- But there are many members here who like that too, right?
That's right, there are, but...
Since I wanted that anime lover character,
and I even added it into my introduction...
But honestly that was the first time
I studied alot about anime.
Eeehh!?
- That's right!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
STUDIED EXTRA HARD!
I recorded every new anime from the beginning...
even everyday, I kept looking at anime.
You studied them?
- Sure did...
There were also fans who've asked "What anime do you recommend??", and I answered that seriously.
- Amazing!
Actually I already prepared the answers regarding that anime series beforehand.
- You just wanted to get their attention?
Yes.
Even though I often presented myself
like Mayuyu, but...
...of course I made mistakes here and there.
- Mistakes?
Back then, me and Matsumura who like anime for real...
... did a show on Convention Day.
Here's the VTR...
SEPTEMBER 2011
NOGIZAKA 46 CONVENTION 2011
We're anime lovers, Matsumura Sayuri and...
... Kawago Hina.
Her hair!
We'll try our best to dance with the ending song of
Suzumi Haruhi no Yuutsu, [Hare Hare Yukai],
Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuutsu = anime about a girl's adventure,
Suzumiya Haruhi looking for supranatural things
Please enjoy, here we go!
- Here we go!
2011?
Ah, so cute!
What is this? 2011...
- Amazing... It's been five years.
Matsumura's voice is outlandishly bad.
That sounds bad.
They really did this!
I don't understand.
Wait a sec...
In order to look good, what did you
become?  - With song like that...
Ah, this song.
- Suzumi Haruhi no Yuutsu?
Please say something!
Okay, I did a show like that once.
- What is this?
- You didn't like it?
Actually, I know nothing about [Hare Hare Yukai]
nothing at all.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
PRETENDED TO KNOW
Really?
The night before that show, Matsumura
taught me how to sing that song, but...
When we were on stage that night, I thought
since I can't sing the song...
I didn't sing.
- Eh, that's cheating!
So you just Lipsync'd?
Yes, Lipsync. I did a Lipsync...
And that's why we could only hear
Matsumura's voice?
- Because the effect of her terrible voice was too strong!
Yes, in order to respect the animators,
and for my future's sake, I didn't sing along!
What a cunning girl!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
ROAD TO BE MAYUYU
Yeah!
- You couldn't sing it.
Actually, mistake like that happens often.
Like when Matsumura talked about this topic,
I understood a little.
Then there was an information from member regarding my
unclear character and I went too overboard.
That's why I stopped with Mayuyu as a target.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
GAVE UP TO BE MAYUYU
So this was your decision.
- Yes, I stoppped to be like Mayuyu-san.
And my next target was...Ja~Jyan~
Sashihara Rino! Yeah, Sashihara-san!
Kawago's IDOL target 2
HKT48  SASHIHARA RINO
- What do you mean?
This one is harder...
- Precisely!
Back on Nogidoko, I really wanted
to be a character like this.
On variety show...
- Is this "Really wanted to be like her"?
Were you being serious?
Yes but...
I wanted to be an idol
who's good on Variety Shows.
The one who can speak bluntly.
- I see!  - That's a good target!
You serious?
- I saw it, with hard work on variety...
... she successfully become a center.
- Ah, that's right.
That's why I decided to be like her.
- I see.
Yes, I already set my heart.
But then there was a big happening.
And that was...
Ja~Jyan~
Model.
What do you mean?
I already wanted to be a model
and of course...
... even I became an idol, that dream still
lingered inside me.
So you're interested?
- Yes, even though I'm not too focused
on this matter, surely...
There's a feeling of "wanting to draw attention
with my pretty face" like that.
So you've stopped to be like Sashihara?
- Yes, I wanted to be more beautiful...
- Is that true?
You've wore kendo mask before.
- Yeah.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
REAL MODEL?
We thought that's your character right there.
After that time, I really avoid stuff like that...
What was your target then? Did you want to become more
like Sashi?
- That time...
- Yes, something like that...
And you were okay with that?
- Yeah, that...
But it's only at that time. Honestly deep down
I wanted to be more beautiful.
And in the end, this was my target.
Ja~Jyan~
Kojiharu-san.
- There you go~
KAWAGO'S IDOL TARGET 3
AKB48  KOJIMA HARUNA
Whenever Kojiharu-san appears
in magazine...
... even she's in a group and an idol herself,
but she doesn't look like one.
- That's true!
But even though I thought I could be like her...
... there was a problem.
- What?
And it was...Ja~Jyan~
MY FACE
ISN'T AS GOOD AS HERS.
Okay, the reason why I can't be like Kojiharu...
That's because you two are different!
- Yeah!
- That's right, "My face isn't as good as hers".
So is this the conclusion?
Different?
It's good for you to realize this.
Not only Kojiharu-san, when I look at others' faces...
When I look into the mirror,
and then my appearance.
I became more and more sure that "My face isn't as good".
- I see.  - That's a difficult one.
So I decided to stop being an idol like that.
- You stopped?  - Yes!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
FINALLY GAVE UP...
Okay and I...
- Why tho?
... have an advice for everyone.
- About that?  - Yes!
Ja~Jyan~
Before you pick your target,
check yourself first.
So deep~
- What do you mean?
What do you mean by this?
- I don't get it at all.
This "Before you pick your target,
check yourself first," is very...
"Check yourself", what do you mean?
- That's... your "look".
Is look that important?
- Yes and I...
... only needed four years to accept this.
- I see.
Everyone, try to say this motto.
- Okay everyone, let's do this!
This is cool to be spoken together.
Alright everyone, go!
~Before you pick your target, check
yourself first~
Okay, that's all I want to tell you about.
Thank you very much.
So that's it?  - Yes!
Well from the very first, Nogizaka has been claimed as
an official rival of AKB, right?
But you've challenged many of
AKB members all by yourself...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
ALL ALONE DUEL VS AKB.
Yes, actually back then I didn't know much about AKB.
But after I watched them...
... I found many characters there.
And then I picked one.
... but in the end I'm confident with my own look.
I have become myself.
- Ah so you're back being yourself?  - That's right.
But if we look at the faces of her targets,
she looks nothing like them.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NOT SIMILAR...
Ah, like Mayuyu or Sasshi...
They're not similar at all.
Actually...
- Now her and Kojiharu, it's like heaven and earth!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
SO MUCH DIFFERENCE.
Not similar at all.
What? Who's your target now?
Who should I target now?
- What about Shibata Rie-san?
Shibata Rie = a famous Japanese actress who starred in many movies
One of them is Fast Furious Tokyo Drift, as a math teacher
KAWAGO'S TARGET FROM NOW ON
SHIBATA RIE
Her?
Okay, from now on my target is Shibata Rie-san...
- She gets many invitations from variety shows.
- She's unmatched!
If there's Shibata-san, that Variety becomes more exciting!
- The way she talks can also excite others.
Shibata-san is sexy too!
- Yes, she's sensual.  - Because her breasts are big!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
JUST LIKE KOJIHARU?
I guess others have some target too,
but in the end it's different. Anyone?
I always admire Yamaguchi Momoe-san.
- Ah you've said that.
Yamaguchi Momoe = a famous idol back in '80s
She's famous for her fragile face and sweet voice
Cool, you said you wanted to
be attractive like Yamaguchi Momoe-san.
I thought maybe my aim is too high...
- That's fine since this is just an aim
to be better.
I guess Takayama has some resemblance,
when she sings...
... there were some scenes when she got shot by the camera...
... I thought, "is that Yamaguchi Momoe-san?"
- Yay, yay!
She made a face just like
an idol from '80s.
Like...
No, it's not like that at all. The heck is this?
Like seeing an almost ripe persimmon fruit.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
WHAT IS THIS?
No, it's...
I felt like I can see the dried persimmon!
Like in pain...
- Painful... fragile...
Lonely face.
- Feels like her heart is broken.
I see. But now even though I'm not becoming like her...
Noo~!!! So disgusting~!!!
That camera was slowly moving closer
from there.
He was like "Ah, this seems interesting".
- Clearly that's not an expression she was talking about.
Then was his expression amazing
like Yamaguchi Momoe-san?
I only wanted to show idol's style
back in that era.
Eh, that was good even it's not all...
- It's not all?  - Yes!
So his expression was kinda similar?
Ah, similar enough.  - Lies! Really?
Au... his aura...
See? It's so similar.
Yeah!
THAT WAS AN ANGRY EXPRESSION!
No! That because he was slowly moving closer!
CONVERTED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
Next, an advice from Wakatsuki Yumi...
And the advice I want to tell you guys is...
This, Never Forget Your Own Self!
Yes!
- No, no...
THAT'S YOUR OWN SELF!
So... so because of that?
- Yes!
From my own experience, I want everyone
to never forget your own self.
- I see.
All these four years, I tried many characters too.
Even my characters weren't planned ahead,
it's still exhausting.
Until now, what all of you see is
another version of myself.
So, what kind of person I am?
I understand.
I will introduce my character first.
- This is gonna be a lot!
Well...
- Let's see.
Firstly, the very first character of mine,
Figting spirit.
Yes, I used this one on early days of Nogidoko,
when there was a fitness test.
That was so long ago.
- I know right!
And here's my photo at that time.
- Oohh
NOVEMBER 2011 SUDDEN FITNESS TEST
Written on my T-Shirt, "Fighting Spirit"
- Ah, I remember this!  - Yes, I used that once.
Actually that "Fighting Spirit" t-shirt had nothing
to do with that segment, but I still wore it.
This sounds like Inoki-san's famous slogan...
Antonio Inoki = the most famous ex wrestler in Japan
... and since that was a fitness test, I wanted to have a
fighting spirit to do it.
That's why when there's a hardship,
I hoped there will be a strong effect from this word.
I wanted to be called as "The Girl with #1
Fighting Spirit in Nogizaka".
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
CHARACTER 1 [GIRL WITH FIGHTING SPIRIT]
Like that!
I really wanted to be like that!
- I see, since that sounds so impactful.
That's right, the message is strong.
But there's more.
- More?
I had this from Nogidoko too.
- Nogidoko?
Beat Box.
Well this...
Back then...
SEPTEMBER 2014
WAKATSUKI'S TASK FOR SUMMER HOLIDAY
[BEATBOX] CHALLENGE
The coach who taught me said that
this is quite difficult for women.
Beat Box?
- Even if I could do it, it'll be very difficult...
... since women's muscle structures are different,
so that's why.
Honestly, I've only trained and taught
twice by the coach.
That's how many times I trained before my performance.
I did it and...  - Just twice?
Yes. In the end I still couldn't do it properly.
I see... looking back,
it was TERRIBLE!  - I know right?
- I didn't think it would be that bad.
- Yes!
Yeah even until now.
Yeah...   - Even at that time the coach said
I pulled it off, I thought...
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
Coach thought...
That's right.
The surprising thing is, when we were having a handshake event,
I got visited by some people who looked like they're a bunch of Beat Box pros.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
MEETING OF THE BEATBOXERS.
They did it in your place?
- Yes, they were showing it...
Right when they entered!?
- Yeah!
They were so good!
- That's scary...
That's right. After they're done,
they did "Pssshhhuuu..."
That sounds interesting.
- Yeah but also scary in a way...
Did you do it when they entered?
You were...
- Yeah!
They're must be saying "Hurry let's handshake!"
If they're doing that all the time, when will you give them handshakes?
I got visited by fans like that often.
This is really interesting.
- Then there's more...
Jyan~...Robot!
Why... after you stopped doing
Beat Box, then you became a robot.
I don't understand.
- Now this... alright.
THIS IS VERY INCREDIBLE!
- Yeah!
Isn't this good?
- Right...
Why this?
- The main reason is...
In a questionnaire, there was a question if I want to try
something new, stuff I want to do next.
AUGUST 2015
THE TRAGEDY OF [ROBOT DANCE] IN STUDIO!
Because of that question, I was so sure this could be
a unique thing I could learn.
Since I wanted to learn about
this robot dance, so I wrote it.
And then, at a meeting before the show...
Staff said, "You have to do it today."
But back then, could you only do that dance?
- Right.
The result was, I couldn't dance
but I became a robot instead.
That was the outcome.
- Well...
Even until now, I can still see you doing that!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
CAN'T BE UNSEEN EVEN UNTIL NOW.
That's all we can see.
Yeah...   - Other members did it too,
not just Wakatsuki.
Everyone did it too.
This appeared in handshake event too.
- Since everyone was doing it, it looked like
a big group of robot.
Eh, in handshake event too?
- Some people came to the event
with this robot style.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
MEETING OF THE ROBOTS!
Since he kept doing that, the time
ran out and he got forced out.   - Right!
Actually that...
What's this? Now I'm eager to see
Wakatsuki's handshake event.
- Why only Wakatsuki?
- It was quite a job for Hagashi.
There were different events only in Wakatsuki's booth!
- Exactly, I guess that's the effect of my actions.
- That's good!
What the?
- Moreover, there were queues.
Someone also said "I come with my friends!"
- Yes!
Actually it was a "queue of the robots",
- Queue of the robots?
Everyone became robots when they entered.
- Seriously?   - Yes!
That's why I'm thankful. Yes!
- The iii~Gasha~ Gang!
Wakatsuki did iii~Gasha~ too
She did...
Perhaps I did...
Next, the last one is this... Jyan~
Hashi-kun!
I love that~~!!!
- They love it! Look!
Hashi-kun is something.
- Wakatsuki've made quite some!  - Yeah, like...
It's only one person but with many characters instead!
All these four years...   - Yes!
Why it has to be Hashi-kun!
- About that...
I had a metting with staffs,
they asked me, "What do you want to do?"
DECEMBER 2015
TO LOSE A TOO SERIOUS CHARACTER
TAKING A HUMOR CLASS.
Ah, since there are many people told me "Lately
I'm being too serious."
Perhaps some might said "It must be hard
being a boring person like that."
In the end they prepared a plan for me
to attend a humor class.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NOT AS EXPECTED?
So you're not the one who asked for that?
- I've never said that, but since
they already prepared it, I did it.
There are many other choices,
but you chose humor...
Why not something else?
- They only gave me humor class.
The effect from this event also appeared some time ago.
When we're having a LIVE, there's always someone who called me with
[HASHI-Ku~n!]
Alright, I did the Hashi-kun trick.
But of course I'm not Hashi-kun myself.
Hashi-kun...
- It sounds like you're calling Hashi Yukio-san.
Hashi Yukio = an enka singer and a veteran actor
Besides, I often get this kind of gift too,
LOADS OF CHOPSTICKS.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
CHOPSTICK FLOOD.
I saw that!
I'm always having a trouble whenever
I received chopsticks in that amount.
- Incredible.
Were there people who came and
asked for this Hashi-kun in handshake events?
Ah yes! Someone even put
Hashi-kun on his body...
He put alot of chopsticks on.
- Lot of chopsticks?  - I see.
Someone also asked,
"Is Hashi-kun here today?" quite often!
There's even something like that!
- Did you show them if you had it with you?
I put it right next to me!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
EVENT OF WAKATSUKI & HASHI-KUN.
You're already prepared like that.
- Please, go ahead. I did that.
After we're done, my manager always cleaned them up.
Brought those back?
- This is so funny!    - Yes!
Besides, there's something I want to do
from long time ago.
This is different from those characters
I said earlier.
- What character is this?
Before I forget about it, I really
want to do my best to get it.
- What's that?
I have a dream to be an actress.
LIE!
W-wait a sec, I'm being honest!
- Sorry, I blurted out!
I want to be an actress!
- Well that...
You suddenly said
"I have a dream to be an actress."
That was so different with your presentation earlier.
That's why I blurted out just now.
- I see.
Is that really your dream?
- Yes, from the beginning.
This...
- Even though it's been called a lie before.
To be an actress in drama, I thought
I have to learn by becoming many characters.
- Ah, I see.
So you want to learn
from those characters?  - Yeah!
That way we can seize the opportunities
and still remember our goal.
That's what I want to tell everyone about.
Last but not least...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
COULD IT BE?
This...
What?!
- Eeeehhh~~!!??
We have Fork-kun, here everyone!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NEW CHARACTER EMERGES.
Hold on~!!!
You're adding a new character?
And for everyone here, there's something
Fork-kun wants to say.
She said "There's something Fork-kun wants to say,"
- What?
Wakatsuki's presentation,
has it pierced everyone's heart?
That's all and thank you!
No, this is wrong!
WAKATSUKI'S CHARACTER IS GONE FOR REAL!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
REALLY LOST!
This looks bad!
I see.
- What was that?
If she stays like this, maybe...
We will get tired and won't pay attention to her!
Every character of hers, how do I say this...
- No, no!
After this, what will the genius Ikuta do?
Lastly, an advice from Ikuta for everyone.
This is what I want to tell everyone...
Let It Go, leave it as it is.
Isn't this old school?
What do you mean by this?
- Why?
I think this is very important.
- Really?
After I heard everyone's stories,
For example, pretending for some show or
or doing a fake character so you can stand out.
I guess it's all lie.
That's what I think.
I don't mean to showoff, but up until now
I have never cheated!
Never!
- Because you're being yourself.   - Yes.
Without any ill intention, the results of
just being myself are...
First, there was an incident like this.
- What?
IH = Electric stove, induction without fire
IH Tragedy of Ikuta!
You were in hurry, weren't you?
- This...
- Was this because you're being yourself?
I tried so hard to cook that time.
And unexpectedly drew everyone's attention by making something.
DECEMBER 2011
THE FIRST COOKING SKILL
CHECK
She poured the mixed egg ontop of the IH
like nobody's business.
Then she added some sardine and konbu.  - Precisely.
Konbu =  dried seaweed
Usually used to make some broth
But I did that spontaneously.
- I see.
Even I failed, but
that incident was interesting.
That means, there was no special trick there.
- Yes.
Incredible!
- Yeah.
Then I also received this nickname.
- Nickname?
Ikuta The Artist.
I was seriously drawing at that time.
SEPTEMBER 2013
IKUTA DREW AN [E.T.] AND SHOCKED THE STUDIO!
I received this honorary title as the result.
This happens very often before I fall asleep,
that ET picture suddenly "Pan!!", appears just like that.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NIGHTMARE?
Its style like this is easy to remember!
- Really?
ET...
- I know, I know.
Aside from that, there's something like this too.
GLAY.
- GLAY.
GLAY = Japanese rock group from Hokkaido (Wikipedia)
I sang GLAY's [Yuuwaku] on Nogidoko back then.
NOVEMBER 2014
IKUTA'S [YUUWAKU] FROM GLAY BECAME A
HOT TOPIC ON THE INTERNET.
It got uploaded to the internet.
- I see.  - It became famous.
Moreover, it ranked second
below the real video from GLAY-san.
Amazing!
That's impressive.
- Really?
This came from my hobby singing
in karaoke and I like to sing that song, but...
It successfully attracted attention
of many.    - Ranked second?
Yeah.
- Amazing!  - Yes!
Looking at this, without doing something over the top or being dishonest,
If we do ordinary thing seriously,
we will get the best result.  - That's true!
I guess we can do this from now on.
So everyone, please,
Let It Go, just do it as it is.
That's an advice from me, Ikuta Erika.
Well that's because Ikuta is a super girl.
- No, no!
But a person with this type is great.
Just by doing ordinary things, we will get something extraordinary.
- That's right!
Probably since she's genius.
- Agree.
Look, this kind of face!
Look... look...
This...
This is her normal face, like... um... um
Like a face that understands nothing.
- What's with that face?
- Why is your face like that?
Even though that's normal, why did she become like that?
- Huh?
Ikoma will experience a tragedy!!
Did you rip it?
This summer, there will be an audition!
Seminar for Nogizaka46's Gen 3 audition.
What is Nogizaka46?
What do they usually do?
Question like that will be
answered directly by Gen 1.
The seminar is going to be held in these seven places.
Especially for the girls, we will be waiting for you!
Ikoma, do you like that stuff?
- Yes! I like it very much!
CONVERTED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
Ugh, he'll be like...
- Damn!!!
Ah..
Woah!!
I like a weird person like that very much.
At least you shouldn't forbid this.
This is why you keep letting me doing this.
m 0 3 b 0 3 0 3 0 3 b -7 -2 -10 -5 -10 -8 b -10 -11 -8 -13 -5 -13 b -2 -13 0 -11 0 -8 b 0 -11 2 -13 5 -13 b 8 -13 10 -11 10 -8 b 10 -5 7 -2 0 3
HOUSE!
National Tour "Under LIVE" Kouhoku Series
You can get the information from your phone!