DON! And Nogizaka Under Construction
is underway
we are your hosts, Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
and they are...
Nogizaka-chan~
There’s a lot of them.
Now, with these people are gathered here,
Please announce what we have for today!
Big announcement of the senbatsu members for the 14th single!
We’re already at the 14th single.
That’s really great.
Furthermore, they made an appearance in the Kouhaku.
-Right.
So, from here is a brand new..
The second chapter, isn’t it?
Nogizaka46
for their new single to go on sale
they'll select which members will be performing that song
Chosen last time are these 16 members.
For the 14th single, what kind of members will it be composed of?
We’ll start the announcement from the formation.
Here it is.
This is what it will look like.
We have 17 senbatsu members.
One more member than the last time.
Very well, we’ll start the announcement right away.
Oh, we’re doing it already?
Well then,
3rd row
#11
The first name to be called is…
Sakurai Reika
Sakurai.
Ever so supportive to Nogizaka as its Captain, Sakurai,
Selected as a senbatsu this time as well.
It’s been a while since we have this kind of ambiance right?
Well, it’s kinda like that.
Because I was first, I thought “Uwa.”
Something like you’re not yet ready but “Ah, it started already, I got called.” That kind of feeling.
But from here, it’s the 14th single. What are your feelings about this?
Of course, by having the privilege of performing in the Kouhaku,
I think that the attention given to us will rise immediately.
With awareness of that, I want to be active this year.
I would like the Captain to lead everyone properly.
It is the representation of Captain’s feelings.
What are you laughing about?
It means “I’ll do my best,” right?
That’s true.
What are they laughing about?
-Right?
Yes!
Those kinds of feelings become visible, right?
I’ll definitely lead them forward!
That’s what it was, right?
-You’re pumped up for this.
Were senbatsu announcements always like this?
[We have forgotten how it felt]
Well then…
-omedetou gozaimasu~
Now, let’s keep going.
-Okay.
Next…
Third row,
#17
The next one to enter the senbatsu is..
Hori Miona
It’s Hori!
Hori who has increased her skills in Under,
returning to senbatsu after three singles.
What are your current thoughts?
It’s been a while since I’ve been selected in the senbatsu,
I feel really happy for being selected in the senbatsu after a long time, but,
There are also feelings of frustration.
Little by little, while watching the senpais from behind,
I’m thinking that “It would be nice if I could go in front.”
Hori has gained various experiences too,
and those experiences became her strength. Do your best.
I’ll do my best. Thank you very much.
hai, omedetou, gozaimasu~
There are 15 left.
Next…
#12
The next name to be called is…
Wakatsuki Yumi
Her innate seriousness bloomed into a new character, Wakatsuki also made it in the senbatsu.
Last time, I’m also assigned in the third row but I was given the privilege of doing a stage play.
I was beginning to think that it wouldn’t matter even if I was in the third row position.
But in handshake events,
"Go into a spot where it’s easy for us to see you.” I think they’re saying that positively.
I still couldn’t respond to that, I’m sorry but,
I believe that this is the year to make things happen for Nogizaka.
I’d like to do my best. Yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
Wakatsuki has a lot of things going on too, like stage plays.
-That’s right.
You really are serious, huh? From one aspect to another.
Did you bring it today?
Today is… this is a bit of a proper occasion, so I have to stop.
[Self-restraint from Hashi-kun]
What exactly is a proper occasion?
I think that it's not suitable for the ambiance we have here.
That right there is being serious too, right?
[That’s being serious too]
Please do your best.
-yoroshiku onegaishimasu
Then..
-Yes.
Let’s proceed to the next one.
-Okay.
The next senbatsu member is…
Inoue Sayuri
Inoue with a remarkable growth in stage plays and the like,
selected in the senbatsu for three consecutive times.
Last year, Nogizaka was great as we’re getting bigger one by one.
Because everyone was doing their best while carrying Nogizaka’s signboard on their back,
I also wanted my favorite acting and stage play to become useful.
I want to contribute so that we can appear in other works.
That’s great
It feels like you really have matured.
Please do your best.
I’ll do my best.
The remaining spots… there are 13 spots.
Thirteen.
-Yes.
Next,
3rd row,
#13
The next name to be called is…
Matsumura Sayuri
With her cheerful character that brightens the show, Matsumura,
selected in the senbatsu this time as well.
Hhmm, what do I have to say?
It’s like… Because I have a lot of things that I want to do from now on,
I have to strive for that as well.
What’s the field of work that you want to strive for?
I wanted to do plays.
I’m not really good at it though.
It’s alright, it doesn’t matter.
But the things I want to do came out little by little from within myself.
Therefore, everyone is doing their best in their personal jobs in order to return the favor to Nogizaka.
Even everyone in Nogizaka thinks that it would be nice if the group gets bigger.
Splendid.
-Right?
Please do your best.
That makes it five.
There are 12 remaining spots.
The next senbatsu member is…
Ito Marika
omedetou gozaimasu~
She has expanded her range of activities with her unique tastes, Ito is also a senbatsu member.
Last year, I was also aiming at developing my field of expertise,
and to turn that into Nogizaka’s strength.
Recently, I’ve finally felt that, to be honest.
I feel that everyone is developing at what they’re doing.
Not just the front members, but I think everyone in the group are great.
This year, at least by developing, I also want to make a contribution.
That’s great.
Please do your best.
-Okay.
Now, the last one for the 3rd row, right?
-Yes.
3rd row,
The last one is…
Ikoma Rina
Active in variety as the face of Nogizaka, Ikoma,
in the 3rd row this time as well.
Thank you, thank you.
You also became an adult, huh?
-Yes, I’ve become an adult.
14th single.
-That’s right.
From that time as Taiyou Knock’s center, it could be perceived that I’ve gone downhill.
Personally, I really think that it was an easy place to work in.
There are a lot of opportunities handed down right there.
It’s not making me disappointed but,
It's just that, I hope that more people will be more interested in me.
Well, of course, ideally, getting on any spot is already good enough,
But to get closer to that, you have to make an effort.
Someone is watching, no doubt.
Do your best.
-I will.
omedetou gozaimasu.
From this point, it’s the Juu Fukujin.
2nd row,
#6
First one in the Fukujin is?
Saito Asuka
Expected to carry the next generation, Saito Asuka,
Fukujin for two consecutive times.
Last time, that was the first time I’ve been selected for the Fukujin,
From the beginning, the group has been supported by the front members,
I’ve been thinking that I’m still nothing compared to other members and onee-sans.
The Under members did a live concert at Bukodan,
For the senbatsu members too, the opportunities of work in here are increasing rapidly.
I was thinking, “Ah, I’m not doing anything.”
But aren’t you’re doing something, with modeling and stuff?
But maybe, this gloomy feeling of "I have not done enough" and lack of self-confidence is also a proof of growth.
The things that you didn’t understand before, but now you do.
Right?
Aren’t you a model?
Well, your comrades are here, and altogether…
It’s not like you’re doing everything on your own,
and I think everyone’s collective efforts are important.
That’s a merit of the group, to do things that complement each other.
You get along with one another, that’s what I think.
I’ll do my best.
-Alright.
Please do your best.
Now then, let’s move on.
Next,
2nd row,
#10
The next one to enter the 2nd row is…
Hoshino Minami
With an innocent character, she constantly fascinates her surroundings, Hoshino,
entered the Fukujin for two consecutive times.
Everyone, just like what we’ve seen a while ago,
have different jobs or more precisely, they have strong points.
But I have… none, right?
Really?
You got an amazing personality I think.
-No no no no no
Recently, at a handshake event,
I was told that “Why is Minami-chan included despite having no strong point? You’re really lucky, huh?”
Eh?
Someone told you something like that?
From the beginning, I’ve done a lot of things.
It’s so frustrating right?
Well, of course, comparisons are natural,
and it’s true that I don’t have a strong point.
So I don’t know why I’m chosen.
Then, having a visible strong point will also give me self-confidence,
I want to have that.
Really? Isn’t being cute enough?
The fans also said the same thing, but I can’t stay like this.
Is that so?
I’m already 18 years old.
You graduated from high school too…
-I graduated from high school already.
”Shouldn’t it be something that will make me a strange person?”
”Shouldn’t it be whatever that stands out?” These kinds of feelings will linger within you.
That’s right.
I think so too.
It’s offensive when someone says something like that directly on your face at handshake events.
I’ve thought about that too,
When I was told that, I thought that…
The person who said that is a trash,
That person’s life is somewhat worthless, that’s why.
You’re definitely working harder than that guy.
Then, you’re shaking his hands with a large smile on your face,
but it's not okay.
This is the 14th single and compared to the past, you’re quite successful already,
But with the way you talk right here,
Members with senbatsu experience who came here
brought in new troubles they were facing.
There are those who even cried.
-That was the case just now.
But, it’s been 2 singles since the last studio announcement,
It’s been a while.
-since the last time I’ve had a conversation with Bananaman.
You seem to have a father-figure.
Father-figure?
[Father?]
Well, for me, that really warms me up inside,
-That’s right.
Ah, but, right now, I don’t want you to use that.
We’re supposed to be your Onii-chan, but father?!
[Official Father]
Do your best.
-I will.
Thank you very much.
Now, there are only 8 spots remaining.
Next…
2nd row,
#7
The next one to be called is…
Takayama Kazumi
Takayama who fully displays her strong personality in the show,
also made it in the Fukujin.
Because 2015 has been really fun and fulfilling year,
for 2016, I have dreams that I want to do.
I’m also hoping that Nogizaka will become bigger.
What kind of dream?
Something like.. Nogizaka performing two or three songs in a music show.
It has always been one song for us and it’s not enough to give everyone exposure.
It would be great…
Please stand still.
[Please calm down]
With several songs,
Everyone will have a camera exposure, then everyone will be happy.
For this idea to happen, combining our individual strengths is not a futile effort. I’ll do my best.
Please do your best.
I’ll do my best. Thank you very much.
Then, let’s continue...
Next,
2nd row,
#9
The next one selected for the Fukujin is…
Akimoto Manatsu
Pushing forward on to the idol road she’s aiming for, Akimoto,
entered the Juu Fukujin this time as well.
As for my goal this year, I’d like to be a leading presence in the group even just a little.
For the members who are doing their best in various places..
at the time when they came back, Nogizaka is… how should I put this,
I want to be right there to give stability to the group while they’re at their other jobs.
That’s right, I think that your home base must be strong too.
With assertiveness, right? You want this show to be able to withstand their absence, right?
But if I have too much screen time, I think that will be a bit annoying.
If we cut that part out, it’s all good.
[We’ll do it here]
Is that true?
It’s alright, getting more exposure. This is Nogizaka’s own show after all.
I’ll do my best.
-Please do your best.
Thank you very much.
Now, the last one for the 2nd row.
2nd row,
#8
The last one in the 2nd row is?
Eto Misa
From Under to 1st row, dashing up on Nogizaka’s stairs, Eto,
this time, she’s in the 2nd row.
On the last single, I’m assigned in the 1st row,
and when you look at it, my position fell.
But with this, I’ve been chosen as Under and Senbatsu, then I’ll have experience from all rows.
I have just realized it now.
-Ah, really?
I don’t know what my strong points are, but...
...being in the end row of Under, then 2nd row, then 1st row,
then on the Senbatsu too, having experience in all of those positions,
Even just a little, I think it would be nice if it worked as an asset for the team.
After hearing that you’ve experienced every row,
That is your sense of stability.
No matter what position you’re in, you can get used to it.
Please do your best.
-I’ll do my best. Thank you as always.
Now, the 2nd row is occupied.
Finally, the 1st row. Five spots, right?
All that’s left is the first row,
Who will be called first?
Ikuta Erika
Her unwavering spirit continues to leave a strong impact, Ikuta,
she's in the first row this time.
After hearing everyone’s stories,
Each one has a wonderful strong will,
they also have various thoughts.
Being in the first row,
I want to spend these days without compromising anything.
But in my case, I often… what was it?
I ponder with it too much.
The pressure is too much, it will make you feel really small.
With a positive sense, I’ll set myself free,
I'll stretch the antenna of my interest to various things,
Then it would be nice if I could transmit various kinds of myself.
Even if you’re feeling pressured, it seems that you’re able to push it aside though.
Yes, but it’s really something I don’t have to face head on,
because I won’t be able to accomplish anything.
I made a barrier so that I can’t feel or encounter that pressure,
because there are a lot of things I want to do.
-Ah, is that so?
For this single to, I hope that I could move freely in a positive sense.
Do your best in leading others forward.
-I’ll do my best.
Now, there are only four left.
-Four.
Next,
1st row,
#1
Next one to enter the first row is…
Hashimoto Nanami
Hashimoto has always supported the group as a Fukujin,
she’s in the first row this time.
My main concern is,
I get sick more often than anyone in the group.
Paying attention to your physical condition is something that must be done as a person.
That’s something I want to do properly from now on,
As one person is given more work, so are the responsibilities.
As expected, I think that there are people around me who are concerned about that.
So that I can respond to it in a good way, I’ll pay attention to my health.
I hope that I can do my best.
Physical condition, to some extent, there are parts where we can’t do anything about it.
But in busy situations, you have to get going to some extent, right?
That’s right.
-Please do your best.
Thank you very much.
The spots remaining are numbers 2, 3, and 4. Three spots.
The next name to be called is…
Shiraishi Mai
Last time, she served as half of the double center, Shiraishi,
this time, she’s in the 1st row position.
In August, it will be 5 years since the group was formed.
When you think of it, time goes by so fast..
But I think there are still a lot to come for Nogizaka,
for myself as well.
We won't get satisfied just because we have already performed in the Kouhaku.
There are still a lot of new roads to go to from here.
I think that there still a lot of things that we have to open up.
That goes for me as well.
With everyone as a group, I think we have to work hard this year.
That’s right, from here on out, you have to put in new efforts, it feels like you’re starting again.
Please do your best.
-Thank you very much.
Who will serve as center for the 14th single?
All that’s left are two spots, huh?
-Two.
There are two remaining spots,
Whose name will be called?
Nishino Nanase
Nishino also moved from being a  double center last time
to a position that supports the new center.
Here, for the nth time,
I’ve been selected for the 1st row for a long time now but,
Even now, I’m wondering why I’m in this spot.
There are also a lot of worries but,
Looking at myself like this,
”Do your best”, or “I admire you”, the people who say these kinds of things have increased.
There are also hopes that these kinds of people continue to increase.
Because of those people, gradually, ideals like “I want to become like this”
These kinds of ideals are coming out from within me.
Well, while thinking about why,
Right now, these things that you want to get done,
I wonder if you have accomplished them to some extent?
We’ll look forward to it.
I’d like to do my best.
Okay, do your best.
Thank you very much.
Now, all that remains is the Center.
Very well, the announcement for the Center.
Who will be selected as the new center?
Fukagawa Mai
hai, omedetou gozaimasu~
Fukagawa who has just announced her graduation,
With her first center experience, can she decorate that hanamichi?
Hanamichi (lit. flower path) - passage to the stage where flowers are given
Fukagawa, you have announced your graduation, right?
This will serve as your last single.
At the center position
What are your thoughts right now?
Honestly, that feeling of wanting to be happy also exist,
But the feeling of being scared is strong.
But after listening to everyone’s words,
It’s our first single of the new year.
No matter what the reason is,
I was chosen as center so I can't let myself hold the group back from succeeding.
Well, about that…
Up until now, you’ve been doing this with your comrades, and with everyone’s effort, that have solidified the group.
A member who feel at ease, there’s none right?
You should stop thinking about holding everyone back,
Instead, it would be better to think of running through to the end, right?
We’re looking forward to it, on what will it be.
You’re the center, but please lead everyone for the last time.
Please?
omedetou gozaimasu
-omedetou gozaimasu!
Nogizaka46 go out to meet their new Center, Fukagawa Mai.
A brand new starting point!
Getting in here is really that hard, right?
But, I'll say this here over and over,
Don't feel discouraged, do your best.
When your turn came up, so that you could deliver,
you have to prepare yourselves.