DON!
Well, it has begun.
Nogizaka Koujichuu.
We are BANANAMAN. Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Here they are, Nogizaka-chan!
Ah, many!
Well, there are many coming here today.
-What we will do, Himura-san...
-Alright!
the theme for today, please announce it!
Come! New staff recruitment competition!
It is a recruitment competition.
The cue card didn't show up at all.
In "the 3rd Planning Presentation Presentation", Akimoto proposed it.
"Spring's New Staff Recruitment Competition" is accepted and realized.
Presenting the plan that oneself wants to do in "the 3rd Planning Presentation Presentation", Akimoto proposed this.
Each of these 5 managers who wants to set up her activity will present the charm of that!
This time these five managers will report on activity they want to set up.
Ikuta Erika | Ikoma Rina | Matsumura Sayuri | Takayama Kazumi | Hori Miona
One by one in order, they will present the charm of that activity.
After all presentations are done, all members other than those five people will submit a entry application to the activity that they want to enter.
All members other than those five...
at the end, will submit an entry application to a activity they wish to enter.
They will get along better then, right?
By sharing a same purpose.
Right! Although their schools, communities, and friends are slightly different from each other.
Isn't it so, Rotti?
Yes! Different, a bit!
Suddenly the switch is turned on!
First presenter is Ikuta Erika.
Well, so then, let's begin. Ikuta Erika, onegaishimasu!
Ready, start!
Activity that I want to set up is this!
- Scuba diving!
- Good!
When we went filming in Guam, there were some free time.
So I tried to have a diving experience.
Together with me at that time were Matsumura and Nishino.
Firstly, I have a VTR from that time.
Please take a look at that.
Here it is!
Great! You filmed it.
Great! Great!
Who is who?
Who is in the middle?
This in the middle is Nacchan.
Ah! Is it Nishino?
- This one is me.
- That is Ikuta.
- And this one is Mattsun.
- Ah! I see.
How many meter below surface was this?
Because there was no instructor, we couldn't go deep.
- Because you just want to experience it, right?
- We were just in the shallow water.
Even so, it was really enjoyable.
- Enjoyable, right?
- So enjoyable, you know.
Well, because I couldn't hear anything underwater...
Recommended point: silent and mysterious scenery will make you forget troubling things!
I saw a silent and mysterious scenery that made me forgot troubling things.
Definitely, I want everyone to have this experience too.
So I want to set up this activity.
Ocean, right?
Apart from that team of three people, Hoshino also had a diving experience.
Is this Hoshino?
This is Minami.
Eh? Alone?
Why? Why?
You did it alone?
Lonely.
What's the bait?
It's being fed. Feed can be given to fish.
- Why did you do it alone?
- Why alone?
Well...
With Hori Miona and a staff, there were 3 people including me at first.
Those two people...
said "My leg is heavy" "It's hard to breathe". Then they didn't come underwater.
All the time, I was feeding alone, filming alone, and taking photos alone.
Lonely diver.
Eh, what? Hori couldn't go underwater?
(Note) See Nogizaka Under Construction Episode 49.
There's a reason for that.
On the day before, I had experienced Tagada Disco and Reversed Bungee.
So my body was shattered.
Total exhaustion.
- That was hard.
Guam environment is kinda unsuitable for my body.
There was a "Wa~" feeling.
Definitely, it was so hot.
If I took the challenge, it'd be too hard.
Even though you wanted to try it, but you're troubled, surely, right?
Is it about my father?
What happened?
(His father) was unable to relieve ear pressure, right?
It's difficult, isn't it? In reality.
- Then Himura-san, though it's impossible, said "It's okay! Just force it!"
- My father.
"Because it's rare that we are in this place."
"Is it okay? Is it?"
"It's okay! It's okay!" Then he did it.
- After that, on the plane he kept saying "There's something weird", right?
- Kept saying that.
Arriving in Japan, both of his ear drums were torn.
Donbiki
(Note) Donbiki: a phrase that refers to when people get creeped out or turned off by something
Even those who think that it's scary...
I'm sorry for that.
Please rest assured!
- Ah, I'm wearing it, you know!
- Different! Different! It's different!
(Note) Tonikaku Akarui Yasumura's gag in which he told people not to worry because although he apparently doesn't wear an underwear but actually he's wearing one.
Are you wearing it?
Don't look! Don't look!
Because there are proper steps...
Firstly, the main activity to follow is this!
Acquiring a license
- Get a license?
- Acquire a license.
Get a scuba diving license.
Properly, inside this country, it will be safe...
to do it if you are properly licensed.
Inability to relieve ear pressure. There will be no such problem.
- It is easy to get this license, isn't it?
- Right!
About 3 days will be enough.
- Uhm, that's why, no need to be afraid.
- Don't be afraid.
And considering the filming has to be qualified as interesting...
Amami Islands or Okinawa can be the filming location. That's what I think.
Get a license at the beautiful sea of the country.
- At such a beautiful place, let's get a license!
- Isn't it great?
- Isn't it the best?
- Isn't that the best?
Then, when we already get our license...
I'm also an asistant.
Flip collector
- Ordinarily handed over.
- No problem. No problem.
Let's go to the world-leading diving spot!
At world-leading diving spot.
- Isn't that great?
- That's amazing, right?
And the specific locations are...
Thank you.
Firstly is this! Maldives!
It's possible to swim with sea turtles in the Maldives.
Overseas?
Yes! Overseas. Must go!
- Maldives Islands?
- Yes. It's not just Maldives.
The next!
I want to go to Palau too.
- Awesome. Is this presentation not a lie!?
- It's not a lie. Serious.
Properly, staffs consider it.
- About 4 hours from here, right?
- Right. It's near, you know, in fact.
This is Manta ray.
I love Manta ray!
Whatever! What you are saying!
Himurotti
It's full of good thing.
There's no risk in it.
Seriously, so far, if everyone wants to join in, isn't it too much?
Right. I think so.
And if you get the license...
I wonder if our field of work will expand.
For example...
Ikuta to infiltrate world TV program.
Who knows, maybe it'll be able to come true.
- After that, right?
- Right! Right!
It became Ikuta-only (TV show) though.
- Everyone...
- I am not in yet.
- Just to say, right?
- Right, right.
Nogizaka Scuba Diving.
Manager Ikuta is waiting for new members.
Hori, how do you feel when you heard this?
Ah, I'm not interested.
Totally unimpressed.
Eh?! Why is that?!
Awful! Hi hi hi! Awful!
- Well, because she is already put off once, right?
So, that's why.
Even before this, she is already put off.
- No way!
- No interest.
She's been traumatized.
Well, surely, you will get a license. There's plenty of time to phase in.
I'm sure you'll be fine. That's what I think.
How is it, Hori?
I don't have such time.
Why so suddenly?
Was she such a rebellious kid?
Why suddenly so stubborn?
It's from that Guam's time.
(Left) Mysterious Yahoo Championship is held!?
(Right) After this, Ikoma presents mountaineering
Subtitle by Qelopin
(qelopin.blogspot.com)
The next presenter is Ikoma Rina.
Onegaishimasu! Ready, start!
The side activity I want to make is this!
Mountaineering!
Why do I want this activity?
I had gone to Mount Fuji once.
At that time, I was very touched.
Everyone together...
Moment of Mount Fuji climbing
(Note) See Nogizakatte, Doko? Ep 153 and 154
Everyone's face when they reached the summit is great.
When we were on the mountain...
we had a very strong bond.
It was so hard for me to go, but...
Overcoming. Achieving.
I can feel it just by climbing.
Recommended point No. 1: You can experience the sense of accomplishment after hard work.
I think this is really wonderful.
And when it comes to mountain climbing...
everyone, mountaineering can free you away from crowds of hustling people.
Also, at some point it'll be exhausting, but...
in that kind of environment...
we can be healed by the good air in the mountains.
Recommended point No. 2: Liberated from crowds in the city and healed!
It can refresh your body and mind, I think.
It is really popular now, isn't it?
Climbing up the mountain.
I think it's like a theraphy...
from recent exhaustion.
Although it's hard, it's hard to hear the voice of others.
Of course, it will be hard on the way up, but...
please take a look at this smile of Minami-chan.
Hoshino: Full smile
When climbing Mount Fuji...
it is possible to make this person, from her heart, smiled so refreshingly.
- It's from her heart, isn't it?
- From her heart.
But it was really exhausting.
It was like, like, how is it.
"Finally I don't have to climb anymore" like that.
To be honest I forgot to have smiled like that.
I absolutely will not join!
Absolute refusal
She won't be joining.
Eh, which members went mountaineering at that time?
Seriously, altitude sickness was really painful.
The altitude sickness took place at the 8th checkpoint.
I really wondered whether I could step on the ground anymore.
And it ends here.
Because it's so painful and your life might end in the mountain...
I don't want to go mountain climbing anymore.
Remember! Remember this excitement!
- This excitement.
- So you no longer want to climb.
Cornered Ikoma has a secret strategy.
The cornered Ikoma, here, has something up her sleeve.
Climbing mountain is like something old men and women do.
Some people have that opinion, but...
Recent climbing gears are very cute...
and there are a lot of enthusiasts.
- Really?
- So...
I have investigated the mountaineering gears in advance.
The video... is on the monitor.
Here it is.
"Kojitsu Sanso" Ginza shop
Toru Okuda-san
This is Kojitsu Sanso Ginza shop.
In its branch shop, in Nagoya, I am a member.
- A member?
- Yes, yes.
- There are lots of cool outdoor gadgets.
- There are so many wonderful things.
From this Okuda-san, I got a lot of recommendations.
First is climbing bag.
Firstly, the backpack is required when climbing.
This...
Its waist and chest straps can be adjusted easily.
It's really light.
- It's used differently in the city.
- Yes, different.
It's very light and convenient.
During the hike, water supply is very important.
- That's for drinking water?
Right, attached in the backpack.
I always get to drink a little while walking.
It's a really fun way to walk and be healthy simultaneously.
If you have a big tank, you'll keep drinking.
The tank is a little heavy.
Tonkotsu soup or something.
(Note) Tonkotsu soup is similar to pork stew
The idea of a pig.
Dangerous, you might bring sake for that, but not tonkotsu
Isn't that good?
At the peak, wouldn't you want to eat delicious food?
- I want to eat.
- Recently, convenient food has greatly developed.
This kinoko pasta. Just add some hot water and you can eat it.
- It sounds like fun.
- I want to try this.
And next!
Speaking of mountain, it's bear!
Well.. bear.
A bear can possibly come out too, can't it?
There is a countermeasure good. It's a bear spray, like this one.
Can this be used?
This is a pepper spray that will make bears really uncomfortable.
Bear is in fact particularly timid.
They don't come near where humans are talking.
For example, on a road corner...
there will be a pattern where we encounter a bear.
If you use this spray...
It is possible to walk away safely while protecting yourself.
When you meet it at the corner, from your bag you need to take it out.
But it's right here, from here.
Why?
Why are you having a drink at this time!
You will be knocked down before you do it.
But it is easily reachable as it hangs right here.
Does it hang properly there?
- Does it keep hanging on this all the time?
- Yes, it is.
Is it so dangerous?
- It is not that dangerous.
- That's its place.
It could be.
Encountering bears is dangerous.
And one more...
Bee... or snake. If you're bitten...
Use this product immediately.
It will suck the venom out.
What is this?
- Properly.
- This is from some time ago.
Shiraishi, if a snake comes out, it will be okay.
No, absolutely impossible!
You can choose the clothes too.
- There are many kinds.
- Many cute ones.
I have recently been told about climbing women.
It's possible to pick what you like with your own selection.
It's dangerous to fall into outdoor goods.
Ikoma in changing room
It was very cute.
So I took the chance to try it on.
- I wonder what you'll wear.
- What I wear. Here it is.
Ah! Here it is!
This one, and...
great headgear.
Because I care about ultraviolet rays, I use a big hat.
But if it was sunglasses here...
I'll be unrecognized somehow.
Without being seen by anyone.
- Very good.
- Like a pro.
But it's good. Somehow I want to go climbing.
I was so prepared for this...
Because I think it was a great feeling.
So I begin to do shopping in mountaineering.
I might be a good thing.
Taste climbing gourmet
Here you can see the climber gourmet introduced in the studio.
Today, it's this mochi.
- It's mochi.
- Can you eat this?
Eating mochi on the mountain.
Please imagine that you are eating at the summit.
- Got it!
- OK.
Ah, I do not want to eat mochi at the summit.
Wrong. No, no, wrong.
Sorry, sorry.
- What is this?
- This is mochi.
- It's stiff.
- It's hard.
Waters mochi: Add water and wait for 3 minutes
Just pour water into the container and wait three minutes.
- Does this only need to be watered?
- Just water.
Is this boiled water?
Just some water.
Seriously!? Only water?
Ah, great! Great!
- Now it has become mochi.
- It's mochi.
It got so sticky.
- It's okay with water.
- It's amazing how it's okay with water.
It's isobe mochi.
- It's soybean flour.
- It's soybean flour, isn't it?
Oh, but it's delicious.
It's soy sauce powder.
Look at this. It's soy sauce.
It contains a soy powder and seaweed.
Amazing.
The smell, the smell comes out.
Isobe smell.
There's also nori.
- Wrapped in nori.
- Wrap.
- Sticky isn't it.
- It's thick.
Tasty, tasty.
Mochi, mochi, mochi.
What if you eat this at the top?
Cover it up.
It's good to eat these at the top.
Thank goodness.
Delicious.
Who wants to eat the other one?
- Me.
- No, no.
- You've had it.
- This is delicious.
Although climbing has tiring and difficult impression...
For example, in spring or autumn...
- Autumn leaves on the mountain.
- There will be foliage.
Plateau where you can walk for mountain climbing.
- Good, isn't it.
- Something like that is there, really.
Seems like you want to try to shout, don't you?
- Try to shout.
- Have you ever shouted 'Yahoo'?
- A serious Yahoo.
- Serious.
Shouting out loud. You really want to do it.
- It's amazing.
- You do not want to.
Want to...
Yahoo.
Go ahead. Try to do your best.
Serious Yahoo.
Quite, quite a shout.
Great!
- Good, interesting!
- Just do it.
Wait, Wakatsuki.
- How, how much do you like to try it?
- Wakatsuki!
Do it seriously.
- As if at the summit.
As if at the summit?
- No, no, no.
- Great! Feels good.
Actually, I've done it.
Hashimoto, Hashimoto, wanna try?
I've done it too.
- No, seriously.
- A serious Yahoo.
Now try to assume that here is the top of the mountain.
Eh?
- This is a bit...
- The intonation is a bit...
Yahoo! A bit like that.
Himetan.
Try to do it as if here is at the summit.
Is it Himetan?
Loud, loudly, seriously.
Stand up for a while.
At a summit.
Let's scream it out loud!
Wrong. He he wrong.
Serious yahoo. Serious yahoo.
That was not serious yahoo.
Himura-san. Can you show your serious yahoo?
Here is at the summit.
Mr. Yahoo
- Why does it make me laugh like this?
- Do it like this!
Everyone wants to do it at the summit, right.
- Want to do it.
There are a lot of various yahoo.
- That is fun, right?
- Right!
After this, Matsumura will be presenting anime voice acting activity!
Next presenter is Matsumura Sayuri.
This is the side activity I would like to establish.
Anime voice acting.
- Voice acting?
- Yes.
Anime voice acting.
I really love anime.
- All the time.
- I love Anime all the time.
I want to present you this charm of anime voice acting.
I thought I want to set up this activity today.
Firstly, its main activity is this!
Voice acting school.
Well, this exists, doesn't it?
Main activity: Learn the basics by going to the voice acting school.
In here, foundation is necessary in the beginning.
We are really careful about the voice.
- You're doing it right.
- Properly.
- Are you studying?
- Well, really.
It's really possible that you get a job from this activity.
But to be honest with you...
Even everyone who is really talented is auditioned.
In the audition, it won't get you an exact certain role.
There are a lot of people who really aim at this.
It is said that only 1% can be a voice actor.
There a very narrow chance to be a voice actor as it's only 1%.
So firstly, let's start with the basics.
I do not know if one of you might be voice actress in the future.
Even if that is not the case, there may be a possibility that someone might have that voice.
- I think it would be good if you do this.
- Yes.
In order to know the charm of the voice acting here, let's do dubbing impromptu challenge!
Voice acting improvisation challenge!
Heidi role of "Heidi, Girl of the Alps"
Dubbing Heidi role in this scene from "Heidi, Girl of the Alps"
Well, then, I'd really like to try dubbing this scene.
But probably you're not interested.
- Well, first, Himura-san.
- I want to do it.
Himura san, please voice Heidi's role.
Acting as Heidi?
Heidi!?
- Not the old man?
- Yes, Heidi's voice.
Himura-san is famous for producing various voices.
- That's right.
- Right!
Really! You voiced in Minions.
Ah, right, right, right.
In other roles also, he did it. Many.
But all of them are monster roles.
A bunch of monsters.
Never a human being.
Himura Yuki
Bananaman
Voice acting challenge.
So what are you going to do now?
Show me what grandfather has in the house!
Well, it's okay.
You bring those in.
I do not need it anymore.
You're a weird kid.
Why don't you need it?
I want to run around like a goat.
But bring your clothes.
It's cool.
That was enough.
It's hard.
Well, who would like to try it?
Anyone want to try?
Quite a hurdle. This one.
- Me!
- Ah, Rotti.
Will it fit?
- It will fit.
- Please do.
Kawamura Mahiro
voice acting challenge.
So what are you going to do now?
Show me what grandfather has in the house!
Cute cute.
Well, it's okay.
You bring those in.
I do not need it anymore.
You're a weird kid.
Why don't you need it?
I want to run around like a goat.
But bring your clothes.
It's cool.
Well, that's good.
Well, it's as if it's her job.
- It is.
- So good.
She has uniqueness in her voice.
Well, when I'm on the phone...
I have a voice like a kindergarten.
I think that voice will be something.
Really? It's just my voice unaltered.
- But it's fine.
- That was fine.
Well, really...
Is there any possibility of developing something from the activity?
That's right.
This is the goal of this activity.
Final goal, to get to be "anime voice actress" of your favorite series.
This is the final goal.
- Voice actor.
- That's what it means.
Matsumura Sayuri buchou , anime voice acting activity , join!
Nogizaka anime voice acting activity.
Matsumura buchou is waiting for new recruits.
Still more club member recruiting activities!
What is Takayama's club activity?
Nogizaka46 2nd album, Sorezore no Izu.
Premium events will be held for purchasers!
You can apply for an event by purchasing an album.
More details on nogizaka46 official website!
And!?
Manatsu no Zenkoku Tour 2016
Acceptance of Rakuten preorder ticket starts from May 11!
Stage Joshiraku
It is finally starting from May 12!
And then...
Fukagawa Mai Photobook "Zutto, Soba Ni Itai"
To release on June 9!
Do not miss it!
(Right) Next time... The second half of the new club members recruiting!
(Left) In the end who will attract members the most!?
Finally announced entrants!
Finally it will be decided!
What is the result?