m 0 0 l 0 27 l 2 27 l 2 0 l 0 0 m 2 0 l -4 0 l -4 6 l 16 6 l 16 4 l -2 4 l -2 2 l 0 2 m 2 2 m 16 0 l 16 27 l 18 27 l 18 -1 l 16 -1 m 22 0 l 22 0 l 24 0 l 24 11 l 19 11 l 19 9 l 22 9 l 22 2 l 15 2 l 15 0 m 6 18 l 6 12 l 12 12 l 12 14 l 8 14 l 8 18 l 6 18 m 12 18 l 12 20 l 6 20 l 6 18 l 10 18 l 10 14 l 12 14 l 12 18 m 5 7 l 8 9 l 7 10 l 4 8 l 5 7 m 10 9 l 10 9 l 13 7 l 14 8 l 11 10 l 10 9 m 3 24 b 3 24 3 23 3 23 b 7 21 11 21 15 23 b 15 23 15 25 15 25 b 11 23 7 23 3 25
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
Nogizaka Koujichuu
DON! Alright, Nogizaka Koujichuu is starting
and we're the MC, Bananaman, Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu...
BANANAMAN
HIMURA YUUKI
SHITARA OSAMU
And here's, Nogizaka-chan ~
Okay, without further ado,
Himura-san, please announce our segment for today!
- Yes!
To commemorate Nogikoi release,
Ideal Boyfriend Presentation!
In order to commemorate the release of
Nogizaka46's love game...
... in tonight's segment, members who are not allowed
to date will tell us their ideal boyfriend types.
All of you had answered
the questionnaire...
What I have in my hand right now
is the original questionnaire.
They totally wrote it until it's full!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
THE LONG-WAITED SEGMENT.
Up until now, they have never wrote this much
on questionnaire for other segment in this show.
I guess if we release this out,
it will be a big hit.   - No, no, no!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NOGIZAKA46 GUIDEBOOK.
That's right, people
will be interested in this.
Well then, Himura-san...   - Yeah?
- I'm selling this to you for 200.000 Yen...
[ 200.000 Yen = about 2000 USD ]
That cheap?
Without any more waiting, here's
Takayama's ideal man type.
Okay, I'm ready... not too tall.
- What?
That's...   - 110cm...  - That's too short.
- He might be mistaken as an elementary student.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
EXTREME EXAMPLE.
Tall people in general have deeper voice...
- Like Giant Shirota-san,
[ Giant Shirota = Nobuyuki Shirota, Japan's champion of competitive eating (yup)
Choi Hongman =  A 2,18 meter K1 South Korean fighter ]
Ah, right, like Giant Shirota-san, or
that guy, Choi Hongman, both of them are...
- They're not the same!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
EXTREME EXAMPLE.
Their voices are similar!
- Clearly they're more than 110...
But in my imagination,
tall people have deep voice...
... so I think short person might be better...
- How short?
I'm 160cm myself, ehm,
I guess it's okay if he's shorter than me.
You don't want someone as tall as you?
- Is 150cm good?
I think it's cuter.
- So taller is fine?
Yes, a tall person might be fine.
But I think tall person's face is too far, so...
- What kind of person is that?
But when you kiss her it will look sweet,
like when you're on your tiptoe...
Is that too old school?
- If he's shorter then I can just...
But maybe I will get used to it... maybe I...
- How cute ~
No, this is embarassing.
What's this all about?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
THERE'LL BE MANY MEMBERS ACTING LIKE THIS TODAY.
It's okay.
- This is nice, she's that embarassed.  - Nice...
Takayama's next ideal criteria,
having white skin, plus...
His clothings are lame.
- Seriously?!
I just realized this recently...
... one time, I passed a man...
He had this bag
hanging on his shoulder...
... I saw him tightly gripping on it...
I thought,
"That's so cute!"
But it's not only that.
Regarding clothing, I'm also interested in someone who...
... like, I can ask him "What about this clothes?"
and wearing pairing clothes...   - Pairing clothes?
His fashion style might be messy or bad even,
but he's not a picky person...
... so when I say "Try this", he'll say "Okay I will",
while carrying his ugly bag, I think that's adorable...
You got it, right?
Okay, next...
Sometimes stupid, sometimes genius.
- What does that mean?
For example, when we go
to the zoo together...
If he's being stupid, he'll say
"Eh, is that a gorilla or a monkey?"
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
UNQUESTIONABLY STUPID.
That's worrying.
"Eh, is that a gorilla or a monkey?"...
More or less, it's like that
when he's being stupid, but it's adorable...
He always wants to know stuff
he doesn't know, maybe that's...
Is that impossible?
- Impossible? No way...
On the other side, someone like that needs explanation like,
"Ah, that monkey only exists in Japan...
...and it can only be seen in this zoo,"
he's a person who wants to know the details...
-  How troublesome...
Do you think there's a lot of people
with that criteria?
I wanna have a date with someone different...
- You don't like the normal ones?
If I go to the zoo with the normal type of a guy,
maybe it'll be fun, but...
... perhaps it's boring.
- You want someone different.  - Yes, like he has variations.
Sometimes stupid and smart?
- Yes!
And, Takayama's last ideal criteria is...
Please!
- Shoulders?
Shoulders! Now this...
- What do you mean?
Personally, I can't stop talking about them ever.
I'm a shoulders maniac.
- What?
There are round shoulders,
flat shoulders...
... lean like cat's shoulders...
By lean do you mean bony?
Yes, the shape is not too big...
What about mine? These shoulders?
- Himura-san's shoulders are round...
Himura-san's shoulders are super rounding?
- That's right.
What about me...
- Shitara-san's upper shoulders...
... I like them because they look natural.
Like a cat's?  -Yes, yes true!
-  But I'm not lean.
If you're a bit more lean,
you'll get 100 points out of 100.
Yeah, I got a perfect score.
What about Himura-san?
Why do you start to care about mine now...
How many points do I get?
- Himura-san's shoulders score....
... is almost 0 point.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
0 POINT.
Why so low?
But if the shoulders are good,
even if he doesn't fulfill the other criterias here...
Are shoulders that important?
- Yes!
This is a tough call,
but it's really fun...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
THIS SEGMENT, FUN.
Next, here's Akimoto's
ideal man criteria.
Okay.
- Jyan~
Both of his arms are muscular!
Well, am I muscular enough?
Muscular as in it's not just big,
but the muscles are also visible...
Plus, his upper part body has
muscular texture.   - Zennichi...
Zenni... why are you comparing it
with Zennichi Wrestler...
[ Zennichi Wrestler = Japan's freestyle wrestling association ]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
MEMBERS OF ZENNICHI PRO WRESTLING?
But there's a Japanese entertainer
who is also included in this type...  - Who?
He's Downtown's Matsumoto-san...
[ Matsumoto Hitoshi = a member of comedy duo Downtown. ]
Seriously!
He's pretty muscular!
- Very swole!
Matsumoto-san is amazing...
- Yes, he's on a different league...
You just wanted to say Zennichi.
- Yeah, actually...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
IT HAS BEEN TOLD MANY TIMES.
It's definitely Zennichi.
But regarding Zennichi's swoleness,
perhaps I only like the upper arms part...
So Himura-san is very different then?
- What about this?
Appearance-wise,
it's okay...
It's okay?
- You said only appearance matters just now!
Why do you suddenly
talk about appearance?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
OUTWARD APPEARANCE IS NO GOOD?
There's no relation whatsoever!
Next in Akimoto's criteria,
a fatherly figure.
Then...
Jyan~
The cunning sadist.
What do you mean with the cunning sadist?
Like when he's saying, "If you wanna show me your love, you need to be more cheery than that."
I want him to be able to do it direct and bluntly...
- I see.
The stupid and bothersome sadist.
So no matter who is the person he's talking to...
...yeaah!!...
- Like this?
That's the stupid sadist!
- He gets on everyone's nerves...
A man with rigorous personality?
When you ask him, "Where are we going?"
he'll say "Let's just go!"...
It's not like that...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
OF COURSE IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
It's not?
- No that's different...
That's just like a normal person...
For example, "Everyone let's go!" but to you,
"Oi pig, you too!"   - I don't like that...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
WHAT IS THIS?
That looks very bad!
- That's a bothersome idiot...
It's more like that way he talks, like when I'm waiting
for a message reply before we go on a date...
... because he knows I'm waiting for it so bad,
he cancels the date altogether on purpose...
He likes it when he's being treated special?
He wants to see me suffer...
- See you suffer?
Next, Akimoto's ideal man voice is
nasal and raspy.
And the most important criteria is...
Last one,
Jyan~!
Rabbit lips!
- What does that mean?
I... mouth is the a part
of someone I like the most...
Person like that...
So you consider his mouth first?
- Yes!
The first thing I look at
in order to know how cool he is...
... is definitely the shape of his mouth.
And the shape is not usual,
it's more like a bunny's...
What do you mean?
Like pointy?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
THIS ONE THEN?
Here... Protrude your teeth more...
Like this?
Wait, the lower lip...
- This?
No that's not it.
- This is rabbit lips!
No, it's not.
The lower lip should be thicker...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
WHAT ABOUT THIS?
Ahh! What about this?
No that's pretty different...
- This is rabbit lips.
The difference is very far.
Is there a member
who has mouth like that?
Ah, Kazumin! Kazumin!
I like Kazumin's mouth very much.
This, I like this!
- Are those rabbit lips?
It's...
- Duck...
What's wrong?
- Her wrinkles!
Wrinkles are okay!
-  I am totally shocked!
It's okay...
- We're not talking about wrinkles here.
Ah, like that? That part?
- That part is lifted a bit, like that...
And the front teeth are kinda visible...
- Like beaver?  - Yes!
Here,, Akimoto will draw
her ideal mouth shape..
I'm not good at drawing...
- That's bad!  - That's so bad!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
IDEAL MOUTH?
Ah, it looks like Himura-san's mouth.
- Actually it's better than that, it's just that my drawing is ugly...
Look!
This is Himura-san, right?
No! Why?
- So you like mine!
No!
So, I am your type?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
After this too... members' ideal boyfriend criteria will be shown one by one!
What's the surprising criteria for Ikuta, Asuka, and Hoshino?
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUB
ORIGINAL SUB BY: mastoppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
Fatherlike figure... muscular...
What?
Hai, douzo.
This is old lady.
What is this?
- No, no!
Next, presentation about
Hashimoto's ideal man!
Bob haircut.
I like a guy with bob haircut...
- By bob, do you mean...
His face...   - Like that...
- This is bob.
He has bangs pulled from behind...
Yup, that's all me!
- Yes, that's Himura-san...
Is it me?
Then, this part is properly cut...
- Yes, mine too...
What?!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NAGANO?
There it is!
- So it's me?
If Himura-san cut his hairline here
a little bit, it'll look better...
This part in the front?
- All of it...
Everything?
How short should it be?
- No...
How should he cut his hair?
- Not like that...
You mean his bangs, right?
Or do you mean it can't be him?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NEVER MENTIONED.
So it's not me from the very start?
You mentioned my everything...
I'm a full blown bob!
Every part of me is!
Bob style?
- Yes, I'm Bob.  I am Bob!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
BLACK-HAIRED Bob.
Don't involve Himura-san if it's not him...
- You better not involve me from here on...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
ENOUGH?
On previous show,
in lobby, I saw...
...Kasuga-san from Audrey,
and I like such hairstyle.
[ Toshiaki Kasuga = a member of comedy duo Audrey ]
His hair is pretty short, though.
If he cut this shorter...
Is it impossible because he's Himura-san?  - No, no...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
HIMURA IS REJECTED.
"No, I mean Kasuga!",
like that?
Clearly it's not me...
- You need to be direct...
What's wrong with you?
Do you like black hair?
- Black hair is good, I guess.
I prefer black over gold...
- Ah, me too!
Don't say "Me too!"..
We're on same side!
- Black over gold?  - Yes...
Shouldn't that be the opposite?
- Black over gold?
And the second is...
... I like a guy who wears sweater,
like a coach...
What do you mean?
Sweater or training pants are okay...
... someone who's good
with casual style...
Like navy clothes?
That's hai...hai...
[ Nanamin is about to say "high level" in English here. ]
Apa?
Hai, douzo...(Yes, go ahead...)
[ Shitara-san turned it into "Hai Douzo" ]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
PLEASE RESPOND.
The level is higher than that...
Ah you mean there's a puppy print here,
and he's wearing jewelries...
No...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
CHINPIRA STYLE.
[ Chinpira = a low level Yakuza member, like some random thug ]
He's wearing a set of sweter and training pants...
- No, more casual than that...
It's like someone who likes
to eat vegetables...
Vegetables?
And Hashimoto's next ideal type is
the back muscle can be seen from the t-shirt.
Plus...
Cold stare.
- I see.
Ah. I know that...
- Really?
Like, in a glance,
his stare is soulful...
... there are people who do that spontaneously, right?
As if their eyes are that way...
I don't like it
if I'm being looked at that way...
You don't?
- It does seem dreamy, but...
... people with eyes like that make me think,
"I wonder what's on his mind?"
... seems like he always wants to
get my attention, seems tiring.
What you just said matches with Shitara-san...
His stare does look cold.
But Himura-san's stare does look cold sometime...
- That's how Himura-san is!
He's always like that,
even when he's talking... no...
This is an old lady!
Why old lady?
Hasimoto's last ideal criteria is...
Here's the last, date at Kyoto!
- Why so suddenly?
You want to have a date at Kyoto?   - What do you mean?
- I want to know what it's like to have a date there...
I like Kyoto from the beginning, but...
- Ah, that's good...
... sometimes I go there alone...
- To Kyoto?   - Yeah...
I feel lonely if I go alone...
When you're eating, right?
"Ah, feels lonely to eat by myself", you mean like that?
I'd be glad if he can't explain stuff about Kyoto
that I don't know about.    - Ah, nice!
Like if he takes me to a beautiful spot
behind the bushes at night...
... the ground? The ground around the river?
- That area?
... we go there on summer,
spending time while have something to eat...
I wanna go somewhere hidden like that.
- Very good!
But black hair... Himura-san
also wears sweater, right?
I wonder why it's not me.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
THINK ABOUT IT, THAT'S HIMURA, RIGHT?
Himura-san, a date at Kyoto...
- I know much about Kyoto!
I like to eat Yatsuhashi too.
[ Yatsuhashi = Kyoto's sweets, made from rice flour and having many kinds of stuffing ]
That's me, right?
Why didn't you say so?
Ehmm...   - Yes, that's TOTALLY me!
- No, no... that's scary...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
FORCED.
After this,
Ikuta's ideal man is...
Next, here's Ikuta's ideal man.
Okay, first one is this...
His eyes are like James Rodriguez' eyes.
A football player?
He looks cool and adorable.
- Yes, I love eyes like that.
Well he's like that because he's a Colombian, right?
I didn't know he's a
football player...
When I saw a news,
his face popped up...
... that was the first time
I saw someone that cool...
Whoaaa..
- Because of that?   - Yes.
And, next...
- Next!
His nose is like James Rodriguez'.
- Wait a second!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
ALL ABOUT [JAMES].
This doesn't look good!
All five of them could be
"like James Rodrigez'"...
About this,
of course I like the cute shape...
His nose does look like that...
And what's next?
- Next?
Short hair like James Rodriguez'.
- Short hair?
Everyone can have this.
- Short hair is an easy criteria.
I liked long hair
that covers the ears at first.
But about two years ago,
after I met James...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
HAVE YOU TWO MET?
Met?!
You should've said "saw"...
- After I met him, I think short hair looks more refreshing...
I see.   - It's amazing she could meet
someone with ideal face like that...
It is amazing, no matter what he's showing,
I think it's so cool!
Continue please,
it must be his looks too.
- Next...
Okay, stable job.
- What!? It's different?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
DRASTIC CHANGE.
What's this?
It has nothing to do with short hair!
- Scary!
Why do you suddenly pick this?
It's fine even if
he's not a football player, but...
... my own job isn't stable, right?
That's why I think to be with someone who has more stable
and more serious job is a good choice.   - I see..
Next, his hobby is cooking!
Clearly this is a field that
I don't have any proficiency in...
... he can teach me...
... like when we're cooking together,
he'll say "This needs more salt a little bit"...
... affection like that
might be interesting I think.
Speaking about cooking,
have you done it since back then?
- Some time ago, I started a cooking series...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
IS THIS A LIE?
Series?!
The title is
"Swaping The Keyboard with A Cutting Board"
Sounds fantastic.
That's amazing of you to
switch over to something like that.
Next, here are
Saitou Asuka's ideal man criteria.
His body is very lean!
How lean?
- I don't like bony ones...
Are you interested in muscular ones?
Doesn't muscular body look oily?
Wait, I need to step aside for a moment.
- What?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
THIS IS POLICE.
Muscular body looks oily?
It looks oily, like shiny...
- What do you mean?
They apply oil they body!
- Yeah!
But I think muscular body
is always oily all the time...
You don't like shiny ones?
- I don't...
Then, someone who talks like
he's whispering, like doesn't really care...
...and someone who can improve family's income.
What does she mean with "doesn't really care?"
I'm weak for stuff.
- What?
It's not like birthday presents...
Since he doesn't really care...
...he gives me tasty foods...
- Tasty foods?
If someone gives me tasty foods,
I'll just...
... perhaps because
I'm a weak-minded person...
That sounds lame.
- No, I am just like that...
I see. For example, "Here, this tastes good!"
- Maybe I'll like him right away...
You shouldn't say something like that!
- There's a lot of people within that criteria.
After this there'll be many people who
"Here, eat this!" since they don't care...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NO MATTER WHAT SHE'S EATING.
Giving something like that is bad.
Please don't be like that.
I don't like surprise that much.
- So that's that.
I just want him to be direct...
Like, "Today you'll look good wearing this..."
- Ah, that's right.
So that's what you mean
with doesn't really care...   - I like that...
That's cool!
- That's great!
And Saitou Asuka's last ideal criteria is...
Mature...
- Even though he skips around?
Yes.
- This seems bad, he has matured already...
I've never seen an old man or employee
who skips around.
No, I like someone who's usually
serious and adult-like, but...
... when there's happy moment, he skips around...
- So he has such gap?
But is okay if he looks stupid?
- It's okay...
"Waa~haa!!!" like that?
- Yes, like that...
That is a person who has lost his mind.
Maybe since many people say
I'm not innocent...
... so I like an innocent guy like that.
- Oh, so that's why...
But since you just said that,
when there's a handshake event later...
... everyone will be skipping around.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
QUEUING WHILE SKIPPING.
Even when they're told to get out.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
CAN'T STOP SKIPPING.
That'll be a mess.
Next, the criteria of Hoshino's ideal guy are...
... long bangs
and broad shoulders.
He also must has a sexy voice
and wearing cool accessories.
And her last criteria is...
And the last one is...
Hails from Kansai!
- That?!
Why that?
- It's not limited to Kansai only, but...
... the important thing is
the dialect.
Someone like that...
Why? You don't like someone from Tohoku area?
- Perhaps she doesn't know the dialect...
[ Tohoku = an area located on northern part of Japan ]
So areas like Kansai or Kyushu?
[ Kansai & Kyushu = areas located on southers part of Japan ]
Then after waking up in the morning,
he just suddenly...
... makes some joke,
it'll sound nice too.
Since Kansai is funny...
No, that's not just Kansai.
There are many people
who do that too.
If you generalize the Kansai people,
they'll all go...
... "My eyes have opened!!"
after they woke up...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
DEFINITELY NO.
... surely that's wrong!
But this is unexpected,
Hoshino likes a mature type.
I do admire people
who have maturity in them...
... who screams "ADULT!"
"Adult!"
He's saying "Adult!" all the time...
But although he's mature,
he thinks about his joke really hard.   - Pretty good!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
GAG IS IMPORTANT.
Why should he?
What about some light jokes?
Actually anything is okay, but when we're together
and he says "Doumo Doumo", I think that might be interesting...
[ Doumo Doumo = means hello hello, a greeting usually
said at the beginning of Manzai, Japanese's stand up comedy ]
- Like that?
Well then people from
entertainment industry are fine?
For example, when he's joking,
"What do you mean,"...
... and suddenly he says
"Sorry, someone's calling!"
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NOT RECOMMENDED.
That's so bad!
Have you tried the game?
- Yes!
You have?
- Yeah, some time ago.
- Nogikoi?
NOGIZAKA46 TRYING NOGIKOI
Okay, let's enter the academy.
- Okay!
[Shitara]: First day of school?
In this game, the main character
just got transferred to Nogizaka Gakuen.
Here, all of the classmates are
Nogizaka 46 members.
[Shitara]: Wow, this is like
every fans' dream.
The player will be in the academy environment
together with the members...
... and build up a love relationship
with the chosen Oshimen.
[Himura]: Woah, this seems
interesting!
NAMING THE CHARACTER.
Eh, what should I name the character?
- What name?
Hori-kun.
- Hori-kun.
So cute.
- What's the full name?
Minao-kun.
- Minao?
Hori Minao.
- Hohh!!!
Minao...  - You use katakana for Minao?
- It's fine.
CHOOSING OSHIMEN.
"Oshimen may be changed later",
- What, no, that hurts!
[Shiraishi]: Seriously?!
Then choose Manattan as the oshimen
from the very start...
Since it can be changed later, right?
- No, I'll stay with this one.
[Himura]: You can change it?
With the chosen oshimen member...
... player follows the story
to build a closer relationship to be her boyfriend. And...
"Hey, would you eat my handmade sandwich?"
- That's cute...
"I heard it might erase your hunger"
[Ikoma]: Am I like that?
Ah, it popped out...
- So this...
This is similar...   - Here we go!
What if we reject her offer?
- Yeah...
But we don't know
what Minao-san will say...
Just accept it for now...   - Accept?
- Yeah, I'm kinda hungry.  - Okay, option number 1...
"Here you go ~"
"Good Choice!"
Does that it's good?
In the middle of the story, there will be quizzes and choices
that if those got answered correctly
... player will items that can increase
the relationship with oshimen.
And player may get "Nogi Talk" to be able
to chat with the chosen oshimen...
[Shitara]: Everyone will be happy.
[Himura]: This is interesting!
... player can have a talk
all alone with the oshimen.
[Ikoma: Even though they don't
really know each other...
"Sorry, I have a lot of stuff to do today..."
[Misa]: Eh, what is this?
"... but I'll be waiting for the next date.
Where will we go?"
[HImura]: Eh! What's this?
"Somewhere Akimoto wants to go",
"I'll think about it"...
- What would you have said?
What's your response normally?
[Himura]: Woah, three difficult
choices!
Definitely not option number 3!
- Me? Of course no!
[Himura]: This is a very
important decision!
Option number 2 seems good! I want her to pick it.
- Select that option that.
[Himura]: Even the real person
need to be taught.
[Shiraishi]: Neat, she's staring at it.
[Reika]: She read it in an instant.
She replied...
- Yeah...
[Shitara]: Ah, I see.
"Thanks. Let's talk later.
I have many things I want to tell you at school."
"Next time, let's have a real date..."
[Shiraishi]: That's so Manatsu!
"...good night."
- That is so Manatsu.
[Himura]: Will she reply it on break?
He'll fell for it.
Plus, I like to use
[hearts] and [musical notes]...
Doesn't everyone do that too?
OI!!!
Then, when the story continues...
Hold on!
I don't wanna see this!
[Kaz]: Ah, this?
Where did you record this?
[Reika]: Totally normal.
Player can also get a
clip of confession by real members.
Awesome!
- It's embarassing for me to see myself!
[Shitara]: This is what the fans have dreamed about.
[Himura]: This is interesting!   [Akimoto]: Yes.
AND SO, NOGIZAKA46
HAS SUCCESSFULLY PLAYED [NOGIKOI].
Usually, do your faces get covered
then get painted on?  - No!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Minggu depan...Nogizaka46 membentuk klub esktrakurikuler!?
Mereka mengumpulkan anggota dengan menunjukkan kelebihan klub mereka!
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
Of course not.
Settle down everyone...
- Ah, have you worn your skirt?
No, no...
I don't want to go climbing anymore...
It could be Tonkotsu soup...
The title of the second album has been decided,
"Sorezore no Isu",
Album jackets have already been released too.
Ticket reservation process for
"Manatsu Zenkoku Tour 2016" has been opened for the third time!
And, the second Joshiraku will be available
for public at Tuesday, 3 May!