m 0 0 l 0 27 l 2 27 l 2 0 l 0 0 m 2 0 l -4 0 l -4 6 l 16 6 l 16 4 l -2 4 l -2 2 l 0 2 m 2 2 m 16 0 l 16 27 l 18 27 l 18 -1 l 16 -1 m 22 0 l 22 0 l 24 0 l 24 11 l 19 11 l 19 9 l 22 9 l 22 2 l 15 2 l 15 0 m 6 18 l 6 12 l 12 12 l 12 14 l 8 14 l 8 18 l 6 18 m 12 18 l 12 20 l 6 20 l 6 18 l 10 18 l 10 14 l 12 14 l 12 18 m 5 7 l 8 9 l 7 10 l 4 8 l 5 7 m 10 9 l 10 9 l 13 7 l 14 8 l 11 10 l 10 9 m 3 24 b 3 24 3 23 3 23 b 7 21 11 21 15 23 b 15 23 15 25 15 25 b 11 23 7 23 3 25
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
Nogizaka Koujichuu
Tonight, the 14th single hit campaign
in Guam continues!
This time, if the members are able to win the game,
they will immediately get a travel prize.
And in the end, the loser will
do a Skydiving challenge from 4.200 meter high.
Before that, they were competing in getting Guam points
while also enjoying Guam at the same time.
Here there are 6 members left from the previously 8 members.
And who is the only
member left in the end?
Alright, now we're at this location here.
Everyone please have a look...
Beautiful!
- Himura-san, it's so beautiful here.
HAGANIA BEACH
Perfect with that sunset.
- Agree!
And while we're enjoying the barbeque...
... from these 6 members, half of them will win
and the other 3 will stay.
It's gonna lessen a lot...
- Right, we'll do that. Besides, all of Nogizaka
members have gathered there.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
BARBEQUE PARTY
Welcome back!
Did everyone have
fun all day long?
Yeah!
- What did you do?
[Everyone is answering at once]
- I can't hear you!
That sounds nice!
- Bananaman wants to do that too.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
TOO MANY RESPONSES
Okay everyone please enjoy
the barbeque casually!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
MEMBERS ARE ENJOYING THE FEAST
Alright...
So Himura-san, now please announce our next game.
- Okay, here I go!
Survival Dinner with Indian Poker!!!
There's a forbidden word sticked onto their forehead
which they don't know.
3 members who don't get OUTed will win
in a certain time limit.
This is a barbeque where members must avoid
the OUT, and make other members say their forbidden word.
[I'm surprised]
[How fun]
[Delicious]
[Cute]
[Doing janken]
[High five]
And here are the forbidden words...
Each of them must make others OUT
while the game is running!
HORI
NISHINO
ASUKA
FUKAGAWA
IKUTA
MATSUMURA
I'M SURPRISED
HOW FUN
DELICIOUS
CUTE
DOING JANKEN
HIGH FIVE
And Survival Barbeque start now!
While eating, huh.
- Okay, everyone please.
Don't you think this is interesting?
Such experience is very interesting.
This is so fun!
- Amazing!
Have a bite.
- While eating...
Other members are busy taking pictures there.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
UNDISTRACTEDLY ENJOYING
What if each member here tell us about something,
like interesting memories you had today.
Saito Asuka, what do you think
with today's challenges?
Since I entered Nogizaka...
... this is the first time I've worked very hard.
- Ah, I see...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
ASUKA'S HARDEST WORK
So up until now, you've worked harder
on earlier challenges? But you've did it before, right?
What about Ikuta?
For me, of course it was the last one, Sagada... what was it?
- Sagada Disco!   - Yes! Yes! Yes!
SAGADA DISCO
Sure there was an irritating feeling, but
it has gone now and everything is fun.
Matsumura?
I wonder? But people from my
hometown aren't really...
FWEEEEET!!!
Huh!? Why,why?
MATSUMURA
HIGH FIVE
Spotting a chance, Ikuta did a high five!
Matsumura OUT!
Take it off...
- Check it, Matsumura...
Okay, Matsumura 1 OUT.
New forbidden word for her is
"Feeding while saying Aaan"
MATSUMURA
FEEDING WHILE SAYING AAAN
HORI
NISHINO
ASUKA
FUKAGAWA
IKUTA
MATSUMURA
I'M SURPRISED
HOW FUN
DELICIOUS
CUTE
DOING JANKEN
FEEDING WHILE
SAYING AAAN
Everyone please have a talk.
What souvenir do you want to buy from Guam?
Ahh... cookies.
Cookies?
I wanna buy Macademia Choco...
Here, Hori tries to make Fukagawa
says "Cute".
HORI
NISHINO
ASUKA
FUKAGAWA
IKUTA
MATSUMURA
I'M SURPRISED
HOW FUN
DELICIOUS
CUTE
O
I
DOING JANKEN
FEEDING WHILE
SAYING AAAN
What does Fukagawa-san want to buy?
You mean chocolate?   - Chocolate...
Don't you want to buy the toy statues?
I like them since they're cute...
But, what's that... handicraft?
I want it since it's cute...
Fukagawa!
This is bad!   - OUT!
- Check yours!
So clever!
- Haah!!!
Since the handicraft is cute.    - Okay, you have
1 OUT. And here's your new forbidden word.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
JUST AS HORI PLANNED
Fukagawa, what do you think?
Annoying!
Fukagawa's new forbidden word is
"What are you doing?"
FUKAGAWA
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
Then, Hori the tactician tries
to set Matsumura up.
HORI
NISHINO
ASUKA
FUKAGAWA
IKUTA
MATSUMURA
I'M SURPRISED
HOW FUN
DELICIOUS
WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
DOING JANKEN
FEEDING WHILE
SAYING AAAN
O
I
I want that!
- This is the best beef tongue.
Yes! I wanna eat that...
This?
I want that...
- This one?
Just eat it... you want to eat this one?
Which one?
- This...
That one?
- Beef tongue...
I like the edge part of beef tongue...
Two members next to Matsumura the target
are showing her how to do the "Aaan".
HORI
NISHINO
ASUKA
FUKAGAWA
IKUTA
MATSUMURA
I'M SURPRISED
HOW FUN
DELICIOUS
WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
DOING JANKEN
FEEDING WHILE
SAYING AAAN
O
I
I want it, just a bite.
- Eh, really?
You want this?
Aaan ...Eh? Isn't it hot?
It is!
- FWEEETT!!!!
Matsumura, OUT!  - Eh, what?
- Take a look!  - Eh, seriously?
Eeehh!!! Why?
2 OUTs! Now you're leading, that's bad!
- Eh, this is bad!   - Well played Hori!
Here, together with Matsumura, the forbidden words
for Hori, Nishino and Asuka change too.
[I'm surprised]
[How fun]
[Delicious]
[What are you doing?]
[Doing Janken]
[Feeding while
saying Aaan]
[It hurts!]
[Dirty]
[Pick something up]
[It tastes too strong!]
And this time, Matsumura who got set up before,
tries to do a counter attack against Hori.
HORI
NISHINO
ASUKA
FUKAGAWA
IKUTA
MATSUMURA
IT HURTS!
O
I
DIRTY
PICK
SOMETHING UP
WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
DOING JANKEN
IT TASTES
TOO STRONG!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
PAPER ATTACK
She... Suddenly she...
She's showing no reaction...
Sly...
Look at Miona's stare!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
IMMOVABLE
Hori seems like she's got strucked by something...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
STOMACH GOES FIRST
She seems want to end it...
No reaction like that is not good, you know!
Hey you!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
DIRECT ATTACK
What? What's going on?
What's with her?
And here, Matsumura goes to Asuka's place.
HORI
NISHINO
ASUKA
FUKAGAWA
IKUTA
MATSUMURA
IT HURTS!
O
I
DIRTY
PICK
SOMETHING UP
O
I
WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
DOING JANKEN
IT TASTES
TOO STRONG!
Asuka, please that one near your feet...
FWEEETT!!!
I did it!
- Finally she did it!
Asuka-chan...
How fun..
- Asuka-chan...
ASUKA
PICK SOMETHING UP
By pretending to target Hori...
... then she asked Asuka's help to pick something
down there quickly, a clever play from Matsumura!
I did it!
- Finally she did it!
Amazing!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
SUDDEN ATTACK QUEEN
Amazing... Hori...
- Surely this makes her angry!
She used Hori to attack...
And here's the new forbidden word for Asuka.
ASUKA
I'M FULL
HORI
NISHINO
ASUKA
FUKAGAWA
IKUTA
MATSUMURA
IT HURTS!
DIRTY
I'M FULL
WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
DOING JANKEN
IT TASTES
TOO STRONG!
Miona try to touch this with your hand.
Why should I?
- Because this is your Senpai's request.
Well then, please Senpai give an example.
Aah~ Sorry!
- Show it please!
Then, Matsumura utilizes this situation.
Ikuta you wanna do it?
- Nope!
Then the one who lost in Janken has to do it.
O
I
If I don't win, do I really have to touch it?
Why is that?
- Let's try our luck just this once.
Rock, paper, scissor!
FWEEETT!!!!
Ikuta-san...
Ikuta-san, please take a look!
Simple...
[It hurts]
[Dirty]
[I'm full]
[What are
you doing?]
[Doing Janken]
[It tastes too strong!]
Here, Ikuta who got OUT gets a new forbidden word,
and Nishino's also changes with a new one.
[Talking with
Himura]
[Touch someone
next to me]
Then Hori tries to set Nishino up
who hasn't get any OUT.
HORI
NISHINO
ASUKA
FUKAGAWA
IKUTA
MATSUMURA
IT HURTS!
TALKING WITH
HIMURA
I'M FULL
WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
TOUCH SOMEONE
NEXT TO ME
O
I
IT TASTES
TOO STRONG!
Ah, I bought Bananaman-san's new Live DVD.
Really? Have you watched it?  - No, not yet...
Oh not yet.
I wanna watch it with my sister.
- Ah, thank you.
Naa-chan, you've watched the Live, right?
Last year, at "Love is Gold"...
FWEEETTT!!!
Nishino OUT...
Forgive me.
Cheap...
That was so cheap...
And forbidden word for Nishino changes to "Disgusting".
NISHINO
DISGUSTING
This time both of Matsumura and Fukagawa
are targetting Ikuta.
HORI
NISHINO
ASUKA
FUKAGAWA
IKUTA
MATSUMURA
IT HURTS!
DISGUSTING
I'M FULL
WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
TOUCH SOMEONE
NEXT TO ME
O
I
IT TASTES
TOO STRONG!
But...
- Even though Iku-chan has small hands, she's good at piano...
Like the ones piano players have...
- Right...
I always stretch my fingers like this...
Like this?
- Seriously?
Awesome!
Slowly...     - Oh, until it widens?
- I see!
It really opens like that.
- This...
FWEEETTT!!!
Ikuta-san!
- What? What? What?
Please tell me it's not joining hands.
"Touch someone next to me".
Ah, just touch?
Oh, this is bad, Ikuta...
New forbidden word for Ikuta is
"Touch Himura-san".
IKUTA
TOUCH HIMURA-SAN
Then, Matsumura and Ikuta who clearly have lost
are targetting Fukagawa.
- 3 minutes to go!
- Do your best! Come on!
FUKAGAWA
IKUTA
MATSUMURA
WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?
TOUCH
HIMURA-SAN
O
I
IT TASTES
TOO STRONG!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
TURNS INTO A WEIRDO
ANOTHER WEIRDO
Scary! Scary! Scary!
What? What?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
TEA THIEF
Gross...
HORI
NISHINO
ASUKA
IT HURTS!
DISGUSTING
I'M FULL
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
CONFUSING DANCE PARTY
What?
Matsumura who targeted Fukagawa earlier,
changes her target here to Ikuta.
O
I
And Nishino joins this dance party.
What? What? What? What?
Me? Me?
Why it's different from earlier?
Why? Why?
- Ikuta...Ikuta OUT!  - Is that so?
IKUTA
TOUCH HIMURA-SAN
Smoothly made her touch Himura
while danced, this means Ikuta has 3 OUTs, then...
Finished!
- Yup, it's finished!
Alright it's over!
- It's over!
Ikuta got 3 and Matsumura got 2, mean...
... they are definitely picked, and
now we just need the third person.
And here Hori...
... has won the game!
To choose one out of 3 members with same point,
janken will be used.
Okay, everyone ready? Go!
Rock, paper, scissor!
I DID IT!!!
I did it!
- She won!
That was your loudest shout today.
She's really ecstatic.
- She was like "I DID IT!"!
Ready, go! Rock, paper, scissor!
Aaahh~~!!! Nishino!!!
And that means, the one who got picked is...
... Nishino who just lost, together with Ikuta and
Matsumura, those three!
Nishino is still in shock! Nishino...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
UNEXPECTED INCIDENT HAPPENS IN THE LAST GAME OF GUAM TOUR?
WHO WILL JUMP FROM 4.200 M HIGH?
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
Thinking back, it's been quite some time since
the spinning game with baseball bat on beach.
For the last one, this is what we're going to do.
Himura-san, please!
The last one is...
Russian Beach Chair!
This is the very infamous Russian Beach Chair.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A CUSTOM IN GUAM?
I've never heard that!
Ah, that was good! That serious reaction just now.
Eh...5 Guams for you.
WAKATSUKI
NICE REACTION
This is our next segment, huh.
Next segment.
There's one broke chair
out of 3 chairs on the edge of this pool.
If one who sits on it and then falls into
the pool then she will do the Skydiving.
According to the OUT points from previous game,
they will take turns choosing their chair.
Okay, where will you sit?
Mi... middle.
- Middle!
Middle? Okay, it's chosen! On the middle!
Now Matsumura?
That one or near one here?
Okay, the furthest one.
Furthest one? So Ikuta gets the remaining one.
- Ikuta you sit on this side.
So how it is now?
Matsumura, how do you feel now?
Pressured?
Now I feel like I can do it.
Matsumura said that as if
she definitely won't get picked.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
THE RESULT IS UNCERTAIN
At this point, anyone will
have to do it, right?
Alright, Nishino, what about you?
Even though... this seems like I'm the only one left
since I lost, but...
... if I'm here, I guess
it will be okay.
That's right, you did the Macau Bungee once
so Skydiving definitely will be okay too, right?
There must be a feeling like that. Then, Ikuta..
- Ikuta-san...
Eh... It.. it's okay, I guess...
That clearly is a lie...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
CLEARLY SHE'S NERVOUS
You think it's okay, huh.
- Who's the most suitable one to do it?
Fukagawa, who do you think?
Eh, but...
Naa-chan did a bungee once, but...
... for the second time, it seems...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
MEMBER SPECIALIZES IN JUMPING
So, middle?
- The middle one will get chosen?
Shall we start now?
Okay...
Please have a seat...
The long competition in Guam is
finally entering its final phase!
Who will do the Skydiving challenge?
Everyone please sit at once.
Please!
And slowly...
... slowly, and sit now everyone, go ahead!
Huh? Only Naachan...
Kyaaaa~~~!!!!
Ha..ha..ha..
- Iku-chan~
I thought... I thought no one got it!
What? Only Naachan...
Kyaaaa~~~!!!!
I thought no one would fall,
but Ikuta did!
I've never thought...
- Iku-chan~
What's with this time delay of falling?  - What, this?
What happened?
Ikuta, did you think no one will fall?
It felt like the time had stopped earlier.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
TIME DISTORTION
Very nice Ikuta!
- Your expression is interesting!
So Ikuta, you don't like this?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
SOAKING WET IN MORNING AND NIGHT
Nope! She hates this!
This girl really is defeated!
She had a bad luck
for one day in Guam.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A GIRL WITH 6 LOSES
This... never in my life before
I thought I would get defeated like this.
That means...
... the one who gets to Skydive is Ikuta!
Lighten up!
- Give your best!
Okay, we will do it in few hours!
After this there will be Ikuta who gets frightened in Guam sky!
NEXT MORNING, 5:00
The next day, 5 in the morning...
Alright... Please...
Okay, let's go!
- Let's go!
We are going to Skydive...
Next at the aerodrome, Ikuta
prepares and changes clothes.
GUAM SKYDIVING
TANDEM DIVING $549
Alright Ikuta, please come out!
Oh, nice!
- Amazing!
Please..
- Please.
How do you feel now we
are going to do it?
I don't know what's up there.
- I see...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
UPSET?
I don't know if I'm nervous or scared,
and that frightens me.
For Ikuta whose mind is full of worries,
Fukagawa gives an encouraging message.
Now, even though I got selected
as a center for this 14th single...
... but Ikuta is the one who has to do this,
I'm so sorry.
This 14th single hit campaign
is being entrusted to Iku-chan, and...
... with everyone watching it...
... perhaps the situation will be difficult up in the sky later...
... so please prepare yourself properly.
Definitely...
When we're back later, just let me know if
Iku-chan wants to eat anything.  - Woah! Yay!
I will be waiting for you.
- Thank you for the offer... Yay!
Awesome!
- Pretty good.
Because this is the most important
single for MaiMai...
I think I too have to fully support this.
Since we want a single hit campaign, please say the song title
when you jump later...
... or something else so it can sell well,
please buy it, like that...   - That's a certain thing.
You can sing it too later...
- You do remember the song, right?   - Yeah, I do.
Say it clearly so everyone will buy it
and it will sell well.  - That's right, do that.
If you feel calmer later,
you can try to sing that Finnish song.  - No, no, that's different!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NORTHERN EUROPE SONG IN SOUTHERN LAND SKY
From here on, Ikuta will get ready
to jump alone.
It needs 15 minutes by plane
to reach the jump point.
What Ikuta must do this time is the same with what
Akimoto did, jump from 4.200 meter high.
When the plane keep getting higher,
Ikuta keep getting more nervous.
[staff] The jump is quite high.
[staff] Since it's 4.200 meter.
Lots of clouds up here.
[staff] This is taller than Mount Fuji.
- Even taller than Mount Fuji!?
Bananaman and other members
will be waiting down there when she landed.
Really, so quick!
[staff] Since you're calmer,
you can sing.
That's definitely not easy.
But I will seriously praying for success.
And finally, the 4.200m skydiving moment
has come!
Ah, ah, this is too fast!
Wait, wait, wait!
- It's okay...
Hold on... NO~!
At long last, Ikuta will jump from Guam sky!
Finally the plane has arrived
on 4.200m jump point.
Ah, this is too fast!
Wait, wait, wait!
- It's okay...
Hold on... No, no~!
For the sake of 14th single success, Ikuta
jumps from the Guam sky!
Ah, she jumped.   - That was too quick!
- Really?
Ah, right, she's jumped!
Eh, she looks small, cool!
Ah, that one, huh! I can see it clearly!
- Iku-chan~
The red one...
It will be very awesome if she can sing that Finnish
song while she's coming down.
Well that's different...
Ikuta's spinning around!
- Is that okay?
A special service just for her!
- Ikuta's really spinning there...
Since Ikuta's landing still in a while...
... please enjoy the replay
of Guam Tour.
Everyone, go recording, give your best!
You can't spin slowly!
Is this happening...
That must be good. If we're talking about Southern Island,
this is a must thing to do.
Surprisingly Inoue, Inoue...
Look, she got out...
Let's Go Bread...
- Let's go bread?
...2, 1... Ah, sorry, I pressed it too early.
Sorry, it's too early...
Ah...Himura-san!
America!
- Minus 10 Guams!  - Eh, why?
Danger, danger, danger!
FWEEETTT!!!
Look, finally!
- Yay!
Ah, I thought no one would fall!
Ikuta~!!!
- Oooii~
I~ku-chan~!
- Iku-chan seems used to it...
Ah, here she comes!
Woah, watch out...woo~
Oooo~~!!!
She did it~
Finally landed...
Let's go everyone...
Ikuta!
- Yay~
Yeah!!!
High five!
How was it?
It was so terrifying when I jumped.
- Terrifying?
Very terrifying!
But when the parachute opened and we floated,
it felt calm...
The view... I enjoyed it...
- Finally you calmed down?
But when I jumped...
I wanted to talk something, yet I couldn't at all.
- Because of the wind pressure?
I wanted to scream, but this mouth of mine
was always open...
I couldn't say the hit campaign at all
- Are you for real now??
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A FAILED HIT CAMPAIGN?
You didn't do it?
I wanted to, but I couldn't speak,
my breath... the wind pressure, really...
But you did move your mouth, right?
My mouth was open all the time, so I just did
"Haaahhh" like that...
But you did say the single title and the release date, right?
I didn't, since I couldn't speak...
- Please tell me you're lying!
Seriously!?
- Then what were you doing?   - No!!!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
ONE MORE TRY?
But...
That..
- But you did sing that Finnish song, right?
I couldn't do it at all! Seriously!
But that was very great.
- Agree!
I could see it clearly
when you did the jump.
I was like, "Ah there she is!"  - You guys saw it?
- Yes, we did!
Fukagawa, she landed safely in the end...
That was awesome!
I'm very thankful she could land safely.
Thank you for your hard work!
We've did many things in Guam,
and for the last one...   - You did it.
That means you're all successfully
praying for this 14th single hit.
And lastly Ikuta, please say the single title once again,
and ask for support.
Please support us so this 14th single
"Harujion ga Saku Koro" can be a massive hit!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NEXT... SEGMENT WHERE SAITO ASUKA TRIES TO BE INDEPENDENT!
ASUKA'S MOM REVEALS SOME SURPRISING FACT!?
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
No, no...
That's primitive, ancient method!
Since I like Okayu...
Okayu... so your mom is the one who likes Okayu?
The long awaited "Joushiraku" art show part 2,
finally will be held!
Starting next week, registration by
mobile system will be opened. Don't miss it!
Fukagawa graduation and birthday concert will be
combined with "Manatsu no Zenkouku Tour 2016"!
Reservation opens from mobile system!
As we can see, there's someone with different costume
on team Fukuoka.
For the Softbank west region opening match,
Ikoma made an appearance.
I'm very nervous...
Please try GIGA 120!