m 0 0 l 0 27 l 2 27 l 2 0 l 0 0 m 2 0 l -4 0 l -4 6 l 16 6 l 16 4 l -2 4 l -2 2 l 0 2 m 2 2 m 16 0 l 16 27 l 18 27 l 18 -1 l 16 -1 m 22 0 l 22 0 l 24 0 l 24 11 l 19 11 l 19 9 l 22 9 l 22 2 l 15 2 l 15 0 m 6 18 l 6 12 l 12 12 l 12 14 l 8 14 l 8 18 l 6 18 m 12 18 l 12 20 l 6 20 l 6 18 l 10 18 l 10 14 l 12 14 l 12 18 m 5 7 l 8 9 l 7 10 l 4 8 l 5 7 m 10 9 l 10 9 l 13 7 l 14 8 l 11 10 l 10 9 m 3 24 b 3 24 3 23 3 23 b 7 21 11 21 15 23 b 15 23 15 25 15 25 b 11 23 7 23 3 25
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
Nogizaka Koujichuu
DON! Alright, Nogizaka Koujichuu is starting, we're
the MC Banaman, Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu...
BANANAMAN
Himura Yuki
Shitara Osamu
- Onegaishimasu~
And here's Nogizaka-chan!
Pyo~Pyo~
Okay...
What's that?
- Asuka...because she's a bird...
[ Asuka [鳥] = A kanji where Asuka means bird. ]
So that's Asuka's pose?
Alright, what will we do today?  - Yes!
Himura-san....  - Here we go!
Saitou Asuka's Independent Segment!
DOING SOMETHING FOR THE FIRST TIME!
Okay, that's what we're gonna do.
Yes and it was in this show too...
...actually she didn't know Radio Taisho.
- That's right!
Then, there were foods and drinks
she never tried before.  - Yes, that too.
And we gave questionnaires to the other members, to see
if there are something else she never did before.
Actually there are so many things!
- Wuah!!!
Without further ado, information from Ikoma.
Even if she's an idol, when it comes to clothes
she didn't really think about it...
...so if she wanted to buy some clothes, she said
she always went with her mother.
But now even if she went alone...
...she always sends the pics of the clothes to her mother.
If her mother says OK, she buys them.
That's why she never really buy her own clothes.
Really?   - Yes.
- Why? You can just buy it, right?
There are many stuff I buy
together with my mother...
...that's why, until recently,
there were nothing I bought on my own...
...but lately, since there's no time...
...like when there's a solo job,
we can't go together...
I took pictures of stuff I found
then I sent it to my mother...
...and recently I often send those pics to Marika...
Do you ask Marika-chan to pay for them?
- Why... why her?
I like her style since ever...
...and lately we've been talking
alot about clothes...
- I see.
...so I wanna know her opinions.
Is this one ok? Like that.
- If Marika and your mom say no, you won't buy it?
Yes, I've never bought something with my own decision.
Even though you think it's something good, but if your mom says
no, you won't buy it?  - I won't.
We also gathered many informations
about this from the other members.
Akimoto too, do you know about this?
But this is not about clothes. We were having
a handshake event back then...
Asuka said, "I wanna wear
cat's ears for the event"...
She asked me if I brought it with me
since I often did...
I got the black and white ones, then I asked her, "Which one do you want??"
She couldn't choose it without hearing her mom's opinion
and then they were having a discussion for about three hours.
Oh really...
- Just between the black and white?  - Yes.
You discussed it with your mom?
- I did.
It's really difficult, is the black one better?
Or something like, "Ain't it too mature?"...
...I really don't understand stuff like this. I was doubtful too
if I should wear cat's ears or not...
I was confused, which one should I wear.
So you can be that confused too.
- That's right!
Yeah but I couldn't choose one...
- But you could use this confusion of yours.
If only you asked, which one,
black or white? The fans might be happy...
Maybe someone will say
"White one seems better",
So in the end, which one did you choose?
- It was the white one...
Why?
My mom said since my clothes was white that time
so get the white one...
The result of three hours of discussion?
- I was asking which one is better...
...also I had to choose which clothes,
it took about three hours.
- Ah, about that too?
But if on that day Akimoto brought the pink one too,
"What about this one?", would you panic?
I won't wear it.
Maybe I'd take the pic and I send it to my mom.
I wanna know her opinion.
...But then if there's something else...
I see...
Next, a surprising information from Nishino!
She too...
...when she's having a breakfast, she has to be spoonfed...
Like when there are two of us, she wants to be spoonfed too...
- Directly to her mouth?
- That must be a lie.
That's not true, right?
- This one?
For real?!
- Eh!? The rice...how does she do it? How?
Every morning I take a bath.
After that...
...when I dry my hair with a hairdryer,
I use both of my hand.
But I can't waste time.
So when I'm using my hairdryer,
my mom is spoonfeeding me...
Ah...at the same time? Like this?
- Yes, that's right.
But she doesn't always do that, right?
- She does every day.
EEeehhhhHH?!!
When was the last time you did it?
- Eh!? Today I did it too.
How much food?
- Eh, the entire breakfast...
Rice... everything?
- Everything.
For example, there are rice, fish, and miso soup...
It'll be done in sequence, started from
the miso soup...
-Seriously?!
...then, the fish...
- Your mom is awesome! That's really awesome!
This is surprising, there's someone like this...
It seems that there's nothing
she can do alone. Yeah maybe.
Was there something like this in Nininbaori,
"Eh, eye, eye, that's eye!". Was there?
[ Nininbaori = comedy skit of two people, where one person
acts as a hand for the other person.NUsually it's an eating scene.]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
COMEDY OF PARENTS AND CHILDREN
Nope...
Ain't that difficult?
- No, my mom is really good at spoonfeeding...
- Maybe she's used to it.
Next, an information from Akimoto...
She also can't open
cans and bottles by herself...
...so for example in the dressing room, there's another member
sit next to her...
...she'll give it to her and ask
to open that...
You can't open juice can?
Well this...about juice can...
...I can do it since high school.
But I couldn't do it until
third year in junior high school. Now I can though...
- You can do it now?
What do you mean you couldn't back then?
I thought, my nails might be
get ripped if I did it...
...so I didn't wanna do it.
- Really? Is there any can structure like that?
But I thought I couldn't and didn't know how.
Plus, I didn't really like canned juice,
so when there's a photo shooting alone...
...I bought it from the vending machine,
and I thought I was gonna drink it...
...since I was always worried my nails would get ripped,
I didn't open it and
ended up throwing it away.
Huh!?
- You throwed it away
because you couldn't open it?  - Yes.
This...Himura-san...
Your nails won't get ripped, you know!
Now I can do it.
It was like two years ago.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
TALK ABOUT PRESENT
How did it happen?
When the adults drink sake...the sound of the can...
I was interested in that...
But since I thought my nails might get ripped,
I always worried, so I didn't do it...
The first time I did it...
...it was at home.
- Home? what did you open?
I rarely drink soda...I wanted to hear it...
- But of course since the sound when it opened...
My mom bought it, then with "Ready? Go!~"...
With "Ready? Go!~"?!!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
BIG HAPPENING
Using "Ready? Go!"? means your mom couldn't do it too?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
FIRST ONE FOR SAITOU FAMILY?
My mom opened it in front of me,
then she said "You do it like this,"
- She was teaching you?
"Like this"...  - Your mom teached you, "like this"?
- I saw that...
...then, "Ready? Go!" like that...
- Then it went "Psssh"?
Was it interesting?
- It was.
She even had to say that...
- She had to be guided. But that's a canned juice, right?
I can.
- In the end she can do it, but...
...are there any other things she never do?
So we gave her challenges like in this VTR.
[Kaz] : Can?
What's this?
How do you open this?
[Shitara] : You've never opened a can?
[Shitara] : Dangerous, dangerous!
[Shitara] : No, no!
That's not how you do it...
Eh!?
[Himura] : That's wrong!
Why? Should I use this?
Eh!? How do you...
[Shitara] : Yup, like that...
[Shitara] : No, no, that's dangerous!
[Shitara] : Careful! Careful!
[Himura & Shitara] : Huuh, that's pretty scary!
[Shitara] : Ah, thank god...
I can't do it...
[Shitara] : Even bottle?
[Shitara] : Seriously? Really?
Ah, this thing again...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
THE ONE TOOL THAT DESTINED TO BE BACK
[Himura] : This thing again!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
BIG INVENTION?
Eh! It's not like this?
[Shitara] : This gotta be a lie!
What about this?
[Misa] : Ah, dangerous!
I don't know the right grip...
[Shitara] : Ah, giving up? Just go home!
[Shitara] : Both of them can be used right?
[Himura] : Yes.
[Himura] : You want to pierce with that!?
[Shitara] : That's...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
NEW FUNCTION FOUND?
[Himura] : Using that?
[Shitara] : But that's for cork.
[ Cork = Bottle lid made from wood. ]
[Shitara] : She stops?
Oh!
Ah, there!
It's opened!
[Himura] : Finally it's open.
Alright!   - I see.
- It's unbelievable  - Yes, just can.
So you can't open a can?
- Can... I don't know how to
use the tools...
Staffs too didn't teach me how.
They didn't tell me...
They didn't teach me anything...
- Why didn't you ask them?
OI! OPEN THIS CAN!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
LEAVE IT TO BROTHER!
That's very rude.
Now we'll teach Saitou Asuka how
to open a can, but actually...
Is there someone else who can't do this too?
Eh! That's quite many?!
Huh!?
This means a sudden segment!
Nogizaka46 tries to open a can for the first time.
Nishino, try this.
How do you do it...
- It's scary...
No it's not.
- What do you mean "scary"?
I don't know how to use this...
This side seems difficult, this one...
- Would you look at that...look!
Seriously? Is this for real?
Using this, their generation...
Judging by the grip, she looks like
she doesn't know how...
Like this...
- Yes.
This.
- It's a hint!
Okay, that's how you hold it!
And you're still look confused!
Your faces look so confused!
Oh! Hold on...
No, no...
Primitive! Primitive!
That's how ancient humans open a can!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
STONE AGE?
Not by bashing it.
And now, let us teach these Nogizaka Chimpanzee
the proper way to open a can
Alright everyone look...
You put this part...
Here, and then...
- Observe!
Ah, that's awesome!
- Nope, nope...
Like this...here, you guys try it!
You do it like you're chopping vegetables.
You hold the can and then...
- Try it!
Look!
- Ahh!!! I can do it!
It's easier, isn't it? Next, try it too.
- Here, do it!
Pierce it...
...then swing!   - Yes, yes, yes!
- How was it?   - It was easier!
Come on, one by one try it!
- Hmm, it's way easier.
All of you will be accepted in this factory.
You'll get paid 1.500 Yen per day.
Can you do it?
- So, Sakurai?
Chop this part, from there...
- Well? Can she open it?
From there, then you move....yes, yes, just like that...
Ah, amazing!
- Try it, one by one.
See! What the hell is going on today?
- Good, good!
Ikuta, do it!
Ah!
- Well?
How was it?
You don't need to force it
- Finally huh?
Here, you too!
Next, Itou too...
Haah!!!
- So you can do it. How was it?
Amazing~...
And Hori too...
Yeah, yeah. Easy, isn't it?
- How was it? You can do it right?
Stuff like this must be taught?
- Uh huh...
What if we do this until the show ends?
Right, right!   - Well?
- Ha~ yes!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Finally the Nogizaka Chimpanzees evolved.
After this...Asuka's mother will make the studio even hotter.
Then, if we use this part here...
CONVERTED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
No, no. This looked like an amazing thing just for this show...
This part inside is dangerous, look...
Look it, Hori you too.
- This...
Next, an information about Saitou Asuka
from Eto is...
The most surprising thing for me is,
she couldn't cook rice.
Aah, clearly. Have you ever
cook rice?   - Never.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
DOES NOT WANT TO KNOW?
Never, huh?
- Have you never cook too?
Back then I helped my mom cooking, but...
...if you mean made my own dish,
then no, I never did it.
That's why this time we'll challenge her
to make a fried rice for the first time.
Just some fried rice.
- How did this end?
She also bought her own ingredients.
Everything was done by her. Okay, here's the VTR.
Tonight's menu is
Saitou Asuka's First Fried Rice
Red rice (Musenmai)
Salada
Carrots
Bacon
Eggs
Oil
Salt  Pepper
Shouyu
Soybean-flavored snack
Candy
Cow's milk
High quality spices
(To be brought home)
[ Musenmai = A rice product that has been washed first.
You don't have to wash it again if you want to cook it.]
Here are the things you need
When she bought the ingredients, she also grabbed
some snacks and drinks.
Plus, she also bought some food
for her to brought home.
[Shitara] : For home too.
First, cooking the rice.
[Shitara] : Oh, it's the first time?
Put the rice into the Rice Cooker.
[Himura] : Whoa this is great!
[Asuka] : No, not at all.
Maybe this much...
Pour some water too,
"I guess it's good.",
Yeah I guess it's good...
[Shitara] : Because it's Musenmai, huh?
Oil...
Then he also put a little bit of salad oil.
[Himura] : Eh!? Why would you put that in?
Next, set the timer on the Rice Cooker,
and the cooking starts.
Done!
Next, preparing the ingredients.
[Shitara] : Why is this look like Pilaf ?
[ Pilaf = A kind of fried rice, usually has
shrimp and some other seafoods. ]
When she peeled the carrots, why didn't she rotate it,
so she just peel only one part.
[Shitara] : Oh no! Why do you know nothing about this?
Is it okay if I peel it like this?
[Himura] : It seems she might...
Since she never sliced some ingredients, she
needed quite some time to did it.
[Ikoma] : Nope! That's dangerous!
[Himura] : Is that how you chop them?
But finally she got
the needed amount of ingredients.
Ah, this is tiring. Looks like this is good enough.
Bacon dan salada too,
finally she have enough.
Because she's tired, she eat some candy to
gain more sugar.
Then she break every eggs she bought just now.
[Himura] : You don't need that much....
Now, we're onto the cooking phase.
[Shitara] : So much! That's so much!
Oh! It's done.
[Shitara] : There's no steam whatsoever!
So dry...
[Shitara] : Ah, you have to cool it down first?
Dry...
First, with the hopeless fire...
...she's frying the rice
without any oil.
[Shitara] : "Hopeless fire"?!
[Shitara] : Isn't that too dry?
Ah!
I didn't put any oil...
Without touching the rice, let's put
the right amount of oil!
Still with her hopeless fire,
the other ingredients also get thrown in.
[Himura] : Why, why the small fire?
[Himura] : This is fried rice.
[Shitara] : Hopeless fire.
It's just salada she saves for the last.
[Shitara] : Is the fire strong enough?
Then she put some of the eggs
that already got stirred lightly, and cook it.
[Shitara] : The eggs. It's eggs hell.
Eh? Is it supposed to be like this?
[Shitara] : What? You didn't put all of it?
It's soggy...
Even with small fire, miraculously
for the first time, the frying sound can be heard.
[Himura] : What the..!?
Almost forgot, she starts to add some spices.
[Shitara] : Ah, right, she haven't add some spices.
Shouyu, salada, salt, and pepper,
added in order.
[Maiyan] : Ah, so much!
[Himura] : Smell..?
[Shitara] : Why does she smell it?
[Himura] : What does it have to do with the smell?
After cooking for 15 minutes...
...she thinks "Ah, it's done!", and it's done.
[Himura] : It's been 15 minutes.
[Shitara] : But this looks...
[Himura] : Not bad.
Saitou Asuka
[FIRST FRIED RICE]
The First Fried Rice.
[Shitara] : It's not come out weird.
[Himura] : Not at all.
So, how is it?
[Himura] : It's quite good even!
So hard...
[Himura] : Is it hard?
[Himura] : Won't it become even drier?
Tastes good.
It's good, but I don't like
the hard rice.
Even though I heard it's good if it's dry like this,
but I prefer the softer ones.
It doesn't taste like this.
I guess it's a success... big success.
Ehm, maybe you can't say it's amazing, but...
...was it bad? But have you eat fried rice
- I have.
Compared to what I usually eat,
that one tasted bland...
But when the staffs ate it, they said
"If I'm starving right now, I'll eat this,"
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
THAT'S NOT A COMPLIMENT
That's why it's
not really a failure too.
- It means I've already mastered the basic knowledge.
Then, you used small fire?
- Yes.
That too..?   - About that...
- Is that the small hopeless fire?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
BASIC KNOWLEDGE TOO?
Yeah, it looks like there's no hope there.
- When cooking, should you use
fire that small? Clearly it's wrong, isn't it?
Well that, slowly I turn the stove up.
Ah, a "Cold Start" type?
[ Cold Start = the way of starting a cold car machine
caused by the cold weather.]
Right, right!
- What's with the stove?
Yes!  - But was that the first time you cook rice?
- Yes, my first time.
We didn't know that until just now.
Even the other members too...
But for the basic knowledge,
I already have it.
- You keep using that words, huh?
Did you go to Guam too?
- Yes.
Did you prepare your own stuff?
Ah, my mom did it.
- Well of course.
Everything? From the underwears and the others?
Yes, everything. When she put it inside she said
"I put it here ok??". She arranged them also.
Eehh~~so kind!!!
Before you said your mom too
helps you wash your whole body?
No, I didn't say that. But when I'm taking a bath...
...she's standing in front of the bathroom's door.
Like, after I watch some horror movie, since I get pretty scared
when I take a bath, I ask my mom to stand there...
Long time ago, I remember asked
Maiyan and Mattsun....
When we were shooting a music video, we went
to an inn in an island...
...because I was scared, and to calm her down,
both of us sang...   - While dancing too...
Well then, please show the dance
you guys did back then.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
MAY YOU SHOW IT?
Unbelievable!!!
- You don't remember it at all?
Then, what's the relationship between
Saitou Asuka and her mom?
Asuka, when she's about to go home like if today
she feel so tired, before she go...
She sends her mom a mail and says
"Today I'm tired, so don't talk to me,"
To her mother?  - Yes.
- Seriously?
This is...scary...
- And heartless too...
Even though she got spoonfed
in the morning.   - Yeah.
No, it's because I'm so tired after work,
so when I'm at home I don't wanna talk...
...my older brother already knew this.
Him and my mom...
...often make some comedy skit.
Like doing some weird things...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
COMEDY SKIT?
- Comedy skit?
...and I always reacted to that.
JSo when I'm tired, I can't react at them...
...I sent a message to them "Today I'm tired,
so please don't do some strange stuff" like that.
And then they won't do it?
- They won't.
What kind of relationship is this?
But since we don't know clearly...
...how about we ask her mom directly?
Ma'am...
[Hello~]
It's Shitara from Bananaman,
It's a pleasure.
[No, the pleasure is all mine.]
- Thank you... excuse me...
Today we heard many stories about your daughter...
...but is it true she has to be spoonfed when she eat?
[Ah...that's true, almost everyday...]
[(Since forever) If she's not got spoonfed, this girl
almost won't eat]
[...that's why...]
- Ah, because she won't eat?
[Since she's still in elementary school, she always got spoonfed...]
- Elementary school?
[...because she got spoonfed alot, even now
it's a habit..]
But ma'am...   [Yes...]
Good evening, this is Himura...
[Ah...thank you for the hard work]
- Thank you...
Well...but your daughter is grown...
[Yes...]
-  Have you never told her to eat by herself?
[Yes back then in her elementary days, I told her to eat by herself]  - Yeah...
[...but now for not being late
and cause any trouble for other members...]
So that's why her mother...
Then about clothers...  [Yes..]
She said she never bought the one she wanted herself...
[That's right, actually she knows like
which one is good for her, but...]
[...maybe she just want to be catered by me. Like
"Mo~om, what about this one?" and send the pics.]
But have you said,
"Just get whichever you like?"
[I also often give her some money...]
[...but the problem is, this daughter of mine
just doesn't have the confidence...]
Even though you're so kind and
do lots of stuff for her...
...but she sends mail when she's about to go home
"Since I'm tired today, please don't talk to me."
[Well that, I understand if
I'm being too spirited...Yeah!]
-  Spirited, huh?
[With my second child...]
[...we always kid around or tell some funny stories...]
[...I actually can't talk some serious stuff.]
That's why if she sends that mail,
then that's it?
[Exactly. At home, this girl
rarely speaks...]
[...usually she's either reading
or looking at her phone...]
[...maybe she thinks her brother and me are annoying...]
[...so she sends mail like that to me...]
[I also like every member of Nogizaka...]
[...but of course I too want to hear something
from my lovely daughter...]
Surely you want to hear she talks.
Yeah you must feel lonely...   [Yeah..]
Ma'am, after this...    [Yes...]
Do you want your daughter to start being independent?
[Yes of course I do...]
Then until when will she keep get spoonfed?
[I'm sorry...]
Ah, no it's okay...   - Of course she wants forever...
- Of course...
[Lately she's been thinking about renting
a place and live by herself...]
- She wants to live alone?
If she does,
you'll feel lonely, right?
[Even though she's 18, but
releasing her seems...]
- Ma'am, do you think she can do it?
[Yes, I think she can. This girl just
doesn't want to do it, even though she can...]
Then if she wants it, then she can do it?
[Yes! Like when I caught a flu,
she could do everything all by herself...]
[WWhen I was sick, she did many things to help me...]
- Is that right?!
[Yes! She likes okayu too like me...]
[ Okayu = Japan-style porridge, softer than
chicken porridge without toppings. ]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
OKAYU FROM THE MOTHER
Ma'am...
- So that's from her mom!
So you like okayu?
[Yes...]
Next time when there's a chance,
I would love to be spoonfed my ma'am...
[Really?!]
- Yes.
[I really want to do it!]
Thank you very much!
Culinary tourism in the best place~!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Next... heated presentations about hometown!
The winner's plan will be accepted and shot!
CONVERTED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
The really amazing thing...
Aomori, Iwate, Yamagata, Miyage, everyone goes to Akita!
Everything that got presented now,
are in Hokkaido...
Akita, Osaka, Chiba, you raised your arm too!?
Lies~!!!
Audience registration for second Joshiraku
will be started from Nogizaka mobile.