Nogizaka Under Construction #52 (16 April 2016)
Shoot At My Hometown? Nogizaka Tourist!
English subtitle by Qelopin
qelopin.blogspot.co.id
Nogizaka Under Construction has begun.
We're Bananaman. Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
And then we have Nogizaka-chan.
Himura-san, please announce the program we're doing this time. / Let's do it.
Will you shoot in my hometown? Nogizaka46 hometown tourist!
5 members who are from rural areas will present recommended tourism spots in their hometown to visit in Golden Week.
Golden week is when many Japanese workers get about a week off around the end of April and beginning of May because of a cluster of holidays.
At the end we will take the majority vote of members other than these 5, and actually go shooting in the member's hometown with most votes.
The first one is Oita prefecture representative, Eto Misa.
Well then, Eto, ready, start!
Eto Misa presents, laid back refreshing Oita sightseeing tour!
As I'm pretty sure most members have never visited my hometown Oita prefecture
this time definitely I want to bring everyone in.
First is this.
Gourmet?
- Good food, right? Gourmet!
- It doesn't look so good.
Firstly, may I? This one is deep-fried Nakatsu.
- Karaage? Karaage?
- Nakatsu karaage
- The karaage is famous.
- Seki Aji.
- Horse mackerel (aji) and mackerel (saba).
- I don't know which is which though.
This one is chicken tempura (toriten).
Toriten is Oita's specialty cuisine. It's chicken tempura.
Even people who don't like karaage will find this gourmet easy to eat. There are still more.
Yakisoba spaghetti!
This is yakisoba spaghetti.
You can eat it at a restaurant called "Rapan". It has an egg, a raw egg on top of it. I have eat it once.
Rapan Restaurant's "Yakisoba Spaghetti" Pasta noodles in yakisoba style finishing, eaten together with raw eggs
- Is that an egg?
- It is an egg.
It is not miso?
On a steel plate (teppan), this is a dish iron plate.
An egg will be buried with noodles on top of it.
Eat the half-cooked egg mixed under the noodles.
The price is just 600 yen.
To order more, 100 yen.
I ate this a lot in my high school days.
- Personally I wanna go there.
- I see.
Still many more like this.
- Black sesame soft cream! (soft serve ice cream)
- Looks yummy!
Have you ever heard of "Kujuu" in Oita?
- Kujuu?
- There is a place called Kujuu plateau (Kujūkōgen).
"Black sesame (kurogoma) soft-cream" of Kujuu plateau
The black sesame soft cream there, it's in a countryside where the cows go around.
The night view is pretty and makes you forget city life and wanting to eat a soft cream.
So far, I've introduced delicious foods. But, there's not only that.
Speaking of Oita, of course
The best hot spring (onsen) in Japan!
Everyone clapping. It is onsen!
Not found in other prefectures, what onsen is that?
Ramune onsen!
It contains carbon dioxide. The moment you enter the onsen, the silver granules stick to your whole body.
Ramune Onsen Carbon dioxide gas of Nagayu onsen dissolves in to the carbonated spring.
- Silver?
- Silver-like thing.
- Silver-like thing?
- Yes! It feels really good. Blood circulation becomes smooth.
And then
Myoban onsen is located in Beppu. It has mud.
- At the moment you go into the onsen, you can be packed in mud.
- Amazing!
Myōban onsen ; Beppu mud bath onsen is expected to have skin beauty effect.
A place called "Shoya no Yakata" is a cobalt blue onsen.
Shoya no Yakata; Onsen which looks cobalt blue by chemical reaction of natural ingredients.
It does not use any bathing agent (bath salts) at all.
Actually, I'd like to show you a photo, not a drawing like this. Such a good-for-nothing drawing.
Certainly
For members ashamed in onsen, there are also onsen you can enter while still dressed.
Enter the best host springs in Japan, everyone, let's aim for the best idol in Japan!
Having that said. That is Oita. I am finished.
Wonderful!
- But this is an onsen tour, right?
- That's right.
- Is it okay for Nogizaka to be naked?
- That isn't okay.
Being naked is a little...
- Is it OK if only the upper half?
- No, no, no, no, no.
Is the upper body safe?
But if you go into a hot spring, you'll definitely need such pictures.
That would be sexy person in charge.
- Then big sister members will take care of it.
- Are they okay?
- Are you into swimsuit? Not really. In public.
- Towel. Is towel okay?
However, the place to wear a swimsuit is not just an onsen. There's also in a pool.
- Many places.
- Pool?
Because of the performance of light, the night is great.
You can see the Oita city at a glance. It looks like a fantasy of light. All together while everyone is in the onsen.
- Well, the light is good, but it's about what you wear.
- The light is important.
Than such thing...
The second is, Hokkaido representative, Hashimoto Nanami.
Hokkaido is such a strong candidate.
A winning candidate
It's because
At this point I already want to go to Hokkaido!
No need for presentation.
I thought so!
- The power of gourmet is great.
- Akita-ken exists, so please wait for it.
Well then let's begin. Ready, go.
- Everyone, I'll ask you straightforward. Anyone wants to go to Hokkaido?
- Yes!
Akita, Osaka, Chiba, raising hands. Oita doesn't wanna lose.
- Hokkaido, right?
- Right.
Hokkaido is really popular as a tourism destination.
Moreover, having vast lands, everything is there.
Everyone, what you're going to present or what you've just presented...
Hokkaido has them all!
Absolute champion.
- That's not true! Not true!
- Ah, I see. Everything is there.
Among them, I've collected what I especially want to recommend this time.
Good, this opening is good.
- The first one is this. My hometown, Asahikawa.
- Oh, Asahikawa.
This is Asahikawa. Thinking about location shooting, this is a really nice place.
The access is good. From Asahikawa, we can go to Biei and Furano, famous tourist spots.
That's unfair!
Among them, what I'd like to recommend is that as soon as you get out of Asahikawa airport, go straight up the hill.
There's a place called Tamura farm.
There you can have a soft cream made from fresh milk
and go out to the terrace
sit down on the shaded terrace and eat while watching the cows.
Tamura Farm - Use freshly squeezed raw
You can taste The Hokkaido.
If you go a little north, my recommended spot is a town called 'Bifuka'.
What can you find there
Genghis Khan (a dish) is very delicious.
- Genghis Khan, right?
- So strong!
- That's awesome, they look like they wanna eat now.
- That's right!
I think there are a lot of people who don't like Genghis Khan because of its smell.
The Genghis Khan here just ate a live sheep a while ago.
It's fresh, but...
- That's scary! - Why is that? Why is that?
It's such an expression, but of course it doesn't smell like that and it looks delicious.
- In Biei, in here, definitely please visit it.
- What is that?
- There's a place called Zerubu hill.
- Zerubu?
- When it's just around early summer, the sunflower field spreads. - Sunflower field?
Zerubu Hill Flower field can be watched with a background of Mount Asahidake and Mount Tokachi
I wanna see it.
Besides that, tulips and various flowers bloom.
You can run that vast flower field with a buggy (4-wheeled motorbike) !
I really wanna go! I love buggy! Buggy is so much fun!
In Otaru, you can do a night cruise through the canal.
- So nice!
- A very beautiful canal called the Otaru Canal
Otaru Canal Cruise - Day and night cruise through the historic Otaru Canal
in the night the canal gets lighted up, elegantly aboard the ship
- So strong!
- I wanna go there!
Everyone, definitely, yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
- Amazing!
- Wonderful!
- Hokkaido, that is very strong.
- This is the top.
- Shiraishi.
- Yes.
How is this presentation?
I think it's good in Hokkaido!
Prompt decision
Hokkaido is very good.
Though she said that the accessibility is good, it'll definitely take an hour or two traveling by car.
When moving to the next place?
- Hokkaido is vast.
- To go to Asahikawa, it takes a lot of time.
Only 2.5 hours to Osaka.
- Hokkaido by airplane
- It's 1.5 hours by plane.
No, but, but
Crushing defeat
Look! This is your time.
Subtitle by Qelopin
qelopin.blogspot.co.id
Third hometown presenter, Akita-ken representative, Ikoma Rina.
Here is the first.
Kakunodate Bukeyashiki (Samurai Mansion)
In Akita prefecture, there's a place where samurai residences are lined up.
Kakunodata no Bukeyashiki
Historic samurai residences and rows of cherry blossoms are beautiful "the little Kyoto of Tohoku"
It is called Little Kyoto, a very beautiful town street.
If you visit it in spring, in the cherry blossom blooming season
with time slip feeling, you can eat dumplings with samurai residences as your surroundings.
It's relaxing.
The good thing of Akita, it really makes you forget city life, from the moment you arrive in Akita.
And because people are kind
when you go to these places, you can feel like you're back home.
Next, my favorite.
I want you to drink Nitte old cider.
There are lots of cider variants, aren't they?
Nitekosaida
It uses water from Rokugo water spring which is chosen as one of 100 famous waters of Japan
I think this is the most tasty.
- Cider?
- Yes.
In the town where Nitekosaida comes from, there are very beautiful water springs called "Rokugo Spring Group"
- There are a lot of water springs in this place.
- It's made from it.
With that clear water, there is not only cider.
Nagashi Somen is a unique way of serving the thin white noodle via flowing cold water, conventionally slide down from sliced bamboo pipe.
There's nagashi-sōmen with everyone, too.
Appeal of nature
That's good. Such thing is good.
Even now you can drink that water, directly.
Drinking water together, the inside of heart and body will be purified by the water.
There is such a thing.
And there's stuff like sweets.
There's a shop called Yamano Hachimitsuya.
Famous shop that sold any kind of honey related product
- Good. Going on these routes thoroughly is good.
- Right! Right!
There is a popular sweets that's quite hard to obtain even for Akita-ken people.
There is cream puff with honey.
Honey cream puff
Sandwich of freshly baked choux pastry filled with honey cream
After all, everyone, with various food offered, I think your appetite has increased.
However, I definitely want you to taste this moderately tender cream puff, made of natural ingredients, that Yama-san shop has to offer.
Here too, not losing to Hokkaido's nor Oita's, there is a delicious softcream.
- They also have softcream?
- Yes, there's softcream with honey.
Finally, the famous place that I want to go to, Oga.
It's Oga. I think everyone has heard about Namahage in Oga.
Namahage in traditional Japanese folklore is a demon-like being, portrayed by men wearing hefty ogre masks and traditional straw capes (mino) during a New Year's ritual.
Oga
Oga's Shinzan Shrine is said to be one of the birthplace of Namahage.
Here we can eat fresh seafood caught in the sea of Japan. And because of that
It's really the best place for refreshing.
And the biggest challenge is that, compared to Hokkaido, Akita prefecture is only passed through.
It is not incorporated into the schedule of the tour! Absolutely!
- 6 prefectures of Tohoku, Hokkaido, only Akita is passed through!
- Eh? Really?!
Aomori, Iwate, Yamagata, Miyagi, only Akita is passed through.
- Why?
- Yeah.
Go Hiromi-san will come! Every year.
Spiritual home
That's it. If Nogizaka comes to Akita, because perhaps people don't know about any other groups, they are going to love Nogizaka.
Let's make supporters here!
Because there are such things, certainly I want to go on location shooting in Akita together. Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Ah, it is good.
On the contrary, well of course Hokkaido is good, but as a location for shooting, everyone has already seen it.
Everyone has seen it, that's why
- If we go to Akita, we can get a feeling that we've never felt before.
- Everyone will appreciate.
Continuing on the fourth presenter, Osaka representative, Matsumura Sayuri.
There was an earthquake of seismic intensity 3 in the Kyushu region at 0:10 in the morning.
Firstly, the first one is this.
Tennōji Zoo
- What?
- That's such an idiot-like tone, ten~no~ji do~but~su~en
Tennoji zoo, it is located in a place called Tennoji.
Anyway, it is cheap.
- Eh?! So cheap!
- That's right!
For adults, 500 yen. Children are free to enter.
Free for preschooler
That's right!
- That sounds like there's no exotic animals there, isn't it?
- No, no, no, no!
They have everything, for real!
- Native to New Zealand, a bird called Kiwi. They have it.
- That's amazing!
Is that the first thing to say?
- Perhaps a bigger one.
- Elephant, like an elephant.
Next, speaking of Osaka, here!
- USJ! (Universal Studio Japan)
- This one is strong.
As for me, I know where cameras are located, all of them!
- Camera? What do you mean?
- Inside those attractions, they will take your photos, right?
In which scenes, in which moments the shutters are pressed, I know all of them.
Amazing.
Right! That's why, in the Spider-man, you use sunglasses, right?
So, when our face is difficult to be seen, at that time only, I will say "Take off your sunglasses now!"
- It will be perfect!
- Amazing!
We can take pictures with Spider-Man!
Amazing! Everyone is happy.
Thank you so much.
Alright, next! Kanjōsen Tamatsukuri (Train)
Osaka Loop Line, Tamatsukuri Station
Why such a tone.
Here, through the on-site broadcast, the station attendant always says ....
"Tamachikubi"
Chikubi means nipple.
What do you mean?
- Tamachikubi is said for Tamatsukuri.
- That's right.
"The next is~ Tamachikubi~ Tamachikubi~" It's said that way.
Perhaps the station attendant is aware of this.
- Really?!
- That is a famous thing.
- Then we go there to hear it?
- Go there to hear it.
- Nishino is from Osaka too.
- Yes.
Does Osaka have a lot of nice places?
Well, it seems to me that there's no other choice but USJ.
USJ dependency
Eh, why? There's more to it.
Lastly, the fifth presenter, Chiba prefecture representative, Takayama Kazumi!
Good points of Boso! Gourmet trip! I want to do it.
First of all, I too will start from here. Soft cream!
Soft cream. Everyone pushes forward their soft cream.
These are the soft creams that got the 2nd and 3rd place in the TUNNELS-san's (comedy duo) ranking.
What ranking is that?
In a TV show called "Tonneruzu no Minasan no Okage deshita", there was a location shooting about soft cream in Chiba prefecture.
- I've seen it before.
- Thank you so much.
- And Chiba got its 2nd and 3rd position.
- That's TUNNELS-san, what did you thank for?
Personnel of the show?
Biwa soft cream
Biwa (loquat fruit) Club
Peanuts soft cream
Kimura Peanuts
And among them, in the 2nd place is Biwa Soft Cream, and in the 3rd place is Peanut Soft Cream.
- It looks delicious.
- It's really really delicious.
What is in the 1st place?
The 1st is the Mother Farm's
- Ah, still in Chiba?
- Yes, soft cream.
- The best three are all in Chiba?
- Yes, that's right.
Farm is strong, right? As expected.
Defeat to the farm
Farm's milk. Farm's milk is strong.
Going on, here it is. Ikamenchi.
- I wanna try it.
- Somehow I know about it.
Ah, you know?
"Ikamenchi" at Kamashinnikuten
Popular menu of minced squid tentacles and vegetables shaped into patties and deep-fried
Since I was young, I grow up eating ikamenchi very often.
Recently those who listened well to the TV show gave it a try.
There are people who can wait in a long queue to get it.
Truly, its tastiness level is worth that much.
For a magazine called "Spirits", a long time ago, when I did a photo-shoot as if I was walking in hometown
Our manager was also coming there.
The manager spontaneously said a single word.
Delicious!
Staff acclaim!
- Looks alike. Looks alike.
- Delicious!
He said it was "So delicious!"
- He looked delighted.
- Why do you draw the manager saying delicious?
- He was very happy.
- Ah, because members are familiar with him.
And then, next is this. Local Chinese cuisine, Houkirou-san.
- China?
- Eh, Houkirou.
This is a pretty high-class Chinese restaurant.
Rather than going there quite often, actually I usually go to that place when I want to celebrate, on special occasion.
What happened last time, when I became the Boso tourism ambassador, the restaurant president greeted me.
That is where this restaurant president said this to me.
At the inauguration ceremony of
Boso ambassador
Boss of Restaurant
Please come to eat here next time.
In that case we will offer the fine cuisine
not to be found on the menu
Please come to eat here next time. In that case we will offer the fine cuisine not to be found on the menu.
- Ah, very good!
- It's strong!
And then, I received his business card.
- So, this is in case you go there.
- In case if I go.
Perhaps everyone can eat the high-class food that  you probably don't usually eat in Tokyo otherwise.
- Ah, great!
- I want to go!
And speaking of high-class dishes in Boso, here it is.
There's a well-known shop surrounded by rice field.
This, its name is deliberately hidden.
Perhaps if I say it out, it will be too crowded.
Even now it's relatively crowded.
If we have a chance to go this place, its name certainly has to be revealed though.
This is an upscale French restaurant that uses fish taken in the local area.
For a course meal that definitely costs you tens of thousand yen in Tokyo, you can get it at relatively affordable price here. I really recommend it.
Well, for other regions, even the nearby ones, as expected, it still takes some transportation cost.
Because by one-way bus, really, we can go for 2000 yen ...
- Obviously its accessibility is the best.
- That's right!
Best for budget
If you save the money to eat delicious foods, you can perhaps eat the best food. High-class one.
Finally, I've brought sashiire (gift snacks)! Some sweets.
Sashiire is a Japanese custom of giving, usually foods and drinks.
Here Takayama uses bold strategy of sashiire using daifuku fresh cream from Takayama Seika confectionery that's in her hometown Minamiboso city.
Daifuku is a Japanese mochi dessert stuffed with a sweet filling.
- Wow, many variants!
- Right! There are many tastes.
Pretty! Very cute.
- Have members eaten this sashiire usually?
- We have. Love it. Delicious.
- Which one do you recommend?
- My recommendation, I like the pumpkin one.
I shall eat the pumpkin then? / Certainly!
Cannibalism! / Not cannibalism!
Then, the members sitting behind, other than the presenters. Except the presenting members.
Chiba prefecture yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Chiba prefecture yoroshiku onegai...
Delicious!
Because this is a rare cheese, it feels like Japanese and Western collaboration. Tasty!
- Wow, delicious!
- Really? The pumpkin is tasty?
It's pumpkin cream.
I want to eat pumpkins. Give me pumpkins.
Delicious!!!
Takayama Seika-san, this is an awesome cream you make!
- Eh, so happy! Thank goodness!
- This is awesome!
- We've never heard.
- Delicious!
- If we knew, we would've brought it too.
- I have never heard of it.
And near that Takayama Seika
In Nogizakatte Doko #95 & #96 (4 & 11 August 2013) Takayama told a story of ghost tunnel, and Nogizaka46 visited it at night.
There's ghost tunnel! Nearby
Local spiritual spot
I think it's good to have the tour on the day, then visit it on the way back home.
Chiba-ken, definitely, yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Well, the presentations of those five have done, but if anyone has a question
like "Can you do this if you go there?" or "Do you have this?" If you wanna ask
Oh, Akimoto.
After all, when going on the location shooting,  I think that interaction with people is important.
"I know that people in that place have such warmth!" I want to know about it.
Anyone wants to appeal about it? Like "there's this kind of people"
About people. My hometown has the impression of bad teenagers (yankee)
in the lower part of Chiba, like in Kisarazu.
But, in our generation now, that yankee thing is over. It's rehabilitation age. Everyone is good people now.
former yankee = good person
But I somehow understand.
- Everyone is good person.
- All in all.
But on location, a motorcycle gang there will be interesting.
Ah, I see! Those who did such activities, in my father's generation, still exist.
Such stories are interesting.
When he got into the train, suddenly he's dragged. And his head was thrown with a block.
Runaway in Boso!
- His head was thrown?
- His head was thrown.
It's too intense!
Well, that's the kind of story that I've heard.
Is there anything else?
Ah, Matsumura?
In Osaka, really, as you know, everyone is warm.
They are warm and caring.
I frequently became a lost child in Osaka.
At that time, I didn't ask directions to anyone, I'd just call out.
Elderly woman and man would ask "Are you lost?"
And then they showed me the way.
And because the atmosphere is very exciting
perhaps it's going to be fantastic if Nogizaka goes there.
No problem if anyone gets lost?
No problem at all.
We'll be treated as famous thing.
Treated as famous thing.
- That's more like when you're in Akita or Chiba.
- No, no, no, no.
If it's Akita, because people just stay in their home
Oi, oi, oi, oi! You just dissed Akita prefecture.
So then, last appeal one by one before majority voting.
Because there is no handshake event held in Kyushu.
- That's right.
By all means, not only people in this Kanto region but also let's make Kyushu people become Nogizaka fans.
So everyone let's go to my hometown Oita!
Then, Hokkaido.
In the last year's nationwide tour, when Hokkaido was skipped, Hokkaido fans were pretty upset.
In order to solve it, everyone, would you like to go to Hokkaido?
Akita.
A town where pureness grew up, Akita prefecture.
- Sounds so real.
- Like a real candidacy.
- By all means, would you like to go?
- Like a Prefectural Assembly election.
Akita is waiting for Nogizaka46!
Next, Osaka.
I think there are many good places around the country.
Everyone, let's play in Osaka's Universal Studio!
Universal is the most enjoyable, you know~
- I see.
- So strong.
Finally, Chiba!
Let's eat Chiba-ken's delicious foods until the evening.
It's called Tokyo Disneyland, but it's actually in Chiba (at the tip of Chiba).
After 6 PM, everyone let's go to the Disneyland!
Chiba's last resort!
It got out! It got out! It got out! It got out!
- The Disneyland got out!
- Splendid!
Who will win the hometown location shooting!?
With the 5 members closing their eyes, other members vote by raising their hands.
Which earns the most votes and chosen as the shooting location?
The number one is ...
The location shooting is in Nogizaka Under Construction episode 62.
IT'S CHIBA PREFECTURE !!!
Location shooting in Chiba-ken! (5 votes)
Chiba prefecture.
Maybe it's because of the last appeal.
I've got no choice.
So strong!
So then, I think I want you to go soon (to location shooting)
I'm happy. Thank you so much.
So, really, you as the tour guide with the staff-san will decide "do this, do this, do this" like that.
- Eh, I'm happy.
- Takayama, please.
Alright! There will be "Good things of Chiba" tour.
Please count on me, everyone!
- Good bye!
- Bye bye!
If I have to cry (fake cry), I will cry!
Next episode, presentation of plans that members want to do.
What plans do members want to do?
Starting on April 19, national tour by Under Members will kick off!
And then, after the broadcast ends, mobile 2nd pre-order of 2016 Summer Nationwide Tour ticket will start.
2nd Joshiraku (stage play)
From April 21, beginning accepting pre-orders via Nogizaka46 Mobile.
Furthermore, 2nd album release decision.
Individual handshake will be held in commemoration of the release.
The 3rd "Plan that I want to do" Presentation Competition!
← Sudden adoption of the studio creates surprising expansion!
⠀                        Next time is... 3rd Presentation Competition →
Subtitle by Qelopin                                                                                       ⠀
qelopin.blogspot.co.id                                                                                  ⠀
The unknown side of Asuka.
The plan that I want to do is this!
I think we might do it.
Is it a birth of a new painter?
Studio becomes a whirlpool of chaos after exhibition of drawing.