==SUB UTAMA MULAI==
==SUB UTAMA SELESAI==
==KOTAK PENJELAS MULAI==
==BENTUK KOTAK BIRU===
==KOTAK PENJELAS SELESAI==
==KETERANGAN KUNING MULAI==
Source lirik Ieven Polkka: roykinan.blogspot.co.id
.::KETERANGAN KUNING SELESAI::.
==PENJELASAN TAMBAHAN==
==CREDITS==
Nogizaka Koujichuu!
BANANAMAN
Himura Yuuki
Shitara Osamu
Don!
Nogizaka Koujichuu has started. We are the MC, Bananaman, Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu.
And here they are, Nogizaka-chan~
Ssssyn!
Well, Himura-san please announce our program today.
Alright~
The 3rd
Do it for me! The 3rd Planning Presentation Competition!
Do it for me!
PLANNING PRESENTATION COMPETITION
Today's program is to present members' project planning.
Those that look interesting will be chosen to be done in the next occasion.
First presentation will be delivered by a 2nd Gen member who's too strong, Hori Miona.
Presenter
HORI MIONA
Well. The plan that I want to do is this.
Jang!
Don't forget that 2nd gen members also want birthday festival!
Yes. That's right. In Nogidoko time, all 1st Gen members...
There was a period in [Nogizakatte, Doko?] where members' birthmonth is celebrated by showing their photos from birth until now, life flashback VTR project.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
...have done birthday festival. Actually 2nd Gen members have never done it at all.
- I have seen it much on TV...
- Yes yes.
... in the birthday festival they had a trip,
... or chosen as fans' oshimen.
We really want it, but...
2nd Gen members are forgotten, just like that.
In fact we had prepared our photos...
Perfect stand-by
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Hehe, we want to do it.
- Indeed.
- I see, forgive us, okay.
You know, Manatsu-san was once forgotten...
... then she cried, didn't she?
- Aaa, yes, I cri..cried.
If I was asked to cry, I will cry!
Tears is also stand-by.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
It's not like that you know!
No no...
It's not like you can make a system of when you can cry.
Universal theory of tears.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
- It was not like that.
- You know, Akimoto entered in the middle...
[Akimoto went on hiatus from September 2011 to October 2012 for academic reasons.]
... then if she was included, the time would have been a bit messy. You missed it, right?
Akimoto Birthday Festival Crying Incident
At that time, Akimoto who joined in the middle is the only one whose birthday VTR is not made until the project ended, then she cried after recording.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
That's right, surely missed it.
As if forgotten, and then you just burst into tears when we played the recording, like that, right?
Yes, true.
"Eh, why?" Because you felt you didn't get a part in the birthday festival.
- Well, because it looks like it's for 1st Gen members only, right?
- Yes, like that.
Because anyone else have done it, I thought...
"Ah maybe because I entered in the middle, nothing I can do about it"  Then I just burst into tears.
Hori thinks because she may cry, then she cried, like that?
Yes
Specialist in crying gland business?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Not "yes" you know!
- Well because you haven't done it, that makes you want to do it.
- Certainly.
Wouldn't it be better if, instead of birthday festival, we do another thing?
That's it. I think so. If we do it...
... why doing that exact same thing again.
Perhaps we come to their house.
We, the seniors, come to their house.
- So you can also look at old albums, like that?
- Yes, look around.
Location innovation.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
And also looking for other things.
- I see.
- Like, "Eh, what's this? Oh it's a meter..."
... body height meter.
There are some lines in the wall, like that?
What if it's NG to come to their house? If there is prohibition.
Some are like that you know.
Well, in that case, we do it using a fake family.
Fake house location.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Your way of thinking is amazing!
Do not do it. Absolutely
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
As long as it's not revealed that it's a fake family, right?
As if it's her legit home, then she says "This is my home"
Fake family audition.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Suggestion from 2nd Gen members will be taken into consideration.
Presenter
FUKAGAWA MAI
Next presenter is, who will graduate soon, Fukagawa Mai.
Jajang!
Haven't known Saito Asuka well yet.
- Saito Asuka?
- Yes.
While working hard in modelling, she also is really into variety show.
The person herself doesn't want it.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Really into variety show?
Asuka-chan the fallen bird, but...
... there's a side of Saito Asuka that's still unknown for this 1 year.
And I found it, let me show you, here it is.
Jajang!
Individual drawing skill.
Right? Nogi members whose drawing is unique are Hori and Ikuta. But...
Not only those two, Saito Asuka too has the same talent.
- Oh really?
- Yes.
Hidden painter.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
I think... what if...
How about we do a drawing activity with a particular theme, then we see each member's drawing.
Well, if so, let's do it right away!
So, Fukagawa plan will be carried out.
A drawing ability check, live in the studio.
To discover other drawing talents, all members also do the same.
Well, here is the first theme.
Ah, I see.
Goroumaru with his Routine move.
Eeee? Difficult.
Well, simply Goroumaru the athlete in your imagination is fine.
Artistic taste check
First drawing theme is a Rugby athlete with a unique style, Goroumaru.
Everyone knows it, right?
I don't know.
Don't know.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Are you serious?
That's Goroumaru, you know!
Well, in handshake I've done Goroumaru pose.
Pose modelling.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
In handshake?
Yes, but I don't know his face.
If so, for Hori, just try to draw what's in your imagination.
- Alright.
Painter who's handicapped onward.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
But if you look at them, mostly are drawing in confusion. But Ikuta doesn't look confused at all.
A genius-like drawing style.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Already know, "This must be like this!"
Ikuta, the folk song you sang that time is quite popular, right?
- Ah, really?
- That Finnish folk song.
Ah, there is someone from Embassy of Finland.
He personally asked me to come.
His comment says that he has watched it. "Visit Finland sometime!" he said.
- Visit it!
- I want! I want!
That's... from Embassy of Finland?
- Yes, right.
- Cool.
Well, since Ikuta has finished drawing, how about we listen to her singing that song.
- Is the music ready? Ready?
- Enough! It's enough!
But, you know, because it is a request from Embassy of Finland.
- That's true.
Finnish folk song
Ievan Polkka
♪ Nuapurista kuulu se polokan tahti jalakani pohjii kutkutti ♪
Amazing!
Already has the lyrics memorized.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
♪ Ievan äiti se tyttöösä vahti vaan kyllähän Ieva sen jutkutti ♪
♪ sillä ei meitä silloin kiellot haittaa kun myö tanssimme laiasta laitaan ♪
Cool!
Everyone else, keep drawing, okay!
♪ Salivili hipput tupput täppyt äppyt tipput hilijalleen. ♪
BGM for drawing.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
This is...
... great, isn't it!
I want to see the comment personally.
♪ Ievan suu oli vehnäsellä ko immeiset onnee toevotti. ♪
♪ Peä oli märkänä jokaisella ja viulu se vinku ja voevotti. ♪
This is cha... chaos.
Chaotic situation.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
♪ Ei tätä poikoo märkyys haittaa sillon ko laskoo laiasta laitaan. ♪
It's already like in a dream.
Only 1 person who is singing.
♪ Salivili hipput tupput täppyt äppyt tipput hilijalleen. ♪
New religion?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Why is that?
♪ Ievan äiti se kammarissa virsiä veisata huijjuutti, ♪
This is really cool.
♪ kun tämä poika naapu... ♪
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Awesome!
- Got commented by Embassy of Finland.
- Definitely go there okay. Then you sing along with folks there.
Ah yes, that back chorus actually is made from real people voice.
- So it doesn't use any music, thus...
- Tumbab-tumbab.
Yes, one dream of mine is to do that.
♪ Tumbab, Tumbab, Tumbab ♪
♪ Nuapurista kuulu se polokan tahti jalakani pohjii kutkutti ♪
Ikuta is singing along.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
♪ Ievan äiti se tyttöösä vahti vaan kyllähän Ieva sen jutkutti ♪
Because the drawing activity is finished, we start off from Saito's drawing.
Artistic taste check
Well, let's start.
Scary! Scary!
Like a potato.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
So this is the drawing.
Funny, eh? Here, the interesting part is the fingers.
Finger tips are in other dimension.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
- Yes, right, Goroumaru pose.
- Is this Goroumaru pose?
The pose is not like ninja, so I think it's complicated. Then I asked Ikoma how many fingers are upward.
Oh I see.
This is really drawn based on the athlete's pose, isn't it?
Yes, I think his hairstyle also more or less is like that.
Why do I feel I've seen this person somewhere before?!
A known face.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Perhaps it's someone we know.
Well, it's alright.
From the characteristic, it's understandable.
- By the way...
- There is also something like this.
Ee...
It's from Hori.
Grandpa!
Old Goroumaru.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Scary~
Well, this is because she doesn't know Goroumaru.
You don't know, right?
His hand, have you been told about it?
I've been told.
How is it?
♪ Why.. would... why would it be~ ♪
Tetsu and Tomo
Like this, isn't it?
♪ Why.. would... why would it be~ ♪
Ikoma.
Cool!
Hoo~ Skillful!
This is like anime.
Ah, but the buttocks part is nice.
Because I'm bad at it, these drawings amaze me already.
Whose is it?
It's Shiraishi.
Eee~
Shiraishi too is in the bad drawing group.
Like an artist.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Right?
I can't draw it.
Ah, this.
Based on his body form...
Body here, facing here, then doing this, right?
Bon odori?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
[Bon Odori, meaning simply Bon dance, is a style of dancing performed during Obon, Japanese Buddhist custom to honor the spirits of one's ancestors.]
His pose is like that.
Like that, right?
It's Matsumura.
- Gundam.
- Preschool kid.
Cute~
Scary.
Ee~, what's that?!
Ghost fingertips.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Scary~
How many fingers you drew?
No idea how many she drew.
But at a glance it looks like a lively primary schooler, right?
Here's Eto.
Just like an old man catching a bread.
Why is the pose?
Why is his hand doing banzai?
- Goroumaru is definitely like this.
- There's no other pose.
If not like this, then he can be doing this.
There's nothing other than that.
Why this pose?
- Doing banzai.
- Because I don't know...
And this is too.
Akimoto.
What's this?
This...
Here, part of space and time in his body vanishes.
Half mysterious.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
That, how is that?
Space and time distortion.
On that side, there's nothing.
- So its part of space and time is eaten.
- A creature like this doesn't exist.
I was confused about where to put the other hand.
Becoming like this, right? Then this side here vanishes, like that.
This too is a ghost.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Part of its space and time is missing.
This is it.
It's Takayama. Takayama.
Praying.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
If someone who's driving sees this, "Ah, it is human"
Like a mountain.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Is that a mountain? Eh, it's a human actually.
Goroukyu Mountain.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
This is monster.
Monster.
What is this actually?
- Looking for peace.
- What?
Looking for inner peace.
Well, next...
A picture of criminal, isn't it?
Criminal?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
This is from Hoshino.
- That's why.
- Why did you draw a criminal?
That's... for swimming.
- It has nothing to do with swimming.
- I mean swimming cap.
Indeed, some people use headgear.
But, this clearly is a criminal.
Praying in jail.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
That's a criminal...
Why is he wearing that?
- The facial hair. It should be a goatee in the chin.
- Yes, the facial hair.
Instead it becomes criminal's beard.
And also this criminal's cloths stripes are too thin.
Expression of a prisoner.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Wearing a cap.
This person is funny.
This is from captain.
How can he stand like that!
On an air chair.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
That's bad~
But it's cool.
Sitting on an air chair.
How can he balance himself?
How does he stand?
That pose is actually continuous.
But from here, how can it be like this.
Not anatomical human.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
The hands come out from the chest.
Quite cool. His face looks like a punk.
The front part is also missing.
He looks pessimistic, right?
I usually draw things from the side view.
But, if Sakurai's drawing is colored, it can be cool like American comics.
For example, it is drawn on snack packaging.
m 252.125 63 l 0 63 l 0 0 l 252.125 0
Comment of Embassy of Finland on Twitter: @nogizaka46 Ikuta-san is so Finland-like. (I am) Surprised to see her folk song singing. Go to Finland sometimes!
This show is brought to you by this sponsor.
XL (Xan & Lupit) x Qelopin
qelopin.blogspot.com
Wait, this is also quite good.
Let's see Skillful Team, shall we?
Nishino.
Of course, it's awesome.
Awesome!
What's this feeling? Caaalm feeling.
But definitely this goes into skillful team.
Huaa~ So good!
Hah?
Ah, obviously.
Ito Marika
This...
This has a good atmosphere.
Awesome!
Wah this one is also good. Ah, it is from Fukagawa.
So good!
The anatomy, the pose, and also his back proportion are telling "I will do it"
Great!
Wakatsuki
- Skillful, skillful.
- There's no face.
Well, Wakatsuki is also...
...definitely in the skillful team.
Although it's barefoot.
Here, the body anatomy is drawn seriously.
Next. Lastly, the drawing that was finished first.
The artist's work hasn't been shown.
The most wanted to be seen.
Huuuu!
Someone in another dimension.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Of course.
- What is that?
- This kind of creature very often comes up.
Gorilla
This eye, of the creature.
This creature can transform into many forms.
Showing innocence and oddity at once.
Based on the drawing, it first faces here, then becomes like this.
At a glance it's like baseball.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
A scary creature.
Why does it face here?!
This is a really a calm creature.
As if despite being teased in any way, it will remain calm.
This is wrong.
The works of Ikuta should be put into a studio.
Then we all try to make an exhibition.
Let's have a Nogizaka46 Art Exhibition!
Especially Ikuta's drawing.
Someone who sees it might price it 5 million yen.
Picaso Erika.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Awesome. This is an artwork that was drawn while singing Finnish folk song.
Chaos Queen.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
You seem often singing this Finnish song.
Well...
If we look at the drawing of Saito Asuka, surely...
But this kind of drawing ability does exist!
Art moster.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Seems so.
Wait, we still have one more sheet. Why don't we do it again?
- Is drawing Goroumaru a bit difficult?
- Difficult!
Well, something that you all know. Not "who" anymore.
A primary schooler who is jumping a block.
- Difficult!
- What should I do?
Artistic taste check
Next is a primary schooler who is jumping a block.
The depiction of the jumping moment is the main point.
If...
- If needed, Himura will give an example.
- An example, right?
Everyone, can you please look at Himura's move?
Unexpectedly, I couldn't jump at all.
Next, Saito Asuka's artwork will be checked.
Artistic taste check
It's Asuka-chan. Let's see.
Dan!
Falling?
What is it doing?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
- Is this before or after jumping?
- Before, when in the air.
The chin!
The chin! The chin!!
Boy without chin.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
This.
This is quite exceptional.
- What's wrong with the hand?
- How is this?
A very thin arm.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Huua! Scary!
This, this is like...
...the drawing in American comic and such.
Is this before jumping?
That is in the middle of jumping.
The logical explanation...
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
- This... what's this?
- Jumping block.
- Jumping block, right?
- Yes!
- Not jumping then!
- From here, he looks like he hasn't jumped.
- No, that pose is in the middle of jumping.
- But, he is still on that side, right?
So, it's like this, then, immediately JUMP~ like that.
Backward style.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Jump backward.
He has a good expression.
And this is too.
Quite good, right?
This face can be put on T-shirt.
Lastly...
... the hidden artist will appear.
Well, here are the skillful zone.
Clearly good.
It's Wakatsuki.
- Skillful!
- Cool!
Cool.
- This is quite good.
- What's this?
Marika-chan.
Yaa, skillful, right?
- So cute!
- Awesome!
- This is like it has been drawn 50 times.
- Splendid.
From which part did you start drawing this?
From the block.
- So, it's from the block.
Just like an illustration in school books.
It's Nishino.
- So cute!
- Awesome!
How can you draw so well?
This already looks like a picture from real world.
Absolutely.
- And also the point of view.
- That's right.
Fukagawa also.
So cute!
The boy is cute.
Cute, isn't it?
How can someone draw like this?
- Cool!
- So cute!
For those whose drawing is splendid, do you think this theme is difficult?
- It tends to be easy.
- Because we just need to make one side even to another, so I think it's easy.
Oh I see.
Because those who see it can identify it's a jumping primary schooler, Ikoma and Etou succeed.
Because the pose is identifiable, Takayama and Shiraishi barely succeed.
Akimoto's human with leg only and Sakurai's alien are stilll passed.
From here, the drawings are already "Ah, this is it"
Surely it's Hoshino.
A bit tilted.
Flying tilted.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
This is definitely a picture of Himura, isn't it?
Himura's hairstyle.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
- What's this?
- The head...
Why tilted?
How can it be tilted?
Is this a frog human?
Well...
...the intent was to draw a trouser or western cloth...
He's wearing heattech pant
Underwear and barefeet.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Why wearing heattech?
His body is so visible.
This one too...
... Matsumura.
Well, well.
She is already in a particular zone.
What's this? One of the monsters from Monster Inc.?
Jet engine.
It is taking off?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
"Jet engine"
From here, it immediately takes off, jeet!
Jeet!
From here...
... is the climax. Hori.
Here it is!
Original personal drawing style.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Why is this, Hori?
What pose is this?
This, why is the leg also following?
Spreading legs.
Human without knee.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
- Do you mean like this?
- Yes.
This means both hands and one leg go forward at once.
So it jumps forward with one leg goes forward, like that?
Next is the drawing from Ikuta, the unmatched artist.
This is quite terrifying. Well, here's the last one.
Sensei. Pardon us, sensei.
Thank you for your artwork.
Ikuta World.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Wah, this is quite exceptional.
Ikuta's drawing is once again like this.
This, can you give explanation?
I took different perspective than the others.
Different perspective?
Everyone else draw from the front view. I draw it from the side view.
That's why it's kinda different from the others.
Those are the middle parts.
- These?
- Yes.
Then, the back parts are legs.
So the legs are from here?
Eh, how is it, those legs are branched like this.
Branch point of leg?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Branching in the back part.
If I had a classmate like that, I would be so disgusted that I throw up.
Don't wanna befriend with.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
Instead of landing from above, it will be... Huaaa!
Landing on the block.
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
From above, it's like that. Fuaaa~
Is this drone?   - Yes it is.
This must be drone.
Just add some propellers and it will become a drone.
Hmm... This time...
Actually the plan of Fukagawa is to see the Saito Asuka's drawing skill.
Ah, that's right.
Well, it's good. But in fact, those with better drawing skill are many.
Haa, interesting.
This...
This is also an artwork of an artist.
This is enough.
Well.
But, somewhat similiar.
Similarity between geniuses?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
- Similiar, aren't they?
- Don't they resemble each other?
- They resembles each other.
- If they are put together, a strange creature will appear. Interesting.
The real appearance?
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
The closest one is Saito Asuka's.
Let's hold an exhibition.
Yes, let's hold it.
The activity is postponed and will be continued with its planning.
Next, although the drawing session took too much time,
Akimoto wants to hold a new staff recruit competition.
This plan is accepted and will be done.
Please wait for it!
Yeah, the writting is determined though.
The first is this...
- Especially if he's like Choi Hong-man.
- That's too big.
Isn't mucle so shiny?
Appearance-wise, it's okay.
- It's okay?
- Why you keep talking about appearance!
Nogizaka46 2016 Mid Summer National Tour
Its ticket can be ordered via mobile.
Pay attention to the deadline!
Next, ticket of second girl stage play from 2nd Gen members can also be ordered.
Pay attention to the deadline too!
So cute~
The member is blushing...
m 703.375 -262.5 l -707.875 -262.5 l -707.875 28.5 l 703.375 28.5
No, this is embarrassing.
Find out members' ideal type!