Subtitle by Qelopin | qelopin.blogspot.com
Nogizaka Under Construction #56
Come on! New recruits competition!
Tonight's Nogizaka Under Construction
At the third presentation competition, Akimoto proposed...
Note: Third Presentation Competition is in episode 53
The second half of the new member participation contest!
This time, this five people want to establish their activity clubs!
Ikuta Erika
Hori Miona
Takayama Kazumi
Matsumura Sayuri
Ikoma Rina
In turn, they describe the appeal of their club.
For the members other than those five people...
They will submit an entry submission to the club they want to enter at the end.
This week, starts from Takayama's presentation!
Start!
This is the side activity I want to make! Jjyan!
Board game club.
Right? Isn't it just right?
[Relaxed culture]
Is it just right?
Why did I make this sub-activity?
Is it alright?
Is it okay?
[Flip recovery circle]
Board games have unlimited possibilities.
I've already talked about the excellence of life games on the air.
Board games are not just life games.
Did you know that there is a place like this around you?
[Without permission]
Here is a picture of a board game cafe.
- Board game cafe?
- Yes. / That's awesome.
Recently I have been to such a place
I made a coverage report about such place.
There are hundreds of board games on the wall.
So I went there by myself.
And even if you do not know the rules
The clerk would teach you.
So, please take a look here.
Everyone's face looks so happy.
- Look at this closely.
- I can not see their face.
What kind of face do you see when you look at it closely?
- This smile.
- Everyone's smiling.
- Have you recently smiled like this?
- No, I do not think so.
I haven't done 'Yahoo!' recently.
So you didn't do it, right?
Takayama said that she brought a recommended game.
Challenge for everyone!
The recommendation of Takayama was designed in Germany.
Obake Catch
Look at the picture of the card and pick items with color and type different from the card. A quick-picking game.
For example, this card has a red bottle and a blue goblins.
So pick the gray rat.
But if there is something like this item...
You have to pick it up.
The challenger are Bananaman...
Saito Chiharu, Yamazaki, Takayama, 5 players.
[Special rule: You're safe after acquiring 5 cards]
I'm coming, ah! There is a slogan.
"Obake catch!" Please everyone do it.
[Special rule: You're safe after acquiring 5 cards]
When shall we say it?
- In Obake Catch.
- So when we catch it?
Obake catch!
Shitara
Himura
Takayama
Yamazaki
Chiharu
Shitara
Fast! Fast!
So in this case, Chi-chan was wrong at the moment.
If she had one of her cards here...
You have to give it away to Shitara-san.
[Rule: If you make a mistake, give a card to the person who has a match]
- Is this what I'm taking?
- Yes. It's Shitara-san's.
- Is this going to be used again?
- Yes, that is correct.
Obake catch!
Shitara
Yamazaki
It's blue (book). You got to take the blue book.
Takayama
[If there's something exactly like the illustration, you have to pick it up]
So I take the card from Shitara-san.
- Funny.
- Yes, I will.
Obake catch!
Shitara
Chiharu
So fast.
Yamazaki
She's right. I think Rena took one of them.
- If you do not have one, you'd better just run?
- Yes, that is correct
I do not know what it is.
I'll go.
Obake catch!
Shitara
Chiharu
It is not right.
What happened to this?
You should not pick anything with that color or type.
- It's a difficult game.
- It's a little hard.
I will surely catch it.
Obake catch!
Chiharu
The answer is correct.
Chi-chan is correct.
I want to catch something, but I can not catch it.
Obake catch!
Shitara
Yamazaki
- Oh yeah
- I'm going.
Obake catch!
Yamazaki
Fast! Fast!
Funny / I'm going.
Obake catch!
Shitara
Takayama
Chiharu
- You win. / Funny
- I win. I think I win.
- This is fun.
- Obake Catch
It was fun. Thank you both.
Then, we challenge Takayama's recommendation, gokiburi (cockroach) poker!
In this game, players do not show their card, and try to hand it over to the opponent.
A psychological game that's based on whether it is a lie or a real.
If you can not see the lies, your cards will be stacked.
When a certain amount of cards are collected, you are defeated!
This six people will challenge this Gokiburi poker!
Maybe we can continue this. All night.
- It would be fun.
- Yeah.
[Experienced Shitara]
- I'll go to Himura-san.
- Are you going to me?
[Experienced Shitara]
- I'll go to Himura-san.
- Are you going to me?
- This is
- I look stupid.
- It's a frog.
- Himura-san is a frog.
- Not that.
- Not a frog.
Then, open it please.
- Oh, it was a frog.
- Is that a frog? This?
- You take it.
- Two more in the future.
- Me?
- Now it's Himura-san's turn to hand out the card to somebody.
[Rule: you lose if you collect four cards of the same kind or all kinds of cards are collected]
Okay, then, Inoue!
Is this a frog?
This is a frog.
Wait, the personality of Himura-san...
I think I'll say it's the truth, judging from the personality of the Himura-san.
It's a frog.
Ah, it's wrong.
Then you have to take it.
The rat is taken.
- (Asuka) What kind of card is this?
- Kameishi (the worst)
Asuka!
This is a frog.
It's not a frog.
- It's dangerous.
- Is it quite dangerous?
Two more types to go.
We use five types of cards this time.
Inoue will be out once she gets spider and cockroach.
- Then, Shitara-san.
- Oh, you're coming to me.
This is a rat.
Yes, this is a rat.
- Oh~ really~
- Oh, it's dangerous.
It's still okay.
- It's dangerous, isn't it?
- I knew you were going to tell the truth about this.
What is the status now?
Right now, two more rats and she's out.
- Cockroach..
- When this is done, everyone gets set up.
This guy looks like he's gonna get it.
In this case we speculate on each other based on the psychological side.
That's right.
If you look at it now (behind the psychology), it looks like you ought to.
It's definitely a rat card.
- Hee~
- You're reading that. Interesting.
Inoue, what do you want to do now?
- Even if your hand is gone, you lose.
- Yes, that's right.
- So...
- You have to hurry to the stupid guy.
Then...
Nanamin, this is a rat card.
That's a rat card.
It's not a rat.
- It's dangerous.
- One to go.
What's this? Cockroach? / No spider.
It's dangerous because there's only two to go.
When roach card comes, Inoue is out!
How will she get rid of this unfavorable situation?
- What are you gonna do?
- What are you going to do, Sayunyan?
One more roach and you're history.
- It's the end if it's cockroach.
- What should I do?
- It's okay.
- Then Kazumin, this is a frog.
This is not a frog.
Frustrating, frustrating, frustrating!
- It's over.
- Yes, it's over.
Inoue! It's too easy for you to be read.
According to the original rule, the game ends here.
But we continue the game, because it looks fun!
So Hashimoto would you like to try it?
It's a spider.
Look at your expression seriously.
This is...
It's not a spider.
Oh, it was a spider.
This is a bug.
It's not a bug.
- Oh, no!
- Shitara-san. / The cockroach's taken.
It's dangerous! I do not know. I might lose.
So it's a frog.
Frog..
It's not a frog.
I can not do this.
This is...
This is a bug.
This is not a bug.
- Oh, it's a bad idea.
- Oh yeah! Good.
Experiencing a pinched situation, Shitara-san suffers a concentrated attack into a crisis.
If the frog appears, he's out!
It's dangerous for me.
It's a cockroach.
Who is the cockroach?
It's a cockroach!
Well! It's wrong!
- Then, Himura-san.
- Am I right?
Then, Himura-san, please.
This is a bug.
This is...
a bug.
Dangerous.
Somehow I feel sorry. Somehow I feel sorry.
- Ah, Himura-san's turn.
- Is it still me?
He is anxious... this time.
It's a cockroach.
What's going on?
- And then, is it a spider?
- Why did you take it?
When cards become few and become likely to lose...
It's easier to be read because he gets anxious.
It's cockroaches.
- It is not!
- Then Nanamin.
Somehow I passed it.
- It's a spider.
- The spider appears then it's over.
- If it's spider, game over?
- Huh. Isn't it? 1,2,3,4 Oh, right. The spider will come to you.
Dangerous!
It's not a spider.
It's a spider.
Defeat! / Aah!
A bunch of other board games to recommend!
Takayama is waiting for new recruits!
(Left) However, Himura is becoming a sandbag! What the hell is happening?
(Right) The studio becomes a fight ring in Hori Miona's presentation!
The last presenter is Hori Miona!
Well, then Hori, onegaishimasu!
Yes. The activity club that I want to establish is this!
Jajyan!
Nogizaka Action Club!
Well! / What is this?
Nogizaka Action Club, NAC, for short.
- NAC?
- My goal is to be an action actress.
- Is it so?
- Yes, that is correct.
The target actress is...
Playing a role in Biohazard, Milla Jovovich-san.
Note: Biohazard is Resident Evil
- Like this.
- No, wait a minute, isn't it weird?
[Who are you?]
- Like this.
- No, wait a minute, isn't it weird?
- Did Milla Jovovich do this?
- Why is that?
- What's this on her hand?
- It's a gun.
- A gun?
- This is which Biohazard?
- Yes, the second? Was it the first?
It does not matter either way.
[The problem is not that]
Well, Milla Jovovich's action is great, though.
- The wire action is also very good.
- I agree.
I am also very fond of actress.
Nogizaka is also aiming to be an actress.
I think there are many people who want to play.
So let's take action and expand the direction of work.
[One day, as an action actress, an offer might come!]
Well, that's good.
Action club activities are specifically...
Specifically, you can play clean punches or kick.
[Learn the basics of punches and kicks in martial arts gym]
We'll learn from a martial arts teacher.
And wire action.
We'll learn from the gym teacher.
[Acquire wire action skill in gym classroom]
Physical ability (Let's improve it)
It's awesome, it's real.
- I have drawn my goal in illustration.
- Goal?
It's an action I want to learn.
"I want to do someday! This action!" The first is...
jjyan!
Gorgeous spin kick.
Wait a second, look here.
Well, other than the thickness of the legs, it's fine.
What is next to that person?
It's a zombie... anyway.
I really like Biohazard.
- So she's spin kicking?
- Yes, she's kicking.
So it's not the one walking backwards?
The second one is...
This one!
Rolling forward and punch!
Rolling forward and punch, what's that?
If an enemy, for example, Kotoko is an enemy.
What if Kotoko is enemy? A zombie?
- Yes, Kotoko is a zombie.
- Kotoko is a zombie!
Running up there...
First to go there, then the momentum is not enough.
Do you think that something is missing in the picture as well?
So I do the rolling forward.
- It's called backroll.
- After you get close enough...
You punch this way.
I know you want to try this one.
But can you do some action?
Show your kick and check your current skills!
- All right?
- Hold it a little tight inward.
- Is this what you want?
- You have to hold both sides.
Like this? OK
No, wait!
[ Appointment ]
Very bad control!
[Foundation of laughter]
Done? Then I'll go.
(Once here ..)
Wait, wait, wait.
[Unable to match]
Sorry. Hold on a second.
No, no, no variety style.
[Entertainment Style]
I want to see you once being kicked.
- Oh! You have to say "Hai!" and do it.
- Just one time, not many times.
Give a blow to your enemy.
Ready! GO!
Cool! Cool!
I want to do something like this.
After all it is better to learn how to kick like an amateur.
- Yes.
- Then, Wada! / Yeah!
Because Wada does Karate.
Oh, you did!
Karate-experienced Wada's turn to show kick demonstration!
Are you sure? Suddenly, if you get hit by muscle pain, it'll be scary.
- It's cool, too!
- That's right, too.
Well, Hori. / Yes.
Please go ahead.
Is it me?
Ah, I was wrong.
[Wada is ignored?]
What now?
- Hori said "Yes" and then Wada kicked over.
- Oh, sorry, Well, Wada please go ahead.
Oh quite heavily!
Can you learn some more now?
Oh, it's okay, isn't it?
- Oh, why don't you get someone from the back?
- (Anyone ... !)
[Invitation to kick]
[Kawago's sudden appearance]
No, it's not!
- What are you doing?
- What's up? What's up?
- Kawago. What's going on?
- What are you doing, you?
[Himura performing arts]
What are you doing, Kawago?
Why are you playing now?
Kawago!
What is Kawago doing?
It was not even Kawago's turn!
I'm sorry! Really.
- Be careful!
- (go ahead)
[Sandbag Himura]
No, I did not even raise the guard.
.
Come on after I put this up.
After I put this up.
[Honorable Kawago]
[Confused Himura]
- What are you doing? What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
Actually, I'm looking for an action movie rather than a contest!
This is next! It is unfolding, the result of entry submission!
We've listened to five presentations and then members submit entry to department they want to join!
If the number of entrants is zero, that club is dead!
So, what is the result?!
First, Ito Karin!
Scuba Diving
Mountain Climbing
Anime Voice Acting
Board Game
Action
Board game!
Itou Junna! / Yes.
Nogizaka Action Club! / Oh.
Kawago.
Action club! / Oh!
- Did it feel good to kick?
- He was kicked.
- I will never forgive.
- I felt good.
Rotti.
Action club! / Ah~
Eh, action club is great, isn't it.
Kitano. / Yes.
Board game.
Saito Chiharu. / Yes.
Scuba diving.
Saito Yuri. / Yes!
Scuba
Sagara / Yes
Nogizaka Action Club
- She's going to the action club, Sagara.
- Well, Climbing club and Anime club is on the edge.
Sasaki Kotoko / Yes
Anime voice acting / Ah~ Come!
Suzuki Ayane
- Nogizaka Action Club
- It's action club.
Eh, action club is awesome.
Terada Ranze
Mountain climbing! / Oh!
What? I thought because you like anime you were going to anime (voice acting) club.
Himetan! / Yes!
Anime voice acting / What is it, Himetan.
Noujo
Nogizaka Action Club
I see / It's popular
Higuchi
Nogizaka Action Club! / Eh, seriously.
Yamazaki / Yes!
Nogizaka Action Club! / Eh?
Wait a second, Nogizaka Action Club is really popular.
- Miria-chan
Mountain climbing!
Great! Mountain climbing club.
- Maya
Board game
Asuka-chan.
Mountain climbing! / Eh!
That's lie, right? / Eh, seriously?
- Really?
- Lie, why mountain climbing?
It's all cute kids.
(I do not know if there is an angry child)
Hashimoto
Board game
Shiraishi
Nogizaka Action Club! / Ee~ Action
Eto
Nogizaka Action Club
Action club is strong.
Hoshino!
Mountain climbing! / Ee~~ Why is that
Note: Hoshino said that she certainly wouldn't join mountain climbing club, in previous episode (Episode 55)
Sakurai
- Scuba!
- Ah, so it's scuba diving club.
Surprisingly, scuba club members is not many.
Wakatsuki. / Wakatsuki.
Nogizaka Action Club
Akimoto.
Mountain climbing!
Ito Marika.
@H!@#$%
What was he saying just now?
- Lastly, Inoue.
@H!@#$%
Because I did it earlier.
By the way...
Earlier one climbing member said she did not want to join that club.
- Minami-chan
- Hoshino? Mountain climbing club?
The passion of Ikoma is conveyed well.
When Ikoma wants to go somewhere like this...
It will be a good memory if I go up to where she is going.
So I thought that I wanted to go up together.
Asuka
Asuka-chan is surprising too.
I was really hesitant about board games.
I was really hesitated.
I'm not very active either.
My mother likes to climb quite a lot.
I never said anything else.
My mother often invites me to go mountain climbing.
Why is that?
I think she is getting power from the mountains.
On a few days off...
She said "Let's go to the mountain once."
[Mountaineering mama]
- So?
- But I have not been there often.
If I go there for work...
"I like this mountain," I'll recommend it to my mother.
Note:
Board game club will have a farewell activities for Nanamin in episode 17.02.19
Mountaineering club will do frozen waterfall climbing in episode 17.03.19.
Scuba Diving Club
Mountain Climbing
Anime Voice Acting
As you can see, here is new members of the activity clubs!
From now on, within this program, we will report the activities of each club.
Board Game
Nogizaka46 Action Club
Please look forward to that!
[Going around Takayama's Local Hometown Chiba]
Hometown sightseeing is realized!
(Left) Takayama's unique local hospitality.
(Right) Next episode, visiting hometown as tourists in Chiba and Boso
Nogizaka 46 Midsummer's National Tour 2016
Currently pre-order ticket for Rakuten.
Check the official site for details!