DON!
And we're on! We're the hosts of Nogizaka Under Construction, Bananaman, and...
I'm Fukagawa Mai!
And here are Nogizaka-chan!
Alright, there are a lot of them today. Our activity for today is...
Please announce it for us, Himura-san.
Congratulations! Fukagawa Mai's Graduation Activity: Audition for the Second Holy Mother!
Yay!
Alright.
So you're doing a concert in Shizuoka?
Yes. On the 15th and 16th.
And that's your last appearance for Nogizaka?
Yes, it will all end with that.
The end.
So you only have a few days left.
Yes.
So today is also the last time you're appearing here as a member of Nogizaka, right?
Yes, it's the last.
Last Under Construction
I see.
Right?
The last, huh.
We've been doing this together for a long time, so it'll be lonely without you.
Ve-Yes, it's sad.
What's with the Ve?
Was gonna say very sad.
So it was Ve from very.
Yes, a Ve from very.
I see.
Even the inside of my mouth is fat so I stumble over my words.
Fukagawa has been accompanied by her endearing title of "Holy Mother."
With her graduation, the seat for Nogizaka's "Holy Mother" character will be vacated.
To fill in that hole, an audition for the second Holy Mother will be held tonight.
The ones who have put forth themselves as the ones who deserve the title are:
Akimoto, Ikuta, and Hori.
Tonight, the second Holy Mother shall be chosen from these three.
All of you. A Holy Mother will be picked from these three. A new one.
It looks to me like everyone has objections about the choices.
Why these 3?
The air is filled with the question "Why these three?"
Please leave it to me.
Wow.
Full of confidence.
Is this girl being serious? Is she alright?
Well...
She's not fooling around, is she?
No, I think it's fine.
First, these three will state how they deserve to become Nogizaka's Holy Mother.
Our top batter is Akimoto Manatsu.
Let us hear her reason for running for the position of Nogizaka's Holy Mother.
During Nogizaka Under Construction...
For Halloween, we all did cosplay, didn't we?
At that time, I unknowingly did something...
I'd like everyone to please take a look at what I mean. Jan!
I did a cosplay of a Sister.
Oh.
When I did this, I had no idea this would happen.
Sister.
Reasons for becoming the 2nd Holy Mother
Around 2 years ago, she somehow did a cosplay of a Sister!
I had absolutely no idea that we would be holding an audition for the second Holy Mother.
But somehow!
You were already there.
Unknowingly, I chose this costume out of the many choices available.
I became a Holy Mother.
And so, with that...
I was guided by the Holy Mother, and wore that costume.
And now, I'm here taking this audition.
It's like you were guided by some natural power.
Yes. Even years ago, I felt a pull, like a calling.
And so I ended up wearing this then.
And Akimoto has one more reason...
The Holy Mother Approaching
I think everyone here is wondering what this is about.
There's a part of the current Holy Mother, Maimai, that's coming closer and approaching me.
The person herself is shocked!
Yes.
Maimai's shocked.
No, no, no.
She's surprised.
What is this approach that Akimoto felt from Fukagawa?
Normally, when we're waiting, I usually go tsuntsun and chu like this.
And somehow, this has infected Maimai as well!
She has come to regularly go tsuntsun and chu as well.
I'm not just naming myself Holy Mother, the Holy Mother herself is approaching me.
Reasons for becoming the 2nd Holy Mother
The Holy Mother has come to imitate her!
I believe this means I'm already a Holy Mother at this point.
Like you're meant to be the Holy Mother.
Yes.
Did you notice this yourself?
Well, now that it's mentioned, I guess I've noticed this myself too.
Like when I go to tease Manatsu I go tsun! and I think, "Oh, I just said that."
I guess... When it's put that way, I may actually be kind of approaching her...
Cute!
The second Holy Mother audition. The next candidate is Ikuta Erika.
I suppose that people don't really see me as a Holy Mother character.
But I believe I do actually have the what it takes to be one.
I would like to talk more about what this is from here on.
I see.
Now, can you tell me what it is that Maimai always has with her?
Then, Shinuchi-san!
So we're in class now.
Alright, Shinuchi-san.
Perfume... She always smells really good, so I think she always brings her perfume with her.
Also, I don't know if it's for giving it out to everyone, but she always has some chocolate with her.
Ah! Yes!
She gives it out.
So she gives you chocolate?
That's correct. Yes.
Chocolate.
She always has chocolate with her, right?
So you always have chocolate with you?
I like chocolate so I usually have quite a bit of it in my bag.
Is that so?
And you give it out to everyone?
When the members say they're hungry, I give it out to them.
Is that so?
That really gives off that Holy Mother vibe, doesn't it?
Yes.
So, then. What is it that I usually have in my bag?
This.
What is it?
Snacks.
I always carry around snacks in my bag.
However, thus far, I haven't actually had the chance to share them with anyone...
Zero sharing experience.
But, well...
Aren't those for your own consumption?
No, no. It's so that I can deliver when the need arises.
So I habitually save up our snack provisions in my bag.
Snack provisions?
So you don't buy them yourself.
Ah. Yes.
So you steal from the catering service?
Ah, yes. Well, steal- Ah, no, it's not like that! It's not!
No, I don't steal
When we think of Maimai, this is the image we first think of.
Yes.
Loves tricks.
Eh? Really?
Is that true?
She plays tricks quite often.
So you like tricks?
Yes. I do tease people quite often.
What kind of tricks?
Like knee buckling...
Hm, what else? Well, I think I just like useless tricks like that.
Ah, I see.
Well, I also happen to like small tricks.
Reason for becoming the second Holy Mother
Just like the Holy Mother Fukagawa, she likes tricks
I play tricks on members hoping to make them smile.
So you're already doing that?
Yes, indeed.
That's why I thought we were quite similar in that sense.
True, that does make you quite similar.
Yes, exactly. We're similar, the two of us.
But I think Iku-chan's tricks are a bit too much, though.
What's this?
Like when she's sitting beside you, she would pin your legs so you can't move...
And during interviews, she would sometimes hold your hand like she was going to crush it.
High-level punishment game
Why would you do that?
Why would you hold someone's hand hard enough to crush it?
Why would you do that during an interview?
That's so that she won't fall asleep during the interview.
I provide the excitement needed to keep her awake.
Lashings of Love?
So she looked sleepy?
She did look drowsy.
No, I was totally energetic but she still held my hand super strongly.
That's funny.
Wow.
That's just funny. So you clasped her hand.
Like you were going to crush it.
The second Holy Mother audition. The third entry is Hori Miona.
First, I tried thinking about the qualifications of a Holy Mother.
The first is...
Hardly ever getting angry.
If I do say so myself, in my entire life up until now...
Reasons for becoming the 2nd Holy Mother
Has almost never gotten angry
H: I haven't really...
S: No way
Yes, I've hardly gotten angry.
For real?
Yes. Has anyone here ever seen me angry?
Is there anyone here who has seen Hori lose her temper?
There is?
Eh? Well, when her older sister got her mentaiko...
Ah!
She cried in anger.
Well, that was really more of sadness than anger, though.
Hi: So you weren't angry?
H: Yes.
So you weren't angry then.
I didn't really go on a rampage because of that.
I see.
Anger = Rampage?
Yes. It wasn't anger.
So that's the level of anger we're talking here.
So then, why don't I get angry? This is the answer.
It's a waste of one's life.
Wow, that's big.
The message is big huh.
Reasons for becoming the 2nd Holy Mother
Time spent in anger is a waste!
When you get irritated over little things, you cause trouble for the people around you as well.
And you yourself will also feel awful.
I think time spent on that would be such a waste.
You see, I have a very short life line on my palm.
So you're going to die?
Probably...
Probably?
That's...
Were you told this?
Ah, no, I judged it myself.
Oh, so this was just from your own judgment.
Yes.
So since yours is short, you thought you'd be wasting your life if you got angry.
I'm treating life valuably.
Since I've been given this life, after all. I thought I'd properly... Yes.
And now, a question from Hori whose other reason is her desire for doing things for other people.
And now I have a question for everyone. When you hear "Holy Mother," what color do you think of?
Yes, Itou Junna-san. What color do you think of?
Green, I guess.
That's wrong.
Wrong?!
Rejected!
So that's wrong?
What about others?
How about asking others?
Alright then. Itou Karin-san.
Yellow?
That's wrong.
She says you're all wrong.
Well, let's keep on asking until someone gets it right.
Then, Wakatsuki Yumi-san.
White?
Yes. That's correct.
White.
Yes.
Hori insists that the color of the Holy Mother is white.
Her reason for that is...
This is the picture we took after skydiving when we went to Guam.
Please take a look.
I'm the only one wearing all white.
This is, well... I guess because I'm like a Holy Mother...
Holy Mother color from head to toe
I wore white. Unconsciously, I ended up wearing white.
Eh. I suppose...
Yes.
But... I think I'm also wearing whit-ish there.
Holy Mother?
Ah... Well, I think Shitara-san is wearing gray...
Well, well. That is gray...
And now, an opinion from Kawago who named Fukagawa the "Holy Mother."
This is... I'm actually quite angry in my heart right now.
I'm thinking "Why a second one?!"
What's that about?
Right? You get it, right?
What is it? I don't get it.
I don't think anyone else can be qualified to become a "Holy Mother" other than Maimai.
That's exactly why it's the second, right?
Covering it up like that isn't good.
I get that.
I get how you feel like this isn't right.
But if we don't do this, we can't move forward!
Then... I have something to say.
My image of the Holy Mother is red. Not white.
Like a red filled with warmth, passion... Like, kindness without love, it just won't do.
So, then...
So not white?
Not white.
Hori, what do you think?
Maimai...
Hori? Ah, Hori also has something to say.
What?
I absolutely love red!
She loves red. She says she loves red too.
No, no!
Well, I'm wearing red right now, and...
Yeah, you're wearing red.
I don't care about that!
Um... You know those glow sticks fans use to cheer during our concerts? My color's red.
Well, I'm red and red plus heart!
Eh?
Wait, wait.
Wait. Kawago, you're not running for Holy Mother, so that doesn't matter.
Wait a moment. Heart? What do you mean by heart?
Also, I have something to say about Manatsu.
In her official profile, she cheated by 3cm.
Suspected falsification of height.
She's only 153cm but she wrote 156cm.
She's made herself taller?
Probably. Yes, what do you have to say?
That's... Well, a liar definitely cannot become a Holy Mother.
Yes. I think so.
But we don't know yet whether this is a lie or not...
For the record, let's ask her.
So, did you really?
Yes...
Why would you change your height by a little like that?
This isn't good.
No, it's not like that. It's because I was still in high school when I joined the group, so I thought I would still grow taller.
I put my hopes into those extra 3cm.
Next is the second test.
It's time to announce what points of similarity they think they have with Fukagawa.
Yes. When I entered Nogizaka...
After looking at various pictures, there was something fans always told me at handshakes.
They said I looked really similar to Maimai.
Similarities with Fukagawa When she joined the group, she was told they looked similar.
They said that!
Yes.
What? You mean you look alike?
At the beginning? Your faces?
I was told our faces looked really similar.
Oh, is that so? Well, now, I don't really think that's true...
But you may have looked alike in the beginning.
It seems we looked alike back then.
When I entered middle school, there was this girl who looked so much like Oginome Youko.
Everyone agreed that they looked alike, but when graduation came, everyone said that they didn't look alike at all.
What's the point of this story?!
Hori, do you have any common points?
We both like food.
Everyone does.
When you put it that way, that's true. Everyone does.
Common point with
the whole world.
Like do you have the same favorite?
I think that's an important point.
Gyoza.
Ah, gyoza, gyoza.
- Me too!
{Dachou Club state.
Right, everyone.
Gyoza is kinda...
Everyone kinda likes gyoza.
Gyoza.
Everyone likes gyoza.
I like Ghibli.
Me too.
Everyone also likes that.
But do you watch them frequently?
Yes.
I watch them while eating gyoza.
Ikuta, do you have any common points?
I have the same troubles as Maimai when it comes to hair length.
Isn't that just 'cause your hair lengths are around the same?
But do you have any other member you consult about this?
I had a conversation about that with Iku-chan the other day.
Did we?
Since our hair lengths are similar.
Ah, yes around the same.
Yes.
I don't have any memory of having talked with Karin-chan.
This kind of Holy Mother won't do!
Where's the holy in this one?
This Holy Mother won't do.
Well, she's so much of a Holy Mother, she's like a god.
Oh, I see.
She sees everyone so equally, it's not even about who she talked with anymore.
That's true. That's actually quite impudent on Karin's part.
Disrespect towards
the Holy Mother.
I'm sorry. It was rude of me to talk to her.
She has no memory of that, you know.
Next. Among these three, who do the other members think unfit to become the Holy Mother?
Hashimoto. Among these three, is there anyone you think unfit?
If I had to pick...
Miona likes zombies and horror which are pretty much the total opposite of a Holy Mother...
I see.
Reasons for being unfit | Hori   How can a Holy Mother like horror?
I think a Holy Mother normally wouldn't have such interests.
What do you have to say about this?
I think that's prejudice.
Cleaved with one stroke.
As expected!
As expected, really.
Isn't that so?
Cleaved with one stroke. What about Inoue?
I think it's Manatsu.
I have two objections.
Well, the first is that she's a big lying bitch.
That's scary! That's not true! It's not!
Plainly insulting her?
You know, when you say it with that tone...
Mean! So mean!!!
When you say it in that tone, that's a bit too much...
A big lying bitch.
That's not true!
Is she a lying bitch?
She always says on her blog and all that she's really good at cooking.
And she's always telling us members that she'll cook something for us.
But she hasn't made me anything, not even once.
So it's that I'll cook for you fraud. So she says that to almost everyone and doesn't make you anything?
Ah... I see.
Reasons for being unfit | Akimoto   Suspicion of "I'll cook for you" fraud
It's not like that. I am cooking for them, but there's an order, right?
Then when I think about who I should cook for first...
There are people who end up being much later on the list.
Finally, these three members will announce which member they think is unfit to become the Holy Mother.
I think it's Iku-chan.
I think she's unfit. The first reason is because I can't find even a single healing quality in her at all.
Ikuta... not even a single healing quality.
Reasons for being unfit | Ikuta   Can't find even a single healing quality in her!
Yes. And there's one more reason.
What's more is that she actually causes harm.
Harm?
Yes.
She would keep on talking to you in the bus even when you're tired.
And she would endlessly keep throwing questions without answers at you in the plane for a full one and a half hour.
I really wanted to sleep.
Reasons for being unfit | Ikuta    Endlessly asks questions without answers!
Questions without answers?
Like "When do people die?"
The annoying type.
So it's those philosophical types of questions...
It's that level.
Ikuta, who do you think is unfit?
I think it's Hori-chan.
Oh? Hori is unfit? Why?
Her life line is really short, right?
Yes, she said that earlier.
Mine reaches up to the back.
Woah.
If you trace it, it reaches up to here.
You could totally reach 130 years with that.
Yes. It reaches up to here.
Seriously?
Yes.
No way!
Really? Is it connected?
Yeah, yeah, it's connected.
No, you say that, but is it even possible for the line to reach up to the back of your palm?
Are you sure that's connected?
Yeah, it is.
Holy Mother of crude speech.
No, no, it's impossible for the line to reach up to the back of one's palm!
Isn't there a break somewhere in the middle of the line? Is it really connected?
I'm telling you it does!
No, no way it does, it should stop at the edge of your palm!
Really?
Really!!!
No way.
It's connected.
What's with this sudden talk?
I don't get it. I don't get it either.
Kawago, do you have any last words?
I do really have something I want to say.
If Maimai wasn't the current Holy Mother...
Then she would definitely be one of the candidates here.
If so, she wouldn't talk badly about any of her fellow candidates.
"I think it's Iku-chan."
Reasons for being unfit | All Three If it were Fukagawa, she wouldn't badmouth anyone!
"I think it's Manatsu." First of all, it wouldn't turn into that kind of conversation.
She would probably say something like "But I think everyone here is kind..."
She would definitely say that.
Your love for Fukagawa is too strong!
It is.
She would never kick down anyone.
I do get that.
I get it. I do get that, but her love for Fukagawa is really too strong.
She's fanatic.
I see.
You're scary, Kawago!
Wouldn't it be better to change it?
If you say Holy Mother, the truth is... Probably not one member is satisfied with calling any of them that.
Why these 3?
Please wait, Matsumura-san.
We've gone through this whole process, and now you're saying we should change the Holy Mother audition?
Yes, let's change it.
So what should it be instead?
Greed.
Greed Queen?
Greed Queen Competition?
Greed Queen...
Becoming a Greed Queen... You guys had absolutely no desire to become that, right?
We're here for the Holy Mother audition!
Why would these three come for the Greed Queen audition?
I'm sorry, but since we've come this far, I don't think we can decide the Greed Queen just like that.
Greed Queen.
For the Greed Queen, we should just hold a different audition some other time with the title of Greed Queen on the line.
Sorry about that.
And the examination ends here.
Who will be chosen as the second Holy Mother?
Nogizaka46 second Holy Mother audition.
The successful candidate is...
There is no one qualified!
No one is qualified? What do you mean by that?
Well, this is the answer.
This is the answer.
Why?
It's because your un-Holy mother-like qualities stand out too much.
Well, if I had to put it plainly, for Akimoto, for example, this came up: A lying... bitch.
Lying Holy Mother.
That's right. There was that shocking... that shocking insult was hurled at her.
If someone says this about you, you just can't be a Holy Mother.
And for Hori, when she asked what the color of a Holy Mother was...
When people said colors other than white, it was the way you said "That's wrong."
That was... Well, it was cold... and it felt rather condescending...
Scary, right?
It was scary!
That's right. Well, Fukagawa, we have this result today.
Yes.
Well, I feel sorry since they went through the trouble of running for the position.
But since this is a nickname Hina gave me...
I want to keep treasuring it as I live on.
Ah, I see. So you'll keep treasuring it then.
This is it.
So, is it not possible for Kawago to inherit this nickname?
Ah, well, I think that a Holy Mother is a Holy Mother for life, so I'm just a human being.
Devil?
I'm fine with devil.
Devil Kawago then?
Devil Masami-san?
A letter to Fukagawa.
Maimai, do you remember?
Yes. Well, this time, this was a secret from Fukagawa.
All of the members wrote letters addressed to Fukagawa.
Yes.
And, well, we can't have everyone read each of their letters here...
So, as the captain, Sakurai will be their representative.
Yes.
Alright.
So we'll have Sakurai read the letter she wrote.
Maimai! Congratulations on your graduation!
Thanks!
Ever since you announced your graduation,
I've been secretly wondering how you're feeling from time to time.
You have a fluffy image and you give off a strong naive impression...
but you actually have a very strong sense of responsibility and you think about a lot of things.
So I feel like you're a girl who carries various burdens.
You're going to be alone from now on, and I think you'll then have even more burdens to carry...
but to us members, Maimai is always going to be a very important person we'd like to protect...
so when something happens, we'll definitely come and protect you. We'll come and help you.
That's why you should step into this new beginning without any worries.
Maimai, everyday, my pace~
Super congratulatiooooons!
Thanks!
Here are all of the members' letters.
Everyone, really, even though you're so busy, thank you so much for this.
They're all here.
This time, we have one more letter.
Mom?
It's from your mother.
Oh, her mother!
We received a letter from her and I will be reading it for her.
Mai, congratulations on your graduation.
It has been 4 years and 10 months since you passed the audition for Nogizaka 46.
Now that I look back on it, it feels long, yet it also feels short.
Even though I live in Shizuoka, I always looked forward to seeing your smile on TV, in magazines, and on the internet.
So those days were also very fulfilling for me.
In that time, there were happy times, fun times, and there were times you called me on the phone while crying...
Whenever you were down, I got worried and wanted so much to just rush to your side...
but instead I told you on the other side of the phone line how I wished that tomorrow you could do your best again with a smile, that you could believe in yourself and keep working.
I see all the members of Nogizaka as if they were my children and they are very dear to me.
I believe it's also because you always had the best, most wonderful friends by your side that you were able to overcome a lot of hardships.
It would be great if you could still keep in touch from time to time even10 or 20 years from now and keep on being friends, wouldn't it?
I'm looking forward to the path I'll be walking with you from here on as well.
Let's go on a trip together again, okay? Love, Mom.
So there were times you cried while talking to her on the phone?
Yes.
Well, I believe all of the members have it tough when it comes to worries about work...
So, it's like, there are things I can't bother other members with...
So, I... When I reach my limit, I would often call my mother then and ask her to listen to me.
It seems your mother also wanted to rush to your side, but she endured it and talked to you on the phone instead.
Finally, we have some words of gratitude from Fukagawa for the other members and for the fans.
Um, first, to all the members...
Well, it's not that we won't see each other anymore after this recording...
But when I graduate... well...
Then those fun times we spend while we're in the waiting room...
Like... Even outside work...
Those times we spent outside work were really a lot of fun for me...
So when I think about how I won't be able to experience those fun and lively times anymore when I become alone...
I feel really sad... But... Well...
It's not like we'll never see each other again, so... I hope I could keep on being friends with everyone for a very long time from here on as well.
And... For the all the fans watching the show who have supported me... Um... Starting from "Where is Nogizaka?"
At the beginning, I felt like I wasn't very good with variety shows, but with our very warm staff...
and Bananaman-san, and with all of the members...
I was able to be at ease in our recordings for around 4 and a half years, and I always looked forward to our recording sessions.
From here on, I would like to support this show as a viewer...
So, everyone, please keep on supporting Nogizaka46 from here on as well. Thank you very much.
Congratulations!
And that's that...
So for the last time, let's have Fukagawa end the show for us.
Everyone, thank you very much!
And please watch Nogizaka Under Construction next week as well!
Until next time!
Thank you very much!
Thank you! Goodbye!