Timing, Typeset by Yuuki
TL by S_Tetsuya
QC by TechiNeru46
Nogizaka Koujichuu
DON!!
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway!
We are your hosts, Bananaman!
Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu!~
And over there are...Nogizaka-chan!~
There are a lot of them today!
Himura-san, please announce what we're doing today
Nogizaka no.1 Cool Girl, Ayane-chan
Let's make her smile!
Suzuki...
She already sit over there..
Cool Girl!
What do you think, Suzuki?
You don't have to bother.
Up until now,  during Koujichuu..
Suzuki Ayane who never take off her cool face mask
What should be done to make her smile?
Tonight, we will try to do it.
Of course, among members...
ever seen her smile?
Of course!
-She did?!
- Thank goodness
She ever laugh?
She did!
Is that so?
Miria-chan, both of you are close, right?
Yes, we often eat together.
- Eat together?
Ever see her laugh?
She did!
She usually more talkative.
Really? She usually talk a lot?!
In front of members, she's not like this
She talk a lot?
Her voice also pretty loud.
Seriously?!
So, she talk a lot?
She talk a lot more than me.
Then, why she become like this?
At Handshake event, she's also pretty talkative.
She's not shy either.
For example, at live concert?
She also talk,but just at big concert...
- Then, just in front of us...
You talk a lot? At dressing room?
Yes, I did.
[Mysterious delay]
Ano.. just now it was like a broadcast..
You talk a lot?
Yes.
Really?
You like to talk?
I do...
Why are you stopping?
[Mysterious Freeze]
This Suzuki...
We'd like to see her laugh out loud.
We really do!
She usually so quiet.
With that then...
..members will do something that might make Ayane-chan laugh.
Ayane-chan will be giving score using these boards.
Um, excuse me.. Suzuki-san, would you please?
"Amusing...", this one "Very amusing".
"Normal" and "Tensagu"
[TL note: Tensagu : abbreviation of Tension Sagacchau (making one's tension down]
yoroshiku onegaiitashimasu!
What about that just now?
Try to rate that one!
Normal~
Thank you so much!~
Well, indeed there's nothing interesting happening right now.
- There's nothing happening, right?
Thank goodness! Tensagu didn't show up.
Our top batter,
Nogizaka's most lovable member,
Akimoto Manatsu!
Can she make Ayane-chan show her smile?
Well then, Akimoto...
Go ahead!
Being an idol, you have to smile, right?
That's why...
I'll do "Smile even at a hard time"
I'll begin!
3..2..1!
.....
#(:°o° )#
Rating time.
It's rating already?
There's still more?
Nothing.
How is the rating, Ayane-chan?
A little bit amusing!
That was a little bit amusing!
Her face is a little bit amusing, right?
There's something funny in between her cuteness.
I see!
Thank you so much!
- That was pretty good!
- It was pretty interesting!
After I'm done, I see Ayane-chan face..
..at that moment, I can feel cold sweat from my body.
- You can't see her face directly, right?
I can't stop shaking.
Oh well.
Entry No.2
The one who always smiling, Takayama Kazumi.
Will she succeed in making Ayane-chan smile?
Here, I will do something..
..named "Jinchu Illusion".
Pardon, but what was that?
[TL Note: She's doing illusion with her "philtrum"(a little groove between nose and lips)]
"Jinchu Illusion"
Jinchu Illusion?
Then, I'm going.
Starting from boomerang.
Ooo~
It's gone!
It appears!
- She's laughing!
- Ah, she's laughing! That's all!
[Nice touch]
Philtrum Illusion
Your philtrum disappear and then coming back.
What was that?
In the past, I did it at some show.
Maaya is laughing when she saw me at the monitor.
That's why I try to do this to Ayane-chan.
That's true!
In the back, Wada is laughing!
I really like this one.
Philtrum Illusion?
Philtrum Illusion.
So, this is rarely shown?
It's rare.
It's true I'm not doing this quite often
- Ah, Is that so?
How is Philtrum illussion rating?
Go ahead!
Eh~!
[Normal]
Eh? Wait a minute!
- Wait a minute!
Even though you're laughing?!
This is still "Normal"?
This one is amusing because it's done by Takayama-san
but, the joke itself is not amusing at all.
[The joke is ordinary]
So strict!
The rating is so strict!
Because it's done by Takayama that this is amusing?
I see. I see.
Because she's laughing, we thought the rating will be good.
So you did take some notice at the joke, right?
Yes.
- I see. I see.
But she said this is quite amusing.
- That's right
- Thank goodness!
Thank you so much!
It feels like some kind of joke competition, right?
That nervousness is there.
The atmosphere is a bit scary, right?
For Ayane-chan smile
Members show off jokes to burst of laughing!?
This show is presented by these sponsors~
Let's continue, next...
WAKATSUKI!!!
Here it comes!
There she is!
- Wakatsuki.
Entry No.3
Humor class graduate..
Nogizaka's No.1 comedian..
Wakatsuki Yumi
I'll stretch my height!
What is this?
What's wrong with her?
What? What?
[It gets in]
Eh?
She's really laughing!
That's all!
What is this?
She's laughing out loud!
Asuka-chan also laughing hard.
[Asuka also IN]
What is this?
I really like this.
Ayane and I really like this joke.
[Favorite joke]
Is that so?
If it's like that, the rating should be good, right?
And then, will "Very amusing" appear?
"Amusing"!
- "Amusing" appears.
I thought "Very amusing" will appear here.
I also thought so.
Asuka-chan, do you think it is "Very amusing"?
Very amusing!
[Laughing when recalling]
Just recalling that makes her laughing.
You're still laughing?
This one is"Amusing"?
Because I've seen this joke before...
[Lack of freshness]
It's not fresh, huh?
Then, the first time you saw it, its"Very amusing"?
Yes, very amusing.
- Ah..! - I see.
Because this is the second time..
This is very strict indeed.
Hashi-kun, everyone has seen it.
That's true, but...
There's something new.
[There's something new?]
A new Hashi-kun joke?
What will you do? Continue?
But I'll wait until the atmosphere is better..
I see, then later..
[Hashi-kun is preserved]
Onegaishimasu
On the other hand, this girl is amazing..
You're amazing, Wakatsuki.
Then, let's go on..
Hori!
Here she comes.
Up next...
Nogizaka's weirdest girl..
From the same 2nd Gen who has been together for a long time
Hori Miona
Um..
I'm coming from Gifu.
Ayane is from Akita.
Among 2nd Gen members,
only both of us coming from the countryside.
In the early days, we stayed at the hotel together.
Because we are always together..
I've got a lot of footage..
Before practicing Nogizaka songs..
At the lesson class..
before the choreographer come and taught us the dance move..
..that was the dance lesson.
Both of us had some practice at hotel.
So, you're not doing this right now?
You have the VTR?
Yes!
If you show her this, she'll laugh?
Yes.
Ah.. I see.
Joke with a video.
That's right.
I see.
Then, please watch it!
We thought we're dancing correctly!
It's a perfect dancing.
How is it?
Well, the fans will be glad seeing that.
VTR that bring back memories.
How is the rating, Ayane-chan?
"Tensagu"
Eh? Tensagu appears.
Eh? Why is it?
This one making your tension down?
I didn't want to see this.
[Backfiring]
Eeehh..?!
I see.
As I thought, it's embarassing?
It's embarassing indeed.
Ah, is that so?
3 years ago, I'm like a different person.
Really? It feels like nothing really...
[Changes that far is...]
I'm sorry but..
it's not really...
For us, there's not much difference.
But, what about at another place...
Hori , shock?
I'm really sorry...
I thought this isn't something that can be shown just like that..
Um.. this kind of thing isn't such a big of a deal.
[On the way of crying...]
Well then..
Let's continue.
Up next..
Noujou and Wada
Finally!
[Strongest Combination]
Both of them is amazing.
Noujou and Wada combo?
Next challenger...
Nogizaka's own comedian
Noujou and Wada
Can they make the cool girl Suzuki Ayane show us her smile?
I'll go first.
Eh? Even though you're conbi?
- This is a series.
- Same series.
- I see.
- Series? this is going to be interesting~
Ready... start!
Um... Maichun!
Maichun...
..she's lacking desire, right?
When we're in Guam...
What is this?
For photoshoot...
we're going to sea, right?
and then...
Wait a minute.
What the hell is this?
Is this already started?
So you're explaining the situation first?
Ah sorry sorry.
Because it makes the atmostphere a bit weird.
Starting from the beginning.
I'm sorry.
Once more
Start
In Guam, we have photoshoot session, right?
..then we're going to the sea, right?
At that time...
We're told to splash the water around, right?
Cameraman-san told us to do that, right?
Everyone doing it, right? Using our hands.
We're doing it normally, right?
then...
Maichun...
because she's lacking desire...
she didn't use her hands..
..instead she used her feet.
Her leg is quite long, right. so...
even though she realize this.
when everyone else using their hands..
Maichun is the only one who...
like this..
It's over?
up next... Wada
Maichun ,when we're doing rehearsal, through the mirror..
the moment she realize her body posture is bad..
Thank you so much.
Maichun.. Maichun..
I see..
Jokes about Shinuchi twice in a row.
Maichun series.
Usually is it bad?
Usually indeed it's bad.
That's so bad!
Is it really that bad?
It's really like that.
How is the Shinuchi jokes rating?
There it is!
"Amusing"!
"Amusing" appears!
That was pretty good.
This is amusing?
Seeing that, it was pretty amusing.
You know about this?
I don't know.
What about that water splashing?
About that water splashing, I wasn't there
but the one about "fixing body posture" I know about that.
Is that so?
But its not quite "Very amusing".
That's right
Because it feels a little bad (towards Maichun)..
about Maichun?
What a kind girl!~
Don't say bad things to others~
[Mocking others banned]
It's not like that.
It's not our intention.
From the challengers so far...
"Very amusing" has yet to make it appearance.
Now it's time to set up some strategies.
That's why,for a while, I'm sorry...
Now, Ayane-chan will use eye-mask and headphone
and it's time to set up some strategies.
We'd like to make her laugh louder.
If it's needed...
we can help you set up the atmosphere.
[Making funny atmosphere]
Making the atmosphere here..
Everyone play along.
-That's right
If everyone participates, it should be fine.
Actually, what is it that she really likes?
Something surreal?
Seeing someone who isn't that good at dancing..
that was her favorite.
She really likes to see a bad side of another people
Whose dance that she ever laughing at?
Ever laughed at?
Even though, I dance like usual.
But when she's looking from behind, she laugh at it instead.
Is that so?
- Is your dance weird?
I ask her "why are you laughing?'
then she said the way Yuuri-san dance is amusing.
[Reason to laugh: Zero]
She said it like that?
There's that sure thing joke, right Kawago-san?
There's is thing like that?
I have 3 of them
[3 Candidates]
but the "Masai tribe" joke isn't even that funny anymore
So you didn't do it anymore?
The chance is she won't laugh.
Why did you want to be "Masai Tribe"?
There's this ippatsu-gei that might make Ayane-chan laugh
Ippatsu-gei?
[TL Note: Ippatsu-gei = One-shot gag]
You never shown it before?
I've never shown it before.
It's a bit scary, right?
- That's right.
And the other one?
The last one...
is a game that I'd like Ayane-chan to participate in..
it's like "Say it 10 times" game.
We can also use Saito Yuuri dance.
You think, who should go first?
Starting from me, then Yuuri...
I see.
Up first, is "someone who has the most unique character" Kawago
Can she make Ayane-chan show us her smile?
I'm going to do something that I assume it's amusing
I'll do my best to do it. Please watch it.
It sounds good, you know?
I'll do something that I think it's amusing~
This should be good~
Then, let's get started!
Here it comes!~
Cream Pan!
After that...
There's a game that I'd like you to participate in..
Participate?
Whatever I said,
please answer with "Shizuoka"
-"--- --- ---"
-"Shizuoka"
Understand?
I'll begin~
- Tokyo
- Shizuoka
- Osaka
- Kochi
- Shizuoka
- Shiozuka
Amazing!
[Failure]
It's over!
Get back to your seat!
How is Ayane-chan rating?
"Amusing"
Unexpectedly it's that?
- Eh? That was amusing?
For Kawago level, this is quite amusing.
Because it's Kawago who did it, it's good enough?
How is the game supposed to be?
Supposedly, she can't answer that back.
I've tried this to 10 members
All of them can't do it.
This is the first time, someone can actually do it.
Really surprising.
With that speed just now, she should be failed to answer that?
It should be impossible.
But she answer that with ease, you know.
[Unexpectedly, succeed]
No one can do it, huh~
Next, Is there no one else?
Who's next?
- Is there anyone else?
Hai!
OH! Saito Yuuri?!
Go ahead!
I'll do it.
Last entry, Saito Yuuri!
..with her bad dancing, aiming for 'Very amusing".
Ready..
[Arakajime katareru romansu~]
Wait a minute! Really?
She's laughing, you know.
Embarassing! wait a minute...
How is Saito Yuuri dance rating will be?
There it is!!!
"Very amusing"
Wait a minute! Because..
She's just dancing normally though?
- Why is that?
I really like her legs.
You like her legs?
The way her legs move is amusing?
- Yes
Hee..?!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?!
That's because, everyone also dance like that, right?
That's right
Eh? It's different?
With that, let's compare it to Asuka's dancing...
1..2
[Arakajime katareru romansu~]
Her movement a bit rough, right?
Like that?
The moment the song started, her face instanty changed.
So that part that "Very amusing"?
Very amusing!
She's smiling!
- I'm so happy. Thank you so much.
We did it!
"Very amusing" appears.
There it is!
- Thank goodness it appears.
Ah.. by the way Wakatsuki!
You said you will do something..
[Hashi-Kun new show]
Ah, that's right.
Almost forgot that..
Are you going to do it or not?
Well "Very amusing" has appeared.
What if suddenly it's "Tensagu"...
but we also would like to see something new..
It's new, right?
It's new. This one use two chopsticks.
[New creation 2 chopsticks !?]
Eh!? You're using two of them?
It's different with the one before?
The first one, using its sleeves..
That's what I told to do..
Now, it's Hashi ga (Hashi)tta
[TL Note: Hashi(Chopsticks) is running!]
Ah! I broke it...
Give your rating, please!
"Very amusing"
- Eh?
Even though she make a mistake there..
After this "Coupling song [Buranko],  first studio performance"
[Buranko]
kimi no koto wo gokai shitetanda
boku wo shiranai tte omottetanda
juubun kyori wo oita tsumori ga
zutto boku wa mirarete ita no ka...
hitotsu aita hajikko no BURANKO
kaze no you ni guuzen suwatte
kogi hajimete shibaraku shite kara
"itsumo koko ni iru no ne" to itta
yurari yurari yureteta kara
kimi no koe ga yuuyake ni
suikomarete shimaisou da
ima boku no
yukkuri BURANKO koginagara
oitsukou to shita yo
ato sukoshi
mou kore kara wa
kotoba nanka nani mo iranai
mae e ushiro e
bokura wa tada sora wo oyoida
mou kore kara wa
kotoba nanka nani mo iranai
mae e ushiro e
bokura wa tada sora wo oyoida
ima yume no naka
jikan no kawa ga shizuka ni nagarete
tatta hitotsu no
BURANKO dake ga koko de yureteru
[I want to tell Bananaman - Nogizaka46 (My one Song)]
I want to tell Bananaman - Nogizaka46 (My one Song)
Members are introduced recommend
songs to two people (bananaman)!
Which song will the be the most echoing to Bananaman?