The several units that exist within Nogizaka46
have presented their activities and unit benefits
this is the 2nd half of the episode where they try
to recruit new members
Back in the 1st half
Hey everybody, since today could really be our last job
Get fired up and do your best!
Here we go
ganbari~
The strongest unit in terms of business
Sayuringo
We'll have birthday parties...
this is just a party group
And then the party unit Inumen
At the cafe it was myself, Yuuri, and Nyaa
But Nishino hasn't left the cafe
And the unit that loves freedom.  Watermelon made their appearance
In the end
which unit will be able to capture the hearts of the Independents and Himura?
Going 1st in the 2nd half
Tulip
Hello everyone
We are Tulip
[ Nice womanly feel ]
The Tulip members are us 6
originally we formed as people who loved Disney.  Myself
Takayama
Chiharu, Kawamura, Kawago. Us 5
we created TeamD
TeamD
The D is from Disney?
That's correct, we formed back then
and since then Maaya
joined us
So we powered up and became Tulip
Why the name change to Tulip?  Where does that come from?
Maaya is Tulip...
Maaya is Tulip?
Any paper you give her, she'll draw tulips
[ Wada's survey ]
She draws tulips on everything
Doesn't that just make her a plain fool!
[ Flower fields in her head? ]
You call yourself Tulip because idiot Maaya draws them?
Maaya is the only one that draws the tulips
Maaya draws them
You draw them?
Even at karaoke, I always sing tulip
The band Tulip?
You're not talking about Zaitsu Kazuo-san right?
hon no chiisana~
That song right?
And here are some of Tulip's activities
We go to theme parks
Now I see
and sleepovers
That's awesome
We'll meetup and play the Werewolf board game through the night
that's back from when it got really popular
About 3 years ago?
Its been 4 years
You've been around for 4 years
Out of all the groups we're the most senior
Is that so?
[ The oldest unit within Nogizaka46 ]
Close to 5 years
As soon as Nogizaka was formed then?
Not that early, maybe after a year had passed, we got along
Is that true?
You became Tulip recently?
No, that was still 4 years ago
So you've spent 4 years as Tulip
You've really bloomed without most people knowing!
[ Not getting noticed ]
But we are oldest.  That is amazing
So you've always gone to theme parks and played werewolf?
That sounds like so much fun
In the beginning we'd sleepover at each others houses fairly often
it was at my house
and also then at Takayama's house
And also we offer more freedom than Watermelon
its never all of us that get together
[ So much freedom, not everyone shows up ]
About 2 years ago
Naa-chan came over and then one time Iku-chan
[ Already has unit experience ]
You've been around so long, people have stopped by
It was about 4 years ago
We happened to be staying
at the same hotel for work, we played Werewolf
and ate ice cream on the beds, I have strong memories of that
That's good
As a group of friends
you guys seem like the oldest unit
So its like you personally choose
to remain an Independent
This is bringing back memories
[ There's a chance? ]
And then we have a motto
here it is
Just enjoy yourself
Those are great words
We started as a unit to enjoy Disneyland
and so this is what we emphasize the most
And here when we take a look at the group chats of Tulip
We'll send a lot of weird and digitally altered pictures to each other
lots of playing around
Wait, so who is who?
What is this?
Hina-chan is really into those altered photos
I make funny pics on a regular basis
What is "an"
Ah, that's me
No way
That's creeping me out
The eyes are pure black
During that time Takayama
there's pictures of her when she was little
It got on the group chat
Since it showed up in a group chat
other pictures of other members when they were small
got sent out.  It became like a childhood
photo competition or something
Here's what it looked like
Who's who?
Ah, Takayama.  Let me think which one is her
Its kind of hard
This is hard
I think mine is pretty easy
She's got to be the girl in red
Correct answer
That's Takayama
After that
Do you know which one is me?
Maybe the one on the bottom right taking a bath?
That's not it
The picture above that one then
That's not me
Its her then
I'm on the bottom left
the one with the bumpy face
Completely different
I look like a boy
Then who are the last two?
Top right is Chii
Seriously?
That's Rotty?
I'm on the bottom right
I never would have guessed
Well that's how we have fun
And then also
Someone throw up one of Himura-san's photos in with those
A picture of an old guy would never make it up there
[ Old guy in his early childhood ]
And the benefits for joining Tulip are
Here they are
You get to eat some of Ami's full course meals
What is Ami's full course about?
Out of us I'm pretty much the one
that's the good cook
What's on Ami's full course?
My ginger pork dish
Who's got that ginger pork?
[ immediate response ]
There must be other things on the full course
I'll make an omelette rice, and also breakfast
[ After everyone stays overnight Noujo cooks her special breakfast ]
You cook for them as a parting gift?
That sounds really good
And then Takayama's mother makes iced coffee
chocolate cake too
[ iced coffee chocolate cake? ]
First time I've heard of iced coffee cake.  Is this popular?
Famous?
Its really good
Iced coffee chocolate cakes are famous then?
Its just as delicious as something a pro would make
She has a license to make iced coffee
So the iced coffee is one of the desserts she makes?
[ They keep the iced coffee chocolate in stock so you'll definitely get some if you go ]
And we always have plenty in stock so everyone gets to have some
oishii
Everybody gets to eat iced coffee chocolate cake
[ The best feature of Tulip? ]
That's the best
And then we have some requirements for joining
here they are
we have to take baths together
Himura-san can't do that one
[ Blocked by the gender wall ]
And that's a hard requirement?
There's no way
But its very important to us right?
Why so important?
Meeting together naked...
That's fine for a group of women
but we're discussing whether Himura-san can join up
That's right
But as long as he doesn't look at us with pervy eyes...
I would never do that!
I'd never do that!
You absolutely would
I would definitely not!
Yes you would!
You have to trust me!
For that, you can trust me!
Trust me
Now it sounds like a weird religious cult
[ It all depends on what's in your heart ]
But you really can trust me
Well, none of us think of you as a man so...
[ That's got to be a shock ]
Yes, that one was shocking to hear
but that's fine.  No weird looks
That really goes both ways
There's no way!  Himura-san is lying if he's telling you he won't have any feelings in there with you
I'm not lying
And why?  Why is that?
Because I'll be a Tulip
Tulip is like the title of an ero mag right?
If we're all Tulip, we can take baths together right?
Even if you're Tulip, to imagine you getting in a bath with them
That's a major problem!
Well I got it, but I don't think its that big a deal
Totally fine right
And with that, we the members of Tulip
are waiting for new members to sign up
That was amazing
Tulip is certainly interesting
Let's ask the Independents what they think
Ikuta, you've already had some experience with Tulip right?
I have some experience and recently
with Ami, Chii-chan, and was it Hime-tan?
we all went out for dinner
It felt like we were really close
So you've got thoughts of joining?
Well yes, a little bit
But still
you'll have to take baths with them
and if Ikuta joins, there's a chance Himura-san will also join
Himura could be a new member
all this could actually happen
Well, if he doesn't look at us with pervy eyes....
[ Easily accepted in ]
This old man will be in your bath.  That's not right!
You'll have to trust me
Regarding that, you can trust me
You'll have an immediate reaction
I won't react to anything
If there's trust its all fine
How about Shiraishi?
That group sounds like it would be really fun
and that iced coffee cake
I'm really curious about that cake
[ The enchanting gateaux chocolate ]
But still, the possiblity exists
that you'll join and have to take a bath with them
Just Shiraishi and the members is fine but
if Himura-san were to join the group
Of course you wouldn't go along with that
Well...
as long as he doesn't look with pervy eyes...
Yes, that's fine
you'll have to trust me there
I would never look with pervy eyes
You definitely would!
As long as everyone trusts me, its all perfectly fine
That can't be
Himura-san in a bathtub with top idols
[ Disturbing imagery ]
He'd say like "Pass the shampoo"
this cannot happen
There won't be anything like that
just pass the shampoo like normal
To say as long as he doesn't look at us with pervy eyes
that's too funny
And the final presentation
the Manatsu-san Respect Unit
We are the Manatsu-san Respect Unit
[ sloppy ]
She messed up
Could you do that again?
We are Manatsu-san Respect Unit
There it is
Looks a bit like Nogizaka's intro
Usually this fingernail would be painted red
It would normally?
Usually as a unit we get a manicure on this finger
So this
symbolizes being permanently connected to the fans
So if Himura-san joined your group
Himura-san would have to keep his pinky manicured?
Yes, any show that he appears on, it would have to stay red
No problem for me
Himura, did you hear her?
Any show you appear on your finger will be painted red.  That would be strange
If you showed up on another show with your pinky like that people would start talking
Why is that?  It's proof that I'm Manatsu-san Respect
[ Shouldn't that be obvious? ]
The story behind the creation of the unit
when Nogizaka was on 46 Hour TV
I came on after Sayuringo
[ Formed as resistance to Sayuringo ]
I thought "What could I do to compete with their unit"
so I got the girls that I liked together
So this isn't a gathering of people who respect you?
But Sagara must respect her right?
You share clothes or something right?
half and half
[ confusion ]
But you do respect her?
I do
These two definitely don't
You do right?
hmm
[ You can see the darkness ]
And the type of activities Manatsu-san Respect are involved with are
There it is, they put out songs also
Single releases and magazine articles
Our own show on Nico Live
You have your own show?
[ Randomly record shows for streaming on Nico Live ]
Its not on a set schedule but Manatsu-san Respect does "I want to see this" themed shows
there's been like 4 or 5 of them
All 4 of you appear?
So it gets them work.  How about the songs?
[ Nidome no Kiss Kara released as the coupling song on the 16th single ]
That's amazing
And our song [ Nidome no Kiss Kara ]
we have a very important role for Himura-san on that song if he joins
Nidome no Kiss Kara?
[ Nidome no Kiss Kara ] has a shout out
There's a part from the guy's point of view in the song
And we've never had anyone to fill in for that part
And I was just thinking who and from where could we do this
but now we've found Himura-san
You already have a job
Let me show you how the timing of it works
Himura-san, if you could remember this
Give it a try
Could you sing the chorus for us?
[ Can't hide that emotional divide ]
nidome no kiss kara me wo samase~
nomikomareruna!~
uttori to kuchibiru~
kasanete shimau saimin~
ichidome wa ore to~
That part
You don't have anyone to say that?
That "with me" part
The song is about everything starting from the 2nd kiss, so the line is make your 1st kiss with me
That's the background
And we don't have anyone to do that
Would you like to try it?
You got it?  Its memorized
[ Quick learner ]
Himura-san is quick like that
"ichidome wa ore to"  Got it
nidome no kiss kara me wo samase~
nomikomareruna!~
uttori to kuchibiru~
kasanete shimau saimin~
ichidome wa ore to!
[ Perfect shout out ]
That's perfect
Is that so?
Is that a good one?
That's perfect
I really don't get the feeling you're all in the same group
[ Idols and a middle aged fan ]
We're the same group. Or could be from now on
If you join it seems you would get these benefits
No problems getting work
No problems?
I mentioned before that we do a show on Nico Live
and doing a show like that on Nico Live
The members send out a message
like "I want to do something like this"
and when I was putting out my photo book
I told the group I wanted to do a release day celebration show
and we filmed that show
everything I could ask for came true
There must be some respect here
Yes, really they came together to help me do that show
Are you sure the "no problems getting work" doesn't just apply to you?
The other members too?
The others also right?
Yes, its true
hai hai
[ Rejecting the unit leader ]
Are they going to be ok?
Those Nico Live shows, myself and Kana-chan have been doing a show for 4 years
And the Nico Live staff that does our show does theirs
Sayuringo did a show
and thats allowed Manatsu-san to do a show
Its like they're enjoying our success
Its not really the draw of Manatsu-san's unit
the shows are from Sayuringo's selling power
These are some really hard feelings
[ Internal blood feud ]
If you entered either Sayuringo or Manatsu-san Respect
you'd have to take on this fight
[ Unavoidable conflict ]
That's right.
So then there are requirements for entering our unit
Here it is
Tell me what it is
You will respect Manatsu-san
and show off your shoulders
That's a harsh one
Making him show his shoulders is going to be hard on Himura-san
So my understanding of what she said
On other shows, your entire shoulder will be exposed
Can he just wear a tank top?
I'd rather just his shoulders be exposed
Just this area?
That's correct
Not sure I can.  That [Unbelievable] show I do will be a problem for me
[ Other than that show its all clear... ]
How about just for Nogichuu...
Seeing Himura-san's bare shoulder on this show all the time would be weird
No way!  Give up trying to join this group
All these conditions for Himura-san haven't been good
[ His partner is worried ]
I wasn't expecting it to be this bad for you
And finally we have the future plans for Manatsu-san Respect
We're going to have a surprise live show on the streets
You sure?  You'd get in trouble
The 4 of us as a unit haven't done any events anywhere
since I want us to do a show
and Sayuringo is trying to play Budokan
that's what she said
and since we get the hand me downs
and don't want to blatantly copy them
Like on the streets of Oomiya, we could stand on mikan boxes
and sing one song and leave
I'd like to keep it low key
The people of Oomiya will get pissed
why are these girls mocking our town?
[ Standing on mikan boxes is enough? ]
Oh, that's your hometown?  That's why
Let's ask the Independents
Nakada
That last part with the live show out on the streets
you're not going to make any money doing that
[ Lacking business acumen ]
How about Higuchi?
I feel like there's a lot of friction between those 2 units
You noticed all the fighting right?
I don't feel like its something I should join in
If you enter Sayuringo you'll be fighting with Manatsu's unit
and if you join Manatsu's unit, you'd have to fight Sayuringo
I don't want any part of that
Shiraishi what did you think of Manatsu-san Respect?
Out of all the units
its not complete awkwardness but
I didn't see much unity within the group
[ The unit covered in darkness ]
In regards to that
if I were to join them
that doesn't seem like much fun
And also if Shiraishi-san joined the unit
you'd then have to respect Manatsu-san
Respect?...that's going to take some time
[ Currently no respect ]
All of the unit presentations are complete
In the end
is there a unit that either the Independents or Himura will want to join?
Let's start with Higuchi then
onegaishimasu
I'll stay an Independent
independent
[ Unable to recruit a new member ]
Why'd you make this choice?
Entering at this point in time seems frightening
Its frightening
[ Just the thought of joining is scary ]
And next its Nakada
what will she choose?
How about it Nakada?
I'm staying Independent
[ Unable to recruit a new member ]
Why?
After thinking about it
forming a team with the Independents and doing activities
I think would lead to more money
[ The sweet part of staying Independent ]
But you won't get any direct leads to new jobs
And that's 2 consecutive misses
Up next
Hoshino
How about it?
Staying Independent
Well we knew it
[ Unable to recruit a new member ]
I thought Hoshino would join a unit
I thought belonging to a group would be good for you
Right now I'm good being alone
[ Wants to be alone ]
That's how she's feeling
And that's 3 consecutive losses
And what will Shiraishi's response be?
So Shiraishi
what do you think?
Independent
[ Unable to recruit a new member ]
They're all staying Independent
Each unit has their charm right?
Obviously they all have their benefits
but joining now is too late
like if I joined Inumen
there's already other members there right
And then the members that join now
I feel like those members would get shut out
[ The exclusionist unit ]
Its true, there's a lot of things to like about Inumen but
they're already such a close group
but its so important to them whether or not you performed in that play
This looks bad Himura-san.  All the Independents
[ 4 consecutive losses ]
Only Ikuta remains
will it all end with zero new recruits?
Is there a unit you'd like to join?
Tulip
[ Ikuta is joining Tulip ]
From Independent
she's going to join Tulip
What?
Why make that choice?
Its like...they all make me laugh
that's why I think it'll be fun
[ Warm reception ]
They got a new member Himura-san
Tulip
Happy right?
So happy
[ What's wrong with you? ]
She's laughing so hard
What happened Ikuta?
No really.  They all make me laugh so hard
They all make you laugh?
You think they're stupid?
[ Completely looking down on all of them ]
Going last its Himura
Will he make a sudden decision to join?
And finally Himura-san
you've heard all the presentations
Is there a unit you'd like to join?
There is!
[ Heart set on a unit ]
You won't remain Independent
Ok
announce the name
of that unit
onegaishimasu
It's Tulip
[ Himura is joining Tulip ]
Please hold on a second
This is all messed up
He wants the bath!
He's definitely thinking about that bath!
He's looking straight ahead though.  Hold on now
This is a major problem
To join Tulip you have to take a bath with them
that was one of their conditions
He seems happy right now, so first of all Himura-san
hai
what was the deciding factor for you picking Tulip?
Because I want to go to Disneyland
[ Pure reason ]
And this has nothing to do with taking a bath with them
Nope, I just want to go to Disneyland
Let's all go!
But there is a condition that you must bathe with them to join
Ah, of course hai
Of course I'll do that, hai
Since I won't be looking at them with pervy eyes
And we won't look at you in that way
Hold on
These members had already consented to doing this
But Ikuta, how do you feel about bathing with Himura-san?
You ok with that?
As long as he doesn't look with pervy eyes
Please put your trust in me then
[ All conditions cleared ]
So now one day
Nogizaka members and Himura
there's going to be pictures of them in the tub
[ Don't miss it? ]
Until that day comes
yoroshiku onegaishimasu