DON!
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
we are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And over there are Nogizaka-chan
What's that about?
And we've started
Himura-san, please announce
what's on the show today
Here goes
Is it only my family that does this? Grand Prix
With the passing of mothers day, on todays show
"Actually these are words only used in my family"
they'll tell us about some strange rules that only apply to their family
By the way, Himura-san's family
Asking me if I have a story?
do you have something?
For us every Sunday
dad always makes curry and miso pork.
Its a rule that we eat that on Sundays
Somehow, Terada started laughing before you even started talking
[ Appears to have gotten a head start ]
You died laughing when he said "For our family"
Did you get a haircut?
Did you get a haircut then?
Yes, I got a haircut
Could you stop laughing at my haircut for a moment?
[ Himura's haircut is a gag? ]
Is there something weird about his haircut?
Its tiny...
Tiny?
This girl is totally insulting me
[ Can't stop laughing at the contour of his head ]
This is normal for me
Actually I'd say its in the best condition I've ever seen
This is what I've always wanted
To have people laugh at this is messed up, this is normal for me
So then when did it start?
When did Nogizaka members start copying Himura-san's hairstyle?
Nakada you've started copying his hair right?
[ Homage to Himura ]
What do you mean its fashionable?
Could everyone stop with the frequent disrespecting?
The first theme
only our family talks like this
our unique way of naming things
Only our family calls it this.  Here's one
Inoue
hai
The machine they use to plow the fields, the tractor
Tractor?  In the Inoue family those
were always called tattatta
[ Tractor = Tattatta in the Inoue house ]
Since it was called tattatta
and everyone around me called it that
I went through life
thinking it was called that
So you thought it was really called a tattatta
I thought it was a tattatta
So when a car goes honk honk, you think its called a honk-honk?
But nobody told me anything
and in middle school
All the way through middle school then
In middle school
one of my friends suddenly said the word tractor
[ 1st encounter with the word tractor ]
For my entire life
now it was like
what is tattatta
Just what is tattatta then?
[ Set free from tattatta ]
Did you tell them "Its called a tattatta"
When did you figure it out?
In middle school
middle school
I did a search for tattatta
[ Teach me internet search sensei ]
You looked it up then
The results I got back were videos I didn't understand
[ Rhythym related results ]
So I didn't know about tractor
so then what if the Inoue family
is hiding something else
But for a word like that
tractors are only mentioned in families with farm land
most people don't have tractors
so it wouldn't come up
Anything else
at your house
where you call something by a different name?
Eto
hai
What does the Eto family have?
Everyone probably loves this dish
its called hayashi rice
[ The Eto household calls Hayashi Rice ??? ]
Everyone loves that?
its like a national dish
Well I think that's curry, but Hayashi rice is close
Doesn't everyone know hayashi rice?
Some people don't
Well then this food that's called hayashi rice
in my family
[ hairai ]
is what we call it
[ The Eto household calls Hayashi Rice hairai ]
You shortened it?
hayashi rice is hairai
Shortened further from hayarai
I went through life calling it that
and I also
about when I was in elementary school
our school lunch menu had Hayashi rice written on it
I thought "What's that?"
then I ate it
This tastes just like my family's hairai
and when I got home I asked my mom
"Are hayashi rice and hairai the same thing?"
She was like "that's right"
She told you that's right
Its funny how she says it
That's right
That's right.  You finally noticed
Our hairai is hayashi rice
hayashi rice...hairaishi rice
But its not even called that in Oita
just at our house
What is hayashi rice?
hayashi rice
That's his Kinpachi-sensei
[ Limited to Year 3 Class B ]
hayashi rice
It really sounds like your mom lost her teeth
hairai
[ Can't say S-sounds ]
Would your mom call it hairai like that?
She'd clearly say hairai
hairai then
hairai
But I'm trying to say it like I have no teeth
its actually impossible to fake that
Not sure what that sounds like
hairai
Sounds like Takeshi-san right?
That's Takeshi-san doing Unbelievable
Coming up, its hairai
[ hairai the miracle experience ]
Terada's family has their own names for things
In Terada's family
they call things differently
and some of the names they use are so weird
so we'll take all those names
and turning it into a quiz for all of you
And with that, it may seem sudden but
Here is the Terada family item nickname quiz
The first object
So the first object
is chon-chorin and chon-chororin
[ What is a chon-chorin? ]
chon-chorin or chon-chororin, either one works
2 names for it then? chonchorin
chon-chorin and chon-chororin
What do you think it is?
Its the chain on a lamp
Ah like pull the chon-chororin to turn off the light
Ahhh...good one.  That sounds like a chon-chorin
Doorbell
That's incorrect
When the chon-chorin rings it means someone is there
Everything about chon-chorin is a pain
You either pull the chon-chorin or its something ringing
But this kind of sound
you probably call it this because of the sound
Around when I was in kindergarten
all the kindergarten kids would likely use this everyday
So its something used by little girls
Kindergarten age girls
hair band?
Ah, that's the right answer
But the image somehow fits
They were always really soft, so we called it that
chon-chorin
The next Terada family object nickname quiz
question #2
This one is still used right now
more by my sister than myself
she calls it chassu
[ chassu is what? ]
Its good morning
You guys like using the chi sound
Like get me a chassu
Could you grab a chassu for me?
chassu chassu
chassu, get me a chassu
Used like get me a chassu
So you get a chassu
Its something you get for people
Something at the dinner table
What does the 3rd class have?
How about Kubo?
What do you think?
chassu chassu
tissue?
tissue
tissue sounds so much better
[ No reason to change the name ]
I don't have a chasu, get me one
And you'd look so foolish
I need a chassu
chassu chassu chassu
Would it be called pocket chassu?
[ portable chassu ]
box chassu
It goes with everyone's meal
So its when you're eating a meal
rice seasoning
That's not it
soy sauce
soy sauce is chassu
I need some chassu on my sashimi
You always have it with your meal
What could it be?
pickled item right
That's chassu.  I'd like to eat some chassu right now
Give me chassu please
Has to resemble chassu
How about Ikuta?
rice bowl?
ah, that's not it
But she's got the right idea
Its something
along the lines of that
That's right
so keep going
tea?
Who just said tea?
That's it.  Its tea
Like get me some tea
Get me some chassu
But tea is much easier to say
[ Additional letters added on ]
How did tea become chassu?
I don't know
Its not mine, its really my dad and my sister
who go around saying chassu
From the living room one of them will say "Grab me a chassu"
What do you call barley tea then?
barley chassu?
[ Usable with all forms of tea? ]
chassu sounds like green tea to me
seems like green
You wouldn't say roasted green chassu?
Everyone drinks tea, I tend to like green tea
my dad likes barley tea, but it all gets lumped under chassu
So everything just becomes chassu
And black tea?
black tea
black chassu?
My brother drinks black tea, its still chassu
Doesn't this confuse your mom?
[ the vagueness of chassu ]
For dinner I always call it green tea
but for breakfast its still called black chassu
[ chassu can only be said at certain times ]
So you have a morning chassu and a night chassu
what if your morning chassu ends up becoming night chassu
[ rush on chassu ]
chassu
Mom, there's an extra chassu here
[ dumb and happy family ]
I've never seen it, but going back
what would happen if someone served jasmine tea?
jasmine tea is just chassu
so its treated like any other tea
Does it become jasu?
[ chassu can be changed to fit the application ]
But black tea is called chassu
what happens with milk or lemon tea then?
lemon tea and
lemon chassu
Well lemon tea
my family would never serve that
forbidden chassu
[ just wanted to say that ]
But there will be some chassu they'd never serve
Do you serve milk tea then?
milk tea is just black tea with milk
So add on milk and its chassu milk
[ Out of control Terada family rules ]
The Terada family slightly strange object name quiz
question #3
So there's one more
One more.  Ah, you mean poto-poto-pottosu
[ magic spell? ]
poto-poto-pottosu
[ poto-poto-pottosu is what? ]
So what is a poto-poto-pottosu
poto-poto-pottosu
Let's do this one without any hints
pot
Ahh, the first part right?
Kind of like chassu.  Following up on chassu
poto-poto-pottosu
Go ahead
When the water
comes out of a faucet like po-po-po
The faucet is all poto-poto-pottosu right now
Turn off the water!
You were the one making the chassu just now
now its all poto-poto-pottosu
And I don't have my chon-chororin
Now I'm curious what poto-poto-pottosu is
poton...
poto-poto-pottosu
But that's the right way of thinking right
you're on the right track
as far as sounds go, keep going
How about Yoda?
poto-poto-pottosu
poto-poto-pottosu, tell us what you think
poto-po
electricity
electric
electrcity
electricity?
The electricity is making everything poto-poto-pottosu
He's acting strange like poto-poto-pottosu
poto-pottosu
poto-poto-pottosu is making it move
ah its quietly poto-poto-pottosu
[ troublesome ]
electricity would make everything poto-poto-pottosu
Wakatsuki has something
coffee maker
That also poto-poto-pottosu
But this one should be easy
Out of all the ones we've done
this is easy
Well a hint then
It has "po" in it
the first part sounds the same
Is it food?
Yes, that's a big hint
potato chips
Yes, that's it!
Why is that longer than saying potato chips?
poto-poto-pottosu is longer
Who started poto-poto-pottosu?
My father
probably
Its your father
and he created chassu too
He likes talking like this
My dad continues to fool around giving these names to everything
He has a tendency to do that
when my sister was looking at this survey with me
my sister provided the chassu one to use
but the moment I said poto-poto-potosu
She said "people will think you're weird, stop saying that"
[ What's the difference with that and chassu? ]
These sound like your father came up with it
since the sounds are similar, chassu and poto-poto-potossu
Definitely feels like it came from the same person
poto-poto-pottosu then, what if its a different flavor?
Is it all poto-poto-pottosu?
All poto-poto-pottosu
Even if its consomme flavor or salted seaweed?
I see
What if its consomme double flavored?
Does it become kosu-kosu-kossosu
[ Already lost the original pattern ]
koso-koso-kossosu
If that is like koso-koso-kosossu
then sushi is usushi-oussusu
[ Hopes to build a collection ]
We have another family
Asuka-chan
Asuka's family has something
I don't really have anything
Well this has a different punch to it from the ones before but
Asuka's family told us about a mistake she made
They say its about a magnifying glass
I call a magnifying glass a telescope
[ Can't see stars with that ]
Well thats a common mistake
[ Calls a magnifying glass a telescope ]
Didn't anyone laugh at you?
That's a telescope to you
The magnifying glass
it becomes that?
In science class she'll be using a magnifying glass
"this is my telescope"
You saw it as a telescope
a telescope
telescopes are like this right
So then corn
toumorokoshi is called
toumorokoroshi
But that's something famous in Totoro
Mei-chan in Totoro
Didn't Mei-chan call it toumoukoroshi
But Asuka-chan isn't saying toumoukoroshi
toumorokoroshi
toumorokoroshi?
You definitely say the koroshi part?
[ toumoro killer ]
There's an extra ro in there. toumorokoroshi
Its supposed to be ko-shi, and she makes it toumorokoroshi
Don't need the extra ro
You force that in there
You've said that since you were little?  Oh, you say it too?
I called it that
toumokoroshi
When you're little its hard to say so it turned into toumokoroshi right
There's also spa...spa?
spaghetti?
spaghetti
Why were you asking how to say spaghetti?  You call it something else right
What do you call it?
spabekki
[ Iwamoto calls spaghetti spabekki ]
You just threw in different letters
[ Becky style pasta? ]
Why spabekki?
Why is this?
Why did you mistake it?
You called it spabekki
So that's
I thought that's what it really was
And then her family also has a unique way of calling things
Ikuta
hai
Ikuta hai
I call grandmother
aachama
I call grandfather iichama
iichama
Where did the aa and ii come from?
Its the aa from obaachan
ii from ojiichan
aa from obaachan
You took the aa from obaachan
And iichama?
The ii from ojiichan
The iichama
Is saying baachama and jiichama bad then?
My grandparents don't like being called those words
Like hey stop calling me babaa and jijii
[ Not fans of the words jiji and baba ]
Ah, that's how it turned into aachama and iichama
They were like just call me by a vowel
Ozono's family also
does something different
Myself
I call my mother cha-chan
cha-chan?
cha-han?
Its not that
Around preschool
another child my age
made fun of me by saying chahan
I remember crying with my brother
You mean like what I did just now?
[ Recreating painful memories ]
You'd say cha-chan
and someone in preschool made fun of you by saying chahan
and I just made that same joke
[ The chahan incident 2017 ]
But it really sounds like chahan
The next rule is
Playing grandpa at ping pong
for your new year's gift
Who does this belong to?
hai
ah Hori
What's this about?
Every year we all gather at grandpa's house
at grandpa's house
there's a ping pong table in the driveway
And grandpa is really good
At ping pong
So then everyone takes turns playing him
and the best players by rank get the best new years present
Not how many points you score, but according to your rank
The best player gets the biggest gift
That's how the money gets decided
How many points for 1st place?
The people that advance can get tens of thousands of yen
Is this like a tournament or something?
There's 8 players
Is that so?
But he's really good
Somehow he got really good
But when I lose
then I don't get so much
How much then?
Like 1000 yen
1000 yen for your new years gift
Because of that my sister
with this system, to get better at ping pong
she entered ping pong club in middle school
[ Seriously going after the prize money ]
She wanted bigger new years rewards
This was her sole reason for entering ping pong club?
Did she get good?
She got really good
after doing it for 3 years
now she always gets big rewards
[ semi-pro ping pong player ]
There was this one family where the father
had all the kids gather up
and he'd throw all his spare change in the air
and at that moment he turned off the lights
all the kids were scooping up the change
[ Inappropriate children game ]
I'd like to know the family that did that
The next New Year's related rule
how grandma splits up her savings of 500 yen coins
Ozono
hai
This is about your grandmother
after one year
my grandmother
She gives out the money after saving up for a year?
hai
How many people is it split among?
5 people
These are all the kids
your grandmother doesn't get any
My grandmother gives it all out
So its your grandmother that gives it out
does she save up the money to give out as a new year's gift?
She does right
How much is she able to save up after a year?  Collecting 500 yen coins
Almost enough to come out
Come out of what?
Come out of your grandmother?
She has a cat piggy bank
Didn't it sound like her grandmother was putting 500 coins in her body?
[ Grandma piggy bank? ]
On new years they shake the money out of her
People forcibly carry your grandma to take her money
and she's like "Put me down"
[ Extorting money from grandma? ]
Are we right?
She has a cat piggy bank
a cat shaped piggy bank
How much money is it about?
Its not counted up
No way
The 500 yen coins
she doesn't count them up to split it
She puts them in stacks of equal height
500 yen coin stacks
She stacks them and levels them off
Well that works
How high is the stack?
About how high?
I don't really remember
Like this much?
Its not that much
That seems like a lot
That's still pretty good
2 high is still 1000 yen
So then this much
this high is 10,000 yen
Just a little while ago
I had loose change in the car
all the change was in one place
I took out all the 500 yen coins and counted them up, 12,000 yen
and there was more than that, I just took out the 500 yen coins
So I've counted it, 12,000 yen is about this high
I've also saved up 20,000 yen recently
From 500 yen coins?
500 yen coins
I think it was this high though
How much is that?  20,000
There's no way
Wait, everyone is having private conversations right now
[ We're in the middle of recording ]
Its about 20 coins
Ah, that's not so much
That's 10,000 yen
The new years gift was separate from the piggy bank
So this is separate
sugoi
That's great. Its extra income
Hold on, they've collected 500 yen coins for us
Is this it?
Check it out!  Look!
This is 20 coins
10,000 yen
What?
See!?  Told you!
That's amazing for the staff to gather up 20 of those
Konjakuan
You borrowed it from Konjakuan cafe
Typical Konjakuan
Nobody had any idea how much money you got
Our investigation only made the range of numbers wider
She was right on
Hold on, she was blatantly cheating right there
[ Shady tactics fest ]
Give us a fixed height before we bring the coins over
That's true
She made me look foolish with her "See I had it"
[ Sensitive MC ]
This is 10,000 yen
is this what it looked like?
It changed every year...
That's normal
She refused to tell us how much she really got
[ All remains unsolved ]
Are you about to scatter it all?
Someone turn off the lights, I'm gonna throw it!
This is Konjakuan's money, can't do that
Himura-san saves his change
I save it all up every year too
I put my coins in buckets
[ bucket savings ]
They look like trash cans though
With Himura-san since he's so exciteable
when he buys something with cash he'll stuff the change in his pockets
so at work when he's changing clothes you hear all that change fall out like DARARA
[ small change waterfall ]
With all the change I have at the end of the day, it all gets thrown in the bucket. BAM!
I'll wonder how much is in there
Well in the past
I'd go to his place to practice gags, I'd take that change and throw it everywhere
[ Extreme troublemaker ]
BOOM it went everywhere
Summers-san threw the whole damn bucket outside
[ Meaner than Shitara ]
But then at the end of the year
you can take that to a bank
they'll change it to cash for you
When I do that I'll get back like 150,000 yen
That's enough to pay for a day of travel
But sometimes there will be weird foreign coins mixed in
sometimes buttons off my clothes end up in there
and I have to apologize to bank staff