DON!
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
We are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And over there are Nogizaka-chan
Reading it from the side its
DA
Nakada Nakada
hai arigatou gozaimashita
So let's quickly get started.  Himura-san
Let's reconfirm your character
Nogizaka eyecatch headline championships
A while back
magazine articles would write eyecatch headlines about the members in their articles
the headline would be based on their character
and were objectively written
This time we'll look back on those headlines
and the members will reconfirm their character as written in the article
Up first
Akimoto's magazine eyecatch headlines
The caption reads "She is owner of the strongest _____ in idol history"
So then we've covered up part of the headline
and before we read the real headline
We asked the members to fill out a survey where they filled in the blanks
The other members could probably accurately answer this
since they know how to describe each other
You may have a point.  There's that meaning too
So then Ikuta
hai
This is how Ikuta filled in the blanks of that headline
She is owner of the strongest
head size in idol history
But that could be true
[ Featuring the head? ]
It said in idol history
Not that much
Ikuta, you believe this?
Yes, this is not a joke
[ Answering seriously ]
This isn't joking around
No joke.  This is it
Yes, that's what I believe
What was that Asuka-chan?  Something weird about saying in idol history?
How about in the history of humanity?
[ Biggest in the history of mankind? ]
Going with biggest in the history of mankind then?
There has to be people with bigger heads
Well, its a charm point for you right?
That's true
Even with a big head
And other answers
Hoshino
Hoshino.  Hoshino wrote this.
DON
cunning
Of course.  That also fits
She just pulled one off
What did she do?
What was that?
You just did something
You puffed out your cheeks or something
Really, I don't understand what she's talking about
[ She really said that ]
That's what it is
When you mention Akimoto
its her cunning ways
of showing cuteness
That's what it feels like
Her idol instincts
well people usually don't say cunning as a positive trait but well
There aren't any others like this
Doing that stuff all the time, and she's not hated by the other members
[ Role of the hated one? ]
People fall for her
So everyone wrote in their answers but
do you remember what it was?
I'm going to say what I think it is though
of course
The owner of the strongest
cuteness in idol history
Ehhhhhhhhhhhhhh~
Why'd it get so uncomfortable in here?
[ Took all the fun out of the studio ]
Shinuchi, what did you think hearing that?
I'm thinking she has some strong resolve
[ Can only show admiration for her mental strength ]
In idol history
You're saying in idol history
[ Have you lost your mind? ]
Himura-san.  Himura-san!
Let it go
[ Can't believe it ]
Easily the strongest in idol history
How about in the history of mankind
The cutest in the history of mankind
But if we're talking about the history of mankind
there's a lot of people that are strong competition
Like who?
who? who? who? whoooo?
Like Aragaki Yui-san
[ She's lost her mind ]
Her against Gakki is an even match then
But doing this shows how strong her will is
And everyone is laughing hysterically but
but Matsumura for example
is the same type
But for me its like, I think I'm cuter than Manatsu
[ And now it begins ]
Someone who thinks that way can say something like that
So then the correct answer
DON
special move
Its her special move
Owner of the strongest special move in idol history
Is this about her ZUKKYUN then?
Ah the ZUKKYUN
Let's take a look at that article
That's a cool outfit she's in
That's remarkable
Her head is about 4 times too big for that body
[ Mascot character? ]
What is that?  For some reason it looks like she's pressed together
That outfit highlights some of Manatsu's weaknesses right?
What's your weakness here?
Well because of my head the hat didn't fit
but also my neck is short, and everything looks cramped
that's why it looks so compacted
Its like this whole area is squeezed in
Its like that whole area becomes my face
So for todays show
all the editors that worked on that article
we asked them why they went with that headline
Those in charge of that article said
they'd seen a lot of Akimoto
they saw what you do, and when they went to see a live show
they said Akimoto-san's ZUKKYUN
had a strong impact
It seemed kind of like she was a heart sniper
so they put her in a cowboy outfit
and it was perfect, and since special move stuck out as a keyword
it made it into the article headline
So that means
I don't have the strongest cuteness in history but
I do have the world's strongest
ability to grab people's hearts
Well the editors
well the editors think something like that
[ These are solely the opinions of the editors ]
The editors right
You have done the ZUKKYUN for a long time
But its like you've always done it but
up to now
it really hasn't taken off
[ Its true ]
There's something about it that bothers me
For the Hime-tan Beam, everyone reacts to it
I get it
After the beam its like WAHH
But for the ZUKKYUN
people react like "huh?"
What is the right way
to react to it then?
Decide on something
I see, I think maybe you should say something
The ones who get shot?
The people I shoot
if they would react
Like "I've been shot~" or something?
If you did that after the ZUKKYUN
How about "I'm hit!"
That would definitely make it better
How about you shoot the 2 of us then?
Give it a try
To the hearts of Bananaman-san I say
ZUKKYUN!
I'm HIT~
Yes!
Yes!  That's the one!
Hold on now
Aren't you putting too much burden on us?
[ The damage remains ]
Could you come over here and do it?
Now face and shoot them
Here goes
To the hearts of everyone in Nogizaka I say
ZUKKYUN
I'm HIT~
That was weird
That isn't very user friendly
And these 2 were incredibly cold
[ Akimoto allergy ]
You got another one?
If you could shoot me
To the heart of Himura-san I say
ZUKKYUN
kan-kon-kin-kan-kin-kon
I'm HIT~
[ Can't imitate that one ]
That was funny
But obviously Himura-san's kan-kon-kin-kan-kin-kon
that's high quality
I don't think girls can do that one
Well, let's see if Wakatsuki can do it then
[ Contractor job from hell ]
Its been awhile since Wakatsuki's done something for us
So Wakatsuki could you say that one for us?
To the heart of Wakatsuki I say
ZUKKYUN
kan-kon-kin-kan-kun
I'm HIT~
[ Perfect ]
See, it does work
And next
Saito Yuuri's eyecatch headline
Here it is.  On a daily basis she's the members _____
The gang leader of _____
gang leader?
And Asuka-chan
ah hai
Here is what Asuka-chan filled in the blanks with
On a daily basis
On a daily basis she's the members' dog
Gang leader of getting everyone in a good mood
What did you mean by that?
What do you mean thats wrong?  You wrote it
On a daily basis she's the members' dog?
dog?
Do you mean she's loved by everyone?
That's it right
Everyone falls for her
and she's beloved
So...a good dog
[ A dog is still a dog ]
But its not a good image
No matter how you put it
So she's beloved like a pet
Good dog
good dog right
So like everyone's mascot
like a very cute mascot
and she's so kind and does so much for us
and then the gang leader of getting people excited
In the dressing room, today too, she quickly finished getting ready
and I could hear her talking the whole time
She's always saying "Talk to me!"
Talk to me?
But that's also very dog like
Ah, so she is the dog
But today, the times I do quickly finish up getting ready
Manatsu sitting next to me
since she was free, I felt like talking to her the entire time
But its not like let's talk
She'll tell Manatsu "Tell me something funny"
Tell me something funny?
I want to hear something funny
But from now on she'll be a pain
when she ZUKKYUNs you, it'll be kin-kon-kan-kin-kun
I'm HIT.  You'll have to do that now
You have to do it
And then next
Inoue
here was her answer
On a daily basis she's the members' butt toucher
Ah, I see
She's the gang leader of overbite hentais
That last part was all insult
Gang leader of overbite hentais?
This touching of butts thing
we've heard that on past episodes
Lately, since becoming an adult, I don't really do that anymore
You don't do that anymore?
So then in 2010?
That was in 2016
So you stopped that in 2016?
That's right.  I don't do that
She does sound like a degenerate
You know you did it!
I didn't do it in that period of time
[ When you did it is not the problem ]
You haven't touched anybody recently?
I don't believe I've touched anyone
She lies
That's a lie
That is not a lie
She comes up and bites me
Bites?
Where does she bite?
My shoulder
Ah yes, I really like that area
She'll come and bite me here
No I don't
Your victims are speaking out!
[ Confess! ]
I don't.  I don't do that
How long ago was this?
Our Birthday Live
at rehearsal
This year
2017...wait 2017!
You did this in 2017 didn't you?
You caught me
Caught you?
So you bite?
That's right
When it gets like unnhhh
when its gets like unhhhh
and I want to be able to rely on somebody
I'll bite
That's frightening
On a daily basis she's the members' shoulder biter
gang leader of the overbite hentais
[ Shocking new headline ]
So she likes stiff muscle more
Are you into cartilege?
I really love cartilege
If that's the case, thats a different story
[ Just likes solid muscle? ]
This area gets firm
Right here.  Here
That's really hard.  Its the bone
You're going for the bone then
I like that part
You bite this area?
Yes, I bite there
How hard is it?
No really, she's drawn blood before
[ Victim testimony ]
That right there
well that's really messed up
Gang leader of the overbite hentais
She bit down that much
I was like "Hey, that hurts!"
You told her that hurts?
When I got upset and said that hurts
she got happy and was like "hee hee"
And here is the correct answer
[ On a daily basis shes the members body toucher.  Gang leader of skinship ]
Thats practically correct
On a daily basis she's the one that touches the members
kawaii
And this
now seeing this
seeing this picture along with the words
it gives her like a slight hint of hentai
different from just your average everyday hentai
And here
Shiraishi who's absent today, we'll see one of her headlines
Taking pride in having beauty that's ______
the universal ______
So then Matsumura
Taking pride in having beauty that's nearly inferior to mine
the universe's dried goods
The universe's dried goods?
Is this some kind of joke?
[ Are you screwing with us? ]
So this inferior to me part
the me part
That's Matsumura then
BRODY-san
they really love me
But don't most of the members get featured on BRODY?
That's what I said too when I met them
And they said they like Matsumura-san the most
They said they liked Matsumura-san the best
And this time with Shiraishi-san doing an article
That's amazing
If that headline were to come out, she'd be like who am I inferior to?
[ Mystery cast of characters ]
Its Shiraishi's article, so why is the caption about someone prettier
Let's see the answer
And here is the answer
Here it is
Taking pride in having beauty that's the strongest of mankind
the universal beauty icon
That's the highest level compliment you can pay someone
Instead of saying Himura-san is the weakest of the amphibians
[ Frog Himura ]
If I were an amphibian there's no doubt I'd be the strongest
[ Strongest of the amphibians ]
In a fight between Himura and a giant salamander
I'd win hands down
And next
Matsumura's eyecatch headline
Ah, the whole thing
Something something something
she excels at these 3 things like a 3 colored apple pen
Was this recent?
And those 3 things
Inoue
Inoue!
Inoue filled in the blanks this way
hai
manzai, skits
comical stories
These are all comedy elements
she excels at all those
She's like Sunshine Ikezaki then
[ Gave birth to all forms of comedy? ]
But if I had to think of a group of 3 things she's qualified for
its manzai, skits, and storytelling
Do you remember this since it was recent?
I don't remember
What do you think it is since BRODY-san loves you?
Since they love me
song, dance, cuteness
The 3 conditions for being an idol
Well lets look at the answer then
punchlines
big eater
the cute character, she excels at these 3 things like a 3 colored pen
Inoue's answer wasn't far off
[ Comedy element was in there ]
And a comment
She's funny
can eat a lot
and cute.  Matsumura-san has an abundance of character for variety
with the exact
same charm a 3 colored ballpoint pen would have
Apple pen, comes from her nickname of Sayu-ringo
That's the explanation
They really put a lot of thought into it
I'm so happy
Those 3 colored pens, if just one color works thats pretty good right
They're saying just me alone is enough right
Well that's likely what the writers had in mind
I don't think that's the case though
Matsumura, cute picture right?
[ Goes silent when complimented ]
And next
Ikoma's eyecatch headline
Born with a disposition for _____
the group's ____
And Nakada wrote
Born with a disposition for leg cramps
the group's stretchman
So then Nakada
With Ikoma-chan, what came to mind was
an image of her always stretching
Not just the legs
Its not just the legs
I cramp up right here
And it really hurts, and then my rear
cramps up as well as my knees
That's with the normal leg cramps?
That cramps up normally
On a daily basis
I'm not failing over but I cramp up
Its weird right
Aren't you lacking something?
I think there's something I'm not getting enough of
So stretching keeps you from cramping up at a live show?
I cramp up just doing this
And because of all that
that's messed up right, so I take proper care of my body
I do my stretches
And then Asuka-chan
Here's how Asuka-chan filled it in
Here it is
Born with a disposition for being a country girl.  She's the group's pickled side dish
Pickled side dish?
That's a total insult
The country part is fine
That's not it.  So that was
she came here from Akita
so at first
she was kind of unrefined but
she's changed so much since then, Ikoma-chan
So it has good meaning, calling her country
I get it
and the pickled side dish part
so pickled items
you're always happy to have them with your rice correct?
Like she's always by your side
In Nogizaka, she's always there
like a pickled side dish
See, she means well
She definitely just thought of that
[ Appropriate statement ]
Ikoma, do you remember this?
You don't?
But often writer-san will write about how natural I am
They write about how natural you are
So then its different from Maiyan
and everyone else's articles, they don't write about cuteness
I never get called cute in articles
more like how my emotions show in my expression
Well then
the answer
here it is
Born with a disposition to play the lead character
The group's featured actress
BRODY-san!
BRODY-san arigatou
Happy right?
And here
are some comments
Much like her beloved NARUTO and
ONE PIECE
she's that kind of lead character
she was born with a disposition to
carry a story
I believe she's one of the chosen ones
That sounds really good
Its Atsumori Bemars
Atsumori?
Wasn't it Atsumori?
Hatsumori
Is that like hot tsukemen?
[ Warm soba Bemars? ]
Next
Saito Asuka's eyecatch headline is?
Well you've said a lot about everyone else
So here it is
When people see her they say [ ____ is a miracle ]
____ bishojo
What could it be?
But first
here is Hori's answer
how she filled the blanks
When people see her they say [ The size of her face is a miracle ]
bishojo from another dimension
But you can see that
Well the size of her face
Hori, could you explain?
Sure, calling it a miracle
the size of her face
If you look at Asuka long enough, you get used to her face
but when you turn this way
its like "Her head is tiny"
Why are you comparing us!
But Nogizaka originally all of them looked tiny
but among them she stood out even more
like walking in the hallways from far away
you wouldn't notice when she walked right past
She's far away...far...far
What?  Where'd she go?
[ Asuka vanishes ]
She's that tiny
For me too it was like...she's far away..far..far
but I always knew where Akimoto was
[ The Akimoto phenomenon ]
Her face size
having large and small here makes it easy to see the difference
But really having extra small and extra large here with us
extra large!
Akimoto, she said it
Everyone's going after me
Shoot them then
Here goes.  To Miona's heart I say
ZUKKYUN
kan-kon-kan-kon-kan-kon
What's the line?
[ Forgot the line ]
That's good.  kan-kon-kan-kon-kan-kon
What's the line?
[ Hori's arrangement ]
So then
looking at this pretty much
the places where there aren't any blanks
It could be this or not doing this is a miracle
They think really hard to get these headlines
but with the writers, of course looking at their articles
its like ah, they use certain words with certain members
[ Writing the obvious ]
So you're comparing.  Akimoto, you do it too?
Up to this point they're able to see everything about me
and I'm happy to see when they write a good catchphrase
But if they don't write it, maybe I'm not pretty
Well that's not the case but
Let's take a look at the answer.  Here it is
When people see her they say [ To have someone like this exist is a miracle ]
That's so good.  I'm jealous
The revolutionary bishojo
When people see her they say [ To have someone like this exist is a miracle ]
Revolutionary bishojo sounds awesome
This
from the editor
BRODY is a magazine that was created to be revolutionary
and I think she was the most worthy of the word revolutionary
The mystique she has
I think is part of her revolutionary beauty
sugoi
So there it is
How about it?  Feels good right?!
[ Refreshingly good review ]
That's the revolutionary bishojo right there
Obviously all of you are looking great in these gravure pictures
But you must be grateful
I am thankful
I am grateful to them but
well BRODY
that's really Mattsun's magazine
but the word revolutionary really does fit
But BRODY-san
they have that much love for all of us
Of course they do
so I don't think its only love for Mattsun
That's true
But they've proclaimed how much love they have for Matsumura
They told me they liked me best
[ Mentioning it again ]
That's right
Matsumura's headline was punchlines
big eater, cute character.  She excels at all of it
like a 3-color apple pen
apple pen
Looking back that's pretty funny
3-color apple pen
But that's taken from Sayu-ringo
But they would always be sure to stick the word cute in there
Well of course
Anyone not had that said about them?
That's never been written about me
No way!
But they would always be sure to stick the word cute in there
Well of course
Anyone not had that said about them?
That's never been written about me
No way!
I really haven't, and BRODY-san in particular wrote
fighting spirit, and then chopsticks
chopsticks user
Fighting spirit...user of chopsticks
That means they watch this show a lot right
Actually for me
not sure if I should be grateful or put blame on it but
I've gotten a ton of chopstick related jobs
chopstick jobs?
Even in commercials, they'll tell me "Please hold these chopsticks"
Ah, that's good
Like what kind of commercials?
Suits commecial
That's not related
You're absolutely right but
they were put here
they wanted the chopsticks left in there
and then for 7-11-san
Everyone else was holding 7-11 snacks, but I was holding chopsticks
That's good,  you stand out
Have there been any weird or funny ones?
I've had Robot Girl
Robot Girl
You did all that here.
pretty much anything bishojo or kawaii