DON!
Nogizaka Under Construction has begun
We are your MCs Bananaman
onegaishimasu
And over there are Nogizaka-chan
New costumes!
So lets get started
Himura-san will announce what's on the show today
onegaishimasu
Nogizaka
comment queen grand prix
What is often asked of someone appearing on a TV show
more than anything its the powerful comment
So with that
with the members on a fake news TV program as the setting
they'll give us their various comments
Nogizaka's #1 comment queen will be decided
The first group of commentators are these 5
And the order of the comments are as shown
They'll try not to repeat the comments of the people before them
So then, live TV start
And we're underway, our live news magazine program
Himura-Ya
Well up next we have
festivals taking place across Japan will be brought to you
This is the "Its a Festival! Go Go!" corner
dozo
Horses ride up a steep hill
a yearly event that predicts the fortune of their crops
The horse jumping Shinto ritual
A few days ago
the festival took place in the city of Kuwana in Mie prefecture
and those riding the horses are from the ages of 14 to 18
Horse and man unite to go up the steep hill
But among this
there are also riders who will fall off their horse
Its a festival with 700 years of history
And the fans run up close to cheer them on
shouting encouragement as loud as they can
That was kind of short
So then for our "Its a Festival!  Go Go!" corner
This is the horse jumping Shinto ritual
Ehh Akimoto-san, how was it?
Well then
these days, having a festival in the middle of town
I feel has been decreasing lately but
Is that so?
Its true
With this festival having 18 year olds
actively participating in the event
Since Japan's future will rest on them
[ Senseless young people angle ]
That's right
hai
Shiraishi-san
How was it?
Well that was amazing of course
it had intensity
the outfits they wore, I learned something from that
Those stood out
Which part?
What they wear on their head
it looked like a Kadomatsu pine decoration
[ Kadomatsu? ]
All the shiny parts of their outfits
I thought were nice
Since they're wearing Kadomatsu looking things on their head
arigatou gozaimasu
How was it Shinuchi-san?
Well, this has been going on for 700 years
so there's a lot of history
involved I think
[ Strange Japanese grammar usage ]
With the added drama of people falling off their horse
I'd definitely like to go over there and see that in person
I see, so which part would you like to see
in person?
Well obviously
seeing the looks on each of their faces
Of course video won't capture it completely
I'd like to experience the lively atmosphere
[ The I'm wrapping this up gesture ]
Nakada-san what did you think?
Since its a festival involving hills
I feel a direct link to it
I'm hoping that one day all of us will get to do a live show there
[ Live show on a steep hill ]
So over there
you want a live show in that long narrow area?
I'm thinking people would want to cheer for us
What did you think Terada-san?
Like climbing that hill
and climbing waterfalls
its all for good fortune right
And people say when koi climbs the waterfall it becomes a dragon
That is the saying
And by the way since I just climbed a waterfall the other day
much in the same way
going up that hill I think would bring good luck
hai arigatou gozaimashita
And thats it for our Its a Festival!  Go Go! corner
[ Coming up...A popular anime adapted into a Hollywood movie ]
That was interesting
I didn't get a chance to really watch, since I was taking notes
Everyone was really concentrating
Honestly the 5 of you, more than I was expecting
covered a lot of area
[ Exceeded expectations ]
But the way Shitara-san turned it over to you
well he kind of fell apart
[ Adlib power...zero ]
And Shiraishi-san also
tried to move the talk to fashion where she specializes
but it turned into a conversation on Kadomatsu
[ Mind focused on New Years decorations ]
Give it some cuteness
Its true but to leave some kind of impression
Its not just about getting your words out
That's right
Its really important to steer someone into giving comments in their area of expertise
But
there was something Shinuchi did that really turned me off
Her "I'm done now" move
[ The signal for I'm finished talking ]
How many more times do I have to pass it back to you?
[ Face says it all ]
I thought using eye contact was preferred
[ Destroying the japanese language ]
Nakada what she said brought
some laughs
Trying to draw a connection between their zaka and Nogizaka
Isn't she trying to push her own group too much?
In that tiny area
you can't have a live show there right?
[ Live show venue from hell ]
Well people realize she doesn't really mean that
its for a laugh
The next group of commentators are these 5
and then
The order of the comments as determined by drawing are as shown
So our news magazine show Himura-Ya
the next corner
is this
Movie Trailer Banzai
that's whats up next
So in this corner
we'll introduce some movies
Everyone will watch the movie trailer
and give their impression of it
So then let's watch
dozo
Major
its all up to you
In the end
Major
will she be able to save the world?
That's hard
So then you've all seen the trailer for Ghost in the Shell
Eto-san, your thoughts?
Well that movie being a SF action movie
and having a woman take the lead role
its something I haven't really seen often
in those movies
What other movies like that have you seen?
Um there is...
well I don't usually watch those movies
[ Instantly backtracking on her previous comment ]
So then I guess
I want to see this!
hai
[ Ran out of comments ]
arigatou gozaimasu
hai
Sakurai-san
It looks like a very interesting movie
I've seen a lot of commercials for it recently, so now I want to see it
And Scarlett Johansson-san is so beautiful
so having such a beautiful actress come out in this movie
seeing her beauty on the video is enough to draw you in
So this movie opens on April 7th then?
I'm looking forward to it
[ Well done ]
arigatou gozaimasu
Asuka-chan
what did you think?
So then
its incredible within that short trailer
there were so many
shocking scenes included
Which part did you find shocking?
Umm...
that huge faced thing
hai?
hai
The woman with the huge face
all her parts
were crammed in the middle
So you want to see this woman's face in the movie?
That's right I'd want to see her face
[ That's the highlight? ]
Well yeah that's it
So Hori-san
hai
I love movies so
I'll often go to a movie theatre
or rent one to watch at home
This one looks like a big SF action movie
All she has are past memories in her mind
If I were left with just my memories
that trailer makes me wonder what I'd do in that case
What would you 2 do if you were left with only memories?
[ Throwing a question at the hosts ]
If I only had my memories?
How would that make you feel?
ah well
you'd only remember your distant memories right
Hori-san what would you do?
if you were left with just memories
As it is currently, I don't have much memory anyway
[ Constantly lacking memory ]
No memory?
I don't have much memory
But, you remember what we just watched right?
I remember
Well if you watch the movie, this will all make sense
[ Reckless conclusion ]
How was it Ikuta-san?
With all the fire like BAM! on the screen
and all the water like SPLASH!
[ Sound effects festival ]
and the glass was like
BOOM! all over
I think that gave it a lot of intensity
for people looking for thrill and excitement
I'd love for them to experience this
of course there's that
but for me well
my heart is weak at that kind of thing
I can't handle all those nervous moments
and I'll be like "Ah, I can't take it.  What do I do"
for those people there's a movie I love that I'd like to recommend to them
[ Recommending something else ]
The movie I really want to recommend
is Les Miserables
I play the role of Cosette.  Its showing at the Imperial Theatre starting in May
[ Plugging her own theatre play ]
Is that a movie?
This is a play
More like a musical
So you'll be performing Les Miserables
So then for this play
I play the role of Cosette
everyone please visit the theatre.
hai arigatou gozaimashita
[ Coming up...an unbelievable animal incident! ]
What's the deal with this group?
[ Full of problem children ]
This group was horrible
In this group, well Sakurai
I feel like she did a good job
Sakurai summed it all together
Other than her
that was bad
[ 3rd rate commentators ]
If Hori really made a comment like that on a show
its like "Is there something wrong with that girl?"
They'd never ask her for her comments again
[ Word terrorist ]
That was a real incident
And Eto, well she's like
Eto, well she did one of those
She comes across as a liar or something
While she's reviewing the movie, she says she hardly ever watches them
[ No consistency ]
And from there on
we had a run on comedy commentators
One show only needs one of those people, out of those last 3
[ 3 of them is too much ]
Don't need 3
Just need 1 to fill that role
Only one
And obviously the last person
Ikuta right?  She really made every second count
But that's the worst, telling people to watch something else
[ Taboo in the industry ]
and its something she's performing in
But that works as a technique
like "Did you really just plug your own show!"
But even if you say that
you can't trash the movie and say "Well I can't watch that"
[ Loses all meaning ]
The next commentators are Nishino
Takayama
Ikoma
Kitano
In the end
what effect will the comment order have?
This is our live news magazine program Himura-Ya
Next up we have home videos from around the world
we're going to introduce a video to you
This is the Himu-Tube corner
and with that let's take a look at this video
dozo
Coming right up
is a beach incident
The string this dog is pulling on.  Where does it lead to?
[ Bikini ]
Its kind of a sexy and somewhat dangerous moment
The beach right
you just saw a dog pulling on a bikini string
Kitano-san, what did you think of that?
I really
love dogs
within Nogizaka46 I'm the #1 animal lover
but as a person
that sense of urgency
that dangerous feeling where the bikini might come off
even if she's being teased
it still looks cute to me
and its a home video that warms my heart
and relieves my stress
Nishino-san, how was it?
That girl was in a desperate situation
trying to get away but
wondering what happens in the end
I'm really curious to know
Probably
someone else came and picked up the dog
and she was able to hold on to her bikini
I see your point
hai
Takayama-san, what did you think?
Well
for me
I feel like I have to get angry
[ Furious? ]
You have to get angry?
Well the dog is cute but
think about how the dog's parents must feel
[ But its a dog ]
Our child
is pulling on
a human's string
You can't call that cute!
[ Criticizing little dogs ]
Calling that cute
is probably what people would do but me
I'd want to give the dog a stern talking to
In the future when I have kids
to keep them from pulling strings like that, I'd have to
sternly discipline them
[ Suddenly going with the parental advice ]
arigatou gozaimasu
Ikoma-san
How was it?
Well, looking at that beach
it looks like a beach getaway
that people can enjoy
but you can also enjoy it with your dog
It was like a "That dog will pull like that"
[ Why is she talking like a madam ]
In that spirit
someday I'd take a dog with me
and I'd hate for that to happen but
it does seem like a fun time
hai
arigatou gozaimashita
That's all
[ Coming up...find out why they line up for these sweets! ]
Time for a commercial right?
[ When worn out, head to commercial ]
Wasn't expecting Kitano to do so well
[ Unexpected comment skills ]
Going first has an advantage
Whatever the first person says is usually good
It usually is good
I was expecting Kitano to say something strange
And Nishino?
Nishino-san was so close
When asked what she thought happened in the end
as a hypothetical question for herself
The moment when the MC asked "What do you think finally happened?"
of course I wanted to hear that she ended up naked
Himura-san really wanted to hear that
Well I just wanted to hear Nishino say the word naked
[ The wishes of a hentai ojisan ]
Takayama-san overall, I'm thinking why'd she go so extreme
I was thinking of Katsuma-san
Katsuma-san
That was you as Katsuma-san?
The tone was low and it almost seemed like you were scowling
And that video was unbelievable
to have such a cute video of an animal like that
For her to say all that would definitely get her cut
[ Doesn't care about unbelievable videos ]
The next to take the comment challenge are these 5
Again looking for comments that aren't copies
onegaishimasu
This is the live news magazine TV program Himura-Ya
So next we have
"Trendy sweets-san. Welcome!" Corner
We'll talk about sweets
the corner where they eat something and comment on it
And what they'll be eating is right here
[ Dominique Ansel Bakery - Cookie shot ]
This is from Dominique Ansel Bakery-san
its one of their popular sweets
This is the cookie shot
The cookie is shaped like a shot glass
and it comes with milk that you pour inside
Don't spill any.  You'll stain your new costumes
[ Poured too much milk ]
Please be careful.  No spills
Please have some of the cookie too
[ Lacking chin ]
The texture
of the chocoloate
with the texture
of the cookie
match well
and its very
delicious
and so
its imaginative
to add pouring in the milk
the playfulness of that part
well I'm not sure society is ready for that
[ Hey now! ]
but people will instead focus on how delicious it is
I see
arigatou gozaimashita
[ Forced comment finished ]
arigatou gozaimasu
It was delicious
hai
oishii
heh heh heh
[ The comment? ]
Ah yes
my impression of this
I should really tell you my impression of it but
[ That's the point of the show ]
That's right, tell us your thoughts
Of course at first glance its something different and interesting
if I were to upload this
on social media
like high school girls for example
[ Only focused on eating ]
so you'd take pictures of it
That's right
Asuka-chan, you've been eating nonstop
Is it good?
When you pour in the milk
the chocolate starts to melt
Now...right now
now its super delicious
Right now!
[ Arrived at a golden moment ]
So as time passes, the flavor changes?
Now then Sakurai-san
hai
Because of those long lines, I haven't had a chance to buy this
[ Brings up the long lines ]
Mmm!
oishii!
Actually
I don't like milk
Ah, the milk then
yes, that's why when it first came out
I was like what am I going to do about the milk
But even people that don't like milk will be able to eat this
People who hate milk can definitely eat this
I'd definitely like people to eat this
arigatou gozaimasu
And next, Hori-san
hai
At first glance
it looks like a glass
That's right
itadakimasu
Hori-san
[ Chugging ]
Hori-san did you drink the whole thing?
But its fine
the 1st shot was to get the flavor of the milk
the 2nd shot will be with some cookie
hai
I think I'd like to try it
Hori-san!
Hori-san?
[ Of course she's chugging it ]
You just drank it all again
Hori-san
Even on the second shot I drank it all
The milk is just that good
[ Can't stop drinking the deliciousness ]
Hori-san
I drank it but the milk is still locked in so don't worry
Hey Asuka-chan
You've reached the bottom!
[ This is can't stop eating ]
Well this is obviously
so humans
humans like to destroy
they have that desire to destroy
This cookie tower
using their own hands
people want to crush it
to get that pleasant feeling
What is she talking about?
[ Confessing her desire to destroy ]
Wanting to destroy a tower with their bare hands then
That's correct
Attack on Titan is popular right?
to get a sense of what that feels like
[ Eating sweets for that Titan experience ]
Don't you want to be a Titan?
[ Dreams of becoming...a Titan? ]
Its true that originally
humans were like that
So you pretend you're a Titan while eating that?
That's correct
arigatou gozaimasu
Saito Yuuri-san
Are you ready to have it passed to you?
Yes. And here we have the Dominique Ansel cookie shot
[ Live in progress? ]
This is like a reporter on the scene
Suddenly with the news report
Its really delicious
cookies and milk are a classic combination
those 2 together
so then no matter how young your kids are
or even for adults, its the best match
I would take some home
and have a party with everyone
arigatou gozaimasu
Its delicious
hai
Hey Asuka-chan
You ate the whole thing?
[ The Titan has finished eating ]
Ate it all didn't you?
Yes, ate it all
Well then?
Sorry for providing such a crude meal
[ From which vantage point? ]
Sorry for the crude meal?
Who are you speaking for?
[ Speaking on behalf of the bakery? ]
arigatou gozaimashita
That's all
[ Coming up...heat comparable to July?  Your weekly weather forecast ]
Hold on now
She eats it all and says "Sorry for providing the crude meal"
[ Out of control ]
The person that provides the food says that
For the person that ate it to call it a crude meal
And then eating food while someone else is making a comment
its not exactly stealing someone's comment
but that's what Asuka-chan did right there
But that is a technique that is used
That does get used as a techhnique
For a morning TV program
that would be unthinkable but
for a normal primetime variety show
they'd go to that person the most to get their comment
[ Valuable for variety ]
What did you think of Hoshino?
So Hoshino
I thought the point about posting on social media was good
those kinds of flat, level-headed comments
she was the commentator that had that
[ High level of connecting with people ]
And then Sakurai
Sakurai was like
she's just good
After simply eating
saying its delicious
its so simple but
I feel that's very important for a food review
That's most important right
Saying the obvious
Properly saying it is important
Nogizaka46
who will win the title of Comment Queen?
Himura has been picked to be judge
Nogizaka46 comment queen is
Its Sakurai-san
Sakurai