DON!
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
We are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And over there are Nogizaka-chan
Ah ha, we have 3rd members
I have concerns
So then please announce
what's on the show today
The senpais are offering full support to the 3rd members
in the counseling room
Tonight
all the things that concern and confuse the 3rd members
the senpai members will use their own experience to perfectly answer their concerns
Today's show is to remove any anxiety that might be bothering the 3rd members
First up its the youngest one
Iwamoto Renka has this concern
I can't shout out "YAY!" in a loud voice on variety shows
What's wrong here?
Can't say it?
That "YAY"..is that the show opening?
Like on TV shows
they'll ask us to yell out "YAY" in response
So its the opening?  What do you do after he yells "over there are Nogizaka-chan"
clap clap clap
But that's your best YAY chance
[ Greatest chance ]
I yell "YAY" daily
[ 1 yeah per day ]
Its like a disease he got from doing this job
But I couldn't do it at first and Himura-san overdoes it
Someone yells "Time for a tape change" and he yells back "YAY!"
[ Viva! Tape change ]
And they're not even shooting during a tape change
Reactions are important in any circumstance
Noone ever got mad from a YAY
But that's our explanation for most everything
But your senpais as idols
at first you guys would yell it right?
Let's find out
YAY!
YAY~
[ These are the senpais ]
Seriously these girls were able to do that after maybe half a year
they were able to pick it up faster than me
I always believed someone had hypnotized them or something
[ Without the presence of Hypnotist Jumonji ]
But its easy to understand her concern
It takes some time for that to come natural
Let's ask a senpai about that
So Matsumura
I think as long as you can get your voice at full volume
you don't have to use YAY
so if you like apples go ahead and yell "ringo"
[ If YAY doesn't work, yell something you like ]
RINGO
So just go with another word instead like ringo?
Isn't apple a strange thing to suddenly yell for a show opening?
Everyone's like WAHH and you're yelling RINGO
But indeed this is a chance to open up your vocal chords
So do you have a favorite food?
Its chocolate
Try yelling chocolate then
You can yell chocolate.  That's a good one
Here goes.  Everybody yell "YAY"
And we've begun
YAY!
CHOCOLATE!
Ah, she got drowned out
But your voice was still soft, can you get louder?
Are you yelling chocolate like you mean it!
[ Was that all out? ]
That was your all out chocolate?
Himura-san will show you how to yell chocolate at full power
Everyone say "YAY"
Here goes
He's about to show you how yelling chocolate should be done
YAAY!
CHOCOLATE!!!
CHOCOLATE!!!!
CHOCOLATE!
[ That's full power ]
kowai
You have to go for it
If you don't get to that level it won't get across
You're yelling chocolate here
You have to get the chocolate across
But it does sound off
First find a food that sounds like" YAY"
Ah, that's right.  A food that sounds like "YAY"
What would that be?
yay
YAY
yokan! yay!
yokan
Ah yokan works right?
yokan!  Does that work?
Do you like sweet bean jelly?
I hate yokan
You love it.  You'll be fine. You love it
[ You WILL love yokan ]
Its rare to hate sweet bean jelly
So do you like iyokan then?
I hate it
Hate it?
What's your problem?
[ Not getting anywhere ]
And next is Mukai Hazuki's concern
When I check my facial expressions in a mirror it looks cute but
on camera it doesn't look cute at all
So this one?
We have our dance lessons
and the mirrors there reflect everything
and also during those lessons
you're always looking at your reflection
During that time, since I'm usually in the back
I'm far away
so there I'll look cute but
Its because she's far back right
But then on camera
like now for example
looking at it
"Huh, I looked so different in the mirror"
What's so different?
Its reversed
Ah, the mirror reverses it
But that happens to everyone, you think you look good for a picture
and you look weird in the picture
Happens to everyone
Takayama this happens to you often right?
Like "What the hell is wrong with my face"
That's right.  In the past I've taken so many really bad pictures
and I had to find ways to improve how I look on camera
like those unfiltered pictures they take
those pictures of me were so bad
so now I don't use a plain look like the one
I'm talking to you with now
Something more like this
I'll hold a look like this
I see that face all the time
that one is the image Himura-san has of Takayama
On music shows I'll look over to Takayama and she's like
She'll either be like this or this
Himura-san's impersonation of her face
but now I understand exactly what she's saying
You do this right?
I do
Takayama is fully aware of these things
I fight to keep this area held in place, but if my eyes go dead its over
This is how it ends up
You did something to your mouth too
[ The mouth is weird ]
Now do it with your eyes locked in your best position
That's still weird
Even the final version is strange
The end is like
yes yes yes
Raise the corners of your mouth
And how about the dead eyes with that?
Takayama, you're still moving your mouth
[ All just bizarre ]
Its the eyes
You only lock your eyes in a pose
I put some force into it
And Sakurai
I also don't come out well in photos
its something I still worry about
According to Cameraman-san, they'll say this angle is good for you
since many of them will tell me that
I've started to figure out my good angles
[ Takes cameraman opinions into account ]
Since your own opinion may not be the correct answer
Maybe when you're discussing your photos for your idol goods
you'll be like "Why did I come out looking like this"
You'll likely have to deal with that
I've already experienced that
I'm sure you've had to agree to do poses you don't agree with
However
it often happens that you'll think you look bad in something when its really not
Himura-san also
That's right. I've been through this
Sorry to talk like I'm at the same level as you are
But it happens to me too
Himura-san, even though he appears like a monster on the exterior
when he's getting his picture taken
there's certain pictures Himura-san hates personally
Like how his passport photo came out weird
Its like Sakurai was saying, you have an affinity for certain cameramen-san
and the cameraman I despise most, is that passport center cameraman
He's the worst
So that
your passport or license photos are for identification
there's no need to look good in those
But the first thing he told me was to part my bangs
I moved my hair like pow-pow-pow
and he kept ignoring me
finally I stretched it out like streeetch
Eh? This is what you want?
Yes just like that is good
Then he asked me to draw in my chin
And he still brushed me off so I did this one
That's how it came out
That's on your passport for 10 years
Really can't stand it
I haven't seen much change in him
in how he looks
but he really hates pictures like that
It happens to Himura-san
And next
Kubo Shiori's concerns
All the dances I've practiced, if I mess up one time the whole dance gets thrown off
I'd like to know how to deal with that if it happens at a live show
Ah, this has to be something common
Are you running into people and such?
During rehearsal
we have our positions
there are times when someone will mistakenly end up in someone else's position
I'll think "What do I do now?"
and if she notices and we get out of sync
that mistake stays in my head
Ah, so it'll get progressively worse
Ikuta what do you think of her problem?
Of course when you mess up
since the mistake clearly shows up on your face
Its kind of like
even if you make a mistake
don't express it, let your face dance
Let your face do the dancing
Of course you need to properly apologize
but not during the performance
Got it
Sakurai
what do you think?
I've also made a fair amount of mistakes
All of you have had your mistakes right?
Of course you have
There's been times I've forgotten the choreography
or I've forgotten where my position is
or I'll forget the lyrics
You're a mess!
[ Can't do anything ]
But I don't believe a mistake is something that bad
since its a live show
Ah at that time
doing everything perfect sounds good but
there's good points to seeing something not go right at a live
If you become too terrified to make a mistake
there's going to be times where it will cause you to freeze up
So you can just regain yourself
I've had to do it before
She said earlier
when someone mistakenly enters into your position
you lose your place
Does that happen often?
It happens
I've also barged into another girl's position
It's like oh no I'm in the wrong spot
But you can keep going
I can keep going
And if you build trust in another girl
she'll let you into her position
They don't just kick you out of there
Ikuta did you use to do this?
How many times have you been out of position?
There's been many times where I've been in the wrong spot and caused trouble for everyone
And there was the story about Shiraishi pushing you forward
Walk out on 3.5
That's right
She comes out on 3.5
She'll miss the position and things get a little off
When you started you must have been nervous right?
I couldn't do it in the beginning its only now that I can do that
arigatou gozaimasu
Next is Sato Kaede's concerns
I waste money like crazy
and then I notice I have no more money
plus my mom won't send me any money
So what's this one about?
I have all the intention to pay for something
You have the intention to pay
I'll take out my money and from what's left
I'll think, I'm not going to use any more of it
so I won't put my money where the cash goes
i'll hide that money in another pocket
Trying to separate out the money you won't use
I separate it but
I'm like just a little bit is fine, and I'll gradually use all of it
until its all gone
What are you wasting your money on then?
Like clothes
and then frequent trips to the konbini
This is a common concern right
it happens on TV shows too
like squandering money everywhere
[ This is a personal concern ]
At happens at work too
this is something everyone has dealt with
Like those students who live on their own
getting all that independence after moving out from their parents house
But your mother won't send money
did she suddenly cut you off?
She used to send money but would say
"Don't keep wasting your money on junk"
Ah, that's right
When your parents give you money
they expect you to hold on to it, and you're telling her the money's all gone
I looked back at some of the texts with my mom
and its all about money
For example?
Its mostly "stop wasting your money"
there was one time she used formal language on me
Its scary when they use that formal language on you
[ I would highly recommend that you refrain from spending money. ]
She's telling you its serious this time
Ah, we have a similar concern
Let's take a look at Yoda's then
The money I saved in a piggy bank gradually gets used up
and is all gone within a month
And that's when all the bills come in
I'll misunderstand how to use money
You misunderstand how to use it?
My piggy bank is a jar
I save all my money in a jar
Since I shop online and its all pay later
You get billed later on for online purchases right
Those bills come and I'll run out of money
So you get the money out of the piggy bank
Its just a jar without any kind of lid
since its just a jar
I can easily take money out
So its really not for saving money at all now
I can budget for cash on delivery purchases but
I'm not prepared for bills that come a month later
Not thinking those bills are coming is pretty messed up
but I'm sure others have dealt with this
Ikuta
I don't really have a desire to buy more and more
and I actually have more trouble deciding what to spend money on
but that need for stuff would make me like
I need to work even more to afford that stuff and everything would turn out ok
I'll think if I just work harder it will all turn out fine
[ Wasting money is fine as long as you're earning ]
So don't put all that effort into saving, find ways to earn more
Got it
And then about your mom not sending any money
if you'd explain your situation in better detail
and tell her the details by phone instead of text, that would be more helpful
[ Explaining your situation will get you that money ]
And then at the handshakes
you need a lot of clothes for those events
and there's a lot of travelling expenses involved
if you explain it in that way
that you're not wasting money and you're really in a bad situation
then the money should come
Understood
[ obedient ]
Nishino, Nishino
what do you think?  You like clothes right
Yes, I do
How do you handle this?
I shop online
You buy something, but now you're out of money, what would you do?
For me, my parents are always so nice to me
Its never been a problem
[ Money has never been an issue ]
But instead
its more about
have an outfit just for the handshakes
don't buy something just for that, decide on a single outfit
But for those handshake events
isn't wearing the same clothes everytime considered wrong in some way?
Its not considered wrong
But wearing the same clothes each time
about that
if everyone brought inside a cardboard box
the clothes they didn't want anymore
and everyone could pick out what they like
and the people that got clothes could give proper thanks
if you did something like that
you wouldn't need to buy clothes anymore
Nah
Well I can't really ask you to do that
[ Can't say anything from his lowly position ]
All you'd be left with are clothes that show bare shoulder
[ Unpopular clothing gets exposed ]
But that would definitely work out
Clothes right
You all want clothes
Lately I've given it serious thought
Serious thought?
Like clothes, what do I really need them for?
You need them!
At first all she wanted was clothes, now at the end she doesn't need them?
[ Extremes ]
And next
the concerns of Yamashita Mizuki
The balance between my face and body is weird
my face is large, I can't line up next to other members
hai
What is this about?
Its kind of
I have a big face
Would you please step up front for us?
The balance is weird?
I don't see anything strange
I have a big face
Which part is big?
Her head then?
The back of my head sticks out
So you think the crown of your head is big and sticks out
The 1st time I appeared on Nogichuu
when I watched from home
it was like I'm the only one with the big face
No way
Seriously?
You really believe you were the only one?
[ How about this one? ]
That made Akimoto get up
Sensei will have to wait till the end to answer
[ You'll have your time later ]
So then you don't like how your balance looks
And Manager-san also
When I look at Asuka-chan in the dressing room
But Asuka-chan, come on
she's almost at an alien level, her face is so small
But her face is so small right, she was sleeping
and to wake her up
I lifted up her head
And it was her foot right?
[ Mysterious mistake ]
That's not it
When I lifted her up
I was like "Ah, her head is so small" so after that
I touched my own head and it was like 2 of hers
[ 2 Asuka heads? ]
Saito Asuka's head?
That's right
First from the senseis, someone else
Like what does Takayama think?
I'm also on the larger side
when I'm getting my picture taken actually if I take a step back
then it makes the other person look big
So I'll step forward
Its better for you to get closer up
What I'll do is put my shoulder behind but keep my head in line with theirs
Up front is better
This group though as a whole
compared to the average
the faces of all of you as a unit is smaller than the average
You understand don't you
I really get that feeling
When I'm walking around the city
and I check out a lot of the other girls
ero ero girls?
[ Looking for ero women? ]
Various other girls right
When I see them its like Nogizaka girls have such small faces and heads
And for me since I was little
my mom would tell me "Your head is so small"
In spite of that, joining this group makes me think I have a big head
I really get that feeling
And on top of that having a big head in this group, you'd still be considered small by average
compared to the normal level
However
this is a gathering of a nationwide collection of girls with small heads that you're comparing youself to
So sensei, here is your chance, sensei
I'll leave this to you
She says her balance is bad
and it troubles her
I wonder what would happen if we lined up
Because you're the one with the huge face
[ Not giving up the title ]
Oh, I mean your head
My face is small
I believe
Could you line up for us?
I've been somewhat curious about this
I've taken pictures with her before, but not side by side
So then allow me to stand next to you
Let's stand along this line
Do it right
If you could get up to that line
Ah of course
like this you can tell
She's way smaller
Akimoto appears much bigger
When you did this trying to match up to the line, that's when I noticed it
when they showed that part on camera
I was watching the whole time
Both of you look down at the line to match up again
Look, you can see the difference
Akimoto's head appears to be huge
She also seems to have more on the side
Why is that?
Well I really can't say why
She has no neck either!
Matsumura, what was that?
Matsumura you just wanted to insult her there
But really I think she has no neck
No neck right
And Mizuki-chan has a long neck
I don't see any problem with her balance
The balance is super good
But from here it really does appear like the same amount of largeness
Just Akimoto is a little huger
That's still bad, especially since you're sitting far away
Right there, you look about the same
But somehow Akimoto has taken this
and made it her charm point
she's cashing in on her head
[ The big head business ]
But you have done something with it
That's right.  Saito Asuka for example
there's many times I'll have to stand next to small faced members
The times we have to line up for pictures
I'll also notice how short I am
when that happens and I have this internal conflict, I know I can't do anything about it
Doesn't matter right
Since being large makes no difference
There it is.  She's Kojima Yoshio
But its a woman saying it
But to be serious, when we take pictures
and someone says that other girls face is so small, it makes me think YAY
But Takayama just said that
rather than trying to hide it by stepping back, the other way feels better for everyone
I just have one problem with that
Like when you look at a lake, you'll fall in?
[ Can't support the weight ]
That's not it at all
Your concern then?
My concern is that Mizuki is so pretty
she's already gotten model work in magazines
Her visual appeal is already complete
So putting her into this world
What world?
My world, the world of big heads
The world of big heads she says
You think you're a creature now?
[ Talking about the spirit world? ]
In that world its Akimoto and Giant Shirota
[ Top 2 in that world ]
But after saying all this
Even if it is Akimoto we're talking about it, her head is actually small looking closely
they can tell at the handshake events
Its really surprising at the handshakes
the people who walk up
Ah Manattan.  EH!?
Your head is smaller than I imagined
That's why for a creature a big head is at around this level
Yamashita is fine
What was her problem again?
[ Quick with the jokes ]
But when I look at Akimoto its like
when I look closely, she looks like a football player
If you had more to your shoulder, you'd have more balance
You should do a gag about the weight of your head
Like ah my head's falling over, time to push it back
Ah yes, something like that
Ah its drooping again, right back up
If you'd excuse me, I need to prop up my head
Yes that one, you should do that
But nobody laughed
Try it like that
Yes yes yes
[ Needs some work ]
Little more practice