DON!
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
We are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And over there are Nogizaka-chan
The Flower's Name
What's this?
The Flower's Name.  What is that?
What is it?
Something you're doing?
The flower has meaning
Has to do with today then?
So Himura-san
hai
Please announce what's on today's show
On today's show we have this
Which unit has the most charm?
The unit presentations for inviting new members conference
hai
So what's this about?
Within Nogizaka
there are separate units
units?
And actually today Himura-san
they're all sitting with their groups
You have placards right?
If you could raise them all at once
Please raise them
dozo
Them too?
Yes they're a unit too
That's the Sayuringo unit right
hai
And then the Manatsu-san Respect unit
I've heard of these
You should know about these 2 units already
Inumen
Inumen?
We're Inumen
Watermelon
Wonder what that's about
And they just said "The Flower's Name"
Tulip
Its Tulip
And then Himura-san
The Independents
[ Gathering of lone wolf members ]
Today, each unit will need to recruit new members
They'll give a presentation of what their activities are like and unit benefits
And if one of the Independents feels an urge to join a unit
they can be immediately accepted in
At the end we'll be asking all the Independents if they want to join a unit
Himura-san also
can elect to join one of the units
You'll ask me too?
Yes, which unit would you want to join
And if you were to join that unit
you'd have to abide by their rules
You don't have to join any of them
You're saying I could join the Manatsu-san Respect unit?
[ Shocking new addition? ]
You joining that group would be crazy
And first
going first will be the Sayuringo unit
There it is
That unit has a lot of influence
[ Ito Karin ]
Ah, that's right
[ Being in multiple units OK ]
She rushed over from the Watermelon unit
Yes, you're allowed to be part of several groups
Hey everyone, we're the well known Sayuringo unit
dozo yoroshiku onegaishimasu
They are well known
They are famous
We are the 4 active members of the unit
so originally
we joined as a group of anime lovers
and since we didn't have any friends
once we formed this unit
its like we all found that we could make friends with others
so then within Nogizaka
I believe we are the pioneer unit without a doubt
Sayuringo was a bigger pioneer than Manatsu-san Respect?
Completely!
[ Treated as the enemy ]
How do you feel about that as a Watermelon member?
The Watermelon unit is a different matter
You're fine with it then
And here are some of our unit activities
We release singles
That's pretty huge
Magazine columns
[ EX_taishu - Sayuringo has a regular Fantasy notes column ]
No way.  This gets you more work then?
They're getting quite a few jobs from this
And then they released the unit single [ Hakumai-sama ]
And the ritual they do right before performing Hakumai-sama live is right here
Allright everybody, since this could be our last time doing this....
[ Each time might be their last ]
ganbari
macchun!
You do that every time?
You always end it with "This could be our last"
[ Unit greedy for business ]
It could be the last
And what are the benefits of joining Sayuringo?
You can be on a magazine cover
Magazine covers?
[ On the cover of Big Comic Spirits ]
And we also get called by gravure magazines
Myself and Sasaki Kotoko had never been on a magazine cover before
but thanks to the Sayuringo unit
It was all Sayuringo then?
[ The unit provides a direct connection to getting more work ]
That is remarkable
You might get more work joining them
There's no doubt our unit is the model of a successful unit
[ Within Nogizaka46 they represent the forming of a successful unit ]
And then they appear to be offering a special perk just for Himura
We also provide this benefit
You can be Mr. White Rice
OH YEAH!!
[ Aspired to become Mr. White Rice? ]
That's right.  We have a song called Mr. White Rice so
together with the fans we say "Ready, set....Mr. White Rice"
there's a point in the show we say that
But we don't have a Mr. White Rice
What happens after that?
Really I just
praise Mr. White Rice with the others
But when I'm in your audience
and you say Mr. White Rice, I always say
hai hai
[ simulation complete ]
That's what I do
hai hai~
They created that mood
So happy
They're really targeting Himura-san for this
I feel bad for doing this to the Independents
this benefit was really only meant for me
All of you can't be Mr. White Rice
We don't know that, maybe one of them wants to take that title
And Ikuta likes rice right?
So Ikuta
you want to fight me for the title of Mr. White Rice?
I'm feeling the pressure
Got that right
hai
There you go
How about Shiraishi? You want my title?
I can't beat Himura-san
Got that right
[ Why the confirmation? ]
And these 4 have something to ask of Himura
What's the reason behind this?
We always wear the same poncho
its those red ponchos
and nobody washes them
and the smell...
[ Some kind of smell soaked in... ]
What is it?  It smells like bondo
It smells like bondo then
Washing it won't get that smell out
That's why I'd like new ones
If Himura-san joins
he could make us new ones right?
Don't think so.  I'd have to buy some right
[ Going along ]
Are you asking Himura-san for money?
For joining?
Its just that I'm not feeling any inclination to join your unit
[ If the problem can be fixed with money... ]
I get making your own costume, but getting everyone's costume...you should stop here
But I could join them
Himura-san could make his own Mr White Rice costume
That's right, since its only for me
Sure, go with a tank top and briefs
hai hai
I see, so I can do what I want as Mr. White rice
And some qualifications for joining our unit
here they are
Cute face and fast with the makeup
Cute face?  They're all fine then right?
[ All clear the 1st requirement ]
Himura-san's face is also ok
Thank god I'm cute
C'mon Himura-san
you're disgusting
[ Forgot he was a monster ]
He could join too right?
Shitara-san meets your cute requirements right?
That's right Shitara-san...I don't know about that
Hey, what's wrong with me!
[ Don't want to call him cute ]
Fast with the makeup
fast makeup
[ All can be done in 30 minutes if its just the face ]
We can all be done in 30 minutes
All of you?
If its just the face, I can finish in 5 minutes
What else is there other than the face?
The hair is something else
I thought there was hair removal or something
That would be another 30 minutes
This area takes 30 minutes
[ Old lady joke ]
And also for those that join
if you have these qualifications, that would be great
finance and business knowledge
business and finance
There's a picture of Himura-san on there
[ Locked on ]
What's that about?
If someone in the unit has financial knowledge
all of us appear on shows
maybe if you could manage us
Himura-san would be good for that
I see
Well I also wouldn't say no to that
[ Someone who's been taken advantage of ]
Need some more control over the business and finances
They think of you as a wallet.  That's messed up
[ Haven't you noticed? ]
This unit wants Himura-san
to join and shell out some money
Overthinking this isn't good
he's only saying this because he's not cute enough to join
Its because he can't join
But I am cute!
[ sensitive to remarks on his cuteness ]
And finally what are the aspirations of these 4?
Here it is
Our own concert
[ Assuming he'll join? ]
That's remarkable
You're going to be the sponsor
I'm not their sponsor
Himura-san is going to sponsor the concert
They've got me at their concert already
How big are your aspirations?
Our goal is Budokan
[ Goal is a live show at Budokan ]
I can't say they can't do it.  They can do it
Can Himura-san appear too?
definitely
All right
Apples and Bananas with grapes
that's the Budokan right!
You sure you want this old man with you?
[ Strong Showa taste ]
So then the best group within Nogizaka
the successful Sayuringo unit
We'll be waiting for you to join
Please head back to your seats
So let's ask the Independents about that
Ikuta, what did you think about the Sayuringo presentation?
Well a lot of that was
targeting Himura-san
not sure if they want me to join
[ Targeting Himura caused resentment? ]
They really went after Himura-san right
What did you think Hoshino?
Eh? Hearing that
I don't have that kind of financial sense
or management skills
[ I lack the required skills ]
She thinks she has to
meet all their requirements
doesn't seem like they're going after me
How about Shiraishi?
Since it was all Himura-san, Himura-san
I also think I couldn't do it
But you're friends with Matsumura right?
We do get along well but
Taking over would be good right?
That sounds more like it
[ Sudden complexion change ]
That happens too right?
Units getting taken over by someone
The next presentation
Inumen
the play
all the members who appeared in the play "All dogs go to heaven"
this is a unit comprised of those members
Here are the main activities of the unit
Dog meetings
Who drew that?
Ah, of course
Isn't that scary with the gun there?
In the play
we used handguns
so its part of the Inumen image
I see
The handgun is a symbol of Inumen
These dog meetings take place
and they occur regularly
mainly at Shinuchi's place
or Saito Yuuri's house
we'll make hotpots
[ Dog meeting = hotpot party? ]
This is basically a hotpot party
even though they called it a dog meeting
If its a hotpot party I'm in
[ No reason to decline that ]
What kind of hotpots do you make?
Soy milk cream hotpots
That's something the ladies would like
or a seafood hotpot
What else do we make?
We also have gyoza parties
[ More food related parties! ]
Its not just hotpots
We also have birthday parties
[ Just a collection of party lovers? ]
What's up with this unit?
And occassionally we'll leave the house
and have karaoke parties
[ All about indulging in parties ]
These are the best kind of meetings
What's the meeting for?
This sounds great
the members have such a strong sense of unity
Up to this point there's been a lot of meetings
[ The parties have full attendance from all the members ]
That's amazing.  Nobody's missed a meeting
Must be fun
Its a dog meeting but mainly what we do is
right here
we vent our daily frustrations
We all listen to everyone's "Well this happened to me recently"
Like airing complaints
We'll voice our complaints and then
we'll comment on a drama we watched
"That would never happen~"
This is just a girls night out type of party
By the way, what are the complaints about?
Stuff you can't talk about it seems
Ito Marika's face just froze
Must be serious stuff right?
But that's because
there's members there who will listen
So this is about private life or work, anything goes
they'll hear out anything
Yes, so if there's anything bothering Himura-san...
[ Was that an insult? ]
So you'd listen to my worries?
That's pretty enticing
[ Favorable impression! ]
And
the qualifications for joining Inumen
You must perform in the play
"All Dogs go to Heaven"
[ What? ]
But nobody can enter your unit with that
impossible right?
Essentially you couldn't be in the unit if you didn't perform in the play but
as of now
for a limited time, anyone can join us
[ It was all a setup ]
That was so close!
[ The one person truly ecstatic ]
So this is a first for us
saying that anybody can join
arigatou gozaimasu. So anyone can join
By the way
if Himura-san were to
join our unit
We'll provide these benefits
He can play the role of dog
I can play the dog role
so what does that mean
That has to mean you'll be the servant...
[ Entering the unit as a dog? ]
He'll be the unit's pet dog?
If they make a sequel of the play
[ If there's a sequel, Himura-san can play the dog ]
if that were to happen we'd love him to play the role of the dog
You sure about Himura-san being able to look like that picture?
He'd have to get surgery right here
[ Nose surgery required to play the role? ]
If I get a reverse mohawk going
dye the sides brown and get the plastic surgery on the nose
And then you'd have to have your fingers glued together
and you'd have to get paw pads attached
[ Also fully recreating the paw ]
Appearing in this play would bring high levels of risk
Higuchi what are your thoughts?
They've already formed such strong bonds
With the strong unity they've already formed
joining in now is like, will I really get along with them
That's what you thought?
hai
Pretty much
they bring in a lot
of their private lives
if I were to join, it would be better to keep it about work
[ Focused on business ]
This unit is more for enriching your private life
I'm all for making hotpots
so I'd like to join in on that
but they've already formed a strong connection from doing the play
Maybe the Independents should throw a hotpot party
[ Forming a new unit? ]
The Independents will become friends
They look like a unit
"Why does everyone feel the need to be in a unit"
[ Blind to their own personal shortcomings ]
That's what would end up happening right
Next is Watermelon
can they draw in new members?
These are the Watermelon members
onegaishimasu
Hold on they already have a set pose
This is the watermelon pose
[ Watermelon pose, proof of membership ]
This is after the watermelon is cut
If you could imagine that
Half a melon then
So you already have a pose
But they say Himura's face is a watermelon
[ watermelon face ]
It does look like a watermelon doesn't it
It really looks like it when I do this
Isn't that the sun?
[ Different part of summer ]
But for Himura-san, this is not something he's good with
Actually I hate eating watermelons
And that is no problem at all
Why are you named watermelon then?
None of us like watermelon
Eh? Why the name watermelon
We all want to stay on diet
out of these members
whoever loses the most weight
that person will win a prize in the summer
when we discussed this it was during summer
and watermelon sounded like it would be a good prize
We talked about it and it became watermelon
[ The prize for winning the weight loss battle was a watermelon ]
watermelon became the prize for the contest
So this is a diet unit?
But its more than that
Myself and these 3
us 4 get along well
and then Nyaa joined in later
[ From Naa to Nyaa ]
They call you Nyaa?  Why Nyaa?
Nishino
Within Watermelon
she's Nyaa
Nyaaa...nyaa
[ Forced into it ]
Nishino, why did you join?
On last year's tour
going around the countryside, only those who wanted to go out
for dinner, I'd go with them
And I was with them a lot
You knew they were the Watermelon unit?
In the middle of the tour
"Ah, this is the Watermelons.  Ahhh..."
[ Not much emotional attachment ]
And the activities of the Watermelon unit
Here it is
[ House party travel ]
[ Unit places importance on their private lives ]
That's it right there
That's the one
Up to now we've done all kinds of things
We've had a beef tongue party
That's all just beef tongue?
We wanted beef tongue
and since beef tongue is something it seems like you can eat forever
I ordered 2kg of beef tongue
[ Purchased 2kg of beef tongue for the party ]
I bought it off the internet
The staff where I ordered it from came over
And they worked hard cutting it for us
This party is amazing
We only ate beef tongue so it became a beef tongue party
And also, I don't have a picture of this one but
we also have our own hotpot parties
You got hotpots too?
[ hotpots are a must item ]
But you have hotpots with the other unit
I'll do hotpots for both of the units
You're like sumo-san then
You're like the sumo chef
[ Makes hotpots daily? ]
So you travel too?
And this has been mentioned on this show previously
For New Years this year all 5 of us went to Hong Kong
That's remarkable. You travel overseas
That's right
But wouldn't it be weird to see Himura-san in this?
Not at all
Just tell me your passport number
and I'll take care of it as coordinator
[ Leave everything to Karin the party coordinator ]
You took care of handling the beef tongue
Having someone like this makes the activities so much nicer
Having her is great.  Allows people to relax
And then we have a motto.  Here it is
[ freedom ]
That's creeping me out.  What is it?
They wrote freedom in watermelon font
Before I mentioned the Hong Kong trip
we freely did whatever we wanted
For example, some of us really wanted to buy some egg tarts
it was me, Junna and Yuuri
and the others were tired
T-chan and Nyaa
they waited at a cafe
so the personal care of each person
takes priority
We watched over their heavy carry-on bags
[ Nyaa in charge of the bags ]
And after that
we had members who had to go and buy other things
Junna and T-chan went shopping
and myself and Yuuri and Nyaa stayed at the cafe
Wait so Nishino?
[ Nyaa always left at the cafe ]
Nyaa didn't move anywhere
Were you ok staying at the cafe?
I watched over everyone's bags, even at the airport
Nyaa did?
But Nyaa enjoyed the trip right?
Super fun!
[ According to Nyaa, she was satisfied ]
And also our group mail
gives a lot of freedom.  Please take a look
I got experience doing kickboxing
Women and models have started doing kickboxing
I did that recently and informed the group
I was ignored and Saito Yuuri wrote she was at a cafe with mama
So not really a conversation
Nishino, what is that?
It's a gross cat
That's Nyaa right there
[ Skin and bones Nyaa ]
Why this cat?
So this is the feel of the Watermelon unit
So then
for entering the Watermelon unit
we have these benefits
There will be many more parties!
[ The parties throughout the year won't stop ]
Right now there's a lot of parties we're preparing for
Lots of parties are lined up
The sweet sake party
Kawago birthday party
Congratulations Junna party
and also planned we have
Karin and Nyaa's birthday parties
So all the birthdays
everyone celebrates?
Did you leave out the udon party?
Udon party.  What's the udon party?
For those who want udon.  Everyone eats udon
Do you fry up some tempura too?
Fried food party
[ mutual understanding ]
Leave it all to me
What's the deal with this guy
acting like he's going to join in
"I want a tempura party!"
[ Likely to join the watermelon unit? ]
And finally some benefits just for Himura
Here it is
You can go to everyone's homes
I can go to your house?
Well the parties happen at our individual homes
you can go have fun at their houses
Got it
And if Himura-san joins, you'd all go to his house?
Ah, I want to come over
Careful. Paparazzi will take pictures of you on the veranda
[ Once again falling prey to FRIDAY's cameras? ]
All 6 of us looking down
It'll be really fun, like I said earlier
at first Nyaa wasn't part of the group but
now after joining us
that's your line
It changed my life.
[ That's a lie ]
You made her say that?
You forced Nyaa to say that
That's not true
You rarely see that smile from her