Continuing on from last time
"Is it only my family that does this?"
the slightly unusual rules in their family will be announced
The first rule
Only the oldest brother gets birthday presents
Who has this one?
That's mine
Inoue
Huh?
What's this about?
The Inoue family puts way too much importance
on Japan's customs
The oldest male is supposed to inherit everything
so he becomes very important
So then only my older brother
gets this special treatment
Its only on my brother's birthday
that we'll travel
and he gets presents as well
On his birthday he gets treated like a god
He gets lots of presents?
Its incredible
Pretty much
for the birthday parties
they do those for everyone but
we don't get presents
So in Inoue's case, she doesn't get any
And I was born in December, so with Christmas
and New Year's close by
all those events get lumped together
Does your brother get birthday cake too?
He gets birthday cake and sushi
So you've never received a birthday present?
I'd get like 10 yen and apples
Why 10 yen?
They're making a fool out of you
[ Don't even bother level present ]
10 yen
Since I don't really get anything
when I first joined Nogizaka
and got a birthday cake from everyone I broke down in tears
[ Tears of gratitude birthday ]
I was like "Thank goodness I was born"
[ Found the meaning of life ]
Its been for generations
That's why its like that
My dad was also the oldest of his family
That's how it turned out like this
He's properly following past generations
That's got to be hard
With regards to birthdays
Nakada
hai
Nakada also has something
In my family
whenever someone has a birthday
At the Hotel Intercontinental
we'll eat at their dinner buffet
Are you rich or something?
[ Celebrity birthday? ]
I'm an only child
if it weren't for that this probably wouldn't happen
I thought this was perfectly normal
when I joined Nogizaka, I realized it wasn't normal
They're all low class right
[ Found the lower class ]
On the same floor
of the hotel
there's a cake shop there.  We buy one to take home
That's why those cake and patissier places are good when you're on your way home
But that cake, how do I say this
I didn't associate the cakes with birthdays
I thought you could eat those anytime
[ Cakes are a part of daily life ]
And the next rule
Sundays are for ramen rice
This sounds normal though
Who does this one?
Asuka-chan
hai
Not normal then
On weekends and holidays
my dad is in charge of the meals
but if for some reason he can't make the meal
then my mom
will make something
On Sundays, she wants to relax so
making food gets annoying
so pretty much the usual Sunday afternoon meal is ramen rice
its just white rice
with cup ramen dumped on top
Stop.  Hold it right there!
[ Shitara requesting police intervention ]
You pour cup ramen on top?
I put the cup ramen
on top
and eat it like that
With the rice?
The rice
with the noodles
The rice isn't on the side?
The rice is under the noodles
[ Ramen on rice ]
The rice is already in there.  This is opposite of what I was thinking
I'll put the ramen on top
and then add the poto-poto-pottosu
[ Terada family original slang ]
You add poto-poto-pottosu to that?
High calories!
Calories so high
And with that
right here she'll make the Saito family ramen rice
Does it matter what flavor the ramen is?
You can use any flavor
But the potato chips should be seaweed and salt flavored
So what flavor is this?  Salt flavor?
salt
Ahh, that's good
Aren't you just normally slurping soup right now?
[ Random taste test ]
oishii
You take this.
Why would you put it on top?
dump it in
Why not just eat it like that?  Like that is fine
You put the soup in too then
Put some in
You could pour more in if you wanted
I don't get why you add the poto-poto-pottosu?
I'm not understanding adding snacks on top of rice
[ High calorie version ]
Who invented this?
Mama.  Mama created this
At my house we eat fat people food
You're skin and bones!
[ All had the same joke ]
Both of us called her skin and bones
The Saito family specialty ramen rice is complete
But what will it taste like?
Is it the same?
No doubt about it...its good
mmmm...its good, its good
[ The strongest combo ]
Its really good but
well it is good
This is really freakin good
Its so good
I'm glad the potato chips are in there
Good texture
And now other members will give it a taste
Good right?  How is it?
How is it?
oishii
Its delicious then
I want to eat it plain
[ Craving cup ramen ]
Why you eating it plain?
oishii
Should we end it here?
You're eating potato chips?
[ Snack time? ]
You just ate a potato chip didn't you
Don't eat potato chips with chopsticks!
[ Eating normally ]
The poto-poto-pottosu
These are really good!  Its salt and seaweed
But really
For over half a year
I banned potato chips
Why?
diet?
hai
But you're skinny!
I'm the one who shouldn't eat potato chips
But after new years
The person who's most worried about weight was eating all that rice
[ Himura's staple diet ]
Its not fair to bring that out here
And then Yamashita has something rice related
3rd class
hai Yamashita
hai
There's something unusual about your rice?
Everyone serves white rice at home right
For us its all salted rice
Salted rice?
We put salt on top
of the rice that's served
It gives it a strong taste
So everyone sprinkles salt on top as soon as its served?
[ Basically salted rice ]
And the family likes this?
We also all like strong flavored side dishes
and carbonated drinks
[ Straight path to unhealthy living ]
We put salt on everything
You really like that strong flavor then
Do you still eat like that?
When I go back to my parents house
they put dressing on the rice
They put it together!
You really don't like plain rice then
Do you like sauces too?
We don't use the sauce
You don't have any sauce?
Sauce, ketchup, mayonnaise, we hate all of it
[ Sauces are forbidden ]
What's the deal with that?
What do you put on liver then?
We put salt on it
Is this because you love salt?
Soy sauce?
We use soy sauce too
we'll put soy sauce and then add salt
What?  Why?
I'll eat soy sauce rice
Eh?  Hold on
You add the salt after the soy sauce?
[ Excess saltiness ]
I want the saltiness from the salt
What's that about?
Salt alone is fine.  Why add the soy sauce?
But I also want the richness of the soy sauce
The self-indulgence~
[ Greedy salt queen ]
But it tastes really good
That's good?
Its like its drenched in saltiness
[ The salt supremacy principle ]
The next household rule
A cabbage tree during Christmas
That sounds so sad.  What's this about?
That one is mine
Akimoto, that sounds sad
Its not sad at all
What is it then?
For Christmas, when my family is having a party
everyone makes food for the party
We'll have like whole roasted chickens
and also steak
within all these extravagant items
its all part of a Christmas theme
So the cabbage in the shape of a Christmas tree is part of the dinner
We do it every year
I see.  So this is one part of a lot of extravagant food items
And you eat it?
That's part of dinner right
I've drawn a picture to make it easy to understand
Easy to understand?
Here's the plate
The bottom of the cabbage is cut
To stand it up.  Just one gets cut like this?
The raw cabbage
gets covered with aluminum foil
and then as decoration
tomatoes and weiners will be stuck into it
So you can eat the main part of the cabbage like that?
That part goes into a hotpot the next day
[ Effective use of the cabbage ]
The raw cabbage is just so you can stick food into it
That's correct
I've got a picture, so please take a look
Its on the right
What?
[ Unexpected party feel ]
Much more extravagant than what I was picturing
Ah, that's fantastic
Actually I would say this is very nice
You're rich aren't you?
[ A lot different from an Inoue birthday ]
They got a whole roasted chicken over there
That's what your parties are like
The one closest to us
That's me and my brother is on the right
This is a great party
Looks like a good time
So that's what it is.  In my mind I was thinking
just a raw cabbage sitting there
and in front of those leaves I'd imagine people gathering around
in front of that one cabbage and saying
Hey everyone
Merry Christmas
[ Sad cabbage tree ]
That's completely different
Even when I'd go back home after a long time
they'd say "Manatsu is back!" and bring out the cabbage
[ Celebration cabbage ]
So these are made for parties
From now on like at the end of the year
at New Years people eat japanese cuisine
But you guys, even though its Japanese food
you dressed it up as western food.
[ Japanese food spy ]
As for food
Kitano
seems like
you do something with dressing
In my family, the dressing
we have 2 types
we have mama's dressing and mom's dressing
Isn't that the same thing?
[ Meaning is the same ]
They are the same right
Does mama's dressing mean only mama is allowed to use it?
No, that's not it
And mom's means only mom can use it
[ Mom's private stash ]
Mama's dressing and mom's dressing are the names
Mama's dressing is sour
There's a little bit of sourness
to that dressing
Mom's dressing has garlic
ah, more of a kick to it
So how did these names come about?
Both are from your mom
Since both are made by my mom
its confusing which is which
When I left the house today
my brother always says he wants mom's dressing
But if I'm going to a filming session and don't want to be hated, I'll take mama's dressing
But your brother in terms of age
Even if he wants mama's dressing, he'll probably say Mom's!
[ Graduated from calling her mama ]
Its hard to say mama
Saying I want mama's
To make him say it
to make him say mama
I'll plot against him
even if I want mom's
Say mama's
I'll make him say it
[ Friendly family ]
The next rule is
At mealtime everyone has a different menu
Who has this?  Everyone has a different menu
hai
Terada's family again
[ Treasury of stories ]
This has to be trouble for your mother
It probably is hard on her
But lately
she's realized other families don't work like this
Mainly for breakfast
myself, my mom and my brother
we'd rather have western food
but my sister and father like japanese breakfasts
That's so selfish...just pick one and eat it
this all happened naturally
mom just made what each person wanted
That's too much
The night before she'd get the french toast ready
[ elaborate breakfast ]
And our cream would also be handmade
so she's a good cook too
actually she's pretty bad...
No no no no
of course she has to be a good cook
She's making handmade cream the night before
you eat and says she's a lousy cook.  That's awful!
But in my case
I'm fine with whatever she cooks but
its my dad
that says my moms cooking
hasn't made any progress in a long time
Your dad is throwing his weight around
I don't get it.  And I even said chassu for him
[ Selfish "chassu" papa ]
So breakfast is all mixed up
For dinner, my sister is particular about her food
because of that　our rice dishes
since sister has fobidden mushrooms
She won't tolerate any kind of mushroom then
No mushrooms
Well some people hate them
Is Himura-san forbidden over there?
My family loves you guys
Ah, that makes me happy
chassu
chassu!
[ At Terada's house, someone's getting tea ]
The next rule
At a travel destination, they must play Life the board game
Playing Life when you travel?
Who is this?
Ah, Akimoto
Each year my family will always in summer
go to Okinawa
and then for Golden Week
we'll go to Miyagi or other places
For those times what always happens
is that Life game will always get brought
the board game
So we'll travel and stay overnight at a ryokan
and then finally late at night around 11 or 12
My mom will say "Let's play" and bring out the game
and everyone is really sleepy
everyone's tired including my mom
and its a given that we have to play
we can't go to bed until we play
[ unspoken rule ]
But everyone is dozing off trying to spin the roulette wheel
everyone's playing just trying to hold on
Everyone's playing the game thinking "this is hell"
we call it "the game of Life from hell"
[ Mandatory bad times ]
Why is this?  Why can't someone speak up to stop it?
My mom looks so happy to play the game every time
Its your mom that wants to play
She must like playing it as a family
But it could be, she's really trying to teach you about life?
[ Way for mom to teach the kids about life? ]
People who want to teach you about life
would never ever use Life the board game to do it
[ The wrong textbook to life ]
Each time mom accumulates a lot of debt and loses
[ The originator accumulates a debt from hell ]
She really enjoys playing the game
Next is an unusual custom
Shouting you're safe after getting out of the bath
What is this? Who's this?
That's mine
Ah, Eto
This one is Eto?
What is this?
Is your bath far away or something?
After getting out of the bath
you open the shutter door right
In that moment in a loud voice I'll yell "I'm out!"
And you haven't toweled off yet?
While still soaking wet
While soaked "I'm OUT!"
When I shout "I'm out!" the family
responds with "HAI!"
Why?  Why?
Is this a way of telling the next person to go ahead?
That's right.  After getting out
if you towel off and then go to the living room to say "I'm out"
you can't save any time doing that
Now I get it
And if you go in but don't come out
this one time I did fall asleep in the bath
This really is to check on your safety?
But still
when they're waiting to confirm you're out with your yelling
you may have already fallen asleep
[ Already too late ]
And if they don't hear you say "I'm out" you've already been underwater for awhile
When my friends come over to stay the night, that part startles them
since its so loud
How loud is it?  Could you do it?
I'm out!
Kind of like that
That's pretty good
Pretty good?
[ What kind of evaluation is this? ]
But I also did something like that when I was little
and recently when I was with family
I also was like
with my family right
When I got out of the bath and yelled "I'm out"
they all replied "You don't have to say you're out.  We can tell"
and that gave me such a shock
I thought I won'd say it then after that
They told you they don't need the update
Indeed, that was their statement
But the parents house
its kind of spaced out
Our place has 2 floors
the bath is right in the middle and just to the left
so wherever you are
so everyone in the house can hear you wherever they are
That's why you yell "I'm out"
And then the HAI replies come from all around the house
That's like
Everyone in your house is on the same page
its nice not to have it all scattered
When I get married I want to continue doing this
The screaming "I'm out" part right
You hope to continue this
But your husband will say this to you
I know, you don't need to yell that
If he does that...I'll have to rethink the marriage
[ Deciding factor for marriage ]
You want to yell it that much
That's pretty important for me
Important to you right
Anyone else have a similar kind of "I'm out"
I do the opposite of Misa, when I enter a bath
in the living room I'll say "Going to take a bath!"
and then go to the bath
"Going to take a bath!" is good too
And I'll also say "Going to the bathroom!"
You inform your family?
I inform them
My family also says when they go to the bathroom
"Going to the bathroom"
You don't scream "I'm out"
[ bathroom updates ]
That would be messed up like
"I'm out of the bathroom!"
That just seems wrong
Telling the family when you're done with everything
Nobody wants to hear that "I'm out"
"We don't need to hear that!"
"Don't want to hear it!"
But some families do say "Going to the bathroom"
Only my dad does that
Dad yells "I'm back!"
we ignore him
[ papa ignored ]
When he goes to sleep
he'll say "Going to bed!"
[ Updates on going to bed ]
Your dad
I feel kind of bad for him
he sounds lonely like
"Hey, I'm going to bed!"
"I said I'm going to bed"
[ Dad seeking attention ]
Feel bad for him right?
When you're playing the role of dad, why do you always have a slide door in front of you?
[ Always heading towards a sliding door ]
"I'm back"
He probably goes to your room to tell you right?
specifically to tell you
He'll search around for Inoue just so he can tell her "I'm back"
I'm back!
Got that!?
But you'd yell that from the entraceway right?
"I'm back!"
He'll open the door to the living room
He'll come up to tell you
That's amazing
That's because nobody reacts to him
That's it
When he goes to bed and says "I'm going to bed!"
I'll reply "Hurry up and sleep then"
[ Give the man some attention! ]
Next up is this rule
taking baths with my older sister
Who does this one?
hai
Yumi-chan
This one is
Instead of when I lived at my parents house
this happens more after moving to Tokyo
After moving to Tokyo, the times when I'd go back home
with my sister
When you lived with your parents you took separate baths
but you grew up and now you often take baths together
[ Grown up sisters mixed bathing ]
But not when you were kids
Nope
I understand sharing a bath as kids
So why?
Somehow the bath is the best
place to talk
its become the best place
Because you can relax
My sister and I both
like to read in the bath
Both of us.  You're in there a long time
Yes, since we take a long time
we'll combine
it cuts down on time
That's right, this makes it much faster
the both of us get in at once
Doing that allows you to take longer baths
The both of us
will read manga in there
With both of you in the tub
But it doesn't make you uncomfortable
since normally you're alone
Being an adult now and doing that doesn't make you uncomfortable?
Not at all
Our family is a little strange
the skinship is pretty fierce
Like the hugs when people come home
They charge into your room and hug you
[ That's a hug ]
That's how foreigners do it
It really like that, there's frequent hugging when we meet up
Yamashita
3rd class
You have unusual bathtime rules
In my family
the bath area
Most people sit on chairs right?
Nobody sits on those.  We all sit directly on the floor
and wash our whole bodies
Sitting directly on the floor
That's right
The floor is rocky
rock?
Is this like the floor at a ryokan?
Kind of like
its black, what do you call it
the floor is made of stones
so with that
it feels good to sit on.  Having your butt poked by the floor
[ Stimulating the butt ]
Is the floor like those foot massage mats then?
A denser version?
Kind of like that but in the floor
There's probably more stones in the floor but
the entire family sits on the floor
And there's a water bucket in there but
for several years nobody has used it
So nobody gets in the bath?  You just all sit on the floor?
[ Religious training? ]
If you don't use the bucket then what?
Its all with your hands.  If you want hot water its with the hands
Have long have you done this?
Its kind of like a family ritual
Beauty trick?
She said ritual
What kind of beauty trick would that be?
[ Splashing yourself with water to enhance beauty ]
ritual
The way you apply water
Yes.  How you get the water
I thought sitting on the floor was normal
Whenever my dad would come in
he'd slide the door open and he'd sit there naked
but it seems that's not normal
Why does he slide the door open?
[ Back to the more pressing question ]
Because he wants to talk
He should just wait a little
But he wants to build communication in the bath
So he sits on the floor
He sits on the floor
such that I can only see his back
I'll think "Ah, he's sitting with us"
[ Laughs at him for doing the same thing ]
I'm also with the group of people that likes to peek
Why is there a group that peeks?
[ Peeking in on papa taking a bath? ]
When my father or brother are taking a bath
I'll make a loud noise to see what they do
You want to see their reaction
[ Bathtime challenge ]
But going that far
Many various household rules have been presented
in the "Is it only my family that does this?" Grand Prix
Who will shine alone as champion?
Of course it has to go to Terada right?
Terada right
It has to be Terada right?
She gave us poto-poto-pottosu
because of that
So then we'll have Terada wrap up the show
hai onegaishimasu
While eating your poto-poto-pottosu
please watch next weeks Nogichuu
So then well...chassu
bye bye
[ chassu = tea ]