Taking part in the prayer for the 18th single to be a hit
are double centers Ozono and Yoda
And their challenge in wishing for a hit
Go underwater, get up close to a sea turtle
and wish for that hit
was the plan
So then the both of them
in order to make this a success
had to get their diving license
In 2 days
working frantically at cramming for the test
arigatou gozaimashita
they were able to get their C-card without issue
There's just one part I don't understand
And part of that
Ikuta who's been wanting to dive for awhile gave her complaint
For these 2 to encounter a sea turtle
its off to the south, to Izu Oshima
Due to a typhoon, it was bad diving conditions
but they still fully enjoyed the dive
And now they're at the point where the turtles are often seen
Ozono: Think we'll see some turtles here?
Ozono: Over there?
They keep missing
and to find those hidden turtles
the both of them continue to swim around looking
However
Ozono: They're not here
Ozono: There's nothing here
On this day underwater
because of the typhoon that came in days earlier
the underwater visibility is at its worst
causing this unthinkable situation
Yoda: They're not here!
Their field of vision is completely affected
and they can't see anything clearly underwater
[ No sight of sea turtles anywhere ]
Ozono: Why aren't they here?
Yoda: What do we do?
They had to consider what was left in their tanks
and on Yoshida-san's judgment
they had to go back
On the 1st dive
they were unable
to find the sea turtles
Not that easy then
Staff: Tired?
I am tired.  How long were we diving?
That was about 40 minutes
eh!
For that next dive I'm going to
find about 500 turtles
Both still
have the energy and will
So here
instructor Yoshida-san
had this suggestion
Yoshida-san, onegai
Well, the sea turtles
there's an area where there's a high probability
of finding them but
its kind of difficult
to dive in that area
And that place
is called a "be on caution" diving point
The currents are exceptionally fast
and essentially
its for mid-level scuba divers
That's dangerous
They just got their licenses a couple days earlier
so what will their reponse be?
Want to try going there?
Let's do it.  Let's go
Let's try going over there then
hai
They want to find a sea turtle no matter what it takes
and full of detemination, its off to the 2nd dive
Yoda: The current is really pushing me!
As expected
this area is for mid-level and up experienced divers
if you're not paying attention, you'll quickly be carried away
and then
[ The 2 of them appear hand in hand ]
Holding hands
the both of them are doing what they can to fight the currents
Doing this alone would be impossible
but together they're ok
This is a good scene
Fitting of the meaning double center
they look for turtles
Ozono: Any sea turtles here?
Yoda: No turtles
Its cruel to say, but all they did was consume time
Ozono: They're not here!
Ozono: They aren't here!
At that moment
one of the guide divers
makes a move in a certain direction
Found one?
Based on the sudden move
the 2 of them desperately give chase
Ozono: Found one?
And what appeared in front of them
Is that it?
[ sea turtle ]
Remarkably
its the sight of a turtle from behind
They got one!
Just like that this sea turtle appeared
and the sight of one
is a symbol of good fortune
Make a wish to it like that
Go!
The 2 of them tried to give chase
however
due to the high speed swimming of the turtle, they can't catch up
ganbare!
Yoda: Its mega fast
They both desperately give chase
however
What? They didn't see it?
This sea turtle they chased after
disappeared from sight
Its fast
Ozono: Did you see the turtle?
Yoda: It got away...
Yoda: I didn't see it
They were so close
In the end the both of them
were unable to confirm the sighting of that sea turtle
They never saw it
And after that they eagerly searched around
for the appearance of another turtle
Ozono: No turtles here. Where are they?
Both of them are flustered
however
the more panicked you are, the more you waste movement
and you'll end up taking more oxygen...a vicious circle
Yoda: No turtles
Ozono: Why aren't they here?
At this point
both of them were low on oxygen
and to continue the exploration was judged to be dangerous
In the end that sea turtle
never appeared a 2nd time
Diving at the entry point I thought would have worked
They were so close
Even though they had no strength left to swim it made no difference
they still didn't want to give up
Was that the last dive?
But if we went one more time we might see one
However
We'd like to try again also but
even the pro divers are saying that's difficult
Its time for the last boat back
and more than anything else
they have to consider the physical condition of the members
Any hopes of going any further
were abandoned
It ends
with a near miss of seeing a sea turtle
We couldn't find one
even though we wanted to find one
Any decision on what's happening in a few days?
We don't know that
don't know
Its just that under these conditions today, there can't be any more diving
Right now its no good
And there's no certainty there will be a next one
So we aren't making a wish? For a hit...
Nature is cruel
and for them seeing the sea turtles ends with a near miss
However at the same time
they fought bravely
for their prayer for a hit single
Now I get it
And with that, on camera
they were able to shoot a turtle, but the both of you
never saw one
And then with the concern over your physical condition among other things
then this time
it ends unfortunately
Is that so?
But they still caught one on camera didn't they?
Isn't that fine? How about it?
I think that's fine, but the 2 of you aren't willing to accept this
You said you wanted one more try
One more time
You want to go again?
I want to go
ah really
But that won't be necessary
like seriously
it makes no difference in your record sales
[ You can not say that ]
Can't say stuff like that
They want one more shot at it
say the 2 strong willed members
So then right here
lets ask the senpais for their opinions
Asuka-chan
What do you think?
Ehh, but for like Zonocchi...
[ Zonocchi? ]
At first she'd cry so much
You mean Zonocchi right?
[ Everyone knows Zonocchi ]
She did cry
But these were just tears from disappointment
And then Yodaccho cried during the shoot of the music video
Yodacchi too?
Yoda is Yodaccho
So she's Yodaccho
[ Confusing ]
Yodaccho was crying
from wanting to try this again
She's like "Give me one more chance"
Its like they're developing so fast
Its just that the opponent is nature
and nature is a very tough opponent to have
Akimoto, what did you think from watching this?
From someone who's been forced to do various things to pray for a hit
really, if you can't accomplish the mission, how bad that would feel
and with all the pressure
There's that too
And before the sea turtle
it was far away but the cameras caught it
what's wrong with them making a prayer to that?
I think that's fine
And since it was in the ocean
if they did a prayer in the ocean, that's basically like a prayer to the turtle
[ Just like that its anything goes ]
Is that bad?
These 2
after joining Nogizaka
the gratitude
[ major gratitude ]
Really for me
gratitude
I really just
want to highlight their effort
I don't think they'd be happy to hear me praising them but
but I want to sing their praises
so as far as I'm concerned they don't have to do anymore
[ Odd speech patterns won't stop ]
Your talking has a lot of pauses
For everyone...gratitude
my...gratitude..won't get across...but
[ Rapping her gratitude ]
They don't have to...do...any...more
Hey...that's enough
I really just want them to stay here and rest
And captain Sakurai?
Their effort really got across
it nearly brought me to tears
I want to tell them "You've already done enough" but...
[ But? ]
What was your 1st thought?
Before saying you've already done enough
I want to tell them they've done enough
but I can tell the regret from this one is still bothering them
Considering their feelings right?
Because of that I'm unsure what I should be telling them
Let's ask Shinuchi then.  What should we tell them?
[ Sudden offer ]
Like this is probably going to keep bothering you
If someone asked you for advice on radio, how would you answer?
[ Say something to save the listeners! ]
There are days like this
What kind of radio show is this!
[ Screw up MC ]
There's radio shows like that?
This is Shinuchi's [ There are days...like this ]
[ Sounds like a Sunday afternoon show ]
But now
after hearing from everyone else
How about it?
Want to go?
I want to go!
OH!
[ Unwavering determination ]
But going again doesn't necessarily mean you'll see one
He's right
nevertheless
hai
Really
yeah
That's remarkable
Of course being the 18th single double centers
not praying for a hit single is unacceptable
So you're going?
We will!
If you don't see one, this is the last time
One more time
If that happens, one more
You're turning us into a scuba diving show!
[ Nogizaka Under Water? ]
Please find one this time
They're going out one more time
Do your best
ganbarimasu...ganbarimasu
This is something right
Seeing this makes you happy doesn't it Shiraishi?
It does, they're reliable
That's right
We'll bring back a sea turtle
No, don't bring one back
[ That would be a problem ]
That's a completely different mission
If you brought one it would be "Take it back!"
They'll be like "Here, take it!"
You're going just to pray to one
We're not asking you to bring back a turtle
[ Increased anxiety ]
To encounter a sea turtle
once again its off to Izu Oshima
for Ozono and Yoda
This time
for a higher probablity of finding one they'll do a morning dive
They get onboard an overnight ship
to arrive at Izu Oshima at 5am
Let's find that sea turtle
We will definitely find that sea turtle
We're not coming back until we find one
This time the diving area
considering the ocean conditions
will be at Ounohama
Since today we have to find one
we've prepared a secret weapon for you
What is that?
A fan?
This is an underwater scooter
This time another failure will not be tolerated
to go out further and search for a longer time
this time they'll use this underwater scooter
Definitely
we'll find that turtle and pray for a hit
Think the conditions are right to find one?
It doesn't matter what the conditions are, we're finding one!
[ Revenge diving start ]
With strong determination in their hearts, diving start
Its been 2 weeks since their last dive
before using the scooter, they have to get their bodies reaccustomed
Yoda: I think its warmer than last time
[ Looking confidently at the camera ]
Yoda: sugoi!
Yoda: I want to use the scooter!
Yoda: Looks fun
After getting used to the water
Yoda quickly wants to try the scooter
Yoda: WAH!
Yoda: This is super fun
After only 5 minutes she's mastered the scooter
On the other hand
for Ozono
Ozono: It hurts. It hurts
During the dive
there appears to be something wrong
Are you hurt?
Ozono: My ear hurts. I can't clear it
Can't clear out your ear?
[ Ear hurts due to water pressure ]
As you dive the water pressure builds
and its causing Ozono's ear to hurt
If you pinch your nose
and keep your mouth closed
you can clear out the pressure from your ears but
her body isn't responding
and she's unable to release the pressure
and then
Ozono: It hurts, it hurts, it hurts
Ozono: It hurts
Ozono: Somehow my head hurts
And now she has
intense headaches
Staff: Take a seat for a moment
Its decided she can't go any further
and she's back on land
[ crying ]
Feeling disappointed with herself
the tears start to flow
On the other hand
unaware of Ozono's situation
Yoda heads for the open seas
The prayer was to happen together
before they knew it they had become separated
and then
Yoda: That was one!
The camera attached to the scooter is turned in the opposite direction
to show whats in front of her
Remarkably
its the sight of a sea turtle
suddenly Yoda has camera footage of a sea turtle
Yoda: They're so fast
As she desperately tries to close the distance on it
in the end
once again a sea turtle disappears out of sight
and a 3rd chance to pray for a hit is lost
Both look down in silence and have taken on damage
in the end, what will they do?
Seeking revenge the 2 have failed on their 1st dive
and here
suffering from headaches
Ozono, who was forced to retire halfway, is asked about her health
Ozono, what's the plan?
I'm going
I'll go
Staff: Take a quick break
Staff: We'll see how you're doing after a rest
[ Take a quick rest and we'll check on you ]
In any case, its a quick rest
and see if she's up for a second round
[ One hour later ]
I'm diving
What'll I do if it starts hurting again?
Its not like she's become fully energized
and still appears concerned about not being able to dive
and then
under these conditions
they get a boost of encouragement from someone special
Sakurai - Sorry I can't be there with you but I'll be waiting
for both of you to return with a smile! We'll be working nonstop
after Osaka and it'll be tiring, so fight on without getting hurt!
And that was
something sent by Captain Sakurai
a couple of text messages
She's been really worried about you
she saw your diving video and it really moved her
and she's been checking in to see if you're ok
They aren't alone
Sakurai
as captain is giving her support
After getting her message
its time for dive #4
this time
thinking of Ozono's physical condition
they won't use the scooter and move slowly
Ozono: I'm ok
The deeper down they dive
the more burden it puts on your head and ears but
Yoda: Sure it doesn't hurt?
Ozono: Doesn't hurt
Yoda: That's great
Ozono: No pain at all
Ozono: Its happiness
Ozono's anxiety is completely gone
now they just have to find a sea turtle
A lot of turtles rest there
so they look closely within the ocean seaweed
and then
at that moment
Ozono: That's a sea turtle
Ozono: WAH!
Ozono: WAH~ sugoi!
Its as if
the turtle had been waiting for them
as it calmy swims right in front of them
Yoda: Yes!
Yoda: Big one!
Yoda: sugoi!
Ozono: kawaii
Ozono: Its so pretty
Seeing the turtle at close range
has the both of them deeply excited
Yoda: We have to pray for a hit
Yoda: I wish for the 18th single to be a hit
Ozono: I wish for the 18th single to be a hit
And finally on the 4th dive
the pray for a hit 18th single campaign has been accomplished
Ozono: We did it! I'm so happy
Ozono: Thank goodness
Starting from when they got their license
it took about 4 days
and finally they've reached the conclusion
After that
all their past hardships were forgotten
as they found more sea turtles
Ozono: Ah! sugoi! There's another one!
Yoda: So happy
For a little while after
like a dream they spent more time with the turtles
And their final dive is complete
Ahh that was great
We prayed for a hit
That was great
And right here
for their 1st prayer for a hit
we'll look back as their new song plays
NIGEMIZU
sea turtle version
The prayer for the 18th single to be a hit
was a big success
Thank goodness