DON!
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
We are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And over there are Nogizaka-chan
Welcome back
Well its true
Even though that seems like awhile back
in reality for us that took place yesterday
TV Tokyo's Music Festival
Of course
But seeing them do it, your version yesterday was much cuter
[ Himuko...kawaii ]
That look was really cute afterall
So then
Himura-san, what's on today's show?
To know more about the new centers Ozono and Yoda
let's give them some back up!
3rd members Yoda and Ozono became the new centers
in order to ease the concerns these 2 may have
tonight we've prepared a show to get to know them better
First up
the 3rd members will introduce some insider information about them
And the insider information Umezawa has about center Yoda is
She forgets her stuff way too much
She'll forget her backpack on the inbound bullet train
and then forget her phone on the outbound bullet train
You're not going to have anything left
[ Round trip - zero baggage ]
Has the train ever left with your stuff on it?
Manager-san will run and alert the station workers
and get my stuff back just in time
Ah, so you do get it back
Leaving your stuff on the train is an extreme hassle
Its happened to me.  And me too actually
I've done that
And they're called smartphones, but that smart part
they'll fall in that space between the seats
They should make fat phones
So you won't forget them
And Iwamoto says you forget to close the cap
on your water bottle and your bag gets wet
I did that 3 days in a row
What are you doing?
And the bottle will be full
Himura-san does that
[ Also common practice for Himura-san ]
There's times when the cap is only on partially
But making that mistake 3 days in a row
it doesn't make you think, I better screw the cap on tight this time?
I don't have any of that kind of memory and attentiveness
So you don't remember the cap coming off yesterday?
I don't
Each time its a fresh new mistake
[ Each mistake is a new encounter ]
And we have more
From Sakaguchi
At school
she's forgotten her pencil case and brought a remote control instead
Well those are both black
Because both are black
[ Color issue ]
To bring your remote control
its sounds fairly clumsy but
you really did that?
At what point did you realize it was your remote?
I can't open my pencil case
Did you notice at the end?
Sensei, this won't open!
But remotes will open up
they snap open
[ Now where's my pencil? ]
There could be a really tiny pencil there
And then her lesson clothes
she frequently forgets her shoes
and since the members don't carry 2 changes of clothes with them
she'll borrow the clothes they arrived in if they look easy to move in
This is Nakamura saying this
If I come in wearing pants
she'll say "Well that's better than dancing in this skirt"
let me borrow your pants
Who's let her borrow their clothes?
That's a lot of them
Those clothes are getting sweaty during lessons
and you have to go home wearing that?
Has she borrowed Tshirts from people?
The Tshirt would be the worst
I've lent her Tshirts and pants
and she'll return them a couple days later
I'll go home wearing my lesson gear
Yoda will wash the clothes for me
and return them later
But we have no idea if this slob actually washes the clothes
Do you really wash them?
I wash them 3 times and return them
Why 3 times?
[ Over washing ]
Why would you wash them 3 times?
And this happens often?
Only when I'm in the lesson room
that's when I'm most focused
so many times when I'm free from lessons
I'm not thinking ahead
How about if you keep a memo pad so you won't forget things?
I don't carry one
[ Irritated ]
You should keep notes on your phone or something
But she forgets her phone...
[ Unable to find a solution ]
And something from Yamashita
Coming out of a beauty salon, her bags, wallet and jacket
she wasn't carrying any of it
and she didn't notice until we started walking outside
But you have to pay the beauty salon
We went to the salon together
You went together?
And manager-san came along with us
Manager-san took care of paying the bill
So then Yoda and I went outside
and she wasn't carrying anything, and its the middle of winter
and she wasn't wearing her jacket
She forgets everything she brings with her
That's right
I don't notice anything and space out
You're like Himura-san
[ Real life mini-Himura ]
You're fine right now but
keep doing this and the people around you will say you're hopeless
hai
You listening Himura-san?
[ You've got the same problem ]
Next
insider information about Yoda from Yamashita
She gives people her half-eaten food
She'll take her food
This girl is messed up!
[ uninhibited ]
Isn't that messed up?
Why does she forget everything and eats like "OY!"
"You need to eat some of this!"
She probably doesn't say it like that
Let's ask her
That's bad
I don't think she yells OY at them
People bring in food or there will be catering
and she'll eat half her food and say she doesn't want the rest
and then she pushes that food on the other members
That true?
I want to eat it but
I'll think if I eat all of it I'll get fat
hai
I'll give this to you
and they'll take it
at first when I offered the members food
they'd eat it for me but
recently they haven't been taking my food
Who's taken her half eaten food?
That's many of them
This is amazing
Do Umezawa and Mukai often take Yoda's leftovers?
hai, I'll eat it
Umezawa, what will she give you?
tuna fish onigiri
she'll take one bite from it
She's doing this with onigiri too
So she's trying to give you her half eaten onigiri
She'll say "I knew I didn't want this.  Want it?"  And I'll eat it
And Mukai?
You take the food?
I've always
been like the bento leftovers girl
[ In charge of the leftovers ]
You take all the leftovers
But like today there's so many people, so you don't want to do it?
That's right
If Yoda eats all of it she'll feel guilty or something
so she'll always eat half
And I can't tolerate throwing away food
I'll feel like I have to eat it
Just eating half a bento seems unthinkable to me
At least offer the food after opening it
give them a chance to take the food at the start
I accept a lot of food too
I'll take food and give food
You take food
give and take
Give and take
Carbohydrates
everyone's trying to avoid them
people are always giving me just the rice by itself
[ That's a different story ]
If you're giving out food at least offer the side items
Giving her just rice is the worst
Using her to dispose of the rice like that
[ Mukai rice disposal ]
If its a dumpling bento do you eat all of it?
I'll eat dumplings
You'll eat those dumplings right
I eat those
She'll eat just the plums sitting on the rice
[ animal feed? ]
You're like Mukai will eat it
Its not like that
Whoever is there at the time, it turns out Hazuki
is always around
Its whoever is there with you at the time then
And Hazuki loves eating anyway
Yoda, you're frightening
Next
insider information on Ozono will be introduced
Ozono
Ozono is
baka
What's this about?
You could have offered anything as insider information but Sato just called her "baka"
Just wanted to write an insult or something
Its simply an insult
What's this about?
Its like she really
is like that
[ Ozono is really like that ]
She really is an idiot
I grew up in Nagoya, Aichi prefecture
Nagoya
she'll say that's Nagoya prefecture right?
Ahhh
But that doesn't necessarily mean she doesn't know the difference
When we first started
Denjiro
Denjiro?  Did you just say Denjiro?
[ Denjiro enters ]
Who is that?  Sato?
At first I was Den-chan
Den-chan?
The de from Kaede was used to make Den-chan
The de from Kaede created Den-chan
She noticed that and it became Denjiro
The origins of that nickname...
[ No origins ]
She said
she grew up in Nagoya
and then she said she grew up in Aichi
eh, that isn't what you said before
Yes, but those are the same
But now I understand the difference
And then we were playing a game
When President Trump was getting elected
hai
during that time period, she'd say
President Plankton
President plankton
That's a really tiny president
[ Microorganism president ]
He was running against Clinton-san, and since there was a president Clinton
No that's not it
That's not it she says
The person that wasn't Trump-san
that person
I remembered that name as Plankton
[ Clinton = Plankton ]
That's where the mistake is then
Did you know that was the wife of former president Clinton?
Plankton?
We're not talking about Plankton right now
[ Not part of the conversation ]
And then Nakamura has some information regarding Ozono
Ozono loves kids way too much
Ah, this sounds good
Nakamura
She really does love little kids
Its like
when she sees babies on TV commercials
She'll look and say "I want a baby!"
yabai
[ The way she says it ]
That proclamation is messed up
People will get mad. Babies aren't pets
I want one
You want a baby then?
You want to raise a child
I want to be by their side forever
With the baby right?
Why do you like the little kids then?
Because it looks like they aren't thinking of anything
[ Unique reason ]
That's crazy
crazy
Your reason for liking kids is messed up
If that's so, you should like animals too
I love animals
You like animals too
since they don't appear to be fully self aware
there'd be no apprehension
and we could play together
And there are others saying how much you love kids
Umezawa
hai
We'll often go out to eat together
and we were eating on a terrace with kids playing outside
And she kept saying "kawaii, kawaii"
When we left the restaurant
she went after those little kids
That's not good
She said "kawaii"
as she ran towards them
And those kids don't know who she is
they were like "Eh?"
And their mother
was like "Who is this girl?"
The mom was there?
The mom was there of course
Sounds scary
[ Horror? ]
Sato
We were both on a train
and we were sitting at the end of the train, like at the end section
About where the door is, and then
a kid in elementary school got on the train
the whole time it was like "Think I should talk to that kid"
Think I should trip that kid?
Why would they make the kid fall?
[ Random mishearing ]
She said let's try talking to the kid
Did you talk to the kid?
She was considering going up to talk and kept taking peeks
it was like
the kid crept to the other side
Ah, trying to run away
Finally the kid went to a different train car
[ elaborate escape ]
You like kids that much, doesn't have to be babies?
I do. I love them
Seriously?
The 2 of you are like criminals
[ Double verdict ]
Are we ok. The double centers getting arrested would be bad
And from here
to get ready for an appearance on Music Station
they'll prepare first by appearing on Himura station
What about that giant staircase?  Are you prepared to come down those stairs?
And you can't look down
Can't look like that
Watching each step is no good
[ Left foot, right foot ]
And then doing this one
[ Who does that? ]
All of you make that face coming out right?
They all do it!
They have a face prepared for that entrance
Shinuchi is the only one trying to add some coolness to it
[ Woman that stands for her beliefs ]
First the senpais will show how its done
The fictitious double centers
Hori and Asuka will take on the challenge
Continuing on
We have Nogizaka46
[ New song Nigemizu releases 8/9 ]
hai domo
So the both of you are center?
hai
Saito-san
What do you do on days off?
On my days off?
Ah, I'm at home
At home
hai CUT, that won't work
[ Low level of excitement ]
He'll put you on the spot quickly like that
Tamori-san will
Tamori-san will cut to you quickly like that
Keep it going please
onegaishimasu
You're at home
What do you do at home?
I sleep
ehhhhh
hai, please go to standby
[　The End ]
That's about how much time you'll get
That's about right
Next
double center senpais
Shiraishi and Nishino will show them the basics
This version of Tamori-san
is going to rush through your segment
be careful now
Are you ready then?
hai we have Nogizaka46 with us
So now Nishino-san
how do you spend
your summer vacations?
For me, I'm doing live shows
Live?
hai
Are there live shows the entire summer break?
There are live shows throughout
ehhh, no days off then
hai
Shiraishi-san
What do you do on summer break?
What?  They're the same
We tour around different areas doing live shows
The both of you do live shows?
Why is this Tamori-san an idiot?
[ Not a remote possibility ]
Tamori-san wouldn't ask that if they're in the same group
Now then
Yoda and Ozono
will prepare by appearing on Himura Station
hai, continuing on
Nogizaka46 is joining us
hai onegaishimasu
Both of you are center
Yoda-san and
Oen-san is that right
hai
And Oen-san
Oen-san you did kendo?
hai CUT
That's not your name
[ Can't just accept it ]
At that moment you have to say "That's incorrect" or you'll be forever Oen-san
Your name will change to Oen-san right there
And then when you're getting introduced you need to
since you're being introduced
you have to say arigatou gozaimasu
and then there has to be your best grin on your face
Once again its Take 2
Continuing on we have Nogizaka46 here
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
hai
Now then
Sorry to cut in but Yoda looks like a fool
For that point of course
its arigatou gozaimasu or yoroshiku onegaishimasu
but Yoda was doing this
kowai kowai kowai
Can't do something like that
Take 3.  Let's see how it goes
And next we have Nogizaka46
ah, that's good
hai, so this time both of you are the centers
Its Yoda-san and then Daien-san correct
hai
So then first of all
let me ask Daien-san
I'm Ozono
ah its Ozono-san, sorry about that
You corrected him.  Good
Ozono-san, what's something you like about yourself?
About myself?
How about Yoda-san then?
[ Out of time ]
What's something you like about yourself?
There's nothing
Wait, maybe there's something...
then again maybe not
hai. Go to standby please
[ TV time from hell ]
Now that they have experience on Himura Station
the 2 of them will be able to give us their best
And then now
The 2 of you
the people that know you the most
we've received information from them
Who would that be?
First
its Yoda's mother
Oh, her mother
hai
When you come in contact with our daughter the things to be careful of
Her way of countering when I criticize her
she'll say "People learn more from compliments!"
Its something I've paid attention to ever since
What's she doing?
okaasan
hai
Now hold on, what's this?
Did she really say that to you?
hai, that really happened
Is that your mother?
We have Yoda-san's mother on the phone with us
yada yada yada yada
Nice to meet you, we are Bananaman. yoroshiku onegaishimasu
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
arigatou gozaimasu.  Making time for us
This time daughter-san
she was selected as center for the 18th single
As her mother maybe you know
on TV for example she hasn't
told us what her specialties are, so you might know one
I'm not sure this would count as her specialty however
she loves the water
So when she's around water and if there's a diving area around
she's eager to dive right in
Diving area?
So is this like into a river for example?
ocean?
River or ocean or lake, any of them are fine
She'll dive in?
If it were the ocean for example
she'll find a rock high up to stand on
and dive in with a big splash
So would you say swimming is her specialty?
Well, if she goes to the ocean, she'll face the open sea　and start doing the breaststroke
In an instant she becomes a little dot
She becomes a dot in an instant?
[ High speed breaststroke ]
That's dangerous
Your daughter becomes a dot in just an instant
When she finds water she dives in and breaststrokes way out
But still
this is good information for if she has a summer location shoot
We can see her swimming skills in that situation
On the other hand okaasan
does she have any faults or things she's poor at?
We it seems like this information has already come out
This information is out
Her money management skills are lacking
She has money issues
So of course there must be a lot of discussions where she doesn't have enough money
Those are frequent conversations
On the phone that's basically most of the conversation
And then daughter-san
it seems like she makes people
eat her leftovers
So that's...
if it were me, I'd do the exact same thing
She picked that up from mom?
I think so
You want to eat in small portions right?
heh-heh-heh
By the way have you noticed any change in her since she joined Nogizaka?
If its something positive I'd say
and this is something that makes me very happy
When she lived with us, she had a hard time with mornings
and there were so many times when she caught her ride just in time
But now she wakes herself up, dresses herself
and she now properly meets people at the designated time
For me, she's grown up so much in that area
So its been a big jump
Even though it sounds so simple
But her self-awareness is growing
Its a possiblity
From now on her self-awareness gradually
it'll get better and then someday
she can treat her mom to something
Is there anything you'd like her to give you someday?
Must be something
For me
I'd like her to pick me up and travel someplace with her
Where would you like to travel?
Where would be a good spot I wonder
Around the world
[ Big dreams ]
okaasan arigatou gozaimasu
arigatou gozaimashita
What was all that?
She said she wants to travel round the world
We've had that conversation a lot
Is that so?
You can leave stuff behind all over the world
[ Forgotten belongings worldwide ]
hai
And next its Ozono
Ozono hai
We have insider information from your mother
arigatou gozaimasu
Ever since she left for Tokyo, now when she comes back home
in the past she'd help with the dishes
but now she doesn't really help out much
And the grade of clothing she wears has increased
Her clothes levelled up
okaasan, is all this true then?
hai
ah, domo
domo konnichiwa, thanks for taking care of her. This is her mother
Well this time your daughter-san
for the 18th single
what was it like when you heard she was center?
eh?
EH?
hai
I didn't
know this happened
You didn't know?
Ozono, you didn't tell her?
I didn't tell her
Why didn't you tell her?
You've got to be kidding me right?
This came out a fairly long time ago
She didn't tell you?
[ What's wrong? ]
So you didn't hear about this?
Eh?
The senbatsu announcement took place
And for the 18th single
the 3rd members Ozono and Yoda
hai
they'll be featured as the double center
eh?
Its true
EH?
Amazing right?
okaasan, you really didn't hear anything about this?
It was like
it hadn't been announced yet or something
Why didn't you tell her?
How were you going to tell her?
I thought she'd watch TV
and see what happened
That's remarkable
This turned into a shocking telephone call
I'm shocked
And all of us are in studio recording a show
everyone
is now a part of this surprise
[ Somehow became a surprise call ]
This wasn't why we had called you
This show was to dig up more information about them by calling their mothers
We were going to ask you how Ozono is normally
Is it normally like this where she doesn't tell you her news
There are a fair amount of surprises
like she wants to surprise me with it later or something
That's not it!
Its not like that
She asks a lot
Regarding one subject
it'll turn into hundreds of questions
You're totally in your rebellious phase right now
You deny everything your mother is saying
That's not it
So then if you have a story about her
please take this opportunity to tell us about her
Some memories I have from when she was a little kid
When she was little
up to 1st or 2nd grade
she could see ghosts for example
Seriously?
Suddenly we've hit upon something incredible
So she can sense the presence of ghosts?
This was in elementary school maybe up to 1st or 2nd grade
Would she ask you "Who is that person over there?"
That's correct
kowai
We'd be in the car
and she'd say "Who is that old man sleeping on that street?"
[ Suddenly ghost stories ]
okaasan, didn't that scare you at the time?
I'd say "There's noone over there"
Look!
He's looking
right at us with bulging eyes!
[ One of those authentic ghost stories ]
She's telling us something super scary
okaasan, why are you dropping this ghost story on us?
Why would you do that?
But eventually all of this stopped then?
This was only up to her first couple years of school
I think she was watching these kinds of movies or something
okaasan, this has been enjoyable
arigatou gozaimashita
And thank you for everything today
I'm shocked you didn't tell her
She'd ask a lot of questions
But you have no problems discussing ghosts?
Why not tell her about center?
[ Ghosts > center ]