DON!
HAI
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
We are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And over there are Nogizaka-chan
ZUKKYUN!
They gave out a zukkyun
Ahhhh~ is the wrong reply
You're supposed to say "I'm hit!"
To announce what's on today show
Himura-san onegaishimasu
Nogizaka46 Nationwide Summer Tour 2017
Behind the scenes or in public, these things happened
So what do we have here
A Nogizaka46 tradition that also took place this year
the Nationwide Summer tour
This time we'll go behind the scenes to see some things that happened on tour
and we'll all look back on some of the videos the members took
When did you play Jingu again?
was it the start of August?
July?
Ah, was that in July?
No way
It was that long ago?
And Himura-san of course
wait that wasn't Himura-san
So Himuko
[ Are we still pretending its another person? ]
That was 2 days in July then
But your Jingu concert is different from the other tour cities right?
Its different
Thats troublesome, you have to memorize everything again
And you'll change how the songs are performed right?
The arrangements are changed up
First of all well we have this video from the concert in Sendai
I think we should see it
dozo
Nationwide Summer Tour
we'll start from the concert in Sendai
[ Nigemizu DAY3 (8/13) ]
Starting this year, the 3rd members made their 1st appearance on tour
the 1st time performing on the same stage as their senpais
This looks good
[ Mirai no Kotae DAY1 (8/11) ]
We always see Mukai drenched in sweat
And then the debut of Saito Asuka's solo song
[ Katai Kara no youni Dakishimetai DAY2(8/12PM ]
Nice to get a solo
Has to be scarier though
Completely different right?  The solo
Its different
And there's not much choreography involved
What's that? What's going on
I really don't like this
That's great right
So that's how it was
That's from the Sendai concert
And for the 3rd members, how was it Yoda?
Since it was the 1st time for us participating
it was half happiness and half nervousness
furthermore this time
together with Momoko
since we were the double centers
there was a lot of uneasiness
[ Unsatisfied with Ozono? ]
Are you saying you were worried because of Ozono?
Ozono is not the kind of person to do something weird suddenly
That's right
And the 3rd members
have any of you previously been to a Nogizaka concert?
Mukai
Ah, there are some people
Isn't it remarkable to think you're actually performing in the show?
When I'm waving at the crowd, I wonder if anyone is looking at me
You mean the audience
You're not saying enough to understand
[ Only 20% understandable ]
They're looking your way
For me I'm wondering if anyone is waving back to me
They're looking
Like "Aren't you a sweaty one!"
You sweat a lot out there right?
I sweat a lot
At Jingu it looked like
you had just got out of a bath
With your hair looking like that
it gives you the appearance of looking soaked
Well that was the Sendai concert however
from here the members
I'd like to ask the members about what took place
First its Karin-chan
hai
A valuable shot of Asuka
We just saw in that video
that she performed her 1st solo song in Sendai
From just before right?
The first performance
hai
Honestly I had no idea if her performance went well or not
That's right but I asked the members and they said she was really good
And after she finished everyone went over to compliment her
Like "That was great"
They were all saying how great it was
and I have video of her crying from it
She cried?
hai
That's good, you were that worried?
Thats why the crying right?
And when she suddenly broke down, I thought I should capture it
So the video is halfway in
Let's all watch.  dozo
[ A valuable shot of Asuka ]
Really?!
That was really good
I'm really gonna cry...arigatou
Matsumura: She's getting emotional!
Junna: Have more confidence Asuka
Karin: Just a little more Asuka-chan
Junna: You were really good out there
Matsumura: I'm serious, the live version is way better than with a recorded background
Ohhh, that's interesting
Good one
But she did look like she was going to cry
At first there were a lot of compliments
but in the middle when I started to well up
everyone got a smirk on their face
Like this girls about to cry
And when you cry, everyone busts out their phones
[ Doesn't miss anything ]
Doing a solo song must cause a huge amount of nervousness
More than nervousness
since I don't like being out there alone
its more like
all I'm doing is polluting everyone's ears
[ Unusual expression of self-deprecation ]
Everyone wants to hear you
That kind of atmosphere is unbearable
Don't really like it
But then you have the members complimenting you when you get back
Everyone gave me a lot of compliments
This year's summer tour was really fun
Since everyone would come up and talk to me a lot
You saying nobody came up to talk to you until now?
And as you saw there were some tears too
That sounds good
That's something you don't usually see
Today we have a lot like that one
hai onegaishimasu
Next its Takayama
hai
Takayama's is "Unexpected pairings"
The members likely wouldn't think this was unusual
for certain people to be seen together but
for the fans this may be unexpected
so I've brought in this video
[ Unexpected pairings ]
Grain of rice
Ah, its Shiraishi
Admirable! Not leaving one grain of rice on the plate
Was that beef tongue?
beef tongue
One more grain of rice
Who is that behind you?
And yet another grain of rice
What's up with this video?
And this...
is another grain of rice
I've run out of grains of rice
Ah, that's Ozono behind her then
Ahhh, that was unexpected
That was Shiraishi with Ozono
Cutely clinging by Maiyan's side
I shot it
However seeing that, Shiraishi is like
she's weird
[ Class clown side of her ]
Its different right, when she works and then times like that
And this is another rice grain...
[ Why the food review? ]
I have no idea what she's doing
But why Shiraishi and Ozono? Do you 2 get along?
Momoko really likes me or something
So thats what's going on
Ozono, is it because you like Shiraishi?
That was a nod
Like on her blog, she calls me Mai-neesan
Mai-neesan? Mai-neesan
But Shiraishi has taken a liking to her too, since they've gone out for dinner
I took her out the other day
Just the two of you?
hai
What did you eat?
eh was it yakiniku
When its just you two, what do you talk about with Ozono?
I get a lot of stories about Kagoshima
[ Pushing her love for her hometown? ]
Stories about Kagoshima then
And do you remember what Shiraishi talks about?
"So tired"
Shiraishi says that?
[ Mai-neesan looks bewildered ]
Didn't you say "I'm tired"
That was after work
we went out to eat, and it was like "What did you do today?"
and she asked what kind of work I was doing
What's so odd
when the 3rd members showed up to make their introductions
Ozono looked like she was about to pass out
So starting off like that to suddenly both of you going out to eat
would have been hard to imagine back then
Back then I was...
You almost passed out, how would you know?
[ No recollection ]
And the next video is presented by Kawago
As tradition when we're touring on the road, we have a dinner party
Anyone who wants to go can join
So this is something you've done in the past too
This time we had the 3rd members come along
And I took video of it
Lets take a look
[ The traditional dinner party ]
Talk to Ami-chan, say it to Ami-chan
Junna: Hey Yoda-chan, Yoda-chan
Junna: So Ami-chan, she wants people to call her Ami-chan senpai
Please call her Ami-chan senpai
Yoda: Ah, Ami-chan senpai
What's going on here?
Momoko could you call her Ami-chan senpai too
Ozono: Ami-chan senpai
She made it look so painful though
Ami-chan senpai
kawaii
Ami-chan senpai~
Ami-chan senpai is some kind of trend
Looks fun just to say it
Ami-chan senpai.  Ami-chan senpai
HAI
[ What happened to Noujo ]
With the 3rd member girls
I haven't had much time to talk to them before this tour
so I thought this was a good chance
and I actually enjoy being called Ami-chan
[ Is that so? ]
You like being called Ami-chan
I do, and since they're kouhais
then it becomes Ami-chan senpai
Sure its not Johnson-senpai?
Johnson-senpai doesn't sound very cute, but Ami-chan senpai sounds nice
So I asked them to call me that
Among them who says Ami-chan senpai the best?
Like a championship
If this were a competition
Who would be the champion?
The way Yoda-chan says it is amazingly cute
[ The best Ami-chan senpai ]
Say it for us
The winning Ami-chan senpai
Yoda, could you call her that?
Ami-chan senpai
AHHH~
[ What was that? ]
What's that about? She gets happy when she embarasses someone
[ jumbled emotions ]
Sounds like a solo comedian, Ami-chan senpai
[ Solo comedian - Ami-chan senpai ]
I'm Ami-chan senpai!
[ Ami-chan senpai ]
Sounds like a Jinrikisha entertainer
And next we have video of the dinner party from Kawago
Sakurai, when she eats uni
she gets incredibly excited
Sakurai usually isn't like that
This is about Sakurai then?
She gets so happy seeing the uni
Please pay attention to her bizarre movements all the way to the end
onegaishimasu
I don't remember this
[ Highly excited Sakurai ]
itadakimasu
So good!
Its good!
uni-sama is the best!
Reika is all about the uni
You got a good one
Sakurai
That must have been somewhat embarassing
Its embarassing
Most embarassed I've ever been
That's a good video
Seemed a bit like how Ikuta acts rubbed off on you
And it kept coming
remarkably in Sendai
they had so many of those wooden boxes with uni
full boxes kept coming
Well because you had that many people eating
They said eat as much as you want
But you still can't eat that much uni even with that
But that was the best
It was really delicious
But what's the deal with that look you made?
I don't remember doing that
Pretty much
was there something wrong with me there?
You seemed ok.  You still tried to cover up your armpits
What was that part about? That look on your face
and what's this move for?
When I yelled WAH, since I was sleeveless
yabai yabai
[ The lighter version ]
And now Chiharu has her video of the dinner party
We just got highly excited Sakurai, so whats this one?
Highly excited Ikuta
There it is
[ Highly excited Ikuta ]
Is this one of those moments?
This is THE highly excited
I think I have a good one
What's the scene?
This is also a dinner party
In the middle of one
got it
Please take a look
Let's take a look
[ Highly excited Ikuta ]
I ate too much~
So full~
Ate too much today didn't we
Sure did
Isn't that right Kubo-chan?
I'm so full
You did something you don't ever want shown!
You got a good one
That was wonderful
And Ikuta doesn't cover up her armpits
[ Just as nature intended ]
Much different than Sakurai
What were you doing?
I have no idea, even after watching that
I'm thinking "What was I doing?"
Maybe it was the mood in that setting
With all the delicious food and people around
that's how it turns out
And that was after the meal
Yes, after I was full
That's just the happiness coming out then
from eating
You were next to her Kubo?
hai
Kubo was sitting next to her
How was it?
You have no idea what the high-5 was for right?
I also was in a strange mood
Do you usually attend their dinner parties?
I mostly attend them
At that time, Noujo-san was sitting at the same table
I was also asked to say Ami-chan senpai
And this was a different dinner party
And she did the Ami-chan senpai thing again
[ Missionary work ]
You forced them to call you Ami-chan senpai again
Yes, I made them
Now I remember
How did you handle the beef tongue tickets beforehand?
[ Last year Shitara suggested the members have as much beef tongue as they wanted ]
so did they change it to all you can eat beef tongue this time?
No change
No changes?!
It was the tickets again
And also the beef
we got less, now its just 4 pieces
It went from 5 slices to 4 slices
[ Complaints keep coming ]
Less than before then
And you only got 1 ticket again this year?
This year we got 2 tickets
So you got more this time
Could you use up all 2 tickets?
Could you eat 8 slices?
So with one slice, it got cut into 3
and thats what they brought out
One slice
of beef tongue was cut into 3 pieces
and passed around
But there are restaurants that do that
But last year it was only cut in 2 pieces...
[ Beef tongue customer complaints ]
You didn't go over there just to eat beef tongue
And next
Takayama's video
Often Iku-chan on the charter bus, she'll try to make a connection with
the person next to her
That sounds bad, everyone's tired and she's trying to talk to someone
So that does happen
So then I found myself sitting next to her
and usually I sleep on the charter bus
but she got me in a good mood
and together
[ Ikuta in a strange mood on the charter bus ]
Finally we get to see this. I've always wanted to see Ikuta on one of those busses.
I really have no recollection of anything I did on a bus
[ Her last resort "I have no recollection of that" ]
You don't remember
Enjoying myself at dinner
and someone taking a video, I remembered that
But the bus...
Since you don't remember, we should watch
onegaishimasu
Here's the video
[ Revealed at long last! Ikuta on the bus ]
So I'm currently
we just finished our first stop on the tour in Sendai
I'M ON A BUS!
HOW YOU DOIN!
And then sitting on this bus
I'm getting super excited!
Takayama: Is that your Inoki-san?
Starting right now
I'm about to start my bus live show
Are you serious?
Lighting-san!
[ Shinuchi in charge of the lights ]
arigatou...arigatou!
Now then, anyone have any requests?
Shinuchi: While the bus is currently stopped right?
Ikuta Erika solo live
Sendai bus live
Everyone thank you so much for coming
Shinuchi: I want to hear Aimer from Romeo & Juliet
Aimer~
anata dake wo~
aishiteiru~
Anyone else have a request?
Takayama: A song from Les Miserables
Les Miserables?
Ah, stop the show! Cancel it!
Finally got to see it
So that's what it looks like
If she can't remember doing that, thats messed up
you seemed fully aware
[ Shocked with herself ]
Did you remember doing that?
faintly
You put on a live show, you weren't just talking
After the live concert
I was still energized
like I could still do another show after the concert ended
[ Bothersome side effect ]
And you were talking like Inoki-san
I'M ON A BUS!
HOW YOU DOIN!
That part was funny
That happens. When you get excited you talk like Inoki-san
That does happen
Was everyone else there?
If everyone was there, I feel really bad for doing that
[ Everyone else is trying to sleep ]
At that time, Kana was likely
doing something live with a radio station
Over the phone?
On the bus?  That's not good, with all that noise
and in spite of that Iku-chan was like
Shall I sing something?
[ Unwelcome favor ]
The connection wasn't good and even though I needed it to be quiet
she did a lot of singing
In the middle of your interview?
somewhere during the middle
manager-san told her something
and it got quiet
[ Post live show scolding ]
She was particularly loud
Take some more videos
Understood
We can make it an add-on to the live concert
[ Full edition with Ikuta's bus live show included ]