DON!
HAI
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
We are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And over there are Nogizaka-chan
MEN!
OYYY! That's good
Today everyone
is wearing a Hakama
But some of them are wearing something different
The managers
Kind of like new pro wrestlers?
[ Trainee style ]
Himura-san, tell everyone what's on the show today
Movie Asahinagu and
19th single
double prayers for a hit
Tonight, its been released nationwide
starring Nogizaka46
The movie Asahinagu
and the theme song, the 19th single
[ Itsuka dekiru kara kyou Dekiru ]
a prayer for both to be a hit will take place
First we'll introduce some highlights from the members appearing on Asahinagu
I've seen the movie, and they really are doing cool looking sword fighting
We're really doing it
But since you're wearing that headgear
you can't really tell who is under there
Matsumura, you had a stand-in do your fighting right?
Wrong!
You did it?
I worked hard
All of it?
All of it
Really?
Really
You lie!
Why are you talking like this?
The way you said that was crazy
All of it!
Really!
And that was you in the fight scenes?
Mmm..that's me
That's pretty impressive
That is impressive to do all that
First we'll begin with Nishino's highlights
Tons of stair climbing
Please watch these scenes from the movie
This scene was in the play also
hai hai hai hai hai
Emptying out sewage from the septic tank right?
[ Shocking type of training style ]
Was there water in there?
There was actually water in there
So there was water
The weight really did put pressure on my neck area
it was like carry the water up the stairs about this far
and I understood when the director said I had to carry it up that far
Even though they said "Sorry about this"
they filmed it with no cuts
Was the director asleep or something?
[ Naptime? ]
But for the director, since it was such a pretty scene
wish there could have been a little more
Didn't want to stop shooting
Asuka-chan you did that scene for the play right?
I did
That's hard isn't it
That could actually be harder
getting the heaviness across in a play
You had to put your lower body into it more
Showing how heavy something is in a play is hard right
And why are you laughing?
[ Why the laughing? ]
She just looked at my face and started laughing
My face does that to you?
[ Face causes laughter ]
Was doing that really difficult for you?
It was hard on me for a short amount of time but
for the other members
they had to run up the stairs
and they had to do it many times over
That looked tough on them
Was it painful?
It was very painful
The steps to a shrine are so steep
Sakurai, did you do it too?
There was a lot of algae on the steps
Sure it wasn't moss?
Not algae, moss
Are algae and moss different?
Sakurai, were you underwater somehow?
[ Underwater scene? ]
Its moss right, since she won't stop saying moss
[ The moss expert ]
Moss is way different
The moss and the worms
Yes, there were worms there
The worms were falling off the steps
That's how steep the steps are, you have worms falling down
These worms were desperate
What kind of story are you telling us?
[ Worm talk ]
The worms stood out to me
Thats your memory of the stairs
I even gave them names
There were 3 big ones
Saburo
You started with Saburo?
You should start with Ichiro
Saburo was the biggest one
How big was Saburo?
No way!
[ Giant Saburo ]
The name Saburo fits
And the other names?
Jiro
Jiro, makes sense
Why'd you start from the back?
Who named them?
Marika probably came up with Saburo
I get Saburo, Jiro makes sense too
[ Tell us the name of the oldest brother worm ]
Takashi?
Was it Takashi?
I think it was Goro
Goro?  Takashi?
Which one?
[ Unsolved mystery ]
And next its Shiraishi's highlights
Constantly wearing the headgear
Basically I had to wear the protecting headgear the entire time
And even with breaks, it was a lot of trouble taking it on and off
so because of that I just left it on but
I'd get a little hungry...
For drinks I could drink using a straw
Inside the facemask right
Or they could just throw your drink on you
[ Wild way to replenish the body ]
The straw would reach inside the mask but
for food, the manager or others
prepared snack items for us
like gummies or something
I'd have the gummies above me
and in the spaces in the facemask
I'd try to drop it into my mouth
That's good, oh we have video?
A video of Matsumura feeding Shiraishi
What kind of video is this?
Here goes! Filming this?
The violent method
It didn't go in her mouth, doing it like that
Looked like she'd break her neck
Getting food in there is funny
Imagine if you put a bug in there
Or if we threw one of those worms from earlier in there
[ Reuniting with Saburo ]
Next its Nakada's and Saito Yuuri's highlights
Classmate1 and Classmate2 putting all their acting into their faces
We started out as the nameless Classmate1 and Classmate2
When we went with Asahi-chan to watch their club activities
the director instructed us to make a certain expression
kind of like "This is Naginata swordplay?  Huh?"
So I made a face that looked like "Huh!?"
But Kana-chan went for a cute looking expression
Nakada, you forced one in there right?
No, just like director said, my face was "What are we watching right now?"
She said you tried to look cute
hai
No, its still your turn
She says all that but
our roles were as her high school classmates
so they told us to go easy on the makeup
but Yuttan went with her usual amount of makeup
No, that's all wrong!
[ Battle between the nameless characters ]
Did you do that?
There was much less makeup than I'm wearing now
No, no, no, no, it was the same amount of makeup you always use
Both of you are planning out your faces right
Rhythym Naginata
You mean that look?
No its another part
That's the one
Saito Yuuri, that's your ugly look right?
[ Ugly confirmation ]
And Nakada, that looks like Himura-san's impersonation of Takayama
you put your mouth into that pose
That's Takayama's move
A little bit of duck face
and a little shoulder shrug, this is Himura-san's specialty
Cute look isn't it
Such a cute pose
Like "Are those swords~?"
This time its a double prayer for a hit
the 3 wearing tracksuits. You 3 did this one?
hai
Hoshino doesn't seem like she'd do these, but she usually does right?
Well since she always leaves an impression by flopping
[ Brings along her flopping skills ]
Let's take a look then
dozo
[ Of all the prayers for a hit this one ]
[ is the plainest one ever ]
[ plainly ]
[ painful ]
Kazumin is crazy
This is insane
This really looks painful
[ Plain ]
[ happenings ]
This is kind of crazy
don't think I can make 3 trips
[ Expections ]
[ get rid of any expectations and please watch this ]
19th single
prayer for a hit
This time, the senbatsu members
were part of the Asahinagu play or movie right
But for us three
we didn't do any of that
Its not like we didn't want to
I really would have liked to do something
But it seemed like my requests didn't reach anyone
[ Not called up ]
But you 2 have done a lot of these prayers for a hit
[ Hoshino and Akimoto are regulars ]
But to hear "You're up again"
to be a regular is like
well to not have anything seems like it would be bad
[ Already accepted her fate ]
Looking at these steps
I'm not quite sure
what we'll be doing
And with that this time
the movie Asahinagu
we're using the shrine where the Naginata club practiced
and where the main characters of Asahinagu
carried containers of water on their shoulders up the steps
they'll take on that same challenge
Buckets with water
there's 19 buckets for the 19th single
the 3 of them will have to carry them up the stairs
From the last single
the water from [Nigemizu] will be carried even higher
to make this hit bigger than the last
all of it contributing to Nogizaka making the next step
By the way I hear there are 299 steps to climb
They've had stairs to climb for previous prayers for a hit
but those were 86 steps and 139 steps
This time its the most amount of steps
and carrying heavy items back and forth
making this a difficult prayer for a hit however
Is that a lot?
That has to be a lot
How would I know, its been awhile since I've done one of these...gomen
[ Over excited ]
One bucket is about 2 liters of water
Quickly she tries to lift up one bucket of water on each side
Its heavy, but shouldn't be a problem
Following Takayama's lead
the other 2 give it a try
Kazumin-san, is something wrong here?
How do you carry this?
Eh, wait
[ Takayama, adding another bucket of water ]
You sure? That might be too much
You got 2 buckets of water in each of yours?
Just one each. Just one
I've got 2 buckets each in here
yabai
Kazumin is amazing
Kazumin is crazy
Takayama casually doubles the amount of water the others are carrying
making the heaviness of the water look like nothing
In any case I'm taking up 2 on each side
I'm only taking 1 on each side
Minami too
I can't get my body to go straight
You can do it if you let it slide down
Maybe if I move this higher up the shoulders
[ Takayama start ]
Eh, Kazumin just took off
[ Prior experience? ]
That's crazy
Once it starts swaying it won't stop
I can't move forward
[ This looks more normal ]
Look what it does to your balance
that'll make it difficult
[ Two of them struggle ]
The 2 of them are struggling to use the balance rod
and Takayama runs off so fast the cameras can't catch up
Since its been so long since Takayama did one of these, she's fired up
an unbelievable feat of superhuman strength
Her start destroys any image of hardship from the challenge
In any case please watch how Akino and Hoshino do
The difficulty of this won't show on camera!
Wait, that was close
That startled me
Once the bucket starts swaying, it won't stop
So heavy!  So plain!
And they talk less and less as they get tired
and each step gets heavier
Its steep too
And there's no change
just more time filled with suffering
Minami you ok?
I'm tired!
Isn't this crazy?
And here Takayama-san has quickly reached the goal
and she turns around to face the panicking staff
You put the water in there
Arriving at the top
she pours the water she brought up into the container
And then somehow Hoshino makes her way to the top
I'm tired!
Its not coming across on camera is it...
The hardship doesn't show!
Off it goes
falling behind Takayama
Akimoto also arrives at the top
This is pretty much
plain yet exhausting
But nobody will even know how hard
Ah, Minami said the exact same thing
There's no parts where the drama kicks in like DON!
Without a flashy waterfall, people won't get it
And then they carry the empty containers back
down the 299 steps
Aren't these balance rods heavy by themselves?
They are kind of heavy
Finally the first trip is done
and then
Look at this
You're trembling! You're trembling!
Its always Nogichuu's fault
The show always makes my leg spasm!
Each single makes my leg spasm
Maybe now they know how hard this is
But that's real hardship
I'm having spasms too! I'm serious
My leg.  Let's see it
Eh, its not doing it now, hold on...
It was trembling just a moment ago
Huh? I swear I'm not making my leg tremble on purpose
She's just trying to show some leg
[ Trying to get more exposure ]
I swear it was shaking for a moment
Temporary spasms?!
Here we were going to have the water buckets split up however
if each person carried 2 at a time
there would be 1 leftover and who would carry it
and that was how things were developing
however
because of Takayama's enthusiasm
lots of different arrangements can be made
As a result Takayama will take one trip off in standby
she'll rest on the 2nd trip and go up the 3rd time
Hoshino who doesn't want to make 3 trips
much like Takayama did last time, she'll try carrying 4 buckets up
And here Hoshino tries to take up 4 buckets
Ah!
Is your upper body spasming?
Whatever I put energy into will start to spasm...
If I don't concentrate, my body will start shaking
So everyone wants to laugh at me when this happens
this is the result of hard work, so don't even laugh
That tells everyone how heavy it is
Akimoto and Hoshino will now start the 2nd trip
however
I can't move!
Hey I can't move right now...
This has seriously come to a halt
Somebody!
Akimoto-san, this is ridiculous
[ New Akimoto Theatre ]
That's not believable
Due to the accumulated fatigue, even with the same amount of water she can't move up
You overdid it there right
Furthermore
Hoshino, who didn't want to make a 3rd trip, carries up twice the last amount
She really looks like she's hurting
They're in a situation where they can't go up without taking a lot of breaks
and then for Takayama who's waiting
I may have
made this look too easy
[ Reflecting on her over enthusiasm ]
Akimoto's pace has slowed
as for Hoshino who wanted to get this over with
Hurry it up!
Let's take a rest
I'm going!
I want to get up there quick
so the narrator will be like [Miraculously Hoshino carried up 8 liters of water]
[ Worries about the narration of her story ]
We've done too many of these hit single prayers that we can provide our own narration
I'm tired!
However here Hoshino who wants to get this over with runs into a problem
What's the matter?
yabai yabai
Wait
I'll help
I swear I didn't do that on purpose
Really!
Are you serious!
I wasn't trying to make it look good for TV
Are you serious! Do I have to start over?
For real...is this ok?
Hoshino made it to the 3rd flight of steps
but she spilled the water from both of the buckets
But that's good stuff
Does she have to do it over?
I didn't need that.  Doing that kind of thing is not like me
Did you spill the water?
Yes, I spilled it
Not on purpose right?
That wasn't on purpose!
[ Really wants to know if she did it on purpose ]
Should I bring the water up to where you are?
Yes!  Yeah!
Got it!
Probably since she hasn't gotten to do one of these episodes in awhile
she's so enthusiastic about helping us
Kazumin
How many liters?
2 liters
4 liters!
Eh? You spilled 4 liters?
Not on purpose right?
[ Still verifying it wasn't on purpose ]
And with that
savior Takayama takes off carrying the 4 liters of water
[ Remarkably running up ]
She's running
This time for Takayama
full of determination
she's participating in the prayer for a hit
Naachan
I saw her bungee jump off Macao tower up close
I really thought that was amazing
seeing her in such a bad situation in person
Ah, maybe one day I'll want to do something like that
[ Since you'll be able to do it someday ]
[ do it today ]
What she's capable of doing
up to her physical limits
make that
she's determined to go beyond her physical limits
They've made this emotional
arigatou Kazumin
Don't want to fail this one, its fine
Had to be done
That wasn't done on purpose right?
Had no choice then, had to be done
Fight!
I want to live in a neighborhood full of people like her
[ Really one of the good ones ]
[ With Takayama's kindness, both of them head for the top ]
[ Hoshino arrives at the top ]
I made it!
[ Akimoto arrives at the top ]
Made it
This could be bad
My legs are trembling again
[ The 3 of them make the last trip up to the top ]
Takayama's moving so fast
[ As usual, Takayama works to exhaustion ]
And she just went up
However right here
trying to make it look good for TV
the usual suspect moves into action
Ah! yabai!
Eh! Hold on!
[ Sorry to keep you waiting ]
Ah, that's good how she flopped without spilling anything
kowai
Faked it right?
That's wrong! That wasn't done on purpose
Even though I feel the need to capture the moment
Manatsu! You spill anything?
[ Looking out for spillage ]
And then
the 3 of them gathered up their remaining strength
and at last
[ Takayama arrives at the top ]
[ Hoshino and Akimoto arrive at the top ]
So we face this and say a prayer...
19th single
I wish for it to be a big hit
[ 19th single prayer for a hit ]
[ is a big success ]
Takayama you were amazing
Not at all
You seemed capable
I'm capable at doing the jobs that require strength
so coincidentally I could do this one
Isn't balancing difficult as well?
For me, not so much...
So then the other 2 were just acting?
No, that's not right
This time there were a couple spots that looked fake but
really none of them this time were fake
This time?
From this video
Really
You mean just this time?
Not just this time
No, there were moments
When you spun around and was like "I can't stop spinning"
That one was fake
Shiraishi, that could never happen right?
Totally faked!
[ She's heard enough ]