DON!
HAI
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
We are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And over there are Nogizaka-chan
There's a lot of them
konbanwa!
Lets get to it quickly then, Himura-san
hai
Please tell them what's on today's show
Nogizaka
predictions for the future
This will happen in the future!  2017 elections
Once again this year the AKB group
had their usual elections
Not quite a Nogizaka general elections but
the members will predict the future
an election about what will happen in the future will take place
All the members
took part in an anonymous survey
and the results will be put into a ranking and announced
what everyone thinks of particular members will be exposed
The first theme
In the future
this person
is most likely to remain single election
So that's how it is
In the future this person is most likely to remain single election
In 3rd place
With a final vote count
of 5 votes
Eh? 5 votes!?
[ Rumbling about the difference in vote count to the original event ]
This is only among the members, thats why you get a number like this
[ Keeping it internal ]
And it would be weird to get thousands of votes for this
Member of Nogizaka46
Saito Asuka-san
[ 3rd place - Saito Asuka - Congratulations! ]
omedetou
omedetou~
Unsure if this is worthy of congratulations
The reasons
She doesn't seem like the type to stay with one person forever
I can't picture her getting married
She seems like she'd hate following social norms
Those are the reasons they voted for you so what do you think?
Well then
HAHAHA!
She laughs at it
How am I supposed to feel about this?
[ Troubled by the comments ]
But you've thought about getting married like everyone else right?
Based on their family registry
if there are merits
to getting married to that person
[ The pragmatic 19 year old ]
To put it simply
When love is cultivated
the idea that marriage is considered the final goal
I don't really buy into that at all
if there's anything I can gain from getting married
then I'd understand getting married
[ Marriage is not something she dreams of ]
Put in that way, I could understand why
Looking for something to gain
So to have a bunch of money
such that you can achieve a life of stability
using marriage as a system that enables that is good then?
I'm thinking that's really good
The part about living together
there's no way I could be with someone forever
They described her perfectly then
Those 5 votes were pretty heavy
[ Precise predictions about her future ]
This person is likely to remain single.  In 2nd place
With a final vote count of
8 votes
Member of Nogizaka46
Inoue Sayuri
AHHH
[ 2nd place - Inoue Sayuri - Congratulations! ]
Lots of AHHHHs from that one
Maybe everyone agrees with that
The reasons
She routinely proclaims
"I'm not getting married"
Someone has heard you say that
She's capable of earning a living
that will allow her to stay single
Do you normally talk like that?
I do
You don't want to get married?
I don't want to get married
Why not?
There's things that I want to do
so I'd like to
do all of it and not be influenced by someone else
But
there could be a husband out there who won't stop you from doing what you desire
That's why I need
someone's who's super busy and never home
You need like a tuna fisherman-san then
[ Highly restrictive marriage requirement ]
He wouldn't come home for a year
Even without marriage, like we said earlier
being together with someone you like
what do you think of an unofficial marriage
Maybe if there were someone that loved me
There will be plenty of people
Eeee-Eeee-Eeee-Eeee
[ Her face rejects the idea ]
There will be people
In the future this person is likely to remain single elections
who will take the crown of 1st place?
With a final vote count of 12 votes
[ 1st place gets the light show ]
Member of Nogizaka46
Terada Ranze
[ 1st place - Terada Ranze - Congratulations! ]
omedetou gozaimasu
Terada-san dozo dozo
For 1st place Terada
she's presented with a queens robe and tiara
So then 1st place, why was she selected
lets check out the reasons
Her image of the ideal man is too high so no way she gets married
She won't be able to live together with someone
Doesn't seem like she trusts people very much
She's too strong willed and won't back down
Seems like she'd get upset when people don't reply to her.
no way she gets married
There's many opinions like this
Likely
since I'm weird its like
if you believe you can get with me, why don't you go ahead and try it
That sounds like an opinion from god
[ Official notice from heaven? ]
Think you can get with me, go ahead and try
We get along well and often go out to eat together
and she's like [I'm never getting married]
Is she that against it?
She's stubborn
Because she's so strong willed
when we talk about work
When I say "No, I don't think that's the reason"
its crazy
She talks back
You say one thing and she returns it x10
But with that habit, if someone doesn't respond to her
Hey, that was your opinion
[ The suspect confesses ]
Sagara-san is full of complaints right now
This survey is remarkable
But for these three
they seriously don't want to get married
I don't consider marriage to be that negative
As expected from 3rd place
[ The 2 above her are more abnormal ]
You seem disturbed by the comments of the winner
[ Thoughts on marriage are from a different world ]
And now to announce the opinions of some who didn't quite rank in
Shinuchi
So for Shinuchi
if it turned out she was already married, I wouldn't be surprised
[ That already married aura ]
Actually, I'm married with children
[ Housewife46? ]
Seems like she wouldn't get married and mess around with older men
[ pro girlfriend ]
Ah, I can kind of see that
[ Pretty much an insult ]
Shinuchi that's what they're saying but what are your ideas on marriage?
I don't think I could always stay by someone's side
Like if I got married I'd want separate bedrooms
but to say that
you'd gradually get used to it right
And also we're assuming
and this is a major assumption
this is someone that you love
Someone you love
says let's sleep in the same bed, you'd say no to that?
He's right
What are you imagining?
[ In the middle of recording, the face of a perv ]
perv right?
She's the biggest perv of all of you right now
Everyone please watch out for the perv
She's 1st place in most likely to be a perv
[ 1st place in the SKB perv elections ]
And the next theme is
In the future
most likely to have money problems elections
What kind of image is this?
In the future, this person is most likely to have money problems elections
First in 3rd place
With a final vote count
of 5 votes
Member of Nogizaka46
Noujo Ami
[ 3rd place - Noujo Ami - Congratulations! ]
What the heck?
Why is this?
Why?
When we announced the theme
Wada and Hoshino were whispering to each other
and then Wada pointed at Noujo
[ Deciding who to vote for? ]
That's amazing
I was sure she'd make it in
Why then?
She's always carrying a new bag and other things with her
She'll use up all the money she's carrying on her
In Guam
when eating breakfast
Noujo said "I'm out of money, lend me some"
Hold on, she didn't ask me for the money
She didn't ask me.
I was amazed at that one
[ Bugs the show MCs for money? ]
That would be crazy
Shitara-san I'm out of money, lend me some
I heard that story from the staff
that Nouju had used up all her money
I heard the story
I'll use any money that's in my wallet
So you're a typical spender
That's right
She's always carrying new stuff with her
You bought another one? Another one?!
You bought another?  And another?
[ The shock causes slurred speech? ]
That's how you say it?
Like Kaiya-san
You bought another one Mayo!
[ Mayo and Kaiya have nothing to do with this ]
Currently the way they spend money wastefully is shown in these rankings
In 2nd place
With a final vote count
of 6 votes
Member of Nogizaka46
Higuchi Hina
EHHHH~
2nd place - Higuchi Hina - Congratulations! Hinachima?
And the reason.
Hmm
Seems like she'll financially support a bad guy and eventually run out of money
Hina is the only person that can see his good side!
she'd say something like that and hang on to that jerk
So these are the reasons
I understand but
I am aware I could do that
like walking down the street
when I see people who don't look like they can get a meal to eat
when I see them I'm like
Hina will make you some food
[ Merciful Higuchi ]
Better not go to a big public park then
[ Lots of empty stomachs there ]
She seems like someone you can trick
How much money do you have on you today?
Today?
[ The ideal target ]
Why would you even respond "Today?"
Don't say anything
[ Light on security ]
In the future, most likely to have money problems elections
And glorious 1st place goes to
With a final vote count
of 11 votes
Member of Nogizaka46
Yoda Yuuki
[ 1st place - Yoda Yuuki - Congratulations! ]
omedetou gozaimasu
Remarkably 3rd member Yoda takes 1st
And the reasons are
Usually she wastes a lot of money
and will use up all the money she gets from her mother
Goes crazy with the internet shopping
Bought 30,000 yen worth of beauty products
and shocked me by casually saying [ I made a mistake buying this ]
So you spend all your money?
Nope
ah well
[ Denies all charges ]
To say that, she's still not aware she has a problem
Are you the type to spend all your money?
Recently I put 3 piggy banks in my room
piggy banks
The 1st one
I avoid using as much as possible
Got it
But you have no problems using money from that one
The next one
I'll only use out of pure necessity
the last resort one
The last one
is the one I can never use but
After all the money is gone from the first and second one
I know I shouldn't use the 3rd one but I'll think "I'll put in more money later"
You take from the 3rd one!?
[ All piggy banks annihilated ]
Will you casually say "I made a mistake buying that one"
I'm not casual about it, more like "What do I do?"
I already placed the order
Can't do anything when the order is complete?
They charge you for cancelled orders
Isn't cancelling still cheaper?
Of course its cheaper than paying 30,000
That's true...
Don't worry about it!
[ Ojisan spoiling Yoda ]
This is pretty well known among the 3rd members right?
hai
They got her to 1st
[ 3rd members group vote ]
Who do you borrow money from?
Before
I ran out of money for transportation
I asked Aya-chan
Aya-chan
I lent her the money
I handed her a little more than she needed
Sounds good
But she used the leftover money on something else
[ Used up ]
You're joking right!?
[ The charges keep mounting ]
She asks if its ok to borrow money, but she's not paying you back is she
On the opposite end, who here saves money?
Sayunyan
Is that so? So you save?
I've saved up a lot
Is there something you're saving for in the future
The future
is what I'm saving for
Since you'll be living alone
[ Most likely not to get married 2nd place ]
I'd really like to marry an ATM
[ Her ideal man is an ATM ]
She says that often
But you just said you never wanted to get married!
[ Jealous of the ATM ]
That's right
In the future
most likely to hang on to a jerk elections
Its been an election of some pretty awful things
In the future she's likely to hang on to a jerk elections
Here are the announcements from 3rd place
With a final vote count
of 5 votes
Member of Nogizaka46
Ito Karin
[ 3rd place - Ito Karin - Congratulations! ]
omedetou gozaimasu
Ito Karin
The reasons
Karin follows through with everything and is likely to spoil the guy she's with
That's why
She's a genius at spoiling people
Causes people to over rely on her
Its all just opinions like these
You let her do everything
Are you aware of this?
I am aware of it
This woman is quite a catch
[ From a male perspective this is desirable ]
And on this show
she plans out the travel and sets up the parties
I see what they mean
For girls like this
in the end where will they find their own happiness?
[ A lost child throughout life ]
You'll lose a sense of self worth and later wonder what happened
The other day I fried up some tempura
we were having an udon party
And later we talked about tempura
What was the occassion?
For Team Watermelon
You had tempura at a udon party
That time
she made
the tempura for us
Cooked it for you right
No sleeves
She was sleeveless
For some reason she dressed up for this party
And the frying oil was splattering
I told her watch out for the oil
She said she was fine, but she really burned herself
[ You should wear sleeves when deep frying ]
That's dangerous
It was more important to me to serve them hot food
You're just like a mother. Go ahead and eat
[ The embodiment of motherhood ]
Such a good girl
I hope she leads a happy life, but some jerk is going to advantage of her right
Even if he was originally a good person
after getting married I'd do anything for him
Likely in the future
I'll get married to someone thats a self-proclaimed guitarist
[ Scooped up by a bad man ]
I get that, doesn't sound like a good guy
He'll have no accomplishments
[ The type of guy who boasts of his accomplishments ]
When he speaks of his dreams, I'll want to cheer him on
its fine I'll make money for the both of us
[ Woman of convenience ]
Such a good woman
After marriage there are husbands
that want their wives to put on their socks for them
There's people like this
I don't want to do that if I'm making the income
But the guitarist, he'll play the guitar for you
[ Needs to save his hands for the guitar ]
That's when you have to get the socks on him
[ The theory of why guitarists don't put on their own socks ]
I'm a guitarist, I can't put on my own socks
Who is thought of as a pushover
In 2nd place
With a final vote count
of 6 votes
Member of Nogizaka46
Higuchi Hina
[ 2nd place - Higuchi Hina - Congratulations! ]
She made it in
She once said she likes guys who wear those biker gang jackets
Seems like she'd let her man go to a cabaret club even if he comes home late
ah hai hai
Seems like she'd introduce her jerk boyfriend by saying [He's such a man's man right?]
Those manly types are hard to figure out right
These opinions make it sound like
you're into the bad boys
I'm not talking about real delinquents
Those looks but someone that gets things done
someone with a manly presence
Someone that makes you ask "Wait, is this guy for real"
someone you can't figure out from one glance
There you go
Collecting trash?
[ A hoarder? ]
She said at first glance, not a trash collector
At first glance
I will make sure that he's not just some jerk
But if he's like "I'm pursuing my dreams"
and its not working out right now but
I promise to bring you happiness later
Would you please support me?
Then he whips out the guitar
[ The guy that won't put on his own socks enters ]
Before announcing 1st place
we'll announce some opinions about those who didn't rank in
Hoshino
Hoshino?
People saying AHHH
Seems like she'd fall for dangerous looking types
Eh? That's not true
Rough and rugged types
Are you kind of into delinquent types?
Nope, not at all but
I do think I could be fooled by one of them
[ Declares she's easily fooled ]
You think you could be fooled?
Its like Misa
she's worried about my future
and wants to meet my possible marriage partners
You'd do that for her like her mother?
If she were to graduate
and finds someone she wants to marry
I told her I want to meet him
You want to make sure he's legit
That is important
[ Attention ]
Seems like you lack confidence if you think you can be fooled
And why is Asuka-chan laughing so much?
gomennasai
I was thinking of how you said [Misa ga misadameru]
[ Noticed a word pun, dies laughing ]
You're laughing because I said [Misa ga misadameru]
What part of that is so funny?
We need a "Misa confirms he's legit!" segment
What kind of segment is that?
domo! Hey everyone its Misa
[ A show where Misa judges if your date is a loser ]
I'll confirm the best 3 possible husbands are legit
Likely to fall for a jerk elections
And glorious 1st place goes to
With a final vote count
of 8 votes
Member of Nogizaka46
Akimoto Manatsu
[ 1st place - Akimoto Manatsu - Congratulations! ]
yada~
omedetou gozaimasu
You know you wanted to wear this
I did want to wear it
You did it. Congratulations
Does it fit?
[ Huge head entertainment begins ]
And the reason
Seems like she'd put too much into a good for nothing jerk
This sounds like the same thing
Could you hold on a second...
[ The tiara screams for help ]
Move it a little forward
Yes, like that
[ Tiara trying to escape? ]
You've outdone yourself
[ The always reliable master performance ]
She's said that she likes bad boys
You've said that?
Saying I like them
its more like I want to do something to help them
For perfect people, there's nothing worth doing for them
So a bad person that is someone worth saving
I'll fall for them
She's too nice to whoever it is
Ah, got it
No matter how many times he fails
she'll probably say "Can't do anything about that" and allow it
It really is a bunch of opinions like this
Everyone appears to agree
Even if he makes the same mistake again
if he just apologizes, I'll be like "its ok"
Ito Karin, Higuchi, Akimoto
these ladies are awesome
[ Well received by men, top 3 ]
Good traits from a male point of view
Wakatsuki and Sakurai, they did the Memories of Matsuko play
aren't they just like the main character?
I saw it
I went to see it twice
I really sympathized with that character
Did it make you want to go up on stage?
[ Invades the play out of sympathy? ]
That's it!  That's it!
The real Matsuko
Ah, we're ok?
They're telling me that's enough for today
Only had the bad themes today
All insults, but they wanted to do this right
At the end we have a really good theme
What's last?
Last?
What's left?
Even stuck on an uninhabited island, seems like she'd survive elections
[ That's not a compliment either ]
I'm not sure if that's a compliment or insult
Just announce 1st for this one
Just 1st place?
Even if stranded on an uninhabited island she'd likely survive elections
In 1st place
With a final vote count of 8 votes
Member of Nogizaka46
Wakatsuki Yumi
[ 1st place - Wakatsuki Yumi - Congratulations! ]
Wakatsuki
It says Wakatsuki
omedetou gozaimasu
And the reasons
Seems like she could make something to escape
[ This woman never gives up ]
Seems like she'd make something
Just give her a bunch of chopsticks and she'll build something
[ Escapes just by using Hashi-kun ]
I've really
never seen her eat anything
I see. She can survive if she doesn't eat then
She can go hungry for a long time
Even though she has the chopsticks she won't eat
[ The chopsticks are her partner ]
Retimed By Nishinomaru ^.^
Credits to Subber GEES