Nogizaka46 Nationwide Summer Tour 2017
Whether backstage or out in public, these things took place
A Nogizaka46 tradition, the summer nationwide tour
on todays show we'll look back on the videos the members took behind the scenes
Before moving onto the 2nd half
first we'll playback some images from the tour
A special feature of this years tour
Nogizaka Theatre
That's remarkable
Nogizaka songs were completely rearranged and performed
They changed it?
They really changed it, these are brand new songs
The dancing is different
They went to a lot of trouble
Changed how they sing it
To change it this much
how do you remember all that
The songs were made into different genres
And what happened backstage at the Osaka show
first we'll check out Saito Yuuri's video
Somewhat recently
#You may use this pic to post "on a date with the girlfriend now"
getting a picture for that hashtag became popular
when I thought of members I'd like to use for that
who I'd want to take a picture of
it would be a girl who normally doesn't do that stuff
someone who'd hate it and be embarassed by it
someone who would be irresistible
Asuka-chan
I got a video of her
[ #You may use this pic to post "on a date with the girlfriend now" ]
Asuka!
okaeri
Hold on you're getting out of focus
Where are you going now?
To get changed
Hey, can Yuuri come with you?
Get changed
Lets go together
Sure
This conversation is awesome
So you know
those hashtags they use
With Asuka, you can use this to post on a date with the girlfriend now
Reach out with your hands!
Hate it!
Hey, its Yuuri, here's my hand
here
Since they turned on the lights for us
hashtag!
I haven't taken it yet
Pay me! Pay me!
I'll give you 100 yen
#You can use this to post "On a date with Asuka now"
As if...baka!
[ Got embarassed watching it ]
embarassing right
That's pretty good
Supposed to look like holding hands with the boyfriend
wrong! wrong! wrong!
That's not it
That's what it looked like
wrong..wrong..wrong
You said I could use it, so I will
[ Permission granted ]
Its free to use right
It showed how strongly I wanted to change clothes
You started undressing in that
It was like "Take it off! Take it off!"
[ Anticipating a wardrobe malfunction ]
On to the next one
hai
Yamashita
This is "Captain, about my name..."
hai
captain, about my name
What's this one about?
The 3rd members, even as MCs
have gotten more chances to talk with the senpais on stage
And when Sakurai-san as MC turns it over to me
she pretty much has mispronounced my name since the 1st Sendai concert
[ blundering captain ]
Its Yamashita Mizuki of course
That's right, its the Mizuki part that gets mispronounced
and I have video evidence
You have evidence?
I do
Lets take a look then
[ Captain, its Mizuki not Mitsuki ]
Now then lets hear the stories in order
starting with the 3rd members, Mitsuki
hai
Mitsuki?
Anytime you want to call out to the 3rd members, we'll go eat with you
By the way Mitsuki, which side are you with?
ah, now I get it
Well the kanji for her name are utsukushii and tsuki
And then it becomes Mizuki
To mess up someone's name is the worst thing you could do
You sure? I would think murdering someone is worse
[ comparing the 2 is abnormal ]
And this time Wakatsuki
introduced something new
With Sakurai calling her Mitsuki, after that
some of us started calling her Mitsuki
while MC'ing
and so I thought
I'll form a random new unit
[ Show of power against the establishment? ]
I formed a random new unit
The Wakasama unit
Wakasama unit
Formed it during the nationwide tour
Who's in it?
The person in charge of the spoon
the fork
and the knife
[ Limited to cutlery ]
To go with your chopstick character
What do you mean in charge of the spoon?
They do spoon gags?
That's right
eh? You're in the unit?
Yes, I'm in charge of the spoon
In charge of the spoon?
I'm the spoon person
As the spoon person, what's your catchphrase?
I say "I'll scoop all of your hearts"
[ With a spoon only ]
spoon is a good one
Who does the fork?
Sakaguchi Tamami does that
What's her phrase?
Something like "I'll pierce your heart"
ah, got it
So all heart related
[ Already out of ideas? ]
What's left? Fork, spoon....knife?
Got someone for that?
We have a knife person
Who?
Umezawa Minami is in charge of the knife
But for the knife...currently the catchphrase
I'm gonna cut your face
[ The lethal weapon idol? ]
Don't have a catchprase yet for her
But won't you keep adding
Anything else and
you'll lose the connection to the chopsticks
And with more members then what would you say
[ Claims we'll lose the original ]
So why the unit?
At like the live shows
the Sayuringo unit
they made their own video as a unit
and before the show starts
the people who arrived early and are waiting for the show to start
While the audience waits
their self made video
plays to the audience
So you want to do something like that
I'm thinking of doing something similar
A unit with 1st and 3rd members
within the entire group didn't exist
I thought it would be good to make one
Himura-san, you could be the soup spoon
I could say "Eat your fried rice"
[ The proper usage of a soup spoon ]
So Himura-san will join us as the soup spoon
eh? What happened to Himura-san as White Rice-sama?
Sorry and I even blurted out fried rice just now
Don't fry the rice
[ Well said ]
She's saying don't fry it
Up last its the Nagoya show
before looking backstage, here's what everyone saw
Taking place in the middle of the show
Featuring the members in the play and movie versions of Asahinagu
the pole sword martial arts demonstration
Now then here's what it looked like
That's pretty cool
Amazing
So many things that could go wrong
You're right, they could drop it
That was really amazing
What happened backstage at the Nagoya show?
First we have 3rd member Nakamura's surprise video
During the tour
Mukai Hazuki
she had a birthday coming
birthday
And thats why you surprised her?
hai
because of that
all the 3rd members celebrated together
sounds good
Lets take a look then
[ Birthday surprise ]
Where's this camera at? What's happening
They even got a hidden camera
That's crazy, they all let Mukai have it
omedetou!
What did they hit her with?
[ Watch the nose ]
Good one!
That's a good one
You showed no mercy there
What did you get hit with? What was that?
It was a cream puff
That was a cream puff?
After the surprise, that came so quick
Mukai had no idea what hit her
Very good
Surprised then?
Yes, it surprised me
I promised I'd hang out in her room
Mizuki invited me over since she was alone
and I went over
and everyone was there
Was your birthday coming or was that your birthday?
That was my birthday
They made it memorable didn't they
Were you happy?
I was happy
That type of stuff rarely happens
Can't even tell who it is
That's the best
That's...pretty funny
It even matches her Tshirt
Looks like an american cartoon character
funny one
Good comrades right?
Happy to be with them
hai!
What's wrong?
My video hasn't played but
actually I also received a surprise celebration
from Inumen
And seriously our video
is photogenic
[ forced laughter ]
What was the occassion?
At that time I was coming in a few days early
I had a job to do and everyone else would come later
and I was at a hotel
And I was supposed to go alone but went with Sakurai
and when Sakurai and I got back to the hotel
and when I said bye bye to Sakurai
she went into my hotel room without saying a word
[ bad with surprises ]
Even though she had her own room
I was like eh? eh? eh? eh?
everyone shouted out "omedetou"
And when I went in the room
there were balloons and snacks
everything was decorated so beautifully
I have the video
And here is that video
omedetou
ome ome!
First time experiencing something like this!
sugoi kawaii!
Macchun put it on...put it on
I'm so happy! Thanks everybody!
hai....cheese
arigatou
omedetou!
I'm so happy! arigatou
Actually they got me with the cream puff 4 years ago
[ A Nogizaka tradition? ]
Its become a tradition then
They did that for me on tour
Since I became an adult, mine was the photogenic version
Tiramisu too
What was that? Did you say something?
We also had
a tiramisu face party
[ Related story? ]
This seems off topic, up to this point its been surprises
What's a tiramisu face party?
Is this a party where people have a face that looks like tiramisu
[ Get together of people with Mascarpone faces? ]
No, we were working and...who's room was it?
It was Maiyan's room
Her birthday was coming up
You did that to Shiraishi?
But in the end it was Ami that got covered in tiramisu
[ Queen of getting hit in the face with tiramisu ]
Why?
Was this your birthday?
No, it wasn't my birthday
There was no reason for it but
Why get hit in the face with tiramisu?
It was supposed to be Maiyan but
before I knew it I became the target
[ Lay back and see what happens ]
And next
Shinuchi's video from the dressing room
In the dressing room before a live show
some girls like to rest, everyone does their own thing
When I sat down
I could hear Misora Hibari-san
You heard Misora Hibari-san
She's the legendary singer
Misora Hibari-san
When I got up and looked
Noujo and Chii-chan
they were
having some kind of recital
The 2 gang leaders of the dressing room
Yes, they were doing it
I have a video of this
[ Noujo & Chiharu's Misora Hibari ]
[ Aisansan/Misora Hibari ]
[ That's it? ]
That was Aisansan
Its become popular
Like who can do it the best
impersonation right?
In the dressing room we're waiting
and have some free time
And we're not the type of people to sleep
so sing
[ Pair of troublemakers ]
We prefer to sing so
Pretty much don't care do you?
[ Looking to fully enjoy their off time ]
We enjoy impersonating her
And there's still more
Next we're backstage with Kawago at the Jingu show
The Jingu show
Shitara-san was there...Bananaman-san was there
[ Referring to Himura as Himuko to the very end? ]
Nogizaka thinks of him as Himura-san right
The live show went in order from 3rd, 2nd, 1st members
and with the 1st members watching the 3rd and 2nd members perform
it brought out the competitive spirit in us
and just like that the 1st members started forming a huddle
So that happens?
First time
Good...I'd like to see this one
[ The originals just before showtime at Jingu ]
[ Jingu live DAY1 ]
The show the 3rd and 2nd members put on
practically has nothing to do with us
Let's go out there and put on a good show!!
They are fired up
1st 1st 1st 1st 1st 1st 1st 1st
Yesterday the 1st members were definitely the best
WOOOOOOOO~
For today as well
Let's go out there and put on a good show!
YAYYYYY!
WOOOOOO~
All the 1st members. Lets go out there and knock them out!!
YAYYYYY!
Somebody wasn't wearing a shoe
1st 1st 1st 1st 1st 1st 1st 1st
That's good
Pretty inspirational
Like a spontaneous pep rally
Of course in some way or other the 1st members feel they need to lead the group
And nobody said anything
we naturally gathered around like that
You could feel that youthful exuberance
Thats true
It was fun
That's youth
Must be nice
Good stuff
[ sinking in ]
And next its Matsumura's shocking video
Idols are just so cute right
and I really love girls
Eh, what does that mean?
[ Confused ojisan ]
No its pure
Since I love cute...that equals liking girls
huh? What does that mean?
[ Adding more confusion? ]
In any case I like girls
You like looking at cute girls then
Since I like looking at cute girls
being in this group brings me great happiness
but there's one person
Someone not cute?
There's a certain person
Well I've got a picture
Seriously?
Are you kidding me?
You've got an obasan in the group
[ Masquerading as a member? ]
No way!
Who is that person? Who is that?
That's Mukai Hazuki
eh?
That's Mukai?
That's right
Mukai, what happened? You look old
What's going on?
And she looks like this in the dressing room for like 1 or 2 hours
For me its really
And we get to do all kinds of events
and I always look forward to seeing various other idols without their makeup
But this is the worst I've ever seen!
[ Told something cruel ]
I've really never seen anything like this
Its like mom before going to bed
[ Tired from housework? ]
What kind of face is she making here?
You don't have straight hair then?
My hair really wants to curl
if I go to bed without drying it
It turns out like this
So Hazuki
she has a really cute face but she has to live with this hair
so its the hair
Its rare to get your hair looking good, so that's why you like the sopping wet look
Since you want to look your best, that's why you come out all wet right
And the glasses are a bit huge as well
But the more I look at this picture, she gets prettier and prettier
The face is cute
She comes across as a foreigner like Angela Aki-san
Someone who looks like they'd eat at IKINARI STEAK
or Beef Mileage
Someone that saves up for Beef Mileage
And it would appear Mukai's clothing is also pretty messed up
She'll get on a train wearing her gym clothes with her name covered up with duct tape
To wear this, some people like it natural and simple
Are those your shorts from gym class?
and you covered your name with duct tape?
That's...
its like why are you dressed like a failing comedian?
She also wears a blue hawaiian shirt
[ Her look is always changing ]
So hold on
sorry about this but do we have a picture of that one
I have a picture..its insane
And here is that photo
as far as the show goes
we'd love to keep her as is but
I totally understand what she's going through
when I first joined the group
I wore clothes I woke up in
You wore pajamas
I wore pajamas and got ranked by everybody as worst dressed
I was the worst dressed
But now you've seen just how cute I am right
[ Driving home a point ]
So then you'd have good advice for her
I'm thinking I'd like to produce Hazuki-chan
I talk to Maiyan a lot about this in the back
Since she worked so hard
to get into Nogizaka
we're thinking we'd like her to look cute all the time
I see then
I think that's a good idea
But this innocent look is cute too
Think of something you'd like to try
[ Perhaps we'll turn this into a Mukai episode ]
Think of ideas