Continuing on from last week, in order to check their reactions to certain dating situations
the answers the members wrote on their mock test
will be assigned a score by a dating and communications expert
and we'll be able to analyze the hidden dating powers within the members
Continuing on with question 3
On the next day off work, its the first date with the guy you're interested in
while talking on the phone he'll ask "What would you like to do?"
How would you answer?
We'll start with 3rd member Sakaguchi Tamami's answer
For this question Himura will pretend to be the boyfriend
ah moshi moshi
moshi moshi
For our upcoming date, what would you like to do?
I want to look at clothes
Clothes?....Sounds good
More specifically
the stores Tamami has never been able to go to
I want to go see really expensive clothes
You want to look at expensive clothes?
seriously?
Why? Why is this?
And these clothes that Tamami can't afford to buy
could I beg you to buy them?
[ Unabashed begging ]
So that's why
She really got me that time
Did that work on you?
I really would fall for that one
[ Himura takedown ]
What were you aiming for?
Tamami's ideal person
I believe the ideal person would do those things for me
[ Prerequisite - must be somebody that buys her stuff ]
So a rich guy? That's all you're looking for
Someone with a stable income
[ Fixed income or higher ]
About how expensive are these clothes? Luxury brand clothing stores?
About 15,000 yen
Ahhh~
Himura-san don't say "Ahhh" to that
[ He'll buy it ]
The direct begging approach, what will Sakaguchi's score be?
2 points
Thought that might happen, must be some reasons for that
You cannot ask him to buy expensive items on your 1st date!
He'll think you're scamming him
[ Sakaguchi the Scammer ]
He would honestly think that
So what if there was someone you really liked but had no money
compared to someone super rich that you weren't really into
you'd go with the rich guy?
And you really like him but he uses vinyl tape as a belt
[ Dirt poor ]
But he has a wonderful personality
I want someone with a stable income
So you would still pick the rich guy?
mmm...hai
[ decisive answer ]
Ozono is shaking her head, do you feel the same way?
Definitely would not like that
I'd go with the person I loved
money isn't an issue right
But he'd always be like "They're giving out free food...let's go!"
[ Jerk boyfriend enters ]
And next its 3rd member Kubo Shiori's first date plan
ah.......moshi moshi
moshi moshi
So about our upcoming date, what would you like to do?
Himura-kun, do you prefer being indoors or outdoors ?
ah well its kind of cold, so I'd prefer indoors
Then how about a movie or a cafe or something?
ahh, a movie or a cafe...
ok, I got it
So which one?
Ah, I'm supposed to answer
[ Decide now ]
How about a movie then?
ah, got it
By the way, if I had preferred being outdoors, what would you do?
I'm not really into going outdoors, I'd let Himura-kun decide that one
ahh is that so
How about a movie then?
Guess she doesn't want to talk about the outdoors
[ Apparent indoor type ]
But you made it a point to ask him about it
Because I'd want to respect his opinion as much as possible
if asked that question "What would you like to do?"
Leaving all the decision making to me won't advance the conversation
I'm giving him choices
What if he's pushing really hard for like an intense workout type of outdoor activity?
If that happens, I'd agree to do it
Really?
He's like "I'm ready to go mountain climbing!"
[ The kind of guy you've never encountered before ]
The I'll go along with him approach, Kubo's score is
7 points
That scored unexpectedly high
hai
Leaving the options up to him
shows how considerate a person you are
Is that so?
But if you overdo it and don't push any of the activities
he'll think "She's not really interested in this date" so you need to be careful
Ah of course, you have to say a little bit
But if he's like, I hear what you're saying
How about we go our separate ways and fall asleep?
[ Crappy plan ]
If he's asking for that
I'm thinking he must be tired
Fine how about you go to Kyushu and I'll go to Hokkaido?
[ That's just solo travel ]
So'd you say ok to something extreme like that
Well if there's something he wants to eat from Kyushu but he doesn't want to abandon going to Hokkaido
[ "Agreeing to too much" woman ]
That's why I can never go on dates
[ Not suited for dating ]
And next its 3rd member Umezawa's 1st date plan
ah moshi moshi
moshi moshi
About our upcoming date
What would you like to do?
I'd like to go on a drive
A drive sounds nice
And then I'd want to get something good to eat
Want something good huh
But
really anything is ok as long as you keep me entertained
Keep you entertained?
Well I'll do my best!
Got it
That last part puts some big pressure on you
[ Better keep her entertained ]
But those are true feelings right?
That's right. Because actually
I'd want him to decide everything
but at a minimum I said go an a drive and get a good dinner
The restaurant and such
I'd like for him to decide all of that
And at the end, just a little bit
I'd like to put him in his place...a step lower than me
[ Umezawa..always above you ]
So that's the goal
But its just the 1st date
You're at the same level but "Anything is ok as long as you keep me entertained"
[ Queen Umezawa ]
There's some joking around in there
since we're both nervous
Kind of a "just kidding" then right
The "looking down on you" approach, Umezawa's score is
2 points
That was bound to happen
Its just the 1st date, you've put yourself too far above him
Well, she said so herself
Saying something like  "as long as you keep me entertained"
that's going to put a heavy burden on him
He might starting thinking "Who does she think she is?"
Somebody that could put up with all that would be good I think
But even without saying that out loud
he will be thinking "I have to keep her entertained" so you don't need to say it
So you'd like someone you could talk to like that?
I'm not looking for somebody that's perfect but
I want him to be strong
[ You will be a strong man ]
That's basically looking down on him
that's pretty frightful
If those are the features you're looking for, it's going to be hard to approach you
That would make most people nervous
And they have to have a car
That's a given
and the delicious food, sounds like maybe she won't eat anything low priced
And the "Is she enjoying this date? part
You better practice doing some magic tricks or something
[ Push yourself to learn some magic ]
And next its question 4
Its the long awaited 1st date
You're supposed to meet up at 10am in Shibuya
How will you react when you find each other?
For this question as well, Himura will play the role of boyfriend
First, she's the youngest, its Iwamoto Renka's answer
Where in Shibuya should you meet?
How about in front of Hachiko?
In front of Hachiko it is
Whoa! That's Himura!  Himura is standing in front of Hachiko!
[ Himura spotted ]
ah that's Himura
Aren't you Himura?
I am not Himura
Why did you come to Shibuya today?
[ Worst kind of teasing ]
People rip him with that line all the time
I'll be at a golf course and I'll get
YOU! Why did you come to the golf course?
To play golf!
I'm playing golf!
So then ready...
start
ah looking forward to this
JAAN!
Got here right at 10am! That's amazing right!
Right on the mark!
wah sugoi
What? Why did Himura-kun get here so early?
No really, I only got here 5 minutes earlier
You got here early because you like Renka so much, am I right?
Not sure about that
Love you!
arigatou
kawaii~
What's up with all that cuteness!
So that one will get you won't it
That was incredible
That was mega mega cute
From your entrance JAAN
"JAAN" she says
Seeing something like that from a couple in front of Hachiko would make me chuckle
[ Love bird middle schoolers ]
So the JAAN was for impact?
JAAN. For arriving right at 10am
Ah, so that was for arriving on time
Are you feeling embarassed now for doing that?
This part is also very cute
The part after that was also good
What? Why are you here early? Looking forward to this date aren't you?
And finally you said "love you"
For this date, you already reached the climax
[ The peak of their encounter ]
Can't really top that
Maybe you didn't raise your excitement for this? Is this how you normally are?
If its someone I love
because I love them
That's how you are around them
Before we start dating
since it might just be one sided love
I wouldn't say something like that
That's true, once you're dating you can let it all out
Should be a high score right?
No way I could pull that off!
If I tried something like that, it would be bad
She can do that because she's young
She can do it because she's young
If I tried that, I'd get called a needy woman
Matsumura I think could get away with that
Now then, here is Matsumura attempting Iwamoto's date meetup
start
JAAN!
I'm right on time! Amazing right!
Hey Himura-kun, why'd you get here so early?
I kind of got here early...sorry about that
I know why!
You like me so much, you had to get here early. Am I right?
I love you!
But when Matsumura does it
When Matsumura does it, it leaves kind of a good feeling with you
[ Character match ]
I want a JAAN championships
[ Championships scheduled? ]
Points
Hers was really cute
Should be a good score right?
JAAN!
The studio fell in love with Iwamoto and her score is...
3 points
ehh~
What's up with sensei? She's grading her too hard
That's all wrong. That felt like a 10 to me
Himura and everyone felt that could be a 10
According to sensei
Please do not forget that this is a first date
You're being too forward with your feelings before the date has even started
When you come at him with these strong feelings
you risk him sensing danger and pulling back. Please be careful
Of course they want you to remain calm
its true we were in the right mood for yours but
That JAAN! would be like
eh? eh? eh?
[ The cool boyfriend ]
Why'd you get here so early!
But this is the time I normally arrive
[ Calm ]
But I love you!
whoa...whoaaaa...
[ Different levels of enthusiasm couple ]
Talking like that would be messed up
It is the 1st date
Its like since I don't know anything about adult dating
that's the only thing that popped in my head
That's ok!
But I liked the JAAN part
Next is 3rd member Sato Kaede's date meetup
WAH!
WHOA!
WHOA~
OH! what gives?
Did I startle you?
Yes you did
You really surprised me just now
Sorry to keep you waiting
Let's go
Well lets go then
You wanted to startle him?
Talking just 1-on-1 isn't something I'm great at
The WAH!
starting with that kind of mood
I'm thinking everything afterwards will go well
The simple surprise approach. Sato's score is...
7 points
Would have liked to have seen more
Seems cute
Playing a prank like that will calm down the intense date atmosphere
Gives off the image that everyday is full of fun
I also like this type of stuff
I also do it
But in my case I'm more forceful with it
I'm looking to cause physical damage
[ Different meaning ]
When Shitara does that its not startling
it just hurts
WAH! Just like that
That hurts!
So I should put more strength into it?
I should put more strength into it?
If I push stronger...
You want to try that again? Sure go ahead
Why do I have to?
What are we learning right now?
Now then the Shitara inspired version
Sato's date meetup
start
WAH!
It hurts!
That's much better
[ Boyfriend, injured ]
That freaking hurts
There's no protection there
That's even where they aim in boxing
[ Focused on dealing damage ]
But finding a girl that does that, its pretty cute
Not cute at all! Just scary
Makes me think "What the hell was that for!"
And next its meeting Shiraishi for a date
start
ah I think I got here a little too early
ah
Huh?
What? She's not here
Thanks for waiting
I got here a little too early so I bought us some coffee
Are you good with cafe latte?
Yes, I'm good with cafe lattes
So, lets go
Sure lets go. Go! Go!
That was good
That was really cute however due to
the trauma from Sato's just now
When the time came, I thought I was about to get hit again
[ Fearing a rear attack ]
You were scared right?
Is this girl about to hit me again!?
[ Sato's shadow ]
So how was it? She bought coffee for you
kawaii kawaii kawaii
But that was good waiting for him hidden from view
But for the boyfriend not to see you back there waiting its almost a waste
But what if the boyfriend was like
he was a good guy and in the same way
bought some coffee for you and both of you are hidden and waiting
you'd never meet up. What then?
[ Double ambush ]
It got a good response in studio
Shiraishi's score is...
9 points
According to sensei, running up to him from a spot not too far away
this move
its a gesture that will make men kyun the most
From not too far away right
And with just a natural gesture such as this
it says how much she's looking forward to the date
And it shows just the perfect amount of cuteness
understood
The coffee is also a thoughtful move and leaves a good impression
perfect then
It would be the worst if he was hidden and came up to you from behind
Hey, what are you doing?
I was planning to run up to you
[ Wants to show the run up ]
And next its meeting Shinuchi for a date
start
I'm so late
Where could Himura-kun be?
OY!
Himura-kun!
Sorry I'm so late
Are you mad?
I'm not mad
Lets go then
ah, lets go
sorry
What was that? So that reenactment
what was that a performance of?
[ Please explain ]
Don't women look really cute when they're searching for something?
We didn't see enough looking around on that one
I'm thinking the part where you're looking around everywhere
and when you see him "Ah!" that facial expression is just so cute
Got it. If you'd do that again with emphasis on the looking around
Now then, its the retry with a heavy amount of looking around
I'm a bit late for this
Where could Himura-kun be?
I wonder if he's upset with me
Where is he?
Look around...look around
Keep looking Shinuchi
Looking around is cute right? Keep looking
Look harder
You should look around even more
You haven't found your boyfriend, keep looking
You have to keep looking around until you find him
[ The lonely looking all around woman ]
Where is he?
Himura-kun
Himura-san hasn't noticed you at all
Better keep looking
Pure coincidence that he hasn't spotted you
You should get a little closer and keep looking
Its pointless if he doesn't notice you
Keep looking. Did they just cross paths?
[ Crossing paths but not recognizing each other couple ]
You have to look around in a way that he'll find you
Keep looking around
ah little closer
Where could he be?
Where is he?
[ The man who doesn't notice things ]
Notice her. You have to notice her
Where could he be?
Where is he?
Himura-san she's right there
Guess I'll just go home
[ Loneliest BBA in the world ]
Why didn't you notice her?
The reenactment ends in failure, Shinuchi's score is...
7 points
Pretty high right?
According to sensei, looking around restlessly like you're looking for a lost dog
that will make men kyun
When you show him that facial expression of finally finding him
"She was looking for me!"
those kinds of happy feelings will come to him
Even though I wasn't able to meet him
Really sorry about that
sorry about Himura-san not noticing you
[ Insensitive bastard ]
And who will be picked as the dating master?
Mukai gomen
Right now Mukai is praying to be picked, but I don't think Mukai has any chance
[ It won't be you ]
Mukai was the only one praying just now
Will Himura-san pick out Mukai I wonder
I guess we don't really know
She's praying....
You're really getting good at that
[ Genuine ]
She wants that omelet rice
[ Praying for omelet rice? ]
Now then who will Himura pick as the dating master
Iwamoto!
[ Dating master - Iwamoto Renka ]
When you did that JAAN for us
the mood in the entire studio became like WAH
arigatou gozaimasu
So keep doing that for your entire life
[ JAAN Iwamoto ]
Whatever happens
JAAN...JAAN
[ 2017.11.08 @Tokyo Dome ]
Nogizaka46 their 1st Tokyo Dome concert
And what they performed as their double encore
The song picked for the 2 members graduating
[Kikkake]
Ito Marika along with Nakamoto Himeka
on their final stage with their final song
coming out together with the members, giving it all they have
and then.....her last message
The future of Marika and of Nogizaka-chan
will become something wonderful thats filled with intense feelings
I truly believe that
From this point everything about Nogizaka
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
Thanks for taking care of me these 6 years
arigatou gozaimashita
[ Final Live - After the show ]
After the live show
Nakamoto's last appearance with Bananaman, they've come to her to give encouragement
It'll be lonely without you
really?
No really. arigatou
On this show
every time both of you would call me Hime-tan
that made me so incredibly happy
First of all Himetan is something I've always wanted to say
For you
I'm so happy
I'll pass this on to Himura-san, and he'll give it to Hime-tan
[ Bad positioning ]
Now, I'll take it from here
[ Last Janga Janga pose ]
So then
Congratulations on your graduation!
omedetou!
otsukaresama
For real!
arigatou gozaimashita
So we have a present from the both of us
Are you sure?
Of course, this is for Hime-tan
Take a look inside
May I?
Then I'll open it
Its sort of heavy
It might make you a little sad
What could it be? AH! There it is!
[ When you think of Nakamoto, you think meatballs ]
Hime-tan's hidden meatballs
[ Brought back the catchphrase ]
There's so many in here
I'm getting a lot here!
arigatou gozaimasu
But really thanks! Keep working hard! From this point forward
arigatou
From now on Nogizaka-chan, yoroshiku onegaishimasu
You're calling them Nogizaka-chan at the end, it was great during the show too
arigatou gozaimasu
otsukaresamadeshita
arigatou gozaimashita
Sorry about all these meatballs...
I'll eat them all
You still like meatballs?
Who me?
Don't like them so much do you...
When eating rice, I still think of meatballs
Really? I see
You really don't like meatballs do you
Since you're an adult now
As an adult, its no longer proper to say you like meatballs
Nakamoto, congratulations on your graduation