DON!
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
we are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And over there are Nogizaka-chan
New school term~
Now then lets quickly get into it
Himura-san please tell them whats on the show today
Here it goes
My kid is really good Grand Prix....3rd member edition
This would be the 3rd member version
This has been kept a secret from the 3rd members
and their families filled out a secret survey
we'll shed some light on some still unknown parts of their personalities
Now here is what we have first
Highly reccommended photos of our daughter photo studio
The pictures and videos of their daughters they want shown on TV
the parents have picked some out for us
[ Ito Riria - Scouted by a modeling agency at age 3 ]
[ Ito Riria with her beloved pet bunny Fuu-chan ]
Thats mega mega cute
[ Iwamoto Renka age 1 - The 100 point smile ]
[ Iwamoto age 3 - Posing in the backyard ]
[ Iwamoto age 10 - practicing hip hop dancing ]
ohh sugoi sugoi
Did it freeze?
Incredible
[ Umezawa surrounded by her favorite animals ]
[ Ozono age 0 - Smile is the cutest ever! ]
[ Ozono age 1 - Always has her tongue out...caused us to worry ]
[ Ozono age 1 - Tongue out again...worried ]
[ Kubo age 3 - Funny face while floating on an inflatable ring ]
[ Kubo age 6 - At the lavender fields...model style ]
[ Sakaguchi age 0 - Tama as a little girl ]
That's pretty good
[ Sakaguchi - Ballet tournament ]
[ Sato age 2 - She had really thin hair...we were worried ]
[ Sato - Always went to her friends house on a unicycle ]
Why a unicycle though?
[ Nakamura age 2 - At Kasai Rinkai Park ]
[ Nakamura age 11 - Taken by a pro cameraman, the pic we're proudest of ]
[ Mukai - Age 0 ]
Looks like an ojisan
Straight up ojisan
[ Mukai age 12 - Awesome sleeping face ]
She looks like an obasan here
[ Mukai age 13 - After getting out of the bath...out cold ]
[ Yamashita - With her favorite rental dog ]
rental dog
[ Yoshida age 1 - Helping her mother cook, flour everywhere ]
What is this?
Everythings all white
[ Yoshida age 3 - Shichi-go-san Festival in her best clothes ]
[ Yuki at age 3 - Setsubun day as the demon ]
[ Yuki age 5 - Our house mermaid ]
hai
Those were all cute
It was all cute
Ito Riria
hai
At age 3 you were scouted by a modeling agency
So cute
What about this bunny named Fuu-chan?
It was a pet
The bunny was your pet
I had the bunny since about the age of 4
its lived for so long
Its still alive, hasn't changed at all
stayed clean
Well of course, those won't get dirty
[ Stuffed animal? ]
Maybe its bones will stick out around here
[ Zombie bunny ]
Iwamoto...Iwamoto posing in front of a pine tree
This picture is super cute
kawaii
Is this your backyard?
You must be super rich
[ palatial estate? ]
yabai
She's someone pretty high up~
[ Big time compliments on the yard ]
Were you taking lessons?
I've been learning hip hop dance since 1st grade
That was probably from 1st or 2nd grade
1st or 2nd grade?
That's remarkable
So good
Akimoto, impressed right
No that's amazing
my current skill level is probably around there
Well, she is really good
[ Lost to a grade school kid ]
Ozono in all your pictures, your tongue was sticking out
That really was cute
She had a longer than usual tongue and always had it out...we were worried
Since your tongue was hanging out, you eventually learned to reel it back in or something
Anyone ever tell you that?
It was like it was always sticking out
my parents weren't that worried about it but
grandpa and grandma were super worried
[ Why does this girl have her tongue out...? ]
[ The Ozono family tongue issue ]
Thank goodness you learned to how to bring it back in
Shiraishi any of these pictures leave an impression on you?
Those pictures were all just really beautiful
I know what you mean
The pixel count
[ Pixel count appropriate for their generation ]
But Sakaguchi's picture in front of the sofa looked really old
[ Leaves that Showa era impression ]
Good one
Really looks like the hairstyle from when Mori Masako-san debuted
[ The kind of face you'd see a half century ago ]
Nishino, any of these pictures stick in your memory?
Hazuki-chan
Oh that's Mukai...I thought it was an ojisan
[ Infant that looks like an ojisan ]
But the next picture is like an obasan
[ Changed into an obasan at age 12 ]
That's an obasan
I feel like I've seen this before
From back in the dressing room
Mukai hasn't really changed
Is she having a nightmare? She's drenched in sweat
[ The princess sweating profusely in her sleep ]
ah Kubo
Those lavender fields...so you went to Furano
yes, sometime around preschool
We went to Furano on a family trip
I remember it
Really looks like a commercial
LA~ LAA~ LA~
LA LA~ LA LA~
[ One of those deeply emotional commercials ]
If I had been drinking earlier, I might start crying
[ The teary eyed ojisan ]
Then Yoshida
Yoshida was so cute in hers
What was going on there?
You look like some kind of french performer?
[ Infant mime? ]
She does look like one
That's so cute
Look away for 1 second and suddenly there's flour everywhere
she couldn't help herself
That happens to everyone then
Himura-san did that too?
I don't think I ever did anything like that
Himura-san is more like....he would be covered in mud
Look away and he's covered in mud
[ God of mud ]
Yoda
kawaii
This is also so childlike..it also looks like
LA LA LA~
[ Tearjerker stuff ]
Since its Setsubun that's your demon face
Try being the demon
They told me "Why not try being the demon"
I tried it for a little bit
so like, "Yoda try being a demon"
[ Demon Shitara orders up a demon impersonation ]
Try being a demon
[ The humiliated demon ]
That's good...say "try being the demon" and they'll do it
Hori!
Hori, try being a demon
[ Demon harassment ]
Is that a demon? We requested a demon
That's no demon, you turned into something cute
And then there's the mermaid picture of Yoda
kawaii
There's something funny about this mermaid
Its the balance, since she's the bigger kid
The balance makes it look like her head is misproportioned
[ so so mermaid ]
Lets keep moving...here's the next one
She hasn't done this on the show yet....
What is the special talent my daughter does that will definitely be a hit?
arigatou gozaimasu
Thanks for this one
First its something Kubo's parents want us to know about
their daughter has a special talent thats bound to be a hit
She can balance 12 pencils under her nose
Below her nose?!
No way! You can balance 12 pencils here?
By that I mean right here
I'll put 1 pencil and use that as the base to stack up 12 pencils
Today we've prepared some pencils
The special talent as reccommended by her parents
She can stack pencils on her face
And now she'll show us
Let's go ahead then
ready start
13 pencils
What was that you just said?
[ What sound was that? ]
She said "chun-chu-chun" or something
chun-chu-chun
She couldn't say arigatou so she went with chun-chu-chun
You ok, you can't laugh for this
You're good? Go ahead then
First pencil
really 12 pencils? with just one pencil under her nose
eh? they can go on just like that
ah, its all in how its stacked
So with this, is that 5?
Good thing we have these 2 here to hand her the pencils
That's right
Isn't that right Kubo? Good thing you have these 2
[ The pencil castle crumbles ]
Why couldn't you do it Kubo?
Trying to do something you can't even do!
[ Brought shame to parents and child ]
Please don't make me laugh
Don't make you laugh? I'm just standing here
[ The mud god's destructive powers ]
What's up with that? That's so rude
She'll try again for her parents
And she's easily stacked up 7 pencils however
What's the matter Ozono?
eh Ozono what's wrong?
Please give her some silence
Because she's concentrating?
She's concentrating so we should stay quiet?
Well of course we should!
[ Suspected of interfering ]
What? What did I do?
Why are you having pleasant conversations?
Ozono was like
so I asked her what was wrong
Please give her some silence!
[ The kindness backfired ]
Lets make this your last chance
Next its the last challenge
Can she stack up the 12 pencils like her parents said she could?
I feel like Takayama would be good at this
I've never tried, but maybe I could
You could jam a bunch of stuff here right?
[ Upper lip item stacking ]
This is number 10 and 11
ah...sugoi sugoi
10, 11
She can do more right
12, 13
Try and break your record
Seems you can do more
But you can clear with 12
You got it?
ah 12 may be the limit, how about the mouth?
Plant one in her mouth
[ Active cheating ]
ah, get it in there
She did 13...13!
13 is good
If you had started with one in your mouth it would have been fine
[ Start with one jammed in the mouth ]
She already had 12 pencils stacked and you're trying to go to the mouth
[ Suddenly a different kind of game ]
Takayama, could you try it?
Seriously?
And with that....to see how hard it is....Takayama will take the challenge
Why all the chin wrinkles....
I can't make this look cute! I can't!
[ Chin looks like a plum seed ]
What? What?
They said her chin gets wrinkly
Everyone's chin will do that
Why is it like that?
They're right...its all wrinkly
What's wrong with her chin?
You have to pucker up
[ Kubo is wrinkle free ]
Why does your chin get so wrinkly!?
[ Enter the wrinkles ]
Maybe this really is hard
That's not good! Takayama is starting to look hideous
[ Face is losing idol status ]
You can do this
Takayama would never look hideous!
She's cute...Takayama is cute
Takayama looks her best when shot with pencils on her face
[ The woman who looks good wearing pencils ]
Just like that
Kubo, tell her a good spot to stack it
Try placing it above the pencil over your nose
ah, she's getting cuter
kawaii kawaii
Gradually getting cuter
ah this is too hard
It is not difficult!
We have a hardcore coach over here!
[ Hot blooded pencil coaching ]
ah looking good
ah, super cute looking from that angle
When its just 3 pencils you don't look so good though
But once you add more you'll get cuter
ah kawaii kawaii
That's 3 pencils
Go! Go! That's not good
Its too hard!
Don't get mad!
[ The pencils and her mental stability collapsed ]
Don't be so mad!
Don't be mad Takayama
What was that "Ahh..its too hard!"
You scared me
[ Losing her cool from pencils ]
Idols don't talk like that
And next Sakaguchi's mom reccommends she does this special talent
Sakaguchi's is right here
Idols often perform funny faces on air
but her funny face is at a completely different level
There it is!
Is this something you've done in front of your mother?
Only in front of my mother
I've only made this face in front of her
Lately its been
"Don't you think its about time you did it?"
[ Mama believes its a hit ]
Of course when the parents get involved
when their child appears on TV, they want them to do something funny
Its affection
I thought it looked weird and it turned to this
You created this one with your mom
She says its at a completely different level than what the other idols are doing
Would you do it for us?
oh, there's hair parting
Hold on a second
part the hair
[ Sakaguchi mama put her faith in this face ]
Do that again
Please keep her hair out of the way
Now then just a little bit
hold that first face and then do that last one again
And from there
keep keep keep keep!
[ Everyone loved it okaasan! ]
That's a new one
To be honest its cute looking
kawaii
ah even with that its cute looking
Totally cute looking isn't it
I'll never be able to recover from doing that
If you want to see something you'll never live down...Himura-san could you do one
Your fairy one? Which one?
Just this right here is pretty amazing
[ Just this hair parting alone is bizarre looking ]
Who is this? Who is this guy?
When they do it, they're idols, so it ends up looking cute
With that base, its not so weird looking
That's true
Himura-san has this one where he doesn't do anything
that one face he does
I want you to pay attention to the 3rd face he makes
We'll start with the 1st one
Here goes
DON
DON~
DON!
[ Normal one is the strongest ]
That one always gets them!
Anyone can make the 3rd one funny!
[ Funny face champion has descended ]
Only Himura-san can make that funny
Because you have that range
The face where you don't do anything is the funniest
Next is a scoop from Yoshida Ayano Christie's parents
Yoshida's is right here
[ She has a masseuse-beautician certification ]
eh? She's certified?
She's a certified masseuse-beautician
Hearing this everyone's going to want you to massage them in their free time
Want a massage don't you?
So you have a certification that qualifies you for a job?
I could get a job...in high school
my school had masseuse classes
I took the class for 3 years
There was a written part and application section on the exam, I passed it
Is that so
And your mother said this about your certification
I was looking forward to getting treatment from her but she's never given me a massage
That's not right. I didn't enter that school to become a masseuse
But since you're certified she was looking forward to a massage, you should give her one next time
When I'm in the mood, I'll give her one
And with that, before her mother gets a massage, she'll demonstrate her skills on Himura
He's in full makeup but don't worry about it, they'll fix it
Close your eyes!
[ Abnormal staring ]
Its hard to do that unless his eyes are closed right
What's wrong with this salon!
[ Violent massages ]
There are no customers that stare directly at the masseuse like that
I'll keep my eyes closed then
Himura-san...with his eyes closed he's putting his trust in you
[ Attention ]
Why are you raising your right hand?
[ What kind of hand signal is this? ]
You choking me out?
[ Suffocation massage? ]
I'm ok now
There's pressure points on the neck
So it is a relaxing type massage
That's good...that feels great
The hugeness of his face is completely different
Himura-san, how much of that counts as his face?
From there then
That part isn't his face
That's all part of my throat
Hey! What's wrong with this salon!
[ Respiratory damage ]
You weren't the one trying to choke me right?
gomen gomen
Well that was scary~
So you're done
That's it?!
[ Store closed ]
That felt good...yes
Lets move on, here's the next one
Something valuable only to me
What is this one?
For this one the parents
they gathered up something valuable from their daughter
kind of like letters or poems they wrote when they were little
something special they've prepared for us
First its something valuable from Nakamura Reno's parents
[ The picture she got printed in the magazine [Hiyoko Club]]
So she was in Hiyoko Club?
She was printed in Hiyoko Club, here it is
That kid
She's crying
This kid?
That hair is amazing
This is Hiyoko Club
This picture made it into the appendix section of the magazine
The reason for the crying
she broke the photo shoot set and her father got angry and she started crying
Is that so
That moment got printed
But its cute, the crying shot
That hair is crazy, its so frizzy
That's what hair looks like at that age
Light hair can get like that
Next is a precious treasure that comes to us from Yoda's parents
Its a letter to herself from 10 years ago when she was in middle school
Here it is
I'll read it
You're not married
you're not married and won't have a boyfriend I think
but that's not necessarily a bad thing
Believe you'll get those things someday and please keep trying
When things get tough get a pet and you'll be fine
Also, please be careful with your money
Do your best to save enough to take your family or grandma to Hawaii
Well you didn't think you'd have a boyfriend or be married
This is super embarrassing...yabai yabai yabai
embarrassed?
[ Embarrassed its all out in public ]
Weird tears are coming out of me
But you said to believe those things would come some day and do your best
[ Message to self ]
embarrassing
Also, you told yourself to be careful with money
That's something I've always worried about
You were bad with money back then..and its carried over
[ Has a habit of wasting money ]
And then "Do your best to take grandma and family to Hawaii"
Sounds great, take them there
I want to take them to Hawaii
Please do your best then