DON
hai
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
We are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And they are Nogizaka-chan
Its so cold outside
Whats on todays show
Himura-san please tell them
22nd single prayer for a hit!
That's right
The 22nd single goes on sale November 14th
On the way home
I stepped on some dog poop
[ Depressing song title ]
That happens
Kaerimichi wa Toomawari Shitaku Naru
hai
The prayer for a hit is for this song....Nishino
Nishino as center. Her last single
Its the last single for me
You did this one
So you did something amazing for this?
hmmmmmm~
This wasn't a cruel one then?
not cruel
Took the long way back
You did the prayer for a hit...you weren't alone
I wasn't alone
[ Kamakura Jochi-ji Temple ]
22nd single prayer for a hit
WAI~
I'm alone
I've kind of been taken here
[ Jochi-ji Temple is ~46km from Nogizaka ]
This time with Nishino graduating with this single
about 46km from Nogizaka in Tokyo's Minato ward
Kamakura's Jochi-ji Temple will be where they pray for a hit
Afterwards much like the song title
they'll take the long path home visiting places that hold a lot of memories
once they arrive at Nogizaka's Nogi Shrine
they'll make another prayer for a hit to signal the conclusion
46km...ah I get it
Looks that way
She's here!
Here she is
Now its the two of us
A complete stranger has invaded our shoot
[ Some random local? ]
Like an old lady that's good at fitting in
Takayama can get thrown in like that
That's the same entrance as Tamori Club
This time as members keep substituting in
they'll escort Nishino on her trip back home
First we're starting with Takayama
Know this one? This temple is supposed to hold a lot of memories...
It appears this is a place Naachan has been before
I don't recognize it....
The stairs up front
Are you wearing black lipstick?
hai hai hai hai hai
This Kamakura Jochi-ji Temple
is where Nishino and Asuka took the role of double center
and they shot the CD jacket for Itsuka Dekiru Kara Kyou Dekiru
So they're revisiting places with past memories
ah, I don't recognize this
I don't see where we were standing
Was that the spot?  It must have been in this area
I'll be Asuka...
My head's too big maybe I should take a step back...
[ Recreated the CD jacket ]
For some reason Takayama took the role of Asuka
Here at Jochi-ji Temple they recreated the cd jacket picture from a year ago
So today it looks like Naachan will revisit some places that hold some memories for her
that's whats going to happen on this prayer for a hit
These places with memories
will represent Nishino's final prayer for a hit as Nogizaka
The 22nd single
Kaerimichi wa Toomawari Shitaku Naru
we hope it becomes a hit
And then today they'll use this bus to take the long way back to Nogizaka
Inside the bus the members will freely talk about past memories
So pictures
today I've brought a couple Naachan pictures
they asked if I had any
do you remember when these pictures were taken?
I remember this one
That one...
eh Macau?
Yes Macau
So this was probably the day before the bungee jump
ah when we shot on location
Takayama's picture
was from when Nogi Doko did their prayer for a hit tour in Macau
huh? Who's the guy next to me?
That's me!! Its me
[ Macau resident? ]
Who wants ice cream?
I do!
Do you really want ice cream?
This was 2014? This was 4 years ago?
This brings back memories
Various trials of their luck took place
and Nishino was forced to bungee jump off Macau Tower
Don't look down!
Nishino...don't look down!
Nishino...calm down
Stay calm!
She really doing this!?
sugee
She actually jumped after being so terrified
And she jumped right on cue
That was really 4 years ago...
When we took this picture you weren't thinking of jumping were you?
I had no intention of doing any jump
But after that bungee jump
now I can pretty much handle anything that comes at me
That's the image I have
So this is a picture when you were walking around town the day before Macau tower?
ah yes...that's right
So at that moment you had no idea who was doing the jump
not yet
That day we kept shooting
That night we shot in your rooms
ahh that's right
We checked to see how fast you'd come over if staff called you
And then staff called Nishino and she was pretty slow
and from that
I got a bunch of minus Macau points there
And that's what decided it in the end
I still have that image of playing around during the Mannequin MV shoot
[ 4th single Seifuku no Mannequin ]
What I remember was
there was that narrow hallway
and in this narrow hallway I was in the very back
There's no way I'll show up on camera from here
[ She's somewhere back here ]
We were supposed to kind of walk
and do a dance
There was no chance we'd be on camera
But we weren't supposed to abandon our hopes like that
Back then....I do remember a lot of pouting
It was cold
didn't somebody do that scene while making a funny face?
Sayu-chan
tied her hair up in odd places
Just to see if anyone would notice
Nobody said anything about it
[ Small acts of rebellion for being placed in the back ]
Its like "Lets go out there making weird faces then"
As expected, nobody said a word
We weren't on camera anyway!
Remembered a lot of that
We played pranks back then didn't we
Even though it was our first year
So on Kojichuu...Kojichuu
your Taiyo Knock dance
Kazumin's dance
I laughed so hard when you did that
[ Nishino favorite episode - Takayama's low center of gravity Taiyo Knock ]
Another good one...
when they made you eat celery I laughed a lot
[ Takayama's first experience with celery ]
eh what's up with this...it tastes nasty
That was nasty...that celery....
Shitara-san and Naachan
I kind of like the balance between you
Shitara-san at first was super scary
oh really
I was scared of him for a couple years
That so
After a couple years went by
what do you call it
you get the feeling that he's treating you with care
its like
those feelings got across to me
after I realized that
he wasn't scary anymore
There was more to talk about but here the long way back bus makes a stop
and Takayama gets off the bus
Really the bus had arrived before we even knew it
and we weren't done talking so they took the long route for us
[ Took the super long road back ]
It really was the long way back
For that MV you're like "I ain't even on camera"
[ The pouty phase ]
But you weren't on camera so really what were you supposed to do
That wasn't good was it
Well....you didn't show up on camera anyways
[ Not even a small glimpse ]
Wakatsuki did you join in?
It became clear that we couldn't see the camera from where we were at
I thought...I'm not going to be on camera
So you remember it
I do...I was like I'm going to make this fun somehow
[ Scheming from the back of the line ]
So did you make a funny face or something?
Pretty much stuck my chin out
Making a face like that and then moving around a little differently
Still got the "OK desu"
I'm like "That was OK?"
[ No impact ]
So that's how extras rebel
[ The futile resistance of the video extras ]
Inoue tied her hair up in weird places
When the camera stops, makeup-san will jump in and fix your hair right?
I wanted to see how far they'd go to fix me
They didn't come and fix her hair
So you setup your hair like whatever
You're such a bad girl~
[ Playing around during the rebellious phase ]
Revisiting areas that hold memories on the bus taking the long road home
next to get on the bus are...
Wakatsuki, Nakada, Inoue
the members that joined together and went to school together
What's the location on the way home these 4 are heading to?
now then
we have arrived however
Naachan, do you recognize where we are?
I do!
So you remember what this place is?
This is
from Kizuitara Kataomoi's music video
we shot from the rooftop
ahhh...with Nanamin
and with Maiyan...that scene together
I was laying down on my side
This hospital in Kamakura
it was the first single Nishino was selected to center
the shooting location for the music video Kizuitara Kataomoi
Let's go
That was on a roof?
yeah~
eh? you shouted yeah
I didn't know that!
You didn't go?
I went!
How come you don't know then?
So that was a hospital...
eh sugoi sugoi
This was the place then
Kind of a cramped space
I get the idea it was around here
There was a connection between Nishino and dandelions
Enoshima?
This kind of view from a hospital
I love the MV for Kizuitara Kataomoi
That was a good one
The video for it was like
it had a fragile beauty to it
For me I thought it had
a lot of that kind of gentle beauty in it
Since we've come all the way up here how about we recreate the MV?
recreate it?
At this wonderful location
Lets make this live show a success
And with that, relying on Nishino's memories
they'll recreate this scene from the Kizuitara Kataomoi music video
Everyone's waiting
Let's go
Here goes
ready....start
Lets make this live show a success
yeah
Nanase
Lets practice
Everyone's waiting
Let's go
yeah
[ Only able to recreate the setting ]
Then the bus taking the long road home
goes to the next place with memories...its off to Yokohama
1994...the flowers of 94 unit
I have a couple of pictures
some memories
The pictures of our coming of age ceremony
sugoi
[ The 2014 coming of age ceremony ]
Everyone looks so young
really young
everyone did this one when they turned 20
there was like that french restaurant
and the gourmet sushi
Favorite episodes of the 94s
the adult gourmet tour once you reached adulthood
They were split into 2 teams and challenged to eat gourmet food while staying under budget
I remember them doing this
[ Chomping on tails ]
There was plenty of eating
Put all we had into eating
In the early days everyone took busses like this to get around
We took the bus back to Tokyo from Nagoya and Osaka
Those were like 8 hour bus rides
[ At age 22 ]
Everyone would bring their pillows from home
I'm grateful they let us take the shinkansen now
[ Reaffirming their appreciation of the shinkansen ]
So then
we were all at the same school weren't we
same one right
went on that field trip
we all went to Korea
I remember that
[ At age 21 ]
There weren't any friends around so going to Korea with members
rather than a school field trip that totally felt like a personal vacation
I remember I had a fever
I skipped the kimchi factory tour and stayed in bed
[ Absent for the kimchi pickling hands on experience ]
During this conversation
the bus makes a stop at the Yokohama Minato Mirai district
At this bus stop the 94s get off
Which member will ride the bus next?
Taking the place of the 94s on the bus
is Akimoto
Naachan
As they take the long road back what memories will Nishino have?
hai Naachan...right here
do you recognize where we are?
Yokohama
Its Yokohama
Its a place we've been many times
You know the place we've often visited
Pacifico Yokohama
They've arrived at
a place that has held many handshake events with the fans
Pacifico Yokohama
Isn't this where we debuted Kizuitara Kataomoi?
Was it here? I think this was the place
I think they added space
then after that
we performed it for the first time on a truck
I do remember the first performance being on a truck
Yes...for her first song as center
Kizuitara Kataomoi
the back of a truck was turned into a stage
for their performance here in Pacifico Yokohama
konbanwa!
Today its our first performance of this one
I'm super nervous and
this isn't a normal stage
performing on a truck makes me nervous but
And then there were Nishino's thoughts about performing it for the first time on a truck
I didn't want to do that on a truck
That was the first ever performance of it
pretty much
it bothered me
It left behind strong memories for different kinds of reasons
I understand that part
since those are strong memories, actually right now
I'm almost glad those things happened
But at the time
my first song as center...the first performance of that song
truck?
[ The shock of performing on the back of a truck ]
I wasn't into the idea up to the very end
ah is that so
You got a semi truck though...its not like you played on the back of a pickup truck
[ The truck did nothing wrong ]
It wobbled...oh it wobbled
And then the bus they were on travelled to
Yokohama Arena
And thats when Akimoto...
ah
This...this picture
remember this one?
Is that...Yohohama arena?
that's right
Yokohama Arena...the 2nd Birthday Live show
I remember it
after the show
after the show in the hallways
I saw Naachan
you were like "what should I do"
I had my phone and was trying to get a picture and you're like "what should I do"
[ One unforgettable picture ]
For Akimoto this picture
is a picture she'll never forget
Akimoto due to her studies
even being an original member, didn't participate with the group until the 4th single
And for that 4th single
Akimoto Manatsu
Akimoto...Akimoto Manatsu-san?
Is Akimoto-san here?
hai
You've been called...dozo
Right this way
Without ever being involved in the groups activities
she was suddenly selected into Hachi Fukujin
Before Akimoto joined the group
Nishino had made it into Hachi Fukujin but was now dropped to the 3rd row
Well you have no other choice but to do your best
Please keep thinking about your future
Nishino felt she had been dropped to make room for Akimoto
This started a tense relationship with Akimoto
From that point on
they spent over a year not talking to each other
With all that the turning point in their relationship
was here for the Yokohama 2nd Birthday Live
it was when Nishino did this
The words I couldn't say to her back then
I'll use those words to start this song
Manatsu okaeri
Let's do our best together
those words from Nishino dissolved the bad feelings between them
I wanted to be friends
but we never spoke to each other
arigatou...ganbatte ne
That's why for Akimoto, the Yokohama Arena
and this photo she took after the live show
has become an unforgettable treasure
I don't think I've ever gotten that emotional
When that happened
I wasn't thinking I'm going to start something
of course
the reason this all started
I felt the reason was because I was being too childish
Now then before Nishino graduates
the things she couldn't say before...she'll tell Akimoto her feelings
Its like
even though all that happened...like now
how its completely
that ill will
I didn't think it would completely clean up all of it
so then why
how did our relationship improve like this
yabai
when I think why
its definitely because of Manatsu's character
If it were a girl that didn't have Manatsu's character
I don't think there's any way we could be together like this
No...thats not true
This history
its become deeper
between us
Because of that
your graduation
you announced it in front of everyone
When you said "I'm graduating"
I've never trembled that bad ever...it wouldn't stop
I never imagined it could happen
Back to what we were talking about...at Yokohama Arena
okaeri Manatsu
I did say that
But this time for the 22nd single
in the MV for it
Manatsu says okaeri to me....for me personally
that was really
incredible...was that a coincidence?
A favorite scene for Nishino that reminds her of their past history
that scene from the music video is right here
How come Manatsu
says "okaeri" in that scene
its probably
it may just be a coincidence but
sugoi
personally
that was a good point
ah is that so
I'm the one saying it but
it brought back a lot of memories
Its become something we have in common
The bus heading home carrying both of their memories
makes a stop right here
Akimoto will depart here
which member will get on the bus next?
Nishino
hai
Nishino and Akimoto
both of you look like you're about to cry
now I've got a runny nose
Go ahead and show some snot...I don't mind
[ Don't hold back ]
Reminded you of the past then
and you teared up
Its really strange
I'm not trying to cry but watching that
Its because there's a history
We had no idea you two weren't getting along
I had no idea
I thought you were having a good time
Being a part of Fukujin
on the inside...what do you call it
You felt like you had been kicked out
And then suddenly its like
You're like "why you little..."
This girl comes in and I'm kicked out?!
I had those kinds of immature emotions
But still you managed to make up
you told her okaeri
Akimoto is sobbing too right?
I really wasn't expecting that
Its actually turned into a good memory hasn't it
You could say it brought us closer