Catch up with the 1st members all at once
Force the senpais to battle the kouhais
Up to now all the activities only the 1st members have experienced on the show
the kouhai members will suddenly get to experience all of it
This is their chance to fill in their experience gap
Last time it was a drawing battle
we're in the middle of checking the members artistic senses
Tonight we're starting with
these members drawing a horse for us
Kitagawa was good at this wasn't she
am i right?
flipbook manga
flipbook manga then
Does that mean you're no good?
[ Asking the question becomes an insult ]
Please draw a horse
Everybody...the subject is a horse
I'd like to get started....first its
Shiraishi
hai...hai DON
well well well well
This is the first one we're showing
yes! are you serious?
I wouldn't call it super well drawn but...
[ In no way is this well drawn ]
But the horse is good
That's a toy store type of horse
[ mass produced horse ]
She's got some carrots in there too
I would not call it amazingly well drawn
[ Repeated disclaimer ]
Its well in the horse zone
Next one
well this one too
hai
Saito Yuuri
sure sure sure...sure sure
I would not call this one well done either
What's this part right here?
That's its mane
You only have its mane right here?
This horse has a short cut hairstyle
[ summer style cut ]
There's mane here but horses have a lot more mane
forgotten item...
What do you mean forgotten item?
The horse forgot that part
ah I didn't put it on
[ Forgot the wig ]
well sure this is fine
I kind of like the next one
yes this one's from Kitano
What's going on here?
Hard braking
Its stopping and applying the brakes here
[ emergency brakes ]
What's going on here
this one is also just plain awful
The main highlight is that a horse's eyes are so gentle
I captured the kind eyes here by drawing droopy eyes
Somehow when you look at the lines overall
I just don't like this picture somehow
Don't like this drawing
[ Unpleasant somehow ]
Well it is a horse though
And it starts about here
This one is from Suzuki
hai...right here
Same as Asuka-chan's just now
Why'd you draw it so small?
Before I realized it....it was this size
[ Before she realize it....the end of the page ]
But for this one....the back legs are really well done
ah...that's great
What's its problem?
[ weird looking ]
That's a big head
Those legs could never support that head
well its still a horse
I see...next one then
Tsutsui right here
hai
[ dog ]
cute is it?
would this be cute?
This ones messed up
That face irritates me
Is it sleeping then or what?
Horse? Did you draw a horse?
hai
And then its mane....its looking bald
[ A dog with thinning hair ]
Its an ojisan than resembles a dog
[ Looks more and more like an ojisan ]
ah that's a funny one
That's a dog isn't it
right...hai
hai kowai
uwah~ what is it?
[ A new species enters ]
What is this? Its no horse
Not a dog either
Is it a cat?
UmeMayo
hai
Why'd you give it this face?
This was harder than expected...I was thinking what should this look like
The horse?
Should have a longer neck for a horse
Yes I just realized that
Everybody draws the scraggly hair just on its back
[ Special touch on the back hair ]
And then the long legs
[ Part of the tall and lanky clan ]
Those are not horse legs
Kind of resembles Hello Kitty-chan
[ Distant relative? ]
There's a slight resemblance right
Next one
hai next....hai
Kanagawa
[ What is this? ]
This one
I repeatedly told all of you to draw a horse
[ Were you listening? ]
This is really like one of those Bangkok decorations
[ Thai protection symbol? ]
What is this? What's that tail?
Did you draw a reptilian tail?
For horses..to start with
I was thinking of making the tail point up but drew it going down
it came out looking all weird
ah this tail
Not really talking about whether it should go up or down here
[ There's additional issues ]
Its a reptile tail
There's also this
Why? Is this how it walks?
[ Palms facing up ]
That's what this is right
What are those round marks on its feet then?
paw pads
paw pads?
A horse doesn't have any sort of paw pads though
What's this line for?
Its neck line
neckline
There's no such thing
[ Where did you learn about horses? ]
Horses don't have that
Next is from Mukai
Mukai
That face
Isn't this a cow? Yes its a cow
We're looking for a horse
A horse then
What's wrong with its body?
So horses....they have amazing leg muscles
Like when you ride them
That's why the leg muscles
you emphasized them?
That's right...I think I drew that part really well though
You think?
This is lousy
[ Just accept it ]
yes Mukai...this one's no good
[ Its over ]
Next...hai next!
Sakaguchi
hai Sakaguchi
[ Controversial ]
ahh there it is!
This one's not of this world
Now you've done it....we asked you for a horse
It is a horse
This....where's this?
And this? What's this?
What is this part?
The mouth
Then what's this?
That's looking from the side
And this?
Is this coming out of its mouth?
Its feeding on some plants
ah its a tongue
She drew the tongue?
And this? This small line is a tooth?
That's a tooth for sure
With all this space you only drew in 1 tooth?
[ Only needs 1 tooth ]
It rips and stabs food with its tooth and eats?
[ works like a toothpick ]
What's this part?
Maybe its a cloud?
nope
This is part of the horse?
That's its mane
That is not a mane
This is the mane then
hai
So this one
is this guy about 500m long?
[ Tell us the scale of this thing ]
Maybe its bigger than that...maybe people live on it
[ Giant city ]
It could almost be a ski resort
But this isn't the end of the horse category
ehhh~
There's one last one
Who is it?
Kitagawa....Kitagawa!
Yes...the expert at the flipbook manga
here goes...hai
[ Beyond the norm ]
What happened here?
With that amount of time there's not many lines here
plus she's pushing towards the edges of the page
Why'd you go off the page?
How? Is this looking from in front?
from the side
side? Then it walks facing this direction
Like this
it would walk like this wouldn't it
Why couldn't you stay on the paper?
When you said draw a horse
at the very start....ah
well I should draw the legs
the legs are the defining characteristic
so I figured I should draw it out
its like
they turned out bigger than expected
ah you started with the legs and it threw off the balance
I thought "those horse type animals are sure big"
horse type animals are sure big
[ What are you talking about? ]
That was your thinking
Its a good thing we didn't ask you to draw an elephant or whale
[ Would never fit on the page ]
Akimoto
[ Akimoto's horse is right here ]
This one is kind of messed up...yes it is
We didn't ask for a dinosaur
That's a dinosaur face
Next these members will draw
the breaststroke
The breaststroke...is it from the front or rear viewpoint
there's angles to look at it making this a difficult topic
First its this one...hai
Karin-chan
ah this is Karin-chan then
This one came out first? Must be some crazy artistic levels
That's right
Is this as seen from the front?
ah..she drew in the body
At first I wasn't going to draw it in
afterwards I added it...turned out wrong
I didn't see this part earlier and picked it first...now it looks creepy
[ Body unnatural ]
That's our top one?
Lets keep it going then
Right here...from Seimiya
That's a butterfly
It really does look like a butterfly
Either a butterfly or a drone
[ unidentified flying object ]
It really is a drone
What's the situation here? Is the head and torso moving this way?
Swimmer is facing down and this is looking from above
Do they make swimmers wear numbers on their back?
Doesn't happen does it
Seimiya is this what they did where you grew up?
I don't remember
I'm sure they don't
[ There's just no way ]
Tough one
This was a fairly difficult topic
hai next...hai
yes Shibata
[ slippery smooth ]
and naked
This guy is naked
[ full naked? ]
Only wearing a hat
Why is he not wearing a swimsuit?
I forgot....
forgot the swimsuit then
[ Thus completely naked ]
That actually makes him faster in the water
[ This sort of nakedness can be put on tv ]
As long as its not an adult
next...next its
This one's good but
Hoshino
Its that moment right at the start...that pow...pow
[ Coming up for air? ]
This is completely
could this be the view from the bottom of the pool?
ah its like the angle from down diagonal down
down diagonal down?
[ First ever view from that angle ]
down diagonal down!
What's the first down for?
[ useless down ]
Don't need that down
ah it doesn't make sense from that direction but from above
its obasan floating in the water
[ obasan vacation ]
Its an obasan doing some long distance swimming
There are obaasans that do this in the pool
Drawing swimming is so hard
next is right here
Is it supposed to be like this or like this
He's falling! He's falling!
He's falling from above
Vertical then
This guy just jumped off a building
[ freefall? ]
This one...Tamura
This is Tamura
Is this picture of Yurioka Choutoku Q-san
[ Why him? ]
The falling YuriQ
That's not it
Its the proper view from the front
So the rest of his body is bent like this
but still
sure sure...this still looks fine to me
next one right
yes here it is
That's Kubo
Kubo
What happened here?
It looks like a Kaiji impersonator
[ Did you see that? What's over there?! ]
This is the view from the side
Doing this one
And then this type of swimsuit
[ Not wanting to show too much skin ]
So outdated
The swimsuit is so outdated
That's what they make comedians wear for variety
Those aren't worn by normal people
And then
the breaststroke as seen from straight above
here are the artworks of Nakamura and Ito Riria
The breaststroke is quite a difficult topic
well its Matsumura's
[ Scary somehow ]
What is that?
What's wrong with this guy?
Why'd you draw him all hairless?
You didn't give him anything
If you saw this guy swimming towards you....everybody would run for it
[ psycho swimmer ]
ah...that's a cap
its a cap...its a cap
The swimming cap makes him look bald then
headband...
Does look like a headband
[ takoyaki restaurant logo style ]
It looks like a hachimaki headband now
I was going to draw feet but messed up
ah that's where you tried to draw feet
scary right
Sakurai....Sakurai!
Its a cute one
Sakurai
What's the deal?
We asked you to draw the breaststroke
He's all
YEAH! HEH HEH HEH HEH
[ Underpants man screwing around ]
He gets out of the water and is like "YEAH HEH HEH HEH"
That's what's going on
I think its supposed to be a kid
or its an ojiichan
[ polka dots ojiichan ]
What's going on with the swimsuit?
Why this swimsuit?
I wanted to brighten things up
couldn't decide between polka dots and stripes
so I gave him cute polka dots
Completely hairless
Can't really get a sense of the water in this one
And here's the last one
Hori
Hori....ahhh its Hori
What's going on with the B?
B...B which floor? B which floor?
[ Which floor would you like sir? ]
its a kickboard
[ The B is for board ]
Why is he using a kickboard for the breaststroke?
You can't use a kickboard for this
I couldn't do the breaststroke
I used a kickboard to swim so
so this is actually Hori?
[ self-portrait? ]
Hori you shouldn't wear v-neck sweaters like that to swim
shouldn't be wearing leather shoes either
It really is a V-neck
Why these clothes?
The upper part?
The upper half, the lower half, the shoes
[ Going out on the town outfit ]
those aren't shoes...its flippers
flippers?
Why does he have those on for the breaststroke?
people would get mad
With the kickboard and swimming flippers its no longer the breaststroke
You're drawing the breaststroke here
I lost the concept of the breaststroke at some point
Why? I told you
[ Goes opposite of the original concept ]
At what moment are you showing this person?
Coming up for air?
ah that's right...coming up for air
paddling in the water
This face kind of bothers me
What's his problem?
If he's using a kickboard his head would always be above water
That's true
mmmmmm~
mmmmmmmmmm~
mmmm~
Put the kickboard away!
Next...the topic for these members is
A person playing the recorder
eh? What's that supposed to be?
Must be a Matsumoto Leiji-san fan
Do we have Matsumoto Leiji-san over there?
Matsumoto Leiji-san kind of style
huh? what's that?
Our master painter is feeling it today
In the zone aren't you
But of course
We have some talented girls here
To draw at this level in a limited time
yes right here
[ Shocking quality ]
Yamazaki
eh are you serious?
As usual she's really good
sugee
In that short amount of time
seriously?
You even see the fingers covering up the holes
She started with the recorder
but still managed to get the fingers to look right
ah I get it...going over the recorder
She didn't draw over the fingers
Well done
sugoi
next is right here
She drew a little girl
Kakehashi
She has this talent then
good isn't it
What happened to the arms?
In regard to the balance with the recorder
the body is small yet the hands are huge
Well the recorder
she had to get the fingers to go over the top
And the face does look like she's blowing into a recorder
You enjoy drawing then Kakehashi?
I like it
This is good
But obviously
this is my first time drawing someone playing the recorder
That is the hard part
In that short amount of time
sugoi
If we put those 2 together its like
kawaii
You can practically hear the music
[ Picture of music being played ]
yes that was wonderful
so next...
This one....well this one made me laugh
right here
Takayama
At first I thought it was Matsumoto Leiji-san but its more like Adachi Mitsuru-sensei
[ The touch of an influential artist ]
But this one does have a certain touch to it
But when I look at those hands "ah this is kind of horrible"
[ only capable of drawing faces ]
pretty creepy looking
This work represents the true abilities of Takayama
[ Kazumi 100% ]
And then these 3 also
have been selected into the somehow passable category
next then
Haven't heard from out master artist yet though
This one's from Higuchi
Obviously drawing the hands is difficult
Well we expected this
finally reached the horrible zone
The hands
hands are hard right
Nobody in my class played recorder like this
This kid is kind of well...
he seems so poor
[ picture oozes with sorrow ]
Just seems like he's a little poor
That's true
This kid isn't wearing a shirt right?
[ Can't even afford a tshirt ]
Not wearing anything up top is he
There's no lines around his wrists so
not wearing anything up top
Seems like he gets home haircuts
[ okaasan haircut ]
okaasan cut a lot off the top
[ Going strong with the trimming ]
And then the frightening part of Higuchi
its there right
She drew music notes around this kid
[ Higuchi's madness ]
The addition of the notes displays the terror of Higuchi
well still
I can tell that its someone playing a recorder
next one then
It starts about now
Shinuchi came up with this
kowah!
[ balance ]
Scary one right
bottomless amounts of terror in this
The hands proved to be too hard
That part was hard
But that's not the main concern here
[ That's not the problem area ]
Scary right?
This is her personal desire right...make the legs long...make the legs long
[ Habit for showing off a high waist ]
The legs are disturbing too
And that face
Drawing faces too hard?
So Shinuchi was about this level then?
The topic really was difficult
How did the hands turn out like that...
Hands are coming out of the throat
Looks like asparagus
She's eating asparagus
And then....this is our master artist
Ikuta just keeps on improving
Is that so
here goes...hai
[ That mouth ]
You're killing me
This guy is creeping me out
What happened to this guy?
What happened here?
Play the recorder too much and maybe your mouth does this
[ Stretch your mouth to the recorder style ]
What is this? What did you draw out first?
I also started with drawing the recorder
The original positioning of the recorder from the face
probably forced you to stretch his mouth to reach the recorder right
That's how it ended up like this then
That makes sense
Of course just the mouth alone gets this many laughs
[ Now that's a real master artist ]
But it does properly display movement...this one
[ Throws the hips into it ]
It does have an action shot feel to it
Does seem like there is some of that
I wanted to capture him breathing in real deep
Then he's up on his toes on one side
But the face seems kind of good to me
She added a different kind of touch from her usual
Clearly different than past ones
That's right
hai
Here's the last one
The last recorder drawing...still one more
yes this is Yoda's
[ Despair levels of artistic ability ]
That's Galigali Galixon right there
Its Galigali Galixon...you're right
Misunderstood right? We weren't asking for Galigali Galixon
disturbing
I thought everyone would have one like this
I was surprised to see so many good ones
No everybody's was about like this
Here are some of the similar ones
[ All from the same tools ]
These 3 are amazing
They're like classmates
[ Miracle class ]
All classmates here
But of course Ikuta's picture
I'd really like this put on a tshirt
eh I'm so happy
You did a good job of not laughing while you drew this
I took this seriously
But you must have thought "this mouth sticks out too much"
Would you please just say that
[ Asking you to admit it ]
This is properly using your facial muscles to play a wind instrument
But facial muscles don't bulge out like this
It wouldn't come out this much
You must have noticed it didn't look right
He's playing his heart out
[ Not going to admit it ]