DON
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
we are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And they are Nogizaka-chan
Dekkaido~
what's this?
I hope it becomes a hit
Himura-san tell them what's on todays show
onegaishimasu
23rd single prayer for a hit campaign
WOO
Scheduled to release on May 29th
the 23rd single
After you're Dead
[ Song about the afterlife? ]
ah sorry...I remember songs by what it sounds like
after you're dead...
[Sing Out!]
Was it Sing Out then?
So then center Asuka-chan
What kind of campaign was this one?
This time on [Sing Out!]
[ Reminded of After you're dead ]
The song just turned into after you're dead a little bit
along with the lyrics in [Sing Out!]
"happy" and "smile"
those words are in the lyrics
The people around town
they are going to share information with us
They'll share their happiness?
That's right
For that happy....the members have split up into 6 teams
each team will aim to get 20 happys
it'll be an ask the people around town shoot
Finally all the happys collected around the nation
from all the clapping and dance scenes they create
it'll be used to create an original MV for the show
And with that its our 1st team
We have arrived in Sapporo
[ Odori Park Sapporo ]
ah Sapporo
Starting now...here
this place is called Odori Park
here everybody's happy
we'll ask people to share what makes them happy
Still cold over there?
And with that right away
they'll start gathering happy at this store in front of a tv tower
We're going around and asking what makes people happy
The first people to answer are these 2 who run a tapioca store
I've got kids so
oh that's a lot
I got a Facebook friend request from my oldest son's girlfriend
ehhh sugoi
Also her oldest daughter's house had a centipede in it that they got rid of
Her next son has started studying for the entrance exams
Its 3 quite charming happy events in a row
As for the male store owner's happy items
hai
[ Won an election ]
What sort of election?
I was elected into the town council
omedetou gozaimasu
They've somehow run into an "election winner happy-san"
and after that
Could you please tell us what makes you happy?
[ Travelling to Hokkaido for our golden anniversary ]
Its our golden wedding anniversary
eh golden anniversary
How about 1 thing from each of you that you like about the other?
He's kind
I like her kindness
Both said the same thing
[ The ultimate happy husband and wife ]
Among the happy things they collected
Akimoto had this suggestion
When I think of happy what comes to mind is a wedding reception
[ The crux of happy ]
Doesn't that sound right?
And with that while looking for a wedding reception
to gather more happy its off to a place that's very Hokkaido
Speaking of Hokkaido
Sapporo Teine Ski Resort
we've arrived!
This ski resort which has snow still fluttering around in May
exactly what happy will they find here?
konnichiwa
konnichiwa~
They're all on the same ski team so what is their happy?
I got taller
Who got taller?
Who is it?
ah the 2 of you?
I'm curious about the "I've met someone"
Right now!
Really? Happy to meet us?
Do you have a favorite member?
Shiraishi-san....
[ Probably better if they didn't ask that one ]
She's not with them
Here they get a huge quantity of happy from the kids
And since they've come all the way over here
Shall we go skiing?
OHH..
Do you have to know how to ski?
Way too underenthusiastic about skiing aren't you?
Actually these 3 are complete beginners to skiing
Regarding that Akimoto
is the only skilled skiier among them
Is that so? She's an expert then?
As far as the other members
ah but still
AUGGH~~~
[ got scared ]
Sakurai-san is being all timid
sensei!
And here a tragedy awaits Sakurai
hold on now
[ Cameraman falls down ]
amazingly
the most entertaining part of seeing her crash is completely missed by the camera
ah that was no good?
[ Fell down for nothing ]
And then
ahhh WAIT! WAIT!! WAIT!!!
Asuka in standby lost control and started sliding backwards
How come?
After that the 4 of them enjoyed more off season skiing
Here they got an appointment for a wedding reception so they're heading that way
The wedding reception taking place soon
the theme of it is "pranks"
Its that sort of wedding reception
On this day its a wedding reception labelled as a prank
Among the numerous pranks
amazingly
as a prank on the new bride and groom
they're going to make a surprise appearance
The prank
first the 4 of them will make a congratulatory comment
in a video that will play at the wedding
After that the surprise will be when they appear in person
Of course the new bride and groom included
this has been kept a secret from everyone
The surprise launched by these 4
will it make everybody happy?
If they don't care about Nogizaka it could be a problem
onegaishimasu
Its time
Now then the prank will start
First its the video congratulations
What will the reaction be?
Everyone....konnichiwa
We are Nogizaka46
To the new groom Kizuku-san
to the new bride Tomoko-san
on this wedding occassion
omedetou gozaimasu
People appear somewhat confused
but gradually they're going along with it
however
This time here with us
the new bride Tomoko-san is a good friend of mine from way back
[ wedding joke ]
ah really?
ah friend from when?
[ All blank stares ]
Since elementary school for me
So the happiness between these two
we'd like to be a part of their happy...
Doesn't that sound nice
I'd like to share in it
About now to give them our blessing
we'd like to come over there
sumimasen...pardon us
Please wait for us....YAAY~
This is one hell of a prank
ah they did it
ah sugoi....warm welcome
konnichiwa...we are Nogizaka46
This is good...its good
Pardon us
ah she's crying
We are Nogizaka46
[ Prank is a success ]
Seeing the bride in tears gave them some relief
omedetou gozaimasu
First they'll explain the details
and right away they'll ask the couple what makes them happy
Today's wedding ceremony
[ well of course ]
well if that wasn't the answer the other person would get mad
In closing may we ask how you're feeling right now?
I'm completely shocked...I didn't know exactly what was going on
But to receive all these blessings from everyone makes me so happy
arigatou gozaimasu
And then finally
They give their lecture on the dance for the MV
and got a good shot of everyone there doing the dance and they're done
And with that the wedding reception surprise successfully completes
Kizuku-san....Tomoko-san...truly
omedetou gozaimasu
So people have prank themed weddings
were there any bad surprises?
The food didn't stay that tiny did it?
[ never ending prank ]
At the ski resort Sakurai...they didn't get your crash on camera
That was cruel
Can't really help it if cameraman-san falls over like that
In my mind it was a magnificent crash
Felt you did a good job there then
The next gathering of happy
is at Kyushu Kagoshima
the 4 people in charge are going to
Saigo Park located near the airport
First they'll gather happy from the tourists
sumimasen
The first people they call out to...what makes these oniisan happy
Playing with my pet cat
Happy playing with his pet cat
I brought home this kitten
I was thinking of making it a pet
the place I lived at didn't allow pets
So I bought a new house...had it built
[ Bought a house to keep the cat ]
[ Runa-chan ]
That's pretty cute....it is
Looks like a celebrity cat....yes yes! It really does!
[ Not denying the adoration ]
Next...at a glance he looks scary
this man who's here from Osaka...what makes him happy
Meeting a special person
and finding happiness
I've opened up 120 hair removal salons across the country
[ Hair removal salon CEO ]
So right here
this amount of hair
well this side was done 10 years ago
But this is what its like after 1 year
[ Personal monitoring ]
The 4 of them got a happy from the cheerful CEO
Next to gather the happy of some kids its off to a preschool
They receive permission from the school principal
and its off to the classroom with the oldest students
pardon us
konnichiwa
konnichiwa~
Today all of us
have come here to ask what makes you happy
Anyone have something that makes them happy?
hai! hai! hai!
[ Over 20 happys ]
And with that its time to gather up the happys from these energetic preschoolers
Playing in the snow in Hokkaido
golden week?
First time seeing snow then?
Anything happen to make you happy?
At the fish festival
I went fishing and it was fun
you went fishing?
What did you catch?
I forgot...
you forgot then
I went to a night aquarium...it was fun
eh a night aquarium? with mama?
What was the cutest thing you saw?
giant isopod
[ Bathynomus giganteus ]
Was it cool then?
arigatou...arigatou
Now that they've received a bunch of happy
the members have a request
We'd like all of you to dance along with us
will that be ok?
HAI!
For the MV dance scene
all the preschoolers are going to join in
Will the little kids be able to dance well?
Finally they've arrived at the Hula Dance Studio
konnichiwa
They've arrived at
a place with a team comprised of 50 and 60 year olds
Hano Hano
Hula dancing has this happy image associated with it
and that's why we've come in to see you
But your smiles match perfectly with Hula don't they?
I want to copy that
[ Sensei has a strong personality ]
Sensei recommended they try it
and now they'll take on the Hula Dance challenge
[ Ha' aheo PRIDE....Hawaiian version ]
well she's got experience
They already got it down
My teaching style is really good don't you think?
[ self-praise ]
arigatou gozaimasu
Here everyone in the Hula dance studio as well
will tell us what makes them happy
My 93 year old father
we live together now
During golden week the both of us
we went to Ibusuki for a happy date
[ Date with her 93 year old father ]
My parents house is over in Shibushi
after 4 years our home garden is finished
[ Completed their home bamboo grove ]
wah~ huge~
More people have come by for pictures
[ Bamboo grove -> scenic photo spot ]
Finally its sensei's happy
I'm grateful to have met these team members
[ Getting to meet the hula members ]
I was in
poor physical health
At that time all of them gathered up
and they came and helped me with the cleaning
They were all truly busy but came over to help me out
That made me really happy
I truly felt like "I'm so glad I was able to meet these members"
With all these happy people
finally they filmed the dance for the MV and were finished
The happy power that comes from hula dancing
you'd never think they just met...but it came to an emotional finale
Its kind of crazy
it feels like my heart has been purified
arigatou gozaimasu
To the people of Kagoshima...truly
arigatou gozaimashita
The preschool
that's cute stuff isn't it
They were so cute
Cute wasn't it
But still when she told you "I went fishing"....did you tell her
That's wrong
[ Strict happy qualifications? ]
It was basically all positive...that's great!
That's great then
Next they'll gather happy in the Tokai region
It'll be these 3 in charge
The first place they'll visit
the main amusement park for the Tokai area
Nagashima Spa Land
Right away they'll walk around the park searching for happy
So currently
we're asking everyone for recent things that make them happy
The sudden request was given a pleasant ok
what is okaasan's happy?
5th grade Class 3
3rd grade Class 3.....1st grade Class 3
The 3 brothers are in the same division
Its rare for brothers to be in the same division
I'm looking forward to their athletics festival
They're all Class 3
They received a happy full of pride
Next these 2 will ride on the roller coaster
huh? roller coaster
Nogizaka's new song
along with this song
we'd like you to clap along for us
to get more footage for the MV
the theme park visitors will help them out
riding the roller coaster they'll film the hand clap scene for their MV
They got cameras duct taped to their hands
[ And they're off ]
one two....one two....one two....one two....one two...
So my dog
I say one two....to let the dog know its time to pee
[ Clap used to encourage peeing ]
This is for the MV
We're seriously dropping!
You better clap
They aren't clapping
oh no...no no no
Its scary but it felt great...there's good weather here
Felt good during the ride
Next...retaining its historical looking landscape
the lower area surrounding Inuyama Castle
They'll walk around collecting happy
They've got charred rice skewers
ehhh~ EHHHH~
They look so good
First these 3 make it a priority to eat first
oishii
And here they'll ask for happy
After many years I went out to eat with my father
[ Went out for a meal after many years with her father ]
How long had it been?
Probably about 8 years....
My father relocated for work
with me working here our days off never matched up
For golden week I only got 1 day off
we visited a gravesite
and then went out to eat
arigatou gozaimasu
After that for some reason
they would eat twice for each person they asked for happy
Hearing about happiness from everyone
has left these 3 feeling satisfied
While getting their fill of happy and food
its off to Japan Monkey Center
here they won't just search for happy
they'll collaborate with monkeys for the hand clap scene
and try to get a miraculous shot for the video
First they'll go to Japan Monkey Valley
kawaii....there's a bunch of them
the little one...the little one
I hear the sound of rocks being smashed together
I was wondering where that sound was coming from
kawaii
Right here they're successful in capturing a monkey clapping rocks together
The next place they've arrived at
huge hands
First time I've ever seen a gorilla
kakkoii
So huge
Happy Birth
April 20th it turned 46 years old
[ Gorilla46 ]
Says it was born in 1973
same as my father
Since Shitara-san turned 46
Shitara-san
[ Shitara? ]
Why is that me then?
I'll allow it because its cool
Next they'll observe the chimpanzees
Think it'll clap for us?
and then
It might imitate them
Seems to be going along with it
[ happy dance ]
eh? Maybe it really is playing along
And then...
ah it did it...it did it
The miraculous clapping scene is a success
It really did it? Stop lying
Finally the staff will give us their happy
And then
I'm getting married in 2 weeks
[ extreme happy ]
yabai~
He's standing beside me
ehh~
sumimasen....I'm not used to this...the damage
damage....sugoi
Its true...I thought they looked like a good match
I thought...those 2 sure flirt a lot
By the way her boyfriend's happy
His nephew was born on the 1st day of the Reiwa era
And with that the Tokai team
they've collected their 20 happys
Show all of the happys
I feel bad for them
They've been all cut
So Nagashima Spa Land
its sort of famous then...for you know
ah...what do you speak of?
[ What does it all mean? ]
Well I've heard the name but have never been there
you went there a lot?
I've been there often
But thrill rides aren't really my specialty
All 3 of us really aren't good with them
Kitano totally rejected the idea
[ Did not ride it ]
That no good?
Totally off limits
Its safe though
Ride it!
but! We got the chimpanzee to clap for us
that was really something
The chimpanzee right
That gorilla is the same age as me!
That's right...the same age as Shitara-san
Indeed I feel like I remember seeing that guy in elementary school
[ old buddy? ]
That's a classmate of yours?