23rd single prayer for a hit campaign
It was recently released...keywords in the song [Sing Out!]
"Happy" and "Smile"
this show is about people from all over the country sharing their stories with us
The members have split up into 6 teams
and will try to gather 20 happys from different regions
by listening to the stories of the people
Everyone will join in by doing the dance and the clap sequences for us
and create an original MV for the show that's full of happy
This time our 1st team that's heading towards the North Kanto region
is Sakaguchi...Yoda....Watanabe
This time they've arrived at....located in Fujimino Saitama....Keiai Hospital
This hospital is equipped much like a luxury hotel
their maternity ward is incredibly popular even among the locals
Here they'll collect claps from all the people with newborn Reiwa Era babies
So here the newborn babies
[ All Reiwa babies ]
kawaii
kawaii...they've all got little hats
These are babies born in year 1 of the Reiwa Era...they must be very happy
Here the 3 of them have found a baby doctor
Once we ask the sensei who cares for the pregnant women what makes him happy...
What has made you happy recently....onegaishimasu
onegaishimasu
I can't believe it!
[ My daughter was born ]
Born here? Born right here
ehhh~ sugoi
When was she born?
Born in December of last year
Were you in charge of delivering your own daughter?
I was!
eh sugoi!
That's reassuring for your wife as well
I also gave the vaccinations myself
[ Administered shots to his own baby ]
Next they'll ask for stories from a mother who just had her baby born yesterday
kawaii...kawaii~
konnichiwa
so tiny
kawaii~
What's the name?
Ichika
Ichika..so its a girl
She's a girl
Ichika-chan
Now they'll hold the newborn baby
How are you?
You're a healthy one aren't you
Miria-san was once just like this too
She's so tiny
Next Yoda will attempt to hold the baby however
Is this going to be ok?
whoa...
whoa whoa
As long as you support the neck...
[ Moving like a robot ]
Yoda's dangerous
The Reiwa baby along with mama join in on filming happy clapping for the MV
And then
ehhhh~
My 6th grandchild was born
[ People with newborn babies shot dance scenes for the MV ]
In this maternity ward
along with all the happy smiling people
they filmed the dance
Next well as you can see this is really...
Its a wide open space much like an airport
So right here they say it brings good fortune once you see it and is Japan's largest
there seems to be this Happy Heart
The heart they speak of is here
Watarase Water Basin's "Heart Lake"
They say seeing the entire lake will bring happiness
as well as good fortune
so they definitely want to get a shot for the MV however....
Over there is like a really tiny plane
This heart is too big making it impossible to photograph from the ground
At an altitude of 3800m
somebody will take this picture while skydiving for us
"Yes I'll jump!"
anybody here thinking like that?
hai!
[ Hand goes up with zero hesitation ]
really?
hai
you sure?
You'll jump?
Because its
my first ever campaign
Please leave this to me!
[ baka level positivity ]
That's reassuring
And with that Sakaguchi on her first campaign
will represent and make the jump
Staff: Once you see the heart from above
that'll bring you good fortune
since you're already up there
if you could pray for a hit....onegaishimasu
The ones I've seen on tv often then
But definitely
once they give you the word you have to jump
I'm feeling fine right now but
probably once I get in the sky I'll feel scared
In order to get a picture of the giant heart
now is the time for Sakaguchi to go up 3800m in the air
The mission for today
Pray for a hit before the jump
In the sky get a picture of the giant heart
and while falling in midair do some clapping
Since I've gone through so much to make senbatsu
and since I said "I'll do whatever is needed"
ganbarimasu!
With Sakaguchi on board the plane takes off
kowai~
ah yabai
There's no going back now
We're so high up...its so high up
I have no idea what I'm getting into
They've reached the appropriate altitude for skydiving
the plane's exit hatch is now open
sugoi
First its the prayer for a hit
By screaming it in a loud voice will she get the good fortune from the heart?
23rd Single
I hope it becomes a hit!
[ Before jumping pray for a hit single ]
wah she really did it
ah is she laughing?
She just gave the prayer for a hit
the remaining missions are to take a picture of the heart
and do some midair clapping
I see the heart...ok ok ok ok
It required some skill from the cameraman
but capturing Sakaguchi within the heart was pulled off successfully
The last mission was to do some midair clapping for the MV however...
[ There's panic in that smile ]
She finally got herself out of panic mode
and Sakaguchi was able to spread out her arms however
That's extreme wind force
The parachute opens and the freefall is over
Tama-chan!
WAHHHH~
Raise your legs
Thank goodness
okaeri!
Sakaguchi's 1st senbatsu....she didn't clap but
her prayer and the picture of the heart was a splendid success
And for the happy staff-san who have seen the heart several times
they filmed the dance for the MV
and this location shoot is complete
That was awesome...Sakaguchi skydiving
You did it
I did it
Didn't do the clapping then?
wah~ it was like
there was a lot of protocol to follow
I saw the scenery and forgot all about it
Well that's worth a punishment point
[ Sakaguchi gets a point for forgetting to clap ]
Next up its Ikuta...Shiraishi...Takayama....Hoshino
We have arrived at Kumagaya Saitama
The first place they're heading is to the Menuma Rest Stop
Once they ask the employees in the area what makes them happy...
Among these 2 who wrote that their son was accepted into a school
There was 1 happy that caught our attention
What exactly was this one about?
In the past burglars have broken into my store
ehh~
On the last day of a long holiday
[ Going after their sales money ]
So I've really been on guard
and hiding the cash in a bunch of different places
Today went ok
ah that's great
[ Happy to not get burglarized ]
arigatou gozaimasu
And there's others
[ The first meal paid with our daughter's first paycheck ]
That's wonderful
[ Birth of my grandchild ]
grandchildren
Here as well...all the happy people
filmed the MV with plenty of smiles on their faces
Next they're heading to Kumagaya's Sports & Culture Park
Here with the Tokyo Olympics in sight
there's some people here training really hard however....
ah! They're playing!
They're practicing
Is this rugby?
Its women's rugby!
Never seen this before
Seen practicing here
with a guaranteed spot in the Tokyo Olympics
is Japan's National Team for 7 women rugby the Sakura Sevens
From these athletes preparing for the Olympics
they'll get energy and happy from them
as they all dance together
First they'll ask about something recent that made them happy
Among the answers is this story about how extreme rugby can be
My nose which got bent up and crooked
I finally got my nose straightened out
[ Reconstructive surgery happy ]
That's great
During practice I collided with someone
and that bent my nose out of shape
[ broken nose ]
I had the reconstructive surgery over golden week
Since there was a match
I left it crooked
[ Played with a broken nose ]
With these athletes who are constantly competing
many of them said their happy was a day off or a chance to relax
Here's all the replies from the Sakura Sevens...and then
Since you've come all the way out here to Kumagaya
if you'd like to participate in our practice
eh join in?  ehhh~
no no...you're already in your track suits
[ All ready to go ]
That's some variety right there
sure fine...we'll do it
[ Improvement of variety skills in progress ]
Even though they happen to be in track suits
they'll join the Sakura Sevens practice
First they'll start with the basic catch
With the ball falling out of the air
OK
make a solid catch without letting it hit the ground
So then...who wants to give it a shot?
Who will it be?
kowai~
Why are you all looking at me?
[ In tough times go with Takayama ]
First it'll be Takayama taking on the Kick Catch
here goes
ah that's all wrong
[ Why volleyball? ]
Like you're cradling a baby
Cradling a baby
hai...ganbarimasu
OHHHHH~
Got it!  So happy....arigatou gozaimasu
sugoi
arigatou gozaimasu
I did it
Next is when they fight for the ball
they'll get to experience the line out set play
The ball will be coming in from over there but
at the right moment
they lift you up
OHHHH~
You'll do that one for us
I want to do it~
[ Minami wants to try it ]
[ Hoshino's LINE OUT ]
Try to time your jump with when you yell "UP!"
Here goes then...everybody ready?
UP! YAHHHHHHH!!!
[ The loudest scream ever in Hoshino's lifetime ]
You're supposed to jump
Please jump at the same time you say "UP"
ah kowai....here goes
UP! YAHHHHHH!!!!
[ Happens every time ]
[ Shiraishi's LINE OUT ]
UP!
YAHH!!
[ Happens to everyone ]
UP!
OHHH!
arigatou gozaimasu
Finally they'll film them all dancing
To the Sakura Sevens
we'll be cheering for you at the Tokyo Olympics
The next 3 to dance with all the happy people are Suzuki...Kubo....and Sato
We've arrived in Miyagi
yes!
Its Miyagi...didn't you grow up around here?
That's right
With everyone coming to Miyagi
just by having a shoot out here
I'm already quite happy
[ Happy to have a shoot in her home area ]
This is...
so where are we right now?
So this is Matsushima
its famous for having 1 of the 3 of Japan's most scenic views
Today its sunny outside so the view will be beautiful
Its a place I really hope everyone gets to visit once in their lifetime
Thank goodness its sunny....so true
Perfect atmosphere too
These 3 are searching for happy people at
Shiogama City in Miyagi
So this place is Shiogama's Fish Wholesale Market
The locals and even tourists
gather here to check out the freshly caught fish of Shiogama
Ever been here before?
I have! I've been here several times
Is that so? Yes it is
Here in Shiogama
because of the massive Tohoku Earthquake
this was a region that suffered a lot of damage
But at this fish market you won't detect much damage from the tsunami
They reopened for business 2 months after the quake
Its become a symbol of the thriving Shiogama
Really fresh isn't it?
Its mega fresh
uwah! Look at the ikura
That looks so good
Inside the market they've called out to this okaasan
it turns out she's got a surprising happy
Just now
at 10:25
from my 3rd born son
his first child was born
Are you serious?
[ Grandchild born just an hour ago ]
arigatou gozaimasu
How many grandchildren do you have?
My eldest son has 3
so this is #4
That sounds nice....cute baby then?
So incredibly cute
Even for this man who watched the location shoot with a smile
once we ask him for what makes him happy
The energy within Shiogama is the best
The smiles on everyone's faces here is true happiness
Its been 8 years since the recovery
of course the city has gone through some changes
its the look on everybody's faces
Everyone's enjoying themselves which includes the people at this market
but people are visiting
The area is revitalized
I'm truly grateful for that
These cheerful people in the Shiogama Market
also joined in the dance for the MV
The next place they're heading to
was damaged by the earthquake
Its a place that was opened to display the greatness of Tohoku's sea life
Sendai Umino-mori Aquarium
The goal here
is while gathering more happy stories
much like the seals that can clap for you
they'll film the MV together with a sea lion
And with that...in order to meet the sea lion
once they make their way into its habitat...
konnichiwa
konnichiwa!
This sea lion is a little girl
Kahlua-chan
onegaishimasu
Skilled performer Kahlua-chan was going to clap for them however
All right here goes
[ Handstand feet clap ]
ehh~ sugoi
The beat's a little fast though
The chimpanzee was clapping too fast for the beat too
[ Not concerned about rhythm ]
Kahlua-chan who gave a nice clapping performance also has a present to give
Sato will represent the group and crouch down to receive the gift
Please do not move even the slightest bit
Here goes
kawaii
The sea lion stole her lips with a passionate kiss however
all the guests who came for the show
danced along with Kahlua-chan for the MV
After collecting all the happy
the shoot to get the clapping is complete
Kissed you on the lips then Sato?
yes furthermore right before that they fed it a fish so
[ raw fish flavored kisses ]
smelled like raw fish then
after the kiss
Was it trying to feed you the fish?
[ passing the fish mouth to mouth? ]
All the members went to different regions around the country
and collected a bunch of happy
This is the original MV for the show
dozo!
[ The hotel bed ]
[ Taking a taxi... ]
taking a taxi....
[ Waterfall tour with the family ]
These your own happy items?
Keep on passing it on like this then
ah kawaii~
[ My coughing stopped!! ]
Your coughing stopped just like that?
There he is!
the hair removal guy
Sakura Sevens
ah that's the choreography
ah there it is...the surprise wedding reception
Of course there's a bunch of happy people at a wedding
Is she crying?
The animal series here
That really is amazing
skydiving
cute kid
What is a spotted eel? I've never seen one before
[ Turning 46 ]
[ Finding my golf ball ]
ah kawaii
That's kind of amazing...that's good
They're all in sync...that's good
ah the sea lion is doing it
ahh sugoi
kakkoii
May 29th...[Sing Out!] was released
Its a really fun and catchy song
so please give it a listen
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
that's the end
hai...sayonara