DON!
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
We are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And they are Nogizaka-chan
I'll read your fortune
And with that
Himura-san....tell them what's on todays show
here it goes
Get your Reiwa era fortune read!
Rei-1 Grand Prix!
We've now moved into the Reiwa era
and the members fortunes will definitely undergo a major change
and with that tonight
we'll check the members fortunes for the Reiwa era
The sensei who has come to analyze their fortunes is...
Fortune!
hai....dozo....dozo
This seems to have caused a commotion...sensei
Your name please....
if you would
My name is Fortune Nakada
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
Your fortune telling sensei will be Fortune Nakada-san
You sure that's not Nakada Kana?
I'm Fortune Nakada
You look like Nakada Kana though
People tell me I look like her
[ Pretending that Nakada Kana is a different person ]
It appears you just started and are self-taught but
Hamaguchi-san's brother really
he came on the show a long time ago
He's been on before
Hamaguchi-san correct
You were put under his guidance
So you got the true experience
hai
That's Kana!
[ True identity exposed ]
That's not Fortune Nakada-san
in that picture....that's our Nakada Kana
nope....that's Fortune Nakada right there
[ Loose interpretation of the rules ]
And with that today
Nakada under the guidance of Yoiko's Hamaguchi Masaru's little brother
the popular tarot fortune teller
Hamaguchi Yoshiyuki
she studied authentic tarot card reading as his pupil
Together with Hamaguchi-sensei using tarot cards
they'll predict the fortunes of the members in the first year of Reiwa
and they'll announce the highlights they found
Rei-1 Grand Prix
First its the top 2 in money luck for year 1 of the Reiwa Era
and then who got the worst
yes...the 3 people I've picked for these money luck rankings
Inoue-san
Shiraishi-san
and Suzuki-san
ah its these 3
The top 2 and last place in the money luck category are Inoue...Shiraishi...Suzuki
wait why such the grim looks over there?
Nobody wants that last place
Suzuki is making a totally grim face over there
Think you'll come in last?
ahhh....that's such a grim look on your face
Are you thinking your luck with money is bad?
I do not believe so
[ Suddenly denies her previous comment ]
You just said you thought you'd have bad money luck
You thought it would be bad so you made a face
I'm a little confused
Shiraishi
hai
what do you think?
In the past I was told I had a supreme ruler line
[ Good money luck in her palm readings ]
I'd like
some good money luck
Inoue....Inoue looks like she's got luck
I bet she's got real good luck with money
Well?
I'm not sure if I have good money luck or not but I do know that I love money luck
She made that one clear
In 2nd place of Fortune Nakada's money luck rankings is...
Its Shiraishi Mai
[ Money luck 2nd place - Shiraishi Mai ]
That's 2nd place
But 2nd place is still pretty good
That's 2nd among all the members
which is like top of all of Japan
Well here's her card
This is The Lovers card
The Lovers card can apply to your money luck as well
and its really good
its a fun and cheerful type
of time period for you when this card appears
Its a really good
card to get
got it
You seem to be laughing...you ok?
Could you get more specific here?
Like when will this happen?
I am curious about that
So for that part....well
Yocchan-sensei
ehh...he will explain the rest
And with that providing the details on the results of their fortunes
will be Yocchan-sensei located in a separate room
Yocchan-sensei!
Yocchan-sensei
hai
Shiraishi's money luck
she got 2nd place of all the senbatsu members
She's always had a steady fortune power
and the same applies to her luck with money
She needs to be in love with herself
and if she treats herself importantly
this will be really important in the last half of 2019
if she takes proper breaks
that'll stabilize her money luck and then in 2020
after that....her money luck will explode
[ Money luck big bang ]
She's currently 2nd
you're saying its possible she could break away from everyone in 2020?
That's right....she could skyrocket
Within Nogizaka it always seems Shiraishi is about to skyrocket
[ Poised to skyrocket ]
sumimasen
well Nakada...ah Fortune
That's Fortune Nakada....hai
Did she interpret that card correctly?
yes....she nailed it
[ Lenient towards his disciple ]
She passed it immediately to sensei though
arigatou gozaimasu
Nervous aren't you?
kowai~
scary isn't it
You must be confident though Inoue
With these fortune tellings I've always gotten #1 in money luck
[ Mutual love with money luck ]
I guess Suzuki will be last place then
Will 1st place in money luck go to the confident Inoue?
Or could it be Suzuki?
Inoue Sayuri
That's amazing...she got 1st
[ The money dance ]
Must be pretty happy
That's incredible
of course this girl got 1st
money!
[ Capitalistic idol ]
No need to shout out money like that
You got 1st
So she's 1st place in money luck sensei...why is that?
Yes her card is right here
She got the Justice card
This card means she maintains a balance
and that balance may also apply to her income and spending
that's what it means when this card appears
She's got super stable money luck
seriously?
you hear that?
ah thank goodness
I'm so happy
so happy
Do you have any advice for her?
well...
well
Yocchan-sensei will explain all the details
You're the same as an untouched magazine on a magazine rack
[ unpopular fortune teller ]
Let's ask Yocchan-sensei for a little more detail
hai
In the latter half of 2019
her money luck will be incredibly stable
and in this time period
any money that she uses she'll be able to recoup
as a part of that her assets and her asset management
if she were able to get advice from someone that's good at investing
she would even further
increase her good money luck
You did it
I've really done it
That means Suzuki came in last place for money luck in the 1st year of Reiwa
eh her card is right here
eh the Devil card
that's the card that appeared
The Devil card?
Looks similar to the Justice card though
Whenever money luck appears
it sends her to money loan and debt hell
no no...not debt hell
That's it?
[ sensei yoroshiku ]
There's more
The Devil card leads to a pattern of getting deceived
So then in money related manners its like "Please don't trust everyone"
that's an important point
As far as business ventures and work
its possible that she will get scammed
yabai
scam?
And doing that will lead to big failure
understood
So she should be careful with anything that sounds suspicious
with people to go that far
matters involving money or business
once she starts thinking not to put faith in people
she'll constantly have her guard up
But Suzuki is an idol...to not trust people
[ No trust in humanity idol ]
People involved in her work
the people standing here...to not trust them
[ Impossible work environment ]
Its not good to become that type of person
But its good to know so you can be careful
[ Who is this new fortune teller thats coming on to take on Fortune Nakada? ]
Is she acting?
Acting like someone who got last place?
Its gotten really gloomy...anything you can do to help Suzuki?
Fortune Nakada-sensei
Something for good fortune
There's nothing
[ No traces of positivity ]
That's a lot of despair
She didn't give out her fortune
But it'll be ok because today
we have another amazing sensei
for those with bad fortune
they've got ways of improving your fortune
so...Takayama-sensei
Takayama-sensei you've got a way then
I've got something perfect for Ayane-chan
There's a lot of senseis here
She's involved in this stuff too
Takayama has been into telling your fortune from your name
she looked up all the members names on a fortune telling site
Her results for Suzuki are...
overall then....could you please move your hand
Move your hand for us?
huh? Overall its bad fortune?
[ Even her name causes bad fortune ]
According to kanji stroke counts that is true
But for Ayane-chan
if we were to simply change her first name...
You want to rename her?
What kind of names then?
Names such as Suzuki Doremi
Doremi?
Using kanji for 1,2,3?
You write it as Hifumi but its pronounced Doremi
Doremi?
There's also Suzuki Kiki-san
Kiki?
Suzuki Nanami-san
Nanami
Written with 7-7-7?
Using numbers
Suzuki...this is a chance to give yourself a stage name
What do you like? Doremi sounds cute
What's wrong? Got a nosebleed?
If you had to pick...which one would you like?
Doremi
Your fortune is that bad...you've got to get a name change
definitely
Isn't that right Doremi?
hey I'm talking to you
[ Fully accept your name change! ]
You have to respond when someone calls out Doremi
Now then tell everyone your name is Doremi
My name is
Suzuki Doremi
ah kawaii~
cute wasn't it
I was expecting it to be funny but its really good....use that!
Himura-san with an emphatic "use that!"
[ Doremi is a good one ]
Here according to Fortune....other than Suzuki
here are some members who better watch their money luck
This is bad...who is it?
Akimoto Manatsu
[ Watch out for your money luck Akimoto Manatsu ]
What card did she get?
Its this one...the High Priestess card
it came up reversed
ah its called the High Priestess card
high priestess
She'll get all jittery
as well as irritated because of this card
How are you actually right now?
Feeling irritated?
nope....I've been mostly stress free
You're good?
You have a tendency to get defensive and lose money
That means you should stay away from gambling
That would be dangerous
You need to be careful not to waste your money
and really dig into whether you need to make that purchase
is it really something necessary
Are you aware of anything like this?
I don't really have the image of someone that wastes money
furthermore there isn't much that really irritates me
the amount of job offers I'm seeing
is this why I'm not making much money?
[ Seeking a pay raise? ]
However don't worry about a thing
Takayama-sensei has new names for her that will boost her money luck
If we were to keep the name Akimoto
then its her first name....
so right here
what kind of names?
Akimoto Nadeko?
Nadeko?
hai
written with the kanji for snow and collapse and child
Looks like avalanche but its Nadeko
and the others?
Akimoto Maro-san
Maro
what else?
I've also got Akimoto Tomiko-san
Tomiko? Tomiko sounds good
Which one should I get?
Its better if you go ahead and pick out the name you like
Then I'll be Akimoto Tomiko
Akimoto Tomiko sounds good
If you'd introduce yourself to everyone
I am Nogizaka46 Akimoto Tomiko
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
That's not bad
not bad at all
I'm Akimoto Tomiko
Rei-1 Grand Prix
Next its the Reiwa career luck rankings...here are 3 people we're curious about
ehh...Ikuta
Iwamoto
Umezawa
hai...ehhh Ikuta...Iwamoto..Umezawa
Among these 3 its the top 2 and worst as far as career luck
You 3 were called up here because of your career luck..Ikuta
do you believe you'll have good career luck?
ehhh
They've let me continue my work in theater so
it would be great if I could keep doing this
Iwamoto how about you?
I had no expectations going into this
so I'm not sure
Do you think yours could be bad fortune?
I'm thinking I might have the bad fortune
Umezawa
Yours is probably good...you've been active doing stuff
magazines and such
I've got a bad feeling about this
You definitely want good career luck
first we'll announce 2nd place
Ikuta Erika
[ Career luck 2nd place - Ikuta Erika ]
hai
Here was her card
eh the Judgement card
So for this one
When good news is coming
this card will appear
Its a very good card
That means she'll keep getting good career luck then?
That's it exactly
Yocchan-sensei will explain all the details
[ quick pass ]
all finished....already all finished
This year starting in October
that's when her career luck gets especially good
Starting in October?
That's really pinpointed
And then next year in 2020
a new door of opportunity will open for her
idol...singer...musical...something other than that?
Its something other than that
You'll use your musical experience to possibly....spread beyond Japan
We're counting on you
It really seems you'll exceed anything in my range of imagination
Anything could come true
Of all the fortune tellings I've had this one made me the happiest
This is the happiest one
But he says something is definitely coming your way this fall
Fall? But isn't this kind of setting my expectations super high?
what if October comes around and I'm at home waiting for something to happen
[ Preparing for hibernation? ]
That's fine...just stay active with something
Ikuta could get cast into something
Someone got even better luck
These 2
which one got 1st place and which one last?
Don't want that last place right?
But one of you is last
Fortune Nakada has led us to this point
who is the owner of the strongest career luck?
Iwamoto Renka
[ Career luck 1st place Iwamoto Renka ]
You got 1st place...1st!
omedetou
You're 1st place Iwamoto
She can't even believe it
Hard to believe isn't it
I can't believe it
1st place
Getting 1st place among all the Nogizaka senbatsu members is a respectable 1st place
And here is her card
The Empress card
Empress?
What's this card mean?
So this card...
as a woman the card is very alluring
and this one isn't just career luck
among the members its the strongest good fortune
strongest good fortune
hai
eh I'm so happy...
happy aren't you
eh...what is this for? that good fortune applies to everything?
well Yocchan-sensei will explain it
[ Receive and pass drill ]
To explain how great this card is
since your career is idol
the Empress
is someone that stands at the top of everyone
eh Iwamoto is 1st place in this
But among all idols this seems like the best card to get then?
yes as far as fortune power holding this card is the best
from now on...there's more and more coming for her
Things will start to become concentrated on her
this will happen when she's 18
Not yet? How old are you?
That's in another 3 years
She still has to wait 3 years
Hold on now...3 years later is one thing but she got 1st place now
The preliminary arrangements for all that have started
That sounds really good
Its all good for you from now on
ehh...so happy
Must be happy
Isn't that amazing Umezawa?
[ 1st place is blinding ]
omedetou!
Last place in career luck Umezawa
the analysis of her fortune telling is...
The card she got is right here
The Moon
moon?
hai
That seems like good fortune though
Well take a look at this face on the moon
the face looks extremely worried
The eyes are closed and he's looking concerned
So like anxiety
or concern...its those time periods when this card appears
concern and anxiety
hai
Yocchan-sensei
Need Yocchan-sensei then....Yocchan-sensei
The Moon card also serves as a warning
you must be cautious
It doesn't mean bad fortune
warning?
It means she'll get involved in some trouble
even if she thinks she's not involved in something
she could still end up getting framed for something
Someone that she respects
its possible she will be betrayed by that person
Suddenly she'll lose all trust in people
She'll cast a suspicious eye on things and try to avoid things
Having constant distrust of everyone
that sounds like a disgruntled idol
Maybe you shouldn't even pay much attention to what Yocchan-sensei says
Even after hearing my analysis you could get your fortune read somewhere else
[ fortune telling 2nd opinion ]
Coming in last place maybe being suspicious of this result is a good thing
but still.....ganbare
You'll be fine
Its ok because for Umezawa
Takayama-sensei
[ Don't forget about Takayama ]
Do you have a way to improve her fortune?
Yes I do...so
In Umezawa's case this looks pretty good
but let's go ahead and change that Umezawa part
You're going to change the Umezawa part?
Lately Ume has been in a lot of names
its getting used a lot
That's true...shall we keep the Umezawa?
What have you determined sensei?
The last name is really bad
Umezawa is bad fortune....its bad fortune
If we have to keep Umezawa then she'll have to become Doremi
[ Stuck with Doremi ]
If that happened
this group would have 2 Doremis in it
[ Doremi traffic jam ]
What else do you have other than Umezawa Doremi?
I've got Arare
Arare....Arare sounds cute
It is cute
By the way in case she wants to keep her Minami
if I were to change Umezawa it would be these
Takamizawa Minami
Muro....Murofushi
Murofushi Minami
That last one is amazing
Minami Minami
kawaii kawaii
That's like Macaulay Macaulay Culkin Culkin
Minami Minami
But if she changed her name it would be hard to call out her name
She looks like a Takamizawa
If she kept the Umezawa
How about the cute sounding Doremi?
Does Doremi bring that much good fortune?
[ The ultimate of names...Doremi ]
You're good with Doremi right?
Umezawa Doremi
I guess I'll be Doremi
And with Suzuki
everyone be careful
be careful....once you yell out Doremi 2 people will turn around
[ The Nogizaka Doremi problem ]
You'll be the low pitched Doremi
And she'll be the high pitch Doremi
That's a good one
She's tall so she gets the high pitch
1 octave higher Doremi
Doremi~  Doremi~
So if you'd introduce yourself
eh I am Nogizaka46 Umezawa Doremi
oh that's good
And then this year
she'll be playing a much larger role in their activities....Saito Asuka
So for 2019 this Hierophant card
it means she will show the way
She'll instruct people
as well as teach and display leader characteristics
she'll take the viewpoint of instructor
and take care of her kouhais and spend time with them
furthermore doing that will move herself in a positive direction
that's how it'll turn out
Thats what he says
eh I haven't really
Not that type?
I haven't really taught the kouhais anything
[ Asuka's way of letting them be ]
Taught them nothing
So she should actually be teaching
yes there should be occasional people coming up to you for guidance
at those times be like "its better to think of it like this"
once she says those words
it will really have an effect on that person
and that girl will give it her best
and you'll see your teachings be reflected somewhere
Asuka-san's good fortune would then explode
ah...we've got the perfect person....Umezawa!
[ The lost and confused Doremi ]
ehh~
What do I need to work harder on?
you mean at work? yes
But Umezawa-sensei
well
she's a hard worker
she properly understands what's happening around her
and she's tall
she's got a lot of good things going for her
ah but just now
she became Doremi-chan right
We've got the 2 Doremi's sitting next to each other
Doremi...Doremi
[ Tulip sisters ]
she got the name but
She's supposed to be the high pitched Doremi-chan right?
and you have to treat your own name preciously
but when she did her self-intro just now
the way she said "I'm Doremi" was quite low pitched
only the last part was high
Ikuta-sensei even had to complain about it
That was low pitched
[ Pays attention to musical scales ]
What should it sound like?
do-re-mi~
[ Ikuta looking for precision ]
She has to reach that high a pitch then?
Umezawa could you do that with your name then?
do-re-mi
That's not bad....not bad
How about Suzuki?
Suzuki do a normal one
do-re-mi
ah just a bit off-key
[ Harsh criticism from Ikuta-sensei ]
She was off-key? off-key?
[ Here is Fortune Nakada in the middle of a tarot card reading ]
That's all!  Fortune!
Its all over
Nogizaka46
Midsummer Nationwide Tour 2019
3rd round of priority ticketing for mobile members
and general ticketing for the Fukuoka concert is underway
And then general ticketing for the Nagoya concert date
ticket sales are still ongoing
You can find the details on the Nogizaka46 homepage
This is the only place where you can shine
Its too precious
of a time period
Its about to be released
Nogizaka46's highly anticipated documentary
the 2nd chapter
[ Itsu no manika, Koko ni Iru ]
Documentary of Nogizaka46
On July 5th it'll be a nationwide roadshow
Graduation...seems like you won't know what it feels like until you're the one actually graduating