For the 2nd week of this broadcast
the 23rd single
this is the [Sing Out!] prayer for a hit campaign
In order to create an original MV for the show
from different regions nationwide
they're collecting happy stories from people
And then along with the song
they're shooting some clap and dance scenes for us
Since so many people helped out
we still have many more scenes that have not yet aired
And with that the theme of today's show is bonus campaign scenes
of course there's unaired scenes
but also a dance scene with the Yokohama Arena fans
all of it is coming shortly
First these 4 were heading to
to Kumagaya Saitama and here are their happy bonus scenes
Actually at the rest stop
they also met these angels
kawaii~
He's smiling
[ Baby-chan ]
Much larger than those newborn babies from earlier
This baby likes to smile
The name?
Takeshi...the name is Takeshi
Your baby really likes people
Around men...
he gets really timid though
[ Natural born fondness for women? ]
While they have this rare chance
they'll attempt to hold Takeshi-kun
He's really huge
Takeshi-kun
kawaii
konnichiwa~
[ Unexpectedly good at this? ]
kawaii
Takeshi
Takeshi-kun
kawaii
He definitely likes being around girls
up to now its been all smiles for Takeshi-kun however
Its my 1st time holding a baby
[ Minami....concerned ]
Seems scary...definitely don't want to drop a baby
You ok?
Please don't cry
oh! He's got my hair
[ Takeshi-kun also feeling nervous? ]
ahhh~ gomennasai
[ Now he's crying ]
ah he's smiling
okaasan sugoi
She's good at this
she's really good
[ Has prior child raising experience? ]
kawaii~
How come Shiraishi?
You know how to do this?
I studied nursing
After this wonderful meeting at the rest stop
they received happy from the Sakura Sevens getting ready for the Tokyo Olympics
The 4 of them joined in on one of their practices
it turns out they did a couple more things at practice
Up first
Hoshino and Shiraishi gave it a try
the Line Out practice
Now its Ikuta's turn
uwah~ this is scary
remember to jump
hai
here goes
YAHHHH!!!
[ That scream had some sustain ]
arigatou gozaimasu
That's a max score in the thrill department...so fun
[ Sounds like a theme park ride ]
And Takayama will try it too
kowai
Please jump with all you've got
yes here goes
That was mega high up
You did very good but
please don't forget to catch the ball
[ Amazing sky high ]
arigatou gozaimasu...arigatou gozaimasu
And then...
the rugby tackle
Is tackling something anybody can do?
It'll be fine
First she'll show them how its done
tackle?
[ Bones will be broken? ]
The 4 of you
will protect
Hey you can't run away!
[ In the end it's Takayama ]
Can the 4 of them stand up to the tackle?
This is pretty scary
[ Pretty much all up to Takayama ]
eh hold on this is scary...kowai kowai
AUGH! AUGHHH!! AUGHHHHH!!!
[ Tackle had some pity attached to it ]
I can take a little more!
[ More motivation here than your average person ]
a little more please
Will she prevent the tackle this time?
I'll add a little more power to this one
YAHHHHHH!!
[ Tackle comedy skit? ]
[ Coming up its more unaired bonus scenes! ]
All of you look so cool doing this
I'm happy I could experience a little bit of what you do
Maiyan are you going to get into rugby?
Yes I'm going to start playing rugby
Next is these 4 heading to Kagoshima...here are their happy bonus scenes
This is pretty much the southern region of Kagoshima
we've arrived
As a happy spot
this is quite a popular place
konnichiwa~  konnichiwa~
We are from Nogizaka46
we've heard this is known as a happy spot
and have come
What sort of happy spot is it?
This is Japan's only
seahorse aquaculture facility
The seahorses here represent happy
Is that so?
Once you meet a seahorse good things happen to you
eh? ehhh~
I had no idea
What is the happy seahorse all about?
wah! sugoi
[ Seahorses look like dragons ascending into the skies so its a sign of good luck ]
See how its stomach
expands out and looks all white
This is a male
[ male seahorse ]
The female takes care of the eggs using a pouch
then inside the male stomach
the female deposits the eggs
The male gives birth
Is that so?
Also the image of the female leaving the eggs to the male
happens to look like a heart
This is the seahorse symbol of happiness
With all that happy packed in
these are seahorses of good fortune
This time they have special permission to touch the seahorses
If a seahorse curls up around you its a sign of really good fortune
eh? Is that so?
First Inoue and Shinuchi will take the challenge
eh sugoi
It curled around me!
They're really soft
They're soft?
And on Inoue's finger as well
ah it curled around my finger
sugoi
Why do they just come up to you like that?
Next Ozono and Umezawa will try it
looking good
They all run from me....
In the end Ozono never received any happy and that's time up
that left us with 1 unhappy Ozono
Next up these 3 were heading to
Miyagi and here are their happy bonus scenes
Inside Shiogama's Fish Wholesale Market
there were people who told us about their wonderful happy
Since the day of the shoot happened to be Mother's Day there was this suggestion
Is there any sort of message
you'd like to give your mother?
Most of all "thanks for giving birth to me"
Well with those feelings of gratitude
would you like to convey that same message on tv?
[ Suddenly getting up in his personal business ]
This somewhat bashful son
will give his mother a carnation filled with his gratitude
As a mother's day present this is to say thanks for giving birth to me
In the future...
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
arigatou gozaimasu
wonderful
Please give it your best
arigatou gozaimasu
This strategy of pressuring people into making it a happy mother's day
they found more people who would give their mothers a carnation
So actually
of the products they sell here
you can buy what you like
and there's places to eat it
For example there's a place that will grill your food
it can be grilled for you to eat
They'll also turn it into a rice bowl for you if you'd like
Would you like to have some?
Let's eat!
The 3 of them bought fatty tuna, shrimp and ikura
A place that sells rice bowl dishes
let them use their own ingredients
and they were able to create their own original rice bowls
Here's what it looks like
[ Original tuna, shrimp, and ikura rice bowl ]
Look at how the shrimp turned out...its saying "please don't eat me"
itadakimasu
itadakimasu~
That looks nice
ikura oishii~
pop pop pop
Now that they've satisfied their hunger
once again the interviews start
Something they've heard about
any items you've bought at the market
can be made into an original omelet for you
and here are some of the employees
What exactly makes these two happy?
Someone I was interested in contacted me on LINE
Teenager type drama
Are you the same age?
We're the same age
What's he like?
He's funny
and he's handsome!
Can't wait to see what happens
I felt a kyun kyun just now
I'll be cheering for you
and yours....onegaishimasu
[ Saved up enough money ]
I had a savings goal set
I worked hard to save up my money
I saved off a bunch of money
The person you're interested in...what happens next?
I hope we can hit it off
and be able to talk comfortably with each other
same grade? same grade
different class? same class!
This wonderful teenager happy
arigatou gozaimashita
Next for the last part of the MV
its the clapping scene with Bananaman and Nogizaka
On that day after recording....
That was great
excuse me...
all of us kind of have a favor to ask Bananaman-san
So we're making an original MV for the show
we'd like to get some scenes here too
eh...not sure if I can dance
[ Fully motivated? ]
And with that first they'll ask them what makes them happy
hai
[ 46 years old ]
A little earlier...my birthday was April 23rd
same day as Wada right?
That's right
I turned 46
so now I can do this move...I am 46!
[ Shitara46 ]
Next...what makes Himura happy?
Found a golf ball
No this is really incredible...before I had
received a golf ball with the Nogizaka mark on it
To verify the golf ball is mine
I wrote [日] on it
Before I used to hit a lot of balls out of bounds
and I'd lose them
The other day I went to the golf course and hit one out of bounds
I couldn't find the ball I hit but
I found the ball from back then!
[ Reunion happy ]
I'm sure it was mine since it had [日] on it
That made me considerably happy
Finally everyone clapped along to the song
this warm scene closed out the music video
And lastly
the grand dance scene with the fans in Yokohama Arena
Here we'll show you a little of what happened behind the scenes
The main part of the show had finished
and it was time for the encore
Currently for Nogizaka Under Construction
we're creating an original [Sing Out!] MV just for the show
Today we're going to film part of it
right here
Its an easy dance choreography
so if you'd all dance along with us
The choreography lecture will be given by
Akimoto Manatsu super sensei
onegaishimasu
Please leave this to me!
Please bring out both your hands
And with that the mega dance lesson with 15,000 fans starts
Once...
Twice....
on the 3rd one clasp your hands
and raise it just like that
And then here
chomp...chomp....chomp....chomp
Do that 4 times
now close
now open
then raise just the right hand
That's all there is to it
What do you think everybody?
Feels good right
So that right there
the people who think they're too cool to do that
you'll be making a huge mistake
[ Don't be self-conscious! ]
Have fun with it
onegaishimasu...here's the 1st one
onegai itashimasu
I'd like to start it
And with that this is the [Sing Out!] fan version
dozo
Here it comes
Perhaps it was because of Asuka's warning
but many people did their best to remember and perform the dance
there was a major sense of unity in the building
All of you too
please sing LA LA LA along with us
Everybody...give me more
please sing for us a little more
The Nogizaka members
and the 15,000 fans created
an incredible live atmosphere
Here the Under coupling song
we bring you this studio live performance of [Kassouro]
[ Next week...for real this time!  We're going to uncover the personalities of the 2nd members ]
[ I have a message for you - Yamashita Mizuki ]
These last 1 or 2 months
in that time I've been shooting this drama
I've been involved with that everyday
Actually during this period of time
almost half the year is over and I've only spent
about 2 weeks as an active Nogizaka46 member
Its like this is the current situation
[ Yamashita is not in the 23rd single ]
[ Its her 1st time experiencing the feeling of being left out of a single ]
This work I'm getting
getting these different jobs
even though its all thanks to the group
I haven't been able to contribute to that group
sugoi
I personally....
its like
I personally blame myself
I feel like I'm really lacking what it takes
Being able to return to Nogizaka again
I'm personally looking really forward to it so
this summer
I'd like to go all out and do the best I can
[ Yamashita Mizuki ]
[ Makes her return at Nagoya Dome for the Nationwide Summer Tour ]
[ 2019 summer tour - 2nd round of priority ticketing for mobile members starts after the show ]
And here....they announced their graduations recently
its greetings from Ito Karin and Saito Yuuri
We've done a lot of fun episodes with these two
arigatou gozaimasu
It'll be sad without you
One by one then...your message for the fans
And if there's any memories you have from this show
hai
I was always an Under member so
because of that I didn't get to be on the show too much but
but when I did come on
I felt like Bananaman-san would give you a lot of freedom to do what you want
so I started speaking up a bunch
and it felt like I was getting a lot of chances here
In the future as well
I'm staying in show business so I'll do my best
You're doing it then
ah that's great
I'm thinking it'll be little by little
We'll probably meet up again somewhere
Also there were all kinds of
episodes that you helped with behind the scenes
If you ever need a year end "Nogizaka46 trendy words of the year award" episode
[ Self-promotion ]
hai arigatou gozaimashita
otsukaresama
arigatou gozaimasu....otsukaresama deshita
And Saito Yuuri
yes you've taken good care of me all the way from NogiDoko to NogiChuu
To all the fans that watched....arigatou gozaimasu
My favorite episodes from NogiChuu
the game episodes
The competition where you split us up between the Himura unit
and Shitara-unit....there were a bunch of those episodes
In your track suits
That's right
So those allowed us to move around
I thought those episodes were so much fun
To not do those anymore kind of makes me sad but
since I'll still be in show business
ah really
hai
I'll be doing the best I can from here on out
Really the 2 of you
you 2 are so cheerful
Yes they brighten up everything
You really helped us out
It'll be gloomy from now on without them
I don't think that'll happen
arigatou gozaimasu
Ito Karin
Saito Yuuri
Congratulations on your graduations!
omedetou!