DON!
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
We are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And they are Nogizaka-chan
YAAAY~
1st members....2nd members
2nd members~
Please don't act all ashamed
On todays show....Himura-san
hai
onegaishimasu
I still want to know more! Great things about the 2nd members!
Today its Hori and Shinuchi?
You're doing this?
We can let you handle this?
yes please leave this to us
Then is it ok if we go back to the dressing room?
[ You 2 especially need to know more about them! ]
Our Yomiuriland shoot was put up on the internet
Its been 6 years since they joined
in various ways they've shared lots of experiences with the 1st members
On the show few 2nd member topics got brought up for discussion
this time once again to let you know the great things about the 2nd members
Hori and Shinuchi have created the 2nd members timeline
The history of the 2nd members and their activities
we'll use this timeline to reflect back on them
Shinuchi was actually a 2nd member then?
[ Has that grizzled veteran vibe ]
2nd member
Since I'm the oldest
its easy to get it confused
People think you're a 0 member
[ In the group before they even debuted? ]
In 2012...December was the start of recruiting a new audition class
I see so Nogizaka was formed in 2011
This started in 2012?
December is when they started looking for new members
The 2nd members joined the group that early on then?
That's right...about a year since the group was formed
I figured it was like about 3 years afterwards
That happened relatively quick
happened pretty quick
hai
And then in March 2013
the 14 2nd members were selected
In May the 2nd members made their 1st appearance on NogiDoko
It was that long ago?
yes that's right
It seems we have video of the 2nd members 1st appearance
please watch along
[ Ito Junna's 1st appearance at age 14 ]
Favorite foods
kompeito sugar candy
What is kompeito candy?
This is your favorite from all the food in the entire world
and you say its kompeito?
This is your favorite then?
it is
really?
I really like it
So if there was like a conveyor belt of food like how they do sushi
here comes the fatty tuna
then the sea urchin
steak!
And then the kompeito
So you'd take the kompeito over all that?
I'd take it
You'd take that one?!
No way....even if you're starving
[ Kitano Hinako's 1st appearance at age 16 ]
Special skill...what?!
Her talent is magazine shredding
What do you mean? She shreds magazines?
onegaishimasu...dozo
hai
here goes
HAH!
working it pretty hard aren't you
You can probably still do that right?
Take that!
hai
sugoi
[ Shinuchi Mai's 1st appearance at age 21 ]
Tokyo Metro
you can name all the colors
hai
You can do it?
I can
The Touzai Line
that's bright blue
How about another one?
I guess not all blues are bright
The Mita line
You know the Toei Line too?
I can do the Toei Line
You know the Toei Line? yes
really?
What's your deal? You can name the Toei Line?
Who is this?
Who are you?
[ Sasaki Kotoko's 1st appearance at age 14 ]
eh favorite foods
Mentsuyu soup
Come on now
out of all the food in the world!?
Again if there was a conveyor belt of food
and if there's fatty tuna or sea urchin or meat going by
and then you see the kompeito and mentsuyu coming
You're taking that mentsuyu?
I'd take the mentsuyu
You like it that much
Nobody would want that kompeito
Well its that kind of restaurant
[ Terada Ranze's 1st appearance at age 14 ]
I'm 155cm tall
ah you're really 155cm tall?
yes
Your head is small
Kind of like Saito Asuka
Have you met Saito Asuka?
ah..I've met her
Isn't her head super tiny?  It is really tiny
They say you look like her
ah they do...yes
eh but you look like Ikuta too
But recently
Which of them do you want to look like?
[ Forbidden question ]
You don't have to answer that
[ Hori Miona's 1st appearance at age 16 ]
high speed blinking
hai
ready....start
fast...that's fast!
That's really fast
[ Suzuki Ayane's 1st appearance at age 14 ]
Favorite item
airplanes of all types...why'd you get into airplanes?
I don't know why
[ Can't believe she has no reason ]
There has to be a reason why you got into airplanes!
There has to be even the slightest of reasons to like planes...not completely zero
Maybe she likes the Airbus or something
Are you a fan of the Airbus 380 or something?
You saw one in the air and thought it looked cool....give me something
There's got to be a reason
There isn't
You fool!
[ Yamazaki Rena's 1st appearance at age 15 ]
Chaplin's speech in english
hai
To those who can hear me I say
Don't despair
The misery that is now upon us
is but the passing of greed
And the poverty they took from the people
will return to the people
And so long as men die
liberty will never perish
[ Watanabe Miria's 1st appearance at age 13 ]
You touch people's cheeks?
water
water rice cakes and rice cakes are the 3 categories
water is the softest level
rice cakes are the hardest level...which means the cheek has some spring to it
How about Himura?
ah...perfect
sewage isn't it
ahhhh sugee
Well obviously
its been about 5 years since then
there's been some changes....for us too...we were much younger
You've changed...all of your were childlike and didn't fool around
They're all so gorgeous now
That Chaplin stuff
Could you do that now?
I could probably do it
Could you do a little for us?
Be serious now
To those who can hear me I say don't despair
[ Panic... ]
Ito Junna...you still like that kompeito candy?
nope...I hate it
[ Destroyed ]
Hate is a little strong
Back then was it really your #1 favorite food? You said it was your #1
no...saying it was #1 was sort of a lie
[ Based on a useless character ]
That kompeito was a lie wasn't it
Kitano can you still shred magazines like that?
I've shredded a magazine within the last 6 months
This turned into a what's your talent episode
You still keep those skills fresh for 1 more show right
[ Sticking with her talent ]
A person who shreds magazines would get a lot of work
What was that water...water rice cakes thing about?
The hardness of your cheeks
for some reason I judged cheeks to be like water
You're still doing that one even now?
How about it?
For me that one...well yes
I'd like to put that one to rest
[ Miria's dark history ]
Saying you want to end it
all around the world its things like that which are starting up
There's a bunch of stuff like that
How about Himura-san? A lot of time has passed since last time
Give it a try
And with that after 6 years she'll reevaluate Himura's cheeks
Moisture is very important
That's true
How about it? What do you think?
Its sewage
Shut up!
[ Variety skills much improved ]
From that 1st appearance the 2nd members
hardly ever got called on the show
Sure seemed that way
About 6 months later for a senbatsu announcement
Miona suddenly became center
It was that one
The song Vanessa
[ Who's that? ]
You startled me
What is Vanessa?
ah [Barrette] wasn't it
I have no idea what Vanessa is
Even after that
I was expecting them to show up a little but they never came on
They really never appeared on Nogizakatte, Doko
That's right
In January 2014
Kitano
made her first senbatsu for the 8th single
in March I went from understudy to a regular member
I was promoted
That understudy system was only applied to the 2nd members?
just us
In Nogizaka history that's the only time they had understudy members?
That's right
So the 3rd and 4th members
they were left normal
Left as is
That's why the 2nd members have resentment for everybody
[ senpais that are hard to deal with ]
In those understudy days....a surprising normal day of work for them was?
I think even the 3rd and 4th members have experienced this one
Everyday you'd take pictures of yourself
and send them off as part of your daily routine
These used for something?
We sent them as practice for when we post to blogs and such
you only got replies for good pictures
Do the 3rd members do this?
I've done it
You have
Checking how you'd be perceived then?
Only the cute pictures of yourself well
those make you look good
So this was everyday?
You all did this everyday?
And then its hard to picture now...what work did they get as understudy members?
As far as other kinds of work
in the past there was this Christmas Live
For that show the senbatsu members would ride
a sleigh that was pulled by the rest of us
hai
So who pulled this sleigh?
It was myself and Kitano
Even the role of reindeer...since we were all understudies
It was like who's going to get to do it?
Fought over it?
It was fought over
You didn't think it was humiliating?
Since it was like we didn't have any work at all
this was finally a job for us
Even with being deer
Its not deer
[ The baka ruined it ]
This was the role you played though
You were not a deer
All of us lined up and it was like "Kitano and Shinuchi will be in it"
So you were happy to get it?
I couldn't even express happiness
Because of the other members
It was kind of severe
Sorry...the role of reindeer is all mine
[ Condescending reindeer ]
The scene with them as reindeer pulling the sleigh is right here
yada~
This brings back memories
Everybody's a reindeer then
ah that's you pulling the sleigh?
[ The dream job of reindeer ]
That's got to be painful
Its got to be painful to think about
It must hurt to watch this video
This has to hurt
Here we go~
the memories
This is so sad
They're singing though
But they're visible up there
Not getting any spotlight at all
But Hori is riding on the sleigh
Because she was on [Barrette]
They're doing some kind of step move
Some sort of step dance
ah they took off....they left the stage
Watching this video is so painful
isn't it
And you were fighting over getting to do that?
[ The chosen ones ]
The were ahead of you pulling the rope
We just had to hold the rope up and then we were done
But Hori is a 2nd member...
but she centered
So she's allowed to ride on the sleigh
Must have had mixed feelings
But my face didn't seem to show any mixed feelings there
[ Fully taking on her Santa role ]
Well she has to be Santa
For the girls that are 3rd and 4th members
when you see that
you need to recognize they've endured things like that
Really felt like they were buried
That'll make you stronger though
I just wish they would have painted their noses red
[ If you're going to do it may as well go all out ]
At least let us look cute
The 2nd members went through various things in their understudy years
In 2015
they were all promoted to regular member status
The show also had a renewal
and it was the start of Nogizaka Under Construction
Once it became Nogizaka Under Construction the 2nd members
got more chances to appear on the show
Memorable scenes of the 2nd members in 2015
they've been put into a highlight reel
so please watch along
First its the Hori produced episode that became famous
This is Hori Miona's zombie practical joke confidential report
yay
Here is Hori zombie on the way to work
What's the matter?
Are you ok?
KYAA!! WAH!
hold on...wait!  yabai!
hold on....yabai
She went flying....hahahaha
[ Kano cram school type reaction? ]
Next we have the documentary on Shinuchi the office worker
[ She became the world's first ever dual office worker and idol ]
Nogizaka46
Shinuchi Mai
hai....otsukaresama desu
The Shinuchi we see here
has a daily routine that's precious to her
[ Getting water from the water cooler ]
In the office this is what they call her...
[ Water burglar ]
So there's a lot of people here
that I've never talked to before but
they seem to refer to me as the water burglar
Kitano was the victim of this practical joke
and here's her nice reactions
[ Extremely spicy ]
AUGHHHHH!!!
[ nice reaction! ]
hold on...you able to drink some water?
[ citric acid water ]
[ passed out ]
You ok?
The macaron was so bad it made the water disgusting
How about you try the tea?
[ Ultra bitter senburi tea in standby ]
And then some bitter senburi tea was put in standby
[ senburi tea ]
UGHHH~
careful careful
Everything Maichun offers me is disgusting!
Ito Junna....within Noujo's fantasy drama
passionately played the male role
ahhh~ he's so cool looking~
If this senpai were to become my boyfriend
I'd be so incredibly happy
Well this next song is the last one
yada
Actually today
someone very important to me is in the audience
Ami-san
I've always had a crush on you
onegaishimasu
But still
it didn't seem like so long ago but it was pretty far back
Since it was from 2015
about 4 years ago
You do have the male role image
really?
In the future I'll really be looking to do some male roles
ehhh sugee
But its embarrassing to watch?
yes its embarrassing
The look on Noujo Ami's face is also embarrassing
[ Leading actress type of expression ]
That's what brought about [Friend and Sword]
[ Friend and Sword...directed, written, and performed by Noujo Ami ]
That was quite a production
ahh that was good
Even watching Kitano's reactions now its still funny
That was wonderful...had some life to it
The people playing the practical joke looked so stoic
[ Emotionless accomplices ]
Well they are trying to carry out the prank
If that's so they should laugh out loud like WAHH~
or GYAA~ but they're all like
[ No reaction ]
I was nervous since it was my first time playing a practical joke
The people playing the prank made it feel out of place
The 2nd members slowly started becoming more active on the show in 2015 but
Terada Ranze as far as solo work
she started her own regular column at Nikkan Sports
And what does she write about in her columns?
Who are you asking?
[ The incompetent BBA ]
Seemed like you're asking Hori
I messed up
We're counting on you here water burglar
News that takes place in our society
I'll write what my true thoughts are
on certain news topics
It can be found on Nikkan Sports website
Terada's serial column
The articles contain Terada's unique viewpoints on daily news events
Its time for "push the 2nd members comments!"
In this corner
we interviewed staff who work with the 2nd members on a personal level
We'll get stories from their bosses perspective on what makes them so great
And with that we've interviewed...
in charge of Terada's column
Journalist for Nikkan Sports...Yokoyama
This person takes care of you over there correct?
He's in charge
Yokoyama-san
The friendly Yokoyama-san
has given us his comments on what makes Terada Ranze so appealing
When it came time for a Nogizaka column to get started
in order to give hard hitting unique perspectives on the daily news
the person that came right to mind was Terada-san
Terada-san is a person that speaks her mind
She will clearly express her own goals and aspirations
and does not keep her thoughts covered up
I thought she would give us her raw unfiltered opinions for the column
She may be lacking knowledge in certain areas but
she'll conduct her own research and write what she honestly thinks
I believe its an extremely well written column
She's worked with our company for 3 and a half years now....
At our company...
pardon me a second
This is being rude to Yokoyama-san
better to not laugh while reading
Its not like that...the pictures on the screen keep changing
Yokoyama-san looks like the guy from the hemorrhoids commercial
[ We've seen those commercials ]
I get why you're laughing but you have to read his comments seriously
Its like you're making fun of him or something
The hemorrhoids guy
That part is not good either
we don't need to see all those pictures on the screen
1 picture would be fine
I got distracted by it....sumimasen
Start from a little before
These are Yokoyama-san's comments
She conducts her own research and writes what's on her mind...its a good column
she's written this column for our company for over 3 and a half years which is exceptional
others who have had columns for this long a time
would be someone like Sergio Echigo-san
Sergio Echigo and Terada Ranze are at the same level
[ In an elite class ]
Journalist Yokoyama
has his recommendation for what tv show he'd like her to appear on
I'd think she'd be good as a commentator for news programs like [Nonstop!]
She has candid opinions and will push the boundaries of what can be said on tv
Is [Nonstop!] that kind of
its not that kind of aggressive news show
[ No need to push boundaries ]
But I have a hard time picturing that
My image of Terada is like
what was her nickname for potato chips again?
poto poto pottosu?
[ Terada family slang ]
Don't say that one anymore?
Too many people were saying it
Heard it too much?
Even within the family the word has become off limits
Well you should write a column about that
[ Definitely make it an article ]
Also journalist Yokoyama has a reccommended Terada scene to show us
There was a Christmas Live show at Budokan
it was an Under only show with Terada as MC
she gave a speech that only Terada-san could give
He considered it to be a fiery speech
We're going to see it? yes
Here it is
They've always let me say "I want to become center!" however
I know there's people that will say "You'll never be center"
but
I believe....I am absolutely going to make it come true
In my mind its like "who says 1+1 must equal 2"
I don't want life to be predetermined like that
and that's why
for me that 1+1
I'm going to make it equal 100
Are you pissed off?
[ Angry rant style speech? ]
I'm not angry....
Thinking about when they joined the group
so that was Budokan
Budokan
That place holds 10,000 people and you play larger venues than that
you all can talk to large crowds
From pulling that sleigh
to performing in a place like that
That's really a lot of growth and development
I think so too
[ Yonbanme no Hikari ]