This is part 2 of Midsummer Real Life Horror Experiences 2019
First continuing on from last week
they're telling us real life ghost stories in the storytelling category
If they laugh or its not scary Shitara can force a stoppage
Up first in part 2 is Yamashita
This is a story about when I was sleeping at home
From way back I've had several experiences with sleep paralysis
Lately I've figured out how to wake up out of it
and then on this day...there was another attack of sleep paralysis
As usual I attempted to wake myself up out of it but
I was unable to break free of it
and then suddenly
WAH~
WAHH
[ Stiff sounding WAH~ ]
I heard the sound of a crying baby
So scary
so scary~
[ Inagawa-san? ]
hai that's finish
You're laughing at your own stuff
[ Junji caused her downfall ]
saying "so scary" twice like that will make you laugh
I've been wanting to do this
I wanted to do this and just now I even watched videos and practiced
[ The reference material had a bad influence ]
You have to put some feeling into that "so scary"
one more!
one more?
Also the way you say wah~
the wah~ part is usually more sudden
[ stupid sounding baby ]
Start from the "wah" then
Yamashita will start over from the middle
and then suddenly
WAH
WAH~
I heard the sound of a crying baby
so scary
so scary~
with those thoughts I attempted to wake myself up out of it but
on this day I was unable to wake up
Then suddenly out of nowhere hands appeared and grabbed my throat
I was being strangled
I opened my eyes slightly and
standing in front of me was a woman in black
sorori sorori~
around my neck
[ This sororoi sorori? ]
I was being attacked
sorori sorori?
This woman was strangling me by the neck
hai...this is useless right here
[ The unnecessary parts brought her down ]
That sorori sorori stuff
That's the sorori sorori gag
Why would she sorori sorori strangle you by the neck?
Yamashita's ghost story was about
while in a state of paralysis a woman in black strangled her neck
just when she thought she had woken up out of it
she was still there right next to her...that's her story
That story would be really scary if she had told it straight up
That story was wasted
The story is dead
[ Strict eye towards storytelling ]
It has no life to it
Next its Umezawa's real life horror experience
This is
about when I first joined the Nationwide Tour
A story about when I was traveling on tour
I was sharing a hotel room with member Yoshida however
in the hotel room there was nothing to drink so
I went out of the room looking for the hotel vending machines
I got on the elevator
however
inside the elevator
the button that marked the floor with the vending machines
no matter how many times I tried to push it
for some reason it did not respond
Right when I was thinking "is this thing broken?"
KA-CHUNK
Suddenly the elevator started moving
and then that elevator
I never pressed the button but
it stopped on the 13th floor
since the door opened I figured I'd get off
it was pitch black there
and there was something definitely weird going on so
the 2 of us ran back into the elevator
what if
we hadn't made it back into the elevator in time
Thinking about it still gives me the chills
[ Ghost story finished ]
what happened? what's that about?
Its like the elevator moved on its own
then stopped on the 13th floor
When I got off it was pitch dark
You're not saying that hotel doesn't have a 13th floor right?
That part I don't remember
Its possible there wasn't a 13th floor
[ phantom 13th floor? ]
Maybe something had actually gotten on the elevator with you?
[ Came up with a more horror type of scenario ]
The ghost lives on the 13th floor
and wanted to get off on the 13th floor
[ portal into the spirit world? ]
Did you have supernatural experiences before joining Nogizaka?
ah I did
ah you did?
I'd see them when I was little
seriously? yes
I'd see something going up the stairs
I thought it was oneechan but I followed and nobody was there
up to the 2nd floor
Then I'd go back to the living room and everyone was there
Now its 4th member Kakehashi's real life horror story
One day this happened to me
hai
[ Instant kill ]
She's laughing already
Did she say "This is about Alfee"
[ Alfee ghost stories? ]
She said it was about Alfee
You can't do that
You have to get yourself together and recreate the mood
otherwise you'll just end up laughing again
Kakehashi...can she regain her calm?
One day this happened to me
so I
I was sleeping at night when
suddenly the door to the room
I heard a DON DON DON DON DON
but my room...my room
often Rei would visit
[ This is not going well ]
Since Rei often came over
Could I get a do over or something?
[ Not suited for ghost storytelling ]
That's good I like this
I love the way bad storytellers talk when they tell ghost stories
What is this story about?
I got it all mixed up
You kept saying Rei...is that a monster or ghost? What Rei?
I'm talking about Seimiya Rei
The story is about Seimiya coming over?
The story she was trying to tell us
In the middle of the night there was a knock knock on Kakehashi's door
since Seimiya Rei came over often she went to open the door but nobody was there
Was it a ghost? That's what her story was about
Next its a real life horror story from 4th member Kanagawa
When I was in elementary school
many times I would sleep in between ojiichan and obaachan
It was there
that I suddenly needed to go to the bathroom
ojiichan went with me to the bathroom
and when we returned to the room
there was someone next to obaachan
Looking closely...it was...
Michelin Man
[ Michelin Man? ]
I got scared
and asked ojiichan
who is that next to her?
That's what I asked him
[ The storyteller remains serious throughout ]
There's nobody there
was ojiichan's reply
ojiichan....myself....obaachan
and the Michelin Man were all sleeping together
but I was too scared to sleep
[ That would be scary ]
But I was sleepy
I thought I must be seeing things
and when I looked over to verify
It really was the Michelin Man after all
no no...what was that....hold on now
excuse me a second....Kanagawa
This is crazy..what is this? This is a true story?
hai
eh? So around the size of a human? Michelin Man?
Seemed a little bigger than human
It was something huge?
The side of it looked this big
And it was really fluffy
the blanket?
blanket? ah
The blanket was fluffy so it looked fluffy under the blanket
That's not it
Michelin Man?
Its Michelin Man!
[ Direct eye contact ]
Who was were?
ojiichan
myself
obaachan
Michelin Man
[ Bizarre imagery ]
ah Michelin Man was on that side of obaachan
And that completes the ghost stories
who won this grand prix?
Michelin Man Kanagawa takes it!
[ Kanagawa wins the storytelling category ]
So that one was
her impact led to victory
Yes I've never experienced that one before
it was a ghost story that created a new feeling for me
Midsummer real life horror stories 2019
Reporter Category
Here the members will go out to a haunted spot
and report back to us
First it'll be Takayama...Hoshino...Mukai
and Yakubo doing the reporting
And their destination is...
Well this is something I've brought up on Nogizaka Under Construction before
the haunted tunnels...the sub tunnel
[ Also known as Subton ]
So the sub tunnels are supposed to be scary
The locals there know all about it
I'm looking forward to this one
dozo
I pretty much introduced the haunted tunnel on a past episode of Nogi Doko
That was named haunted tunnel but today its a sub tunnel
The sub tunnels...today with my reliable kouhais
there's 3 kouhais here
3?
3 kouhais
Me too?
ah you're no kouhai!
[ Scary mistake ]
First the 4 of them will try to escape sub tunnel one
their goal is to reach sub tunnel two
Mukai: yada yada
kowai
Mukai: eh hold on now...what do I do?
Hoshino: ah is this the tunnel already?
[ Sub tunnel one ]
What has appeared in front of them is known as
Sub tunnel one
There's nothing here
There's nothing in here
Hoshino: ah! everybody look to your left
[ Help me.... ]
eh~
I saw it...I saw it...I saw it
saw it
Staff: Want to stop and look around?
no!  no way!
Hoshino: I've already seen everything
Hoshino: We're doing just fine
Compared to the panicky Takayama and Mukai
Hoshino and Yakubo remain completely calm
Sub tunnel one has a total length of over 80m
They passed through the tunnel without incident
However today's target is the next sub tunnel two
Actually the locals claim more ghosts appear here than the main haunted tunnel
A woman wearing a white kimono and
as well as several different children
there are never ending eyewitness reports of these sightings
And here
Staff: Let's do an inspection
inspection?
To see if there's any ghosts
ahhh are you serious....I don't like the sound of that
At a plodding pace the 4 of them head towards sub tunnel two
when finally
Mukai: The tunnel
Mukai: I can see the tunnel
[ Sub tunnel two ]
Don't want to think about how scary it looks right
be brave
Right away its time for inspection
The method of investigation
one group of 2 will enter the tunnel
once inside they'll do something to attract ghosts
There's a technique to getting the ghosts to gather
First its Takayama - Hoshino pair
They'll draw lots to see who will call out the ghosts
This one!  I think that's a good one
JAAN
What is it?
Well?
Take a water bottle and let water dribble out of it
That makes ghosts come out?
that sounds safe right?
That's not something that will anger the ghosts
sounds safe
Staff: The sound of the water dribbling out
seems to attract ghosts
yada! Please don't tell me that
And then to determine if this really attracts ghosts
they'll be using this ghost radar to verify
Push the switch and the color changes
if the color is green at the end
it means there's no ghosts present
Blue means a good ghost is present
Red...
means an evil ghost is present
It seems this will tell you if there's ghosts
What's up with this radar?
In the end will any ghosts appear?
yada...look at the rough surface...yada
Check it out
its more like a cave than a tunnel
Hoshino: Got a bad feeling about this...its so long you can't see the exit
Its evident that sub tunnel two has a much different feel than sub tunnel one
the both of them are taken aback
and then
UWAH!!
wahhhh~
gomen gomen gomen.....
gomen gomen gomen
gomen gomen gomen...
[ What just happened here? ]
You scared me
you scared me...what was that?
Like a bird? Looked like chicken footprints or something
That's the shape...take a look
You scared me!
you scared me!
what is it?
ah yada yada yada
And then once they reached the center of the tunnel
they'll now try to summon the ghosts
dribble water and they'll come
But its raining outside
Seems we're lucky then
Doesn't that seem like enough
ok...you've spilled enough water
[ Ghost radar time ]
Now that they've allowed plenty of water to drip to the ground
right away they'll use the ghost radar to verify the presence of ghosts
UWAH! AH!
red
But its white now..that means its all gone
See look...its safe...all gone
Could be a good ghost...maybe a good one
AH!
For a moment the ghost radar flashed red
does that mean an evil ghost was nearby?
For the time being they're with some good ghosts so
to commemorate this scene they'll take a picture
This is a scary looking picture
Nothing seemed out of the ordinary
Maybe good ghosts aren't into disturbing people
here the baton is passed to the pair of kouhais
They'll be going deeper inside than the senpais
for a different investigation
JA-JAAN
hai
This sounds really bad
Face a mirror and then bow
That's a bad one
Doing this
is supposed to make the ghost appear in the mirror
The mirror is really close
hai
yah kowee~
sugoi
See anything? There wasn't anything in there was there
hai
Nothing strange happened...
here goes
Its ok...here goes
hai
I'm finished!  hai
Everything here seemed to be fine
nothing there? nothing
And here as well
the radar showed the presence of good ghosts
hai...all ok
The results of the inspection
the sub tunnel has good ghosts inside
but sometimes an evil ghost will be lurking
maybe...
This is the 2nd trip to the haunted tunnels but nothing ever happens
ah!
That first trip...Akimoto purposely tripped and stuff
[ The intent makes it scary ]
Hoshino wasn't scared at all
The ghost radar seemed so fake
What exactly is a ghost radar?
It made it gradually less scary
eh let me see that thing
How does this work? That's messed up if there's a ghost here
That would be crazy...feels like you're checking me
Its blue
He's a good monster
I'm no monster
[ Ghost Himura ]
Next Shinuchi...Nakada...Umezawa...Shibata will report on location
This time these 4 will be testing their courage at...
On the outskirts of Kanto is this abandoned hotel
Currently this abandoned hotel isn't being used however
there has been a murder incident in the immediate vicinity
and several eyewitness accounts of ghosts
This abandoned building is kind of out of control
Anybody here able to sense ghosts?
[ The ghost detecting girl...Shibata ]
Are you the type that can see them?
I don't see them but
I can sort of feel their presence
[ Senses them rather than sees them ]
The test of courage this time
Find these 3 items randomly placed within the abandoned building to finish
These 2 pairs will be in charge of searching their designated section of the building
First Nakada - Umezawa Team will start
Umezawa: eh could I hold your hand?
eh kawaii...this will make it fun
This area is kind of crazy
Umezawa: We're going in?
[ The front lobby ]
This is the reception desk isn't it
elevator...goes to that place we just saw
that's not it...there's a 2nd floor...a staircase
[ Discovered a staircase ]
Going up or down a staircase like that would be scary
closer behind us
Could you get a little closer behind us?
Would you stay closer to us?
For a moment right here in order to search the 2nd floor
they were heading towards the staircase they saw earlier but
Who closed the door?
Was this not the place?
eh~
Stop playing with us...stop it
eh?
I'm positive this door was open before
We peeked in
and said "Its a staircase"
I'm even getting goosebumps on my face...
Did one of you touch the door...
That's not it...its a staircase
Its true
on the other side of that door they spotted a staircase
Nakada and Umezawa made remarks about it
However when they returned a couple minutes later
The door which nobody messed with was now closed
[ Don't come any closer ]
perhaps it was this kind of warning from a ghost
They built up their resolve and the 2 of them headed for the 2nd floor
and then
there was another bizarre incident that went beyond human understanding
eh?
What's going on here....
Surprise!
[ Umezawa yoroshiku ]
Amazingly on the hotel wall Umezawa's name is written
could this be a message from the hotel ghosts?
What were we looking for again?
A Sing Out CD and...
ah! There it is
There it is!
Found one!
But its kind of cute
very cute
They've got the 1st item
Can they safely find the other 2 objects?
From here this pair is in charge of finding the items
The goal is to retrieve the remaining 2 items
First they head to the 3rd floor
ah its a big space
It is a big space
Shinuchi: Start from the right then?
This would be mega scary
Shinuchi: How did it feel to pass the Nogizaka audition?
Shibata: Since I've liked the group forever
In order to calm down the ghost sensing 4th member Shibata
during a test of courage she tosses her a talk show theme
Its a high level technique unleashed by the veteran Shinuchi
Shibata: I'd go to live shows and the handshakes
Shibata: So when I passed the audition
Shibata: I was incredibly happy
Shinuchi: Did you know who I was?
She's trying to be humble but Shinuchi
is fishing for the words "of course I'm a huge fan"
Shinuchi: Did you know who I was?
ah there it is
[ Can't believe she found it ]
There's a stuffed animal here
With unusual timing the item has been found
Unable to get a clear answer from her we're left with a sad Shinuchi senpai
Now the last remaining item
is the Sing Out CD
hai
Wonder if it'll open
ah it opens...pardon me
ok then
Its got to be in here
Shinuchi: So what did you like about Nogizaka46?
senpai Shinuchi
she's trying to give her kouhai a bunch of camera time
and she has passed her yet another talk theme
Shibata: Before I joined...
Shibata: I admired the group
Shibata: Once I joined
Shibata: Its like the senpais
There it is!
[ Once again they find it before she finishes her story ]
all right...we did it
Shinuchi's talk themes did not pay off
but they found the 3 items and this shoot is finished
Or so we thought
They found the items
and when they were going down the stairs
we caught a strange phenomenon on tape
What made you like the group?
eh what would that be...my friends?
Did you see what happened?
Take another look in slow motion
A mysterious flash appeared for a brief moment
and then quickly vanished
On site nobody noticed the flash
it only showed on the video
That wasn't a flash camera?
Was this flash some kind of message?
With all these mysteries left unsolved the shoot completed
You sure that wasn't a flash camera?
Those happened afterwards
[ Unexplainable ]
Only Umezawa was able to make stuff happen
You shouldn't be going around vandalizing places with graffiti
oh no no
been there before?
Never been there before
Do you normally see Umezawa written in random places?
That's scary
And also I went up the stairs and that was the first thing there like DON
It was like a welcome board for you