24th single hit campaign!
Yes its here....finally here
Taking place along with a single release
its the prayer for a hit campaign
This time its the 4th members and new captain Akimoto
climbing up to the top of Fuji to watch the sunrise
Last time they took 2 different routes and started climbing
With a goal of making the climb in one day...they'd take a rest at the mountain stations
On the Fujinomiya route its station #9
which is located 3460m up
On the Yoshida route its station #8
they're looking to climb 3400m to make it there
[ Yoshida Route - 5:40pm ]
Yoshida Route team
currently 3 of them are trailing behind
they've been split up as they make their way up the mountain
Up ahead are Kakehashi...Tamura..and Endo
they're going at a good pace towards the mountain station
hai...station #8
Kakehashi: Made it!
Their journey has been over 5 hours
but they're now at the entrance of station #8
Tamura: You ok?
Endo: I'm ok
Endo: The rocky sections will really get you out of breath
Around then...how about the 3 trailing behind?
That looks painful
ah yabai
They look beat up
Seimiya: I can't produce any energy
Guide: Long rests will make it worse so this is just a 3 minute break
hai...hai
For these 3...rest too long and they'll be unable to move from exhaustion
with just a short rest
somehow they keep making slight progress
However from here
there's suddenly a strong wind
and what they didn't experience last time
a night time climb is waiting for them
And then the 3 people up ahead
its now been over 6 hours since they departed
they've arrived at station #8 elevation 3200m
Guide: You've now made it to a spot that's 3200m up
its the 2nd highest point in Japan
we're higher up than Kitadake in the Southern Alps
Yes...this place where these 3 are
5 years ago
its where Sakurai unfortunately had to retire
ah Sakurai got altitude sickness
For the 3 trailing behind
can they overcome this unfortunate past history?
However the pace of the 3 trailing behind is slowing
Seimiya: Almost feels like I'm being choked by the neck...
She looks completely serious now
[ 6:30pm...6 hours of climbing ]
And then
around the time the 3 ahead of them arrived at the station
the sun has started to set
As for the 3 up ahead
although they're moving up at a steady pace
There's strong winds plus a drop in temperature
all of it quickly saps your strength
That's going to wear you out
Kakehashi: Its getting rough....
And then
They made it?
Kakehashi: Are we there?
Guide: Its the 4th building after this one
Guide: This is the 1st building
eh? eh? eh?
Staff: They've got curry for you there
That's painful...now they're all depressed
However after that the 3 of them kept moving towards the goal
And finally
That's painful...thinking you've arrived like that
Guide: Its right there in front of us!
Is that the destination?
The 3 of them climbed for over 7 hours
and they've finally arrived at todays destination
Tamura: So tired!
Endo: The oxygen keeps getting thinner
Endo: That was tough
Kakehashi: I was way too hungry and that made it more painful
Kakehashi: Even with walking on and on
Kakehashi: Never thought we'd get here
As they get some long awaited food and recover
they'll wait for the other 3 in their team to arrive
The 3 trailing behind
are dealing with the strong winds
and with all the unstable footing
the goal is still to reach the mountain station
ahh she looks dizzy
From here its a series of zig zagging paths
and they keep moving slowly forward however
at this slow pace no matter how much they walk
they're still not seeing any of the lights from the mountain station
It seems like no end to this climb
their bodies already at their limits feel like they're getting a whipping
their mental toughness is also getting tested
ganbare ganbare~
That's good! There's crying isn't there?
That's the stuff!
[ That's what he wanted to see ]
Its been about 10 minutes since
the 3 ahead arrived at the station
They've finally arrived at the place where Sakurai retired
For the 3 of them their bodies and spirit
are close to the limits
Want to see them keep going after seeing them get this far
Kaki: Its tiring
its mentally exhausting
Seimiya: Are you crying?
Seimiya: If you cry we'll all start crying
Kaki: ganbarou
oh? sugoi sugoi
Their teammates are waiting
so they won't stop walking
And then the strong wind
plus the seemingly never ending journey...the 3 continue fighting it
At last...
Kakehashi: Rei!
I was thinking they might not make it
[ 8 hours 15 minutes of climbing - 8:45pm ]
Kaki: I'm exhausted
Seimiya: My heart broke several times...
Seimiya: This isn't even the top of the mountain
Kaki: Mayutan?
Kakehashi: Mayutan is not feeling well
yes...for Tamura
after reaching the mountain station
her health changed drastically
She started showing symptoms of altitude sickness
and she's currently working on recovering
After that
to take off at 1:30am for the summit
they have to physically recover and regain their health
They have to leave at 1:30 then
However after the arrival
more members displayed health issues
In a world where the elevation is 3400m
for the members that used up all their energy up to their limits
its a terribly cruel environment
After that the 6 of them
can they still meet their goal of seeing the sunrise at the summit?
[ Fujinomiya Route 8:00pm ]
Currently they're moving towards the lodging at station #9
Fujinomiya Team has just departed station #8
Following sunset the temperature has dropped
its already dropped below the 10C mark
However for these members
once again they're attacked by forces of nature
The cat ears
You still wore them in those conditions
Remarkably...the wind gained strength
gusts reached speeds of 20m/s which is comparable to a typhoon
wah...20m/s
The temperature also dropped down to 6C under these worsening conditions
And then
Guide: Left or right?
Akimoto: right
Guide: Hurts to move it?
what? Its Akimoto
Guide: Did you figure out a way to climb where it doesn't hurt?
Guide: Walking just normally hurts then?
Amazingly Akimoto
has an injury to her right foot
To get her first aid treatment
its important to get her to the mountain station quickly
Were you really in pain?
That was real...that was a real injury
I just wanted to verify
[ New Akimoto Theater? ]
Be careful!
However not only has the wind gone up a level
now it has started to rain
Are you supposed to climb in these conditions?
Under intense winds similar to a typhoon
somehow little by little
they keep taking small steps forward
And then
There it is!
sugoi
Just a little further
uwah~ so happy
They made it then
ahhh we're finally here
yes!
Fujinomiya Team has finally arrived at their mountain station
Tsutsui: Manatsu-san...
Akimoto: gomen...
Akimoto: I'm ok
Akimoto: All of you fought really hard
Because they missed their expected arrival time by a large margin
the members have to rest as soon as possible
In 4 and a half hours they'll be departing for the summit
[ Fujinomiya Route: 1:30am ]
It was time for the attack on the summit however
outside there was still strong wind and rain
And then...
Guide: May I make a sad announcement?
Hate this right? Its bad however
hmmm today's sunrise
we will not be climbing to the summit
Due to current conditions it was decided not to make the climb
Currently the weather at the summit is also rain
Even if they went up there'd be little chance of seeing a sunrise
furthermore due to the strong winds
unfortunately they have no choice but to cancel the climb
Guide: But we will see the sunrise
Let's go see the sunrise
And then later we discussed
we're still not giving up on climbing all the way up
We haven't given up...the sunrise
we'll watch the sunrise from here
After that
the wind as well as everyone's physical status
once all the conditions become favorable
lets climb up
let's go
Don't give up now
[ Fujinomiya Route - 4:30am ]
And then at 4:30am
wah~
eh sugoi
the sunrise
The rain stopped completely
and the morning glow from the sunrise was faintly visible
There's a good chance they'll get to see a sunrise
Right away they move over to a scenic spot at station #9 for the sunrise
All of them waited for the moment
I see it...you're right
ah sugoi
Also the way it lights up the haze makes it look like a rainbow
I can see it...I see it
It may not be the summit
but seeing a sunrise from Mt. Fuji for the first time
was an especially emotional moment for these 6
hai...here it goes
24th single
[Yoake made Tsuyogaranakute mo Ii]
I hope it becomes a hit
That's plenty right there
They did a strong prayer for a hit to the sunrise
however for these 6 there's still a mission to execute
They must get to the summit
to reunite with the other members
[ Yoshida Route - 5:00am ]
Yoshida Team has also made a change to the schedule
they're watching the sunrise from their station
ah sugoi
That's incredible isn't it
so pretty
eh..incredibly beautiful
sugoi
Kakehashi: Imagine seeing it from the summit...
if we were seeing this at the summit
By the way the view of the sunrise from the summit
looks like this
wah that's so beautiful
ah really pretty
24th single
I hope it becomes a hit
Its a good thing they saw the sunrise
All that remains is climbing to the summit of Mt. Fuji
at the top will all the members be able to reunite again?
[ Yoshinomiya Route - 5:45am ]
You were able to see the Fuji sunrise today right?
hai
So after that
I'd like to attack the mountain summit
You've likely seen pictures of the top before
the top is pure white
Its possible the wind could be worse than yesterdays
It could be a rough climb but from my viewpoint
I'll listen to your opinions
and as your guide I'll make the judgement
Climbing up when they still haven't recovered from yesterday
sounds crueler than anything they can imagine
Plus they still have to consider the climb down the mountain
Right here they'll check the mindset of the members
and then...
Emotionally...if I can move I'd like to try and make it but
but I'm worried about my foot
but...
if I'm able to force myself to go
I'd really like to do it
arigatou
Last night she injured her right foot and things aren't looking well for Akimoto
however as a senpai
and much more importantly as the new captain
she believes she has to make it to the top with everyone
After hearing Akimoto's thoughts what will the Guide decide...
Manatsu-san
Would you be ok with making this station your final goal...
Guide: I completely understand how you feel
I took all kinds of things into account and thought about it
if Manatsu-san would make this her final goal
that's the best move
best
Sorry I know how bad you wanted to go
being their leader
Akimoto
unfortunately must retire halfway
no way!
retire?
Do you understand my reasoning?
hai
Its like
Akimoto: When I took over the role of captain
this is the first assignment I was put in charge of
other than myself..the other members
they're all still determined to make the climb all the way up
and to not be able to participate
as a captain that's completely...
I'm thinking that's completely unacceptable
Along with her sash
she's entrusting her thoughts to the 4th members
Tsutsui: I'll work extra hard to make up for Manatsu-san
arigatou
And then
these 5 now carrying the thoughts of Akimoto
its now 4th members only climbing to the top
[ Yoshida Route - 5:50am ]
Here Yoshida Team as well
came to this conclusion
There's still a bunch of people in recovery
The members who suffered from poor health yesterday are still in bad shape
Kaki...Kitagawa....Seimiya....Tamura
have been ordered to stop by doctors decision
Seimiya: I want to keep trying....
The members had high hopes of reaching the summit however
when thinking about the climb down
the judgement was made to stop them from overworking themselves
With the thoughts of those 4 in mind
Center Endo and Kakehashi
are heading for the summit
They must make it to the top
the final battle against Mt. Fuji has begun
arigatou
Akimoto shed tears as she said farewall to Fujinomiya Team
The 4th members only summit attack has begun
The remaining path up to the summit
is a continuation of really steep cliff
The 4th members climb desperately
they must reach the top to pray for a hit
And then what's this?
Manatsu-san!
love her~
Hey they're doing it
The unfortunate stop by doctors decision
the thoughts of Akimoto captain
must reach the top of the mountain
And then...
Guide: The wind
wind seems to be dying down
Guide: Must be because everybodys carrying it with them
Amazingly the wind gusts from the weather report vanished
thank goodness
[ 7:45am - 18 hours and 45 minutes total time ]
And then just before reaching the top
they've arrived at station #9.5
All that's left is the climb up to the top
See it?
ah I see it!
ah I can see it!
Just a little further!
The peak is finally visible
Yakubo: This next part looks really steep...
Yakubo: Have to be careful going up
Wonder if it'll be ok
Hayakawa: A little worried....
At that moment
Manatsu-san!
There's just a little more left
Shibata: Did you hear that "ganbatte" just now?
The summit is right in front of them
eh is this? Still haven't passed through yet
And then at last
Guide: We're arriving at the true endpoint
Take your time
Keep fighting to the very end
Watch every single step
slowly now
yes!
[ 9:30am - Total time 20 hours 30 mins ]
wah~
We're at the top!
We made it!
Did it!
ehhh~ I'm so happy
Manatsu-san!
we've made it to the top!
They've been updating Manatsu-san the whole way up
so happy
that took a lot of effort
Did the Yoshida Route team make it up?
They walk around the summit looking for the other members
And then...
See them?
OY!
Where are they?
Right in front of us
They'll be so happy to see them
ah over there
In the distance are the images of the other members
ehh
yes!
ah its the cat ears
oh they're all running
Hayakawa: We were able to meet you here!
You fought hard
Hayakawa: Where are the others?
Endo: They're right here
The 2 left on the Yoshida Route
took 2 hours and arrived at the summit safely
This time they were unable to have everyone meet at the top but
the 4th members combined their powers
and impressively were able to conquer 2 routes up Fuji
24th single
I hope it becomes a big hit!
Now then [Yoake Made Tsuyogaranakute Ii]
here is the post Fuji and unreleased scenes version
[ Doing all the things they wanted to do at the summit ]
Its that way!
That's messed up...not sure what to say to that
That's real air from the summit then
Himura-san....Shitara-san
I'm bringing this back to you
Kakehashi: I won!
[ Everybody taking the Fujinomiya Route down the mountain ]
[ Reuniting with Akimoto ]
tadaima!
Manatsu-san!
okaeri!
arigatou
I'm really sorry
eh? arigatou gozaimasu
[ Akimoto wrote letters for the 4th members ]
You gave them money?
ah you wrote them all letters
[ The 2 Yoshida Route members had to walk 30 more minutes on the Fujinomiya Route afterwards ]
[ Both teams share their pictures of the sunrise ]
That's great
Beautiful wasn't it
Manatsu-san!
ZU-KYUN
UFFUN~
arigatou gozaimasu
[ Akimoto had letters prepared for the remaining 4th members ]
24th single hit campaign
was a huge success
That reminded me how brutal the climb up Fuji is
Akimoto in the middle of that you hurt your foot
That was so disappointing
I couldn't move my foot at that point
And then everyone carried my thoughts with them up to the top
When you were gone they sent a lot of messages with that Akimoto chant
Then at the end you give them all some money
[ Using money to win them over? ]
no..that's not what happened
The Yoshida Route members made it so far...they probably want to make the summit
Such a waste to have to stop
How about it? Those who didn't make it want to try again?
[ Immediate rematch? ]
I've developed a fear of mountains
[ Most of Hayakawa's fresh mountain top air has vanished ]
All that air you gathered...this is all thats left?
itadakimasu