DON
HAI
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
We are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And they are Nogizaka-chan
ganbariMaiyan-san
So then...Himura-san
hai
What's happening today?
There's all kinds of stuff going on here
Seems like some girls lost their stage costumes doesn't it?
[ Outbreak of burglaries? ]
That'll make sense later
Lost their costumes you say
Tell them whats on todays show
onegaishimasu
Here it goes
Look at what I can do in one month!
Everybody's goal tournament...press conference!
I messed that up
ehhh....goal tournament?
Today's a goals tournament?
The goals tournament was all wrong
You messed that up didn't you
Goals
Goals announcement press conference?
I couldn't even read that short a line
In order to acquire a new skill during the summer
previously they announced the skill and its time to reveal the results
If they're unable to clear what they practiced
its a punishment game
So it was Seimiya doing the trampoline
and then frisbee dog
was Sakaguchi
Since they can't do those in studio
much like last time we'll have a live feed to them
we'll send out a camera to watch them
Their performances on camera are coming up later
we'll check in on them later
I'd like to get right into it so
this area is probably feeling pretty nervous
[ Super nervous area ]
All the people not in their stage costumes
So are you super nervous?
Must be pretty nervous
I'm nervous
Maybe we should start with Hoshino's backflips?
[ Hoshino spent a week trying to master the backflip ]
just as expected
You did that the last time didn't you?
Yes I did...haven't done it since
Not since then
Well lets get right into it
Up first its Tamura!
[ Presenter Tamura Mayu ]
woo hoo!
[ Completely at ease observers ]
They got really excited for that
Tamura's presentation was on billiards
She challenged herself to do certain trick shots however
never
never?!
Its the first time Tamura has ever touched a cue stick
first she's being taught how to strike the ball
ah...never played any billiards before
So rest the cue stick on the 2nd joint of your middle finger
And how about the all important 1st ever shot?
[ Typical result for a beginner ]
And with that for the time being
she'll practice how to hit the ball straight
Have to hit it straight
[ 2nd practice ]
And now the 2nd practice
She's finally managed to hit the ball straight
The sensei for this one
Japan's best womens trick shot player
Ebe Kaori
What sensei will be teaching is...
2 senseis?
You've got 2 senseis teaching you?
I've seen that shot on tv
ahhhh...look at that
Sakai-san did that one
He did this shot
Called the Machine Gun...its a very difficult trick shot
Tamura will also try it however
Going at a slower speed
ah the balls aren't going in
yes she's spending a lot of time just on hitting the balls
From this day any breaks she had in her schedule
she would go back to billiards practice
Its intense practice for Tamura
By doing that she's also mastered 2 additional trick shots
similar to a pro tournament
she has to make the shot within 3 tries
Tamura is feeling nervous when its finally time to perform
will she be able to make her trick shots?
And with that...so this is from never ever playing billiards before?
That's right
But when you actually tried it
She has natural talent
This time Tamura will attempt 3 different trick shots
If she can do each one within 3 attempts it'll be a clear
The first trick shot she'll attempt is
The Railroad
She'll sink the ball directly in front of her into the pocket
then use the cushions to get the ball on top of the bridge of cue sticks
finally she has to hit the 9 ball in to make it a total success
Well this will be your 1st shot
so there's no reason to be nervous
ah!
eh?!
[ stiff ]
I'm ok
We'd like you to give it your best
Now then here goes...first its the Railroad
onegaishimasu
Tamura is up first
Can she get off to a good start by making her very first shot?
I'm feeling nervous just watching this
ganbare
concentrate
First she has to knock in the red ball
That was close!
uwah! Here it comes
sugee
sugee!
How'd you get it to ride on top
Hustler Tamura
accurately sunk the ball that was in front of her
then impressively got the ball on the rails
and passes on her first try
That is an undisputed clear
[ The Railroad - CLEAR ]
So Tamura
hai
What is this next shot you'll be trying?
The Machine Gun
already?
Machine Gun Shot
This is your 2nd trick shot?
The next trick shot
its called the Machine Gun Shot
She'll hit 6 balls consecutively without them hitting each other
using the cushions she'll sink them all in the pocket
finally she'll hit the cue ball
it'll be a clear once she sinks the 9 ball in the pocket
Did you put a lot of work into practicing this one too?
At first I couldn't get the rhythm down
the balls would often collide
sensei obviously this requires calmness and timing
That's right
The rhythm is crucial so
it might be better to get her fired up to go
ah get her fired up then
Better if she goes in fired up
How should we get her fired up?
oh yeah...bring it!
[ ojiisan aerobics? ]
That's how crusty old men do it though
You saw it right? Will you try it?
Do Himura-san's "oh yeah...bring it!"
[ ojisan harassment  ]
dozo
oh yeah...bring it!
That's the one
That's the spirit
Feeling anxious she did not give into the ojisan harassment
Hustler Tamura...will she be successful?
[ Machine Gun Shot - Attempt #1 ]
hai
That was not a clear
[ Machine Gun Shot - Not Clear ]
Those kinds of misses will happen occasionally
Akimoto just watching along you want to avoid getting nervous
The nervousness squeezes at your stomach all the way over here
Can't imagine she likes the stares of all the members focused on her like that
The senpais are watching...makes you nervous doesn't it?
I'm nervous
senpais gomen....could you turn around for us?
[ senpais are excluded ]
That'll make her laugh
[ Staring at the wall ]
You've still got 2 more tries at it
relax
ganbarimasu
Miss this one and then you'll be super nervous
[ Adding some meanness ]
The pressure is on for her 2nd shot
Can she make it a success?
[ Machine Gun Shot - Attempt #2 ]
We're counting on you
How's it looking?
uwah!
go go go go go go go
Tamura displayed good rhythm and accurate shooting
the balls did not collide and she sunk all the balls into the pocket
the cue ball she hit last
impressively bounced off the cushions and onto the rail
the ball then sunk the 9 ball and its a huge success
Machine Gun Shot CLEAR
[ Machine Gun Shot - CLEAR ]
You've done it
sugee
I felt so nervous watching
That was scary wasn't it
It was
To make that shot so quickly...she couldn't do that previously right?
In Japan that Machine Gun Shot
its only myself and Mayu-chan doing it
[ 2 people only kind of rarity ]
You sure you're not exaggerating?
[ Can Hustler Tamura keep up her winning streak? ]
You've always had those concentration skills from doing all that detailed labor
This girl had that side job before
Her side job making those keyholders
Hustler Tamura...her final trick is the Tube Shot
She'll shoot at the 1-ball using the cue ball
which will hit 2 balls resting on top of tubes
then the 9-ball directly in front of her
using some backspin will go into the pocket simultaneously
Its an exceptional technique used in trick shots
Obviously this shot has a low success rate doesn't it
Up to now I've only made the shot once
Just once?
This is futile!
[ Needs a miracle ]
Just once then?
I almost never make this shot...
She's doing a really tough shot
See look
even just setting it up...
[ The setup also has its difficulties ]
Please don't make a ruckus doing the setup
This shot is so hard that even the setup is hard
The super difficult trick shot
Hustler Tamura
can she make a miracle happen?
[ Tube Shot - Attempt #1 ]
relax
UWAH~
[ All 3 trick shots - CLEAR ]
Made it on your 1st try
yabee...now we don't have enough video to fill this episode
[ worried about running short ]
Miracle Hustler Tamura
she almost never made the Tube Shot at practice
When it came showtime unbelievably she made the shot on her first try
hey....that was incredible
I did it!
You did it!
That was incredible
Shiraishi...what do you think of that?
I was moved!
I'm thinking this girl is a real clutch performer
sensei! She got it on the first try
During practice she could never make the shot
I'm truly shocked
She's clutch
In 5 attempts she couldn't make 1 shot
sensei...there's a really huge grin on your face
great feeling isn't it
That was wonderful
There's no women that can do that shot
really? really?
Its only myself and Mayu-chan
[ Sold as a set ]
You make it sound like nobody is doing this
That's how impressive that shot was
The next to present her results is Ito Riria
Her summer goal
was to complete a difficult action scene
And in the studio...
action!
So you're the boss...
I am the Boss
I must avenge his death!
Why didn't you go down?
Go down like I told you to
What kind of progress will she show us?
This time providing guidance to Ito is....
Shibahara Takanori
He was a stunt actor for the Sentai Hero series
and is currently an action movie director
He has his own studio where he instructs new students
He's an influential figure in the stunt action industry
First its the basics of stunt action
she's learning the forward roll to help her fall safely
She's practicing those
We've discovered a weakness in her ability to roll straight
After that...the punch
and the kick...the basics of strike attacks
She even learned the basics of how to use weapons
They're teaching her a lot of stuff
All the necessary elements of stunt action
she had to learn all at once
what? She's practicing backflips
Ito Riria has taken her first step into the action movie world
All the basics and fight choreography were repeated endlessly
Just what kind of action scene did she make?
They really taught you everything there
yes there was so much to learn
I was really happy to get to be able to do that
You practiced backflips though
That's right
You can do backflips?
nope...that was...
what? Hoshino's backflip....maybe she can do your backflip?
ehh~ those are so hard~
[ Let someone with experience talk ]
so this time
you shot a video
so its your video and then live in studio
there's 2 versions
hai
Now then this is Ito Riria's stunt action
First we have the video version
dozo!
What is this place?
There's places like this
Why all by yourself? What's this?!
what's going on?
She's been captured
so she's been captured?
That's a lot of enemies
That is a lot
Watch out! Watch out! That guy is a baka
What's this baka doing
She broke his neck!
ah yabai yabai yabai
What is this? They're a bunch of extras
These guys are freakin weak
Why is noone shooting?
above! above! above!
watch out!
That's that guy's one highlight
[ Pro style falling to your death ]
yabai yabai yabai yabai yabai
yabai yabai yabai
That guy has a bazooka
Its a bazooka
no way
You're right
yabee
That's a bazooka
She's dead!
ah she survived!
He missed
This is really messed up right now
What are they protecting?
Watch out!
Isn't this going a little too far
There's no way to get through this
yabai yabai...this is useless
She's dead
uwah~ there she is!
Her foot is on fire then
Its on fire right now
What about her foot?
That freaking made the fire go out
[ Stomped out the fire ]
She stomped out that fire
yabee...yabai
smiling...she's smiling
That the boss? Its got to be the boss
sugoi sugoi
Why is this guy hiding his face?
[ Claims the mask is unnecessary ]
Why is that necessary
Her kicks are amazing
There's a backflip
yabee...he's huge
Boss!
The boss is powerful
yabee
The boss is powerful...that guy is ruthless
fast
crazy bowlegged
yabee...that's dirty taking her hostage
She's been captured
To be continued? Where's the rest?
What's this?
Is it to be continued?
Its continuing!
The boss! Its the boss!
ah the boss escaped
What's your problem!
yabee he saw us! We've entered their world!
ganbare!
Give me back my comrade!
She could escape right now
ganbare!
What was that move just now?
sugoi sugoi
High kick finished him
What's happening?
Why did the both of them finish him?
Its over?
You did it!
sugoi
yah sugoi
So the video brought us to this live performance
I get it
So what was the hardest part of that?
It was the wire work
Doing the flips and all was really difficult...several times
I tried and failed and would get tired
that last part you did in front of us
when you simply did this to make your enemy stop..that was amazing
That happened for a moment
The Boss was like
[ imaginary punch? ]
That's a spirit punch
So its a spirit punch
I get the feeling the Big Boss understood the situation
[ Considerate Boss man ]
Its fine...it was a spirit punch
Mostly spirit then
So he performed with you...the Boss
Boss!
How was she as far as a raw action movie star?
Really good reflexes as well as
her focus during practice was incredible
She really memorized all the moves
ahhh...eh?!
Kakehashi is crying?
I cried a little
You cried?
eh? What emotions caused the crying?
Is it all the effort she put into it?
What's wrong?
What's wrong Kakehashi? Why are you crying?
She's gone through that exact same experience before!
[ Fought fierce battles in the past? ]
You've had to fight a guy with a bazooka before?
I thought Riria-san had been shot
You thought they shot her?
Thought she got shot?
Seriously? You're not going to be able to watch any movies then
[ This movie is fiction.  It is not based on any real people or events ]
That's good though knowing she wasn't shot
But we should ask sensei
Taking both scenes into account...the movie plus here in studio
Does she pass or fail? Your judgement please
onegaishimasu
well of course
she passed
[ Doing a difficult action movie scene - CLEAR ]