DON!
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
we are your hosts Bananaman
onegaishimasu
And they are Nogizaka-chan
ready...go...
4-way
moe moe!
sugoi
hold on
They looked like they were going to say it
[ Random countdown ]
I thought really hard for something to say
We hadn't even gone to this side yet
It looked like you were about to say something..and with that
Please announce what's on todays show then Himura-san
Here it goes
Nogizaka's Fall Four Way Battle!
Tonight from the 1s to the 4s
to break down the walls that separate senpai and kouhai
it'll be a real battle that tests the unity of the 4 audition classes
They'll play games where all 4 compete at the same time
and it'll become a 4 way battle
The team that wins each game gets a coin
the team with the most coins at the end
can play a target practice game involving rewards
The 1s look strong though
The 1s and 2s look really strong
But some games require youth more than strength
The others have that youth on their side
eh~ we're young too!
[ Here it comes ]
Yes you're young..but within the group you're the oneesans
That's right
And when you yell out "we're young" like that it definitely means you aren't
[ veteran move ]
The 2s....the misfortunate 2nd members step up for these moments
[ Treated as the unfortunate ones ]
This is when you step up
fight....fight on 2nd members
Now then what is the first battle
Fatal four way tug of war!
What's this? Is this possible?
The rope has been split up into a cross shape
and all 4 teams will simultaneously pull in this tug of war
Each time has a marking at the front of their ropes
first team to get that mark past their own goal line wins
In Round 1 each team has 3 people participating
which team will win it?
Have any kind of strategy or anything?
We've been discussing strategy the entire time
You've been planning this whole time
[ Legit meeting ]
Pretty serious about winning this
sounds good
Who looks strong like a good rival?
The 2nd member team
They look like they'd be powerful
They look powerful
Think you'll win
For us
its the 3s that look strong
Umezawa...Nakamura...Mukai
Looks like they brought out the strong ones for this game
We've got the 2 tallest plus the competitive Mukai
[ Feeling confident ]
Do you have a strategy then?
We've thought about it but this is the first time pulling from the side like this
lets think of a new strategy
[ We're already starting ]
new strategy she says
And then the 4s
The 4s look like they've got some good strategies
I did this in middle school
You did this in middle school?
Out of all classes my class took 1st place
so using the knowledge from that
How many classes was that?
There were 7 classes
You got 1st place out of 7 classes
You were in the winning class?
[ Fatal four way tug of war - Round 1 ]
Once 4 of you all pull at once
That will raise up then
I won't float up will I
[ Himura will float in the air ]
Get off of it before it lifts off
I won't float up in the air will I
Himura-san nobody here is listening to your jokes
[ Concentrating just on tug of war ]
I won't end up like "whoa let me down" then
Is everybody ready?
Here goes
I really don't want to lose...yada
ready
ah it could be over quickly
Its almost over the line...almost over
They pulled it back
Who's got it now?
The 4s are going for it
uwah uwah~ they're really competing
[ Intense battle! ]
That's good...get in there referee
ah! Its the 2s...the 2s
where's it going? where's it going?
The 2s...2s...2s...its the 2s
Now its the 3s...the 3s
Where's it going? Where's it going?
where's it going? oh!
go.....go go go!
Its a long battle...still going
Just a little bit more
ah its over there
Just a little more
little more
This is running long! long!
too long!
too long
That went too long!
[ The carnage ]
3s...the 3s win it
3s..omedetou
too long!
It ended up being that long a battle
Each team looked like they had a chance to win it
sugoi...
The referee is tired too then
You did it
Ume!
We did it!
You won a very long hard fought battle
But look at the 1st members....Shiraishi
Shiraishi...ran out of gas then?
Can't talk...
can't talk
Matsumura
come on...
yabai...
But the 1s had it...the mark was right above their goal line
They were so close
There was a moment where my heart stopped
[ Life threatening game ]
It did look like you had given up at one point
The 2s were so close to winning
The 3s....yabai!
The 3s....yabai?
The 3s...yabai
They dragged us over
They took it that far
The 4s were really close
I wrapped the rope around my stomach
It gradually kept squeezing tighter
Maybe you shouldn't wrap it around yourself
It slimmed my waist
[ Random positivity ]
Fatal four way tug of war
For Round 2 they're adding in 1 more person
it'll be a battle of these 4 person teams
1s
how about it?
If it turns into a long drawn out battle
we'll probably have no chance so
we're going to try and win it early
ah got it...how about the 2s?
We've all got individual roles so
we'll do our best using teamwork
If you can get your 2nd coin here that's a major advantage
We're young over here...she's 15
that's true
We'll be ok
How about the 4s then?
Taking the rope slipping into consideration
our strategy is to do this without gloves
That's fine but without the gloves it could hurt
Plus the rope might stink
[ Tug of wars are known to have stinky ropes ]
[ Fatal four way tug of war - Round 2 ]
Up at the front is good
Minami up front is good
What instructions are you giving?
The experienced people are discussing strategy
If I say it it'll give away our strategy
Could you tell us just a little?
The person at the front...
shhhhhhhh~ shhhhhhh~
[ The Shiraishi wall ]
What's wrong Shiraishi? Don't want her to talk?
We'll talk after its over
Understood...here goes
ganbare
ready
ah the 2s
Looks like its going that way
where's it going?
ah here it comes...its the 4s
I have no idea
where's it going
Right now the 4s have the advantage
Its the 4s and the 3s
The 4s are strong
ah the 4s
Are the 4s strong then
yabai yabai
ah again
its the 3s again
long....another long battle
wah~ here come the 2s
just a little more....uwah
The 4s get the victory
[ 4th members get a coin ]
Once again they're all left in this condition
Does tug of war usually produce this much tv action
four way tug of war is pretty interesting
it is
They should do this on other tv shows
4th members...you did it
You won
The strategy of going without the gloves
stinks?
kind of....
[ The price paid for victory ]
The 3s were so close at the end until the final pull
Lost by such a narrow margin
Right from the start
my hands were trembling from having to use so much muscle
You mad?
[ Angry? ]
Right from the damn start...
[ Pissed off Renka ]
So you're not angry?
I'm not angry
You ok then
Sorry if we've wronged you...
[ apology ]
Take a look at those faces
We worked so hard
That wears you out
Not enough youth....
Its not just your arms
you have to pull using all of your body
eh...there's still more games to play
How about we play this for eternity?
Round 68!
Four way card game!
yay!
They'll draw cards in order
then they'll have to follow the instructions on that card
While maintaining that pose
the game makes you keep adding more poses
Once you can't maintain your pose you get eliminated
the person left at the end gets a victory coin
As a result of janken
here is the order in which they'll be drawing cards
Right away then....game start
Here goes
Hopefully you get an easy one
Rest the card on the back of your right hand
hai....please place the card on the back of your right hand
right hand...back of the right hand
back?
If it falls off you'll be out
hai...I'll go with this
hai clear
Keeping the card steady on the back of your hand is actually difficult
Now then...Ikuta
Keep your upper teeth
sticking out
yada!
[ shocking instructions ]
yada yada~
yada yada
You can say that but you have no choice
There's cards like this?
So there's cards like this
You're going to have to stick out your front teeth
yes that's it
yes that's the way
So there's cards like that
Ikuta...so then
close your mouth and you're out
I have to maintain this while I talk then
ok desu
ah that's good...good
that's scary
Stick out those teeth
Place the card on top of your head
wah yabai
Using your hand to press it down will prevent you from using that hand freely
You can only use your hands to place the card there
Its better to keep your hands free
Is that your pose then? Can't do anything after that
[ Kitano is eliminated ]
The first card got her
gomennasai
yabai
Now then Yakubo
Teeth still out over there? Looks ok
Keep your finger touching your chin
You can get rid of the card
Think about which finger to use
That finger then?
Give me an ok
Why the sudden yes?
[ Bizarre character ]
ok yes!
Can't make any changes
hai ok
What's the advantage of this?
Still easy to draw cards like that?
Its ok! Its ok!
Now then
be careful now
Ikuta doesn't even look like she's playing in this game
She's had her turn
[ You doing anything? ]
She's doing something
so then
Keep you right elbow touching your body
yes right elbow...its that elbow!
The right hand works fine...it was unusable anyway
ok ok ok ok
And Ikuta-san has been waiting
onegaishimasu
Maybe this one says stick out your lower teeth
[ All teeth related ]
That would be an easy one
yes go ahead
Keep your pinky touching the card
What was that?
Card and your pinky
How should I do this one?
How about like this?
pinching it with your pinky works
You're moving it to your left hand then
That good?  hai hai
Keep the card on your neck
Yakubo's next card said to keep the card against her neck
She's chosen to keep the card tucked under her neck
Better to keep her hands free
ok?
Got your teeth sticking out over here? ah yes
[ Currently maintaining ]
Now then...Kubo
This is the 3rd round
Keep both hands touching the card
Is putting it on top ok?
Stacking is fine right
Well you still have to touch the card with both hands
Please touch the card with your hands
going with that?
going with that then? hai ok
Its time for our happy oneesan
oneesan
Next we have
dozo
Use your shoulder to plug up your ear
eh?
Plug up one ear using your shoulder
That's a tough one
Are you good?
plugged up?
kawaii~
Looks like a little kid
Are you lost little girl?
kawaii~
all plugged up then
Its plugged up...
Plugged up right?
Go ahead
And next
Yakubo
[ Impossible to ignore background Ikuta ]
Pinch this card between 2 of your fingers
Pinch the card with 2 fingers
Which fingers then?
pinky finger then...those 2 fingers then
hai
you're good then...hai
Everyone's gradually getting more weird looking
Now then
4th round
Ikuta hasn't broken her pose then? She's ok?
she's ok
Keep your finger touching your mouth
hai...oh!
You can drop the card
Have to keep that elbow touching or you'll be out
ok!
ok
That's ok
Its a good thing she can keep that card on her hand pressed down
That's cute
That's good stuff...everybody
is giving us a good pose
So then Ikuta
4th round
What is it now?
Raise your right hand above your left hand
Raise it higher up than your left hand
Raise that hand
Have to keep the ear plugged up
oh! ok ok ok...still touching the ear
miraculously
her neck has returned to a normal position
[ Natural recovery ]
Wonderful...strong move
That's good
let's keep going...Yakubo
hai...go for it
hai
Keep your hand on your knee
Place your hand on your knee
You won't be able to use that hand...that's impossible
Bending down? that's good
Does that work? Using her hand like that
That one's ok
I'll go with this
If that card on your neck drops its over
You ok there?
She's suddenly stuck in an awkward position
[ In big trouble ]
This is the 5th round now
sugoi
That's cute
That's cute then
She can't pick up the card anymore
Now then
Right here Kubo
drew "raise the pointer finger on your left hand"
but she's already doing that so clear
Now then...Ikuta
ah Ikuta
So you've had your front teeth out this entire time
I'm ok
hai go for it
Raise your right hand above the elbow
Raise the right hand above the elbow?
Need to see it a little higher
Just a little higher
Raise it a little more above that elbow
hai hai hai hai
[ The 1st members are laughing like crazy ]
Now if it drops its all over
Now then....Yakubo
You ok?
I'm good
Yakubo? I'm good
Yakubo has a stage marker stuck to her
sumimasen!
She scraped off one of the stage markers
Pull a card using your own power
hai
You have to read it aloud
now then
hai
Keep the card touching your right elbow
Can you do it?
In this position
Can she really do that?
For that one you can leave the card on your thigh if you want
That's acceptable
You're out if it drops
Yakubo is amazing
She's got all the hard ones
Now her face is totally hidden from camera
ah that's good...just stay like that
ok ok
hai ok...stay like that
ah here it comes
now then
we're running out of cards over here
She's got one
Keep the card touching your right eyebrow
Keep the card on your right eyebrow
Still not touching
ok safe!
ok
That's amazing
Are those teeth out?
Somehow Ikuta looks like she has the advantage here
Can they get their first coin?
all right! ganbaru!
ganbaru!
Here Ikuta draws "cross your arms"
and she manages to clear
What's this? Ikuta's actually in good shape here
You're up Yakubo
What's going on with Ikuta
so then
Yakubo's in trouble...can you draw a card like that?
Is it too much for you?
[ Extreme determination ]
Can the camera get this?
safe safe safe!
What now?
Trying it like that?
She can't even see anything
ah she's holding a card with her neck
Unable to see her face...4th member Yakubo is showing persistence
will she be able to make a miraculous comeback?
ganbare ganbare!
Can't give up now
You're close...yes yes yes
[ Yakubo is eliminated ]
That was impossible
She put up a pretty good fight
Its down to you 2
Its like Ikuta looks totally comfortable
wait wait wait wait
hold on a moment
ah she can't pick up the card
She's out if that finger points down
Can I slide it over?
sure you can do that
I'm picking it up
yes yes yes yes
yabai...Ikuta looks like she's about to go on a rampage
Standing up just like that works
oh very good...just have to read it
I can't read it!
Place the card on your right shoulder
How should I do this?
Its the right shoulder
now then
Aren't you suffering?
Its ok to give up
[ Teammates have surrendered ]
its ok to give up
You can do it
Maybe you can slide it over just like that?
Its impossible with the card between her fingers
yes...like that
you got it
If you can keep a finger pressing down on it
That's acceptable
But like this I can't draw anymore cards
But I can take the chance that she loses first
The next card Ikuta draws
It could say pull out all your teeth
[ Torture ]
Why does she get all teeth cards?
All this work to show her teeth
Kubo is on the verge of elimination
what card will Ikuta draw next?
go for it Ikuta!
now then Ikuta
Kubo is out of moves
Ikuta's front teeth are going to dry out
here it is
Keep the pinky on your left hand pointing down
The pinky on your left hand
Totally easy
yabai
Kubo ganbare!
[ Victory pose ]
Tucking the card is allowed
going for it?
you ok?
tuck it in further...yes!
ah..her fingers are free
ok...use the elbow
yes yes yes yes
uwah...why couldn't you have rolled up your sleeves more
Gotta have the sleeves higher for this
Ikuta's smile seems completely inappropriate for this situation
Its falling! Its falling!
OUT!
[ Kubo is eliminated ]
Ikuta gets the victory
What was that?
now then Ikuta..what you've been waiting for
[ 1st members get a coin ]
The 1s did it
yes!
sugoi
found a way to win it
That was an incredible battle
Ikuta..how's the teeth? Properly back under your lips?
I'm fine...teeth are a little dried out though...