DON!
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
we are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And they are Nogizaka-chan
Mountain!
mountain
Himura-san
hai
Tell them what's on todays show
Here it goes
24th Single prayer for a hit campaign
Its finally here
And with that the single has been released
so per tradition
the prayer for a hit episode
This released on September 4th
I drank alcohol until dawn and now one of my shoes
is gone and I don't really care
[ Drinking song? ]
Longer title this time
Its like that when you're drunk
Where's my shoe?
ah forget it then
[ Commonly found with drunkenness ]
This time they went out to pray for a hit
center Endo...so what did you do?
If you could just watch along...
[ Not going to say it ]
Could you tell us if it was a tough one?
It was tough but if you could just watch along
[ Fine we'll watch ]
[ In August somewhere within the city ]
On this day in August
the 4th members were called together not knowing what was about to happen
For all of you
we've got a mission for you
He's the guy that gives out order now
Prayer for a hit
For the 4th members its their first hit campaign
What will they be doing?
You'll be climbing Mt. Fuji
There it is!
Mt. Fuji then
Mt. Fuji is a tough one
Its something their senpais have experienced before
the cruel climb up Fuji to pray for a hit
This time its going to be all the 4th members doing it
Just like their new song title [Yoakemade Tsuyogaranakutemoii]
they'll climb Mt. Fuji by dawn
at the top they'll all watch the sunrise and do the prayer for a hit
However making them climb up Fuji seemed too cruel for their 1st time
And with that we've brought in a helper
ehhh~
Amazingly its someone who has previous Fuji experience
new captain Akimoto will join in and help them
konbanwa
otsukaresama
otsukaresama desu
By the way...does anyone recognize my hat?
Yes this hat...
its called the Fuji ROCK hat
and its her must have item from the last time she climbed Fuji
however...
What about it?
[ Don't know anything about it ]
That's just wrong
eh? Were you thinking Manatsu-san's outfit is messed up?
[ Weirdo obasan? ]
The new captain purposely wore the hat for this scene and bombs
Even though there's a distinct generation gap
These 12 are going to the top of Mt. Fuji to watch the sunrise
[ The day of the climb ]
On this climb up Fuji
the 12 of them will split up into 2 teams
and climb up using separate routes
In the middle...to wait for the sunrise
both teams will get some sleep in small mountain huts
Finally all of them will go up together to watch the sunrise
That's the plan
Including center Endo it'll be these 6
They'll take the same Yoshida route as the others did last time
New captain Akimoto will lead this group of 6
they'll be coming from the opposite side using the Fujinomiya route
First the 4th member team taking the Yoshida Route
They'll be departing first on the Fuji Subaru Line to get to the 5th station
24th single hit campaign
YAAY!
Staff: Nothing else to say?
[ FINISH? ]
They're a bit worried but the 4th member team climb up Fuji starts
Last time they dealt with bad weather
and to do the climb in 1 day they started early in the morning
This time they're taking off under pleasant weather
Right away once we check in on how the 4th members are doing
Mt. Fuji...
Endo: Every japanese person should try to make the climb at least once
Kakehashi: When I was little
everyday with brother and father
we'd climb a nearby mountain near the house
and be back before it was time for school
[ Mountain climbing family? ]
Guide: Run like that and you'll consume all your energy
Seimiya: Energy!
Those that underestimate the mountain are bound to be punished....
[ mini punishment ]
After that Seimiya
would receive further punishment from the mountain gods
As for Fujinomiya Team...their climb starts
Akimoto: We're just starting...don't you think its already rough terrain?
Yes...on this Fujinomiya Route
right from the start its rocky...its somewhat of a difficult route
Everybody doing ok?
I'm ok
Among them...the experienced one
and more importantly as new captain
Akimoto calls out to the team during the climb
however...
Its been 5 years since I made this climb
that's kind of a long time
Thrown in alone with a group of teenagers is 26 year old Manatsu-san
and obviously you can't win a fight against old age
In order to get the group fired up
the new captain had this suggestion for the 4th members
What should our rally cry be?
Yell something to get yourselves going
I love Manatsu-san~
eh...what's going on...I'm so happy
seriously?
You said it so that's what it'll be
Hearing Manatsu-san sounds weird to me but I'll say it
just say "love her"
hai...here goes
Manatsu-san!
love her~
Here we go!
OHH
[ guest hospitality mountain climbing? ]
Why was that so fun?
However...without realizing it everyone goes silent on this mountain climbing shoot
so then the captain had this suggestion
Since we've gone to all the trouble to do this climb
for a small change of pace
I've put talk themes in here
once I pull one we can talk about it
As expected with it being her 2nd climb up Fuji
the new captain has come completely prepared
How about this one
hai
What do you want to ask Akimoto captain?
OHH~
hai....hai!
Saya-chan
Kanagawa: So then now that you've become captain
hai
How do you want the group to progress?
[ Business interview? ]
That's a fairly huge question
Sounds like a magazine interview question
I'd like people to think "There's still elements of the old Nogizaka there"
Like Maiyan
Nanamin....Mattsun
the 4th members
I'd like to help get all of you to where you become group leaders like them
since I really believe that
I'd like to lead you there
I'll follow you!
Any other questions?
So Manatsu captain
what are your daily beauty tips?
[ That's what you wanted to ask right now? ]
eh what do I say
I eat mochi every day
precut mochi packs
once I run out of the 1kg packages
I immediately buy a new one
[ What is this conversation? ]
That's probably not going to be useful information
Around that time the Yoshida Route team
Last time its where they reunited with Ikuta....they've arrived at Station #6
While they have some break time
2 of the members went missing...
Staff: What are you doing right now?
Kitagawa: Seems like there'd be some fossils here
[ Searching for fossils ]
Kaki: I want to take some rocks home
Kitagawa: Is that not allowed?
Staff: Inside your heavy backpacks?
[ Crazy combo ]
Right here...to give out their current status
they're contacting Akimoto captain
Tamura: We're already at Station #6
Akimoto: ah station #6?
They're at station #6!
that's amazing
Endo: We've got a question for you
Akimoto: hai...what is it?
Endo: ah at this time
well you know
at age 26
you've turned 26
What are your ambitions at age 26?
[ This has nothing to do with Mt. Fuji ]
What would that be?
Its not just about me
it involves the kouhais too
and how they see me
I want to work hard to become someone that can be a leader
Seimiya: arigatou gozaimasu
[ Weak reaction ]
And then the climb restarted
and it seems that girl is at it again....
Seimiya: People will definitely get upset if I run
The naive girl that's not thinking of the consequences
the mountain gods again will punish her
Seimiya: What should I do...
Tomorrow my friend
we made plans to go somewhere
however
I forget to tell her that I won't be able to make it
And I don't have my phone
I have reserved seats
I have the tickets
Much like this Seimiya
lost not just her friend but also her physical strength...
and then
Did the wind get you?
Seimiya: I'm tired...
Seimiya decided to go at her own pace
used up a lot of energy and is now unable to move her feet
ah she's already down
She was all full of energy earlier
However as the path gets more treacherous
as they maintain their set pace
they get closer to the goal one step at a time
Its now been 3 hours and 15 minutes since the start of the climb
same as last time..they'll take a rest at mountain station #7
Like last time they'll check what they brought with them for the climb up Fuji
What is that?
First Kitagawa has brought...
Kitagawa: Its those things that expand in water
[ Purpose? ]
Why would you bring that with you?
Seimiya: What did you bring Saku?
ahhh~
Seimiya: That's from Principal
Endo: My lines from the script
Endo: Theater assistant-san
their words
even now I keep this as decoration
Tamura: Sayaka...
Kakehashi: I brought my Switch
[ When were you planning on playing? ]
Kakehashi: At the top of the mountain I'm playing Super Mario
[ Likes Super Mario Bros ]
Not many people doing that at the summit
And then Tamura
she's brought a stone that gives you a concentration boost
Tamura: Its a letter from Shiori-chan
She said to read it during times of struggle but I haven't read it yet
ah you haven't read it
Possibly if there isn't any hardship
I'm planning to read it at the summit
Tamura: Rei-chan?
That's pretty amazing somehow
Seimiya: I was thinking of bringing 11 mikans with me
But due to Rei's allowance I couldn't buy them
[ Can't afford 11 mikans ]
Kaki brought with her
a picture of 4th member Shibata and
a picture of herself and 3rd member Kubo
Tamura: ah she signed it
Kaki: She said "I like Kaki so I'm signing it"
What's your relationship with Shio-chan?
[ jealous ]
Seimiya: Those look really...beat up
[ cruel comment ]
Kumama?
Its Kumama and Kumachi and Usasa
Kaki: When I was little obaachan gave them to me
Kakehashi: I want this one
[ Wants Usasa ]
Her precious item from childhood....."I want it!"
[ Memories burglar Kakehashi ]
And then they had a warm light meal to heal up
Once again they take off
From here the path up Fuji gets much more difficult
Even with rest the accumulated fatigue starts to tear away at the body
and then around this point there was this change for this team of 6
Guide: They're not keeping up...
Kaki...Kitagawa....Seimiya...these 3
have begun to slow down
This time they put in a rest break at station #8
and they're also moving at a slower pace than earlier however
for this section...for a long time and with heavy bags they must keep going
Seimiya: Just walking a little bit gets me out of breath
The risk of altitude sickness increases in an environment with low oxygen
they have to keep climbing even if their bodies are near their limits
And then for 3 of them the pace
slows even further
Seimiya: This is too rough for my body
I can't keep up with the others at all
Here it was decided that it was too dangerous to make them keep up with the 3 ahead
The 3 of them would drop back
and climb up at a different pace
Yoshida Route Team has been split into 2
After this for these 6 people
another test awaits them
Will they be able to make it to the mountain huts?
As for Fujinomiya Team at station #6
they got a quick rest
and now the 6 of them are heading for station #7
However
what did they spot right here?
Tsutsui: yabah
Shibata: eh sugoi! sugoi!
Guide: Finally the climb will begin
yes...actually on the Fujinomiya route
compared to the Yoshida route its shorter but
its a steeper incline putting more stress on your legs and back
furthermore most of it is rocky
There's depression among the members
Can they cheer themselves up?
Lets go everybody
hai
Manatsu-san!
love her!
Here we go!
OHH!
That was a good one!
And with that the real mountain climbing starts here
Mt. Fuji is a tough climb
Could they hurry up and reach the top
[ Tired of the climbing scenes? ]
Shibata: This is fun!
fun...
does she mean that?
The fresh 4th members seem to be leaving the captain slightly behind
and then
Last time when I fell behind a little
I'd start to worry
oh no!
Good one
That was a real fall
Here she used her ultimate weapon
in an attempt to get some attention however...
Only 1 person came to check up on me
[ Ineffective ]
The Captain's in trouble
Because of the steep incline
to keep from getting altitude sickness by climbing up too fast
they repeatedly take rest breaks during the climb
And then
3 hours after they took off
they've finally arrived at station #7
This team also will check their personal belongings
Ayame-chan
hai
jaan
ah!
Everybody knows what this is?
Hayakawa: Its from Principal
Tsutsui: Back during Principal
the unity among the 4th members
we all became so close so suddenly
During Principal
this good luck bracelet meant so much to me
I thought if I brought it with me I'd be able to fight through this
And then Yakubo also brought something from Principal she kept for memories
That's remarkable
You've all got deep bonds
wonderful
Next its Kanagawa
Kanagawa: So with mountains
I think you'd probably lose track of what direction you're going
And that's why I've brought a compass with me
[ Wrong type of compass ]
Hear me out
its not one of those round compasses
its one of those other compasses
[ meaningless substitution ]
Next its Shibata
jaan
eh kawaii
A picture of her pet dog and
jaan
wahh~ its Kaki
a picture of her beloved Kaki
I love them
jaan
Next Hayakawa has brought a random bag
Once we climb to the top
I'll put mountain air inside
that fresh air
I'll give to Bananaman-san as a souvenir
I'll bring it back to them
seriously?
Hayakawa: Don't you think they've become used to city air?
So then once they breathe in this fresh air
maybe then they'll feel young again
She's assuming we're elderly
[ Worried about their old age? ]
ah but that makes me happy
And then last its Akimoto captain
Right here
[ Cat ears hairband ]
So this...well the fans
recently I've been putting cat ears on the other members
and making them act cute...ManaHara
They call it "Manatsu Harassment"
This time as well on Mt. Fuji
I'd like to do some Manatsu Harassment
Coming up we'll do ManaHara Janken
And the winner
will have to wear this all the way to the top of the mountain
That ok with you?
Please don't be disgruntled...
These 5 want to avoid this any way they can
1 winner will become the victim of ManaHara
Here goes
ManaHara Janken...janken pon~
ah!
Yakubo: ahh..so sad
so sad~
[ The sarcastic 4th members ]
hai
Ayame-chan or Yuna...who will it be
ManaHara Janken...janken pon~
ah!
omedetou!
[ Today's ManaHara-san ]
Tsutsui: eh...all the way to the peak?
That's right
Tsutsui: ehhhh~
put it on
kawaii~
[ Group ManaHara ]
Now that they've gotten a decent amount of rest
the goal is to reach station #9 to get some sleep
Once again they start climbing
To avoid having to climb while its dark out
they've increased their pace slightly
yabah
strong wind
And then right when its starting to get dark
good work
[ Station #7 - Elevation 3030m ]
However they're just reaching station #7
Everybody take a rest
Its still a long way towards reaching the goal of station #9
They'll take some minimal rest
and move on towards station #8
Just resting for 15 minutes...the sun has started to set
they won't be able to avoid night climbing
Furthermore starting right here
Guide: Its really rough terrain here
Its the hardest section of todays climb
ehhh~
However Shibata and Kanagawa had unexpected reactions to this announcement
Kanagawa: I can't wait!
[ Full on climbers high ]
This part is not fun at all
Althought 2 of them seem ready to go
its now a total night climb situation for Fujinomiya Team
In addition to the poor visibility from the darkness
there's also poor footing making the situation worse
These weakened members are then hit with yet another obstacle
These members stuck in a night climb
are then hit with yet another obstacle
wah~ insane wind
Akimoto: Really strong winds
wah~
[ 14m/s wind gusts ]
All of a sudden
wind gusts of 14m/s attack the members
yabah!
She's got the cat ears on
Even in the strong wind
Hayakawa: Painful...
They continue up the rocky terrain for 45 minutes
They finally arrive at station #8
Its tough climbing through that wind
However
they're supposed to spend the night at station #9
There's still 200 more meters to climb
And then after that there's a sudden change to the situation
What's happening?
rain
Will they all safely make it up to the next station?
Mt. Fuji is so harsh
Where's that been?
[ Try saying that during the video ]
And that stuff you brought with you
what was that thing that expands in water?
Kitagawa
With Mt. Fuji...in all that high elevation
I was wondering if it would expand even more
How big will this dog thing expand normally?
[ That would definitely get in the way ]
It gets that big? And then bringing that air to us
Happy to hear that
You thought of bringing back mountain top air as a souvenir
I'm so happy
That's because we're both so old and crusty right?
[ That part concerned her ]
fresh air right
But was she able to bring any of it back?
still don't know yet
Could be a giant dog in that bag....
[ miraculous collaboration ]
ah this bag fits perfectly
then she puts the water in