Tonight the members self produced their video clips
and the finished products will go up against each other
As the Video Clip Queen
she wins the right to produce her own episode so who will win it?
Entry #6
are 4th members Kakehashi and Kanagawa
So the both of you made this together
Please intro your video
Game Over
[ lame ]
Why did you think of that one?
Kakehashi and
Kanagawa
Retro Game Commentary
This time as a lover of video games its me Kakehashi
I also love video games...I'm Kanagawa
We're going to try out some retro games
These 2 will be attempting
released in 1985 for the Famicom system
Super Mario Brothers
A huge hit all over the world
and it started a video game boom
Its this side scrolling action game
Have you ever played Super Mario?
The one where you can fly
You've played it right? I have
I've played this game so many times
The challenge for these 2
From world 1-1 to 1-4
they're going to alternate stages
and make it through without dying
If they die they must start all over from world 1-1 as part of the strict rules
ah there it is! eh this is crazy right here
This is retro style Mario
Himura-san you're in this game right?
I am not that mushroom
Playing world 1-1
with confidence in the recent Mario games its Kakehashi
ah yabai yabai...I wasn't moving
Is that Himura-san? That's not me
eh looks like you've got this
That very first enemy...the goomba
eh sugoi...making steady progress
Isn't there a mushroom there
She didn't get the first mushroom?
You suck!
[ That was unbelievable ]
That was horrible
You died there?! That was an accident
[ 2nd Challenge - Super Mario Brothers ]
You don't run?
She's so bad
uwah...so bad
As soon as you say that
You sure you like games?
You really suck at this don't you
[ Can't watch this performance ]
[ 5th Challenge - Super Mario Brothers ]
yes yes...get that first...grow big
That's basics
Its true have to start out with that mushroom to get anywhere
ah you need the B button dash
Its been about 10 minutes since they started
and they've finally managed to reach world 1-2
Finally
World 1-2 is an underground stage
Kanagawa will take the controls for the 1st time
ah there it is...fire fire
the flower...fire?
fire flower
This is scary..hate this part...can't do this part
I'm going for it!
AUGHHH~  She wasted it!
Am I alive? Its still ok
Kanagawa took her first turn but
she showed us solid operation of the controls
and in one try she clears world 1-2
And then Kakehashi
now tries world 1-3 for the first time
If the goal was to world 2-4...I feel like I could do 2-4
[ Dead in 7 seconds ]
Even after all the work to get to 1-3
its quickly all over and they have to start over
You have to go to the beginning?
And then on attempt #14
they're back to world 1-3
Just now Kakehashi fell and died in 7 seconds
what about this time?
There's a mushroom right there
ok! catch!
What are you doing?!
[ Abandoned mushroom ]
Old video games are totally fun!
[ Super excited ]
eh sugoi
On attempt #14
they've reached the final goal of world 1-4
hold on now...you know something bad is coming
the boss right
drop down! drop down!
yabai yabai yabai yabai
yes! ok ok!
You made it!
ok ok ok ok ok
He's about to come out
He's coming
I could watch people play video games forever
He's right there
This time they must defeat the 1-4 boss Koopa
without touching the fire or its body
touch the golden axe behind him and its a clear
This part is hard
eh back to 1-1?
They finally reached the boss but
she was unsure what to do and took an unsatisfying defeat
After that on attempt #18
once again they're back at Koopa and
I don't know...I don't know what I'm supposed to do
Now on attempt #23
You need to be big before you get there
And after that...
you're always small when you get there
What now! I want to cry!
How many times did you die!
For these 2...because its one mistake and you're dead
you don't want to be tiny Mario
the strategy is to be the powerful Fire Mario when they fight boss Koopa
And now its attempt #35
Once I get here its basically over
She's getting better at this
You can do it....all right then
They finally kept Fire Mario
as they head into world 1-4
This way even if you get hit you won't instantly die
Go then? No need to stop for it right?
That's instant death right there!
That will end it
That's completely no good
Why is this so entertaining?
[ Attempt #41 ]
Because of that careless fall its another 20 minutes
this is now attempt #41
Attempt #41?
I see...you're trying to clear on #46 aren't you
Once again as Fire Mario its world 1-4
ok then...be careful now
ok its clear to go now...dozo
dozo
nice nice nice
You absolutely cannot get hit there!
[ Painful mistake ]
That was for fighting Koopa
She hit the fire right before reaching the boss
and goes back to the usual tiny Mario
Can't go back right
I'm so sorry
You can still clear this part with some skill
Use the dash!
Suddenly did it...she suddenly did it
sudden clear
yabai yabai
I'm so happy
It took about 2 hours
and on attempt #41
they successfully made it all the way through world 1-4 without dying
That was incredibly entertaining
Sorry about all that but I couldn't calm down
That was like going over to a friends house
But Kakehashi was horrible at the start
[ Kakehashi doesn't agree ]
At the end of the stage
you have to B button dash to get the flag
After 41 tries why didn't you figure that out?!
And then...these 2 cleared their goal however
right here they'll take on another retro game
And that game is...
right here...super famicom
I've never seen one of these before
[ The Super Famicom was released in 1990 as the successor to the Famicom ]
This game is called Super Fire Pro Wrestling X
we're going to play this game
So this game...it seems that Bananaman
were really into this game when they formed their duo
we're going to practice it and get good so that
we can play against them in studio
I'd like to do that!
The pro wrestling game Bananaman played all the time as teenagers
The Super Fire Pro series
For this pro wrestling game
both of them took home the console and game for intense practice
Just how good were they able to get?
What's this? Fire Pro?
Fire Pro Wrestling...I really played this game a ton
When we were young we'd go to each others houses to write jokes
but it was mostly playing this game
Played all day
So did you practice?
I got really into it
Its so much fun
Himura-san would setup the computer to play simulated matches
and he spent a year writing in a notebook who would win the championship
[ Bizarre hobby ]
It was like watching pro wrestling when you just watch the computer play
Like "hey that guy is strong"
[ Extreme Himura ]
And with that following all of Kakehashi and Kanagawa's practice
they'll now take on Bananaman one on one in some singles matches
In round 1
its Shitara vs Kakehashi
So I played this game so much
I'm seriously going to give you a beatdown
[ no mercy ]
You strong?
hai
She's lost some confidence
They have this in pro wrestling...that's why I spoke up first
[ Instigated the trash talking ]
Bring it on then! OY!
First they'll select their wrestlers
And Kakehashi has selected...
All Japan...the names are different though
I'll be Vader
Vader...there you go
That's Vader
sugoi
That guy is super powerful
Should I be him?
Stan Hansen! I'm thinking about using Hansen
This would be an awesome match
You'd never see foreigners paired up like this on a wrestling card
This is an awesome singles match
Can't believe I get to do this on a tv show
Now then
oh!
yes! ahh Vader
So there...that timing when you grapple
the timing after the grapple has to be perfect
what? I can't get any moves in
I can't do my moves...ah Vader sugoi
She's been practicing!
hai Boston Crab!
yes...take that punk
please stand up..stand up
eat some of this
[ Shitara goes on the counter attack ]
Vader looks tired
huh? He picked me up
Those are Vader's strong moves
Here's my Boston Crab!
rope! rope! hey rope! hey rope!
[ Loud ringside manager ]
yes!
Hansen! Kick out!
[ Intense battle ]
ah yabai yabai
This looks bad...this is bad
yabai yabai yabai
break out of it! break out of it!
[ peak excitement level ]
ah I lost
give up..that's a give up
[ Winner Kakehashi by Bear Hug: 4min 12sec ]
What was that?
You beat me you punk!
I couldn't pull off any moves
Couldn't do any?
Later on her timing was too good
She practiced hard
I couldn't even get one of my lariats in
That's true
I've lost...Himura-san its all you
May I play?
Next its Himura vs Kanagawa
Will Bananaman win the revenge match?
I'll be Undertaker
Undertaker?
That's an odd pick
You'd actually use the Undertaker on me?
[ Expert level choice ]
Misawa? Let's go with Misawa
Come get me Taker! Come on
strong!
strong
She's got the timing down
Himura-san you have to remember
[ Endless knife edge chop hell ]
timing! timing!
what? I can't get a single move in
That seems strange
You've been doing speedruns or something?
I have
This is so fun...we should all have a tournament
[ Has always wanted to do a tournament ]
Its possible its not accepting any of my moves so would you let me try something
That does happen right
Get your move in
[ Immediate counter ]
Now hold on! Could you let me do 1 move
You've done one
really? Did I really do one?
Are the buttons not working? There's your move
[ Fierce counter move ]
OY ganbatte Himura-san
It would hurt if we both lost
Let me do 1 move please
He's climbing the ropes...go for it!
ah that didn't work
[ Nothing but air ]
Just finish me already...
ahh give up
[ Winner Kanagawa by Bear Hug: 5 min 13 secs ]
She's mega mega powerful
ah...would you let us play another game?
[ A normal part of gaming ]
I'd like to play again someday
play again someday
You punks better remember that!
[ The heels retreat ]
And with that we've seen all the video entries in this Video Clip Queen Championships
Who will be selected as #1?
Now then...Himura-san
The selection for Video Clip Queen...onegaishimasu
I'll announce the winner
The 1st ever Nogizaka Video Clip Queen is
Akimoto Manatsu-san
[ Video Clip Queen - Akimoto Manatsu ]
really?!
[ Her self produced episode is scheduled to air next year! ]
Takayama...this must be disappointing for you
well...
What's the matter? What happened to her?
DON!
And we're...
wait why is staff-san here...
[ An outsider has invaded? ]
I'm a member
ah so you're not camera assistant-san
No I'm not...I'm Akimoto
Not sure why you're sitting there but
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
we are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And they are Nogizaka-chan
ZUKKYUN
ah we got a ZUKKYUN
And with that Himura-san
Its a little late but
lets celebrate Akimoto Manatsu becoming the new captain
With Sakurai having graduated Akimoto took over the duties of captain
It has yet to be fully covered on the show so
tonight's show is about celebrating the new captain
What does the captain do these days?
Do you give out money to anyone without any money?
That would help
"That would help" she says
[ onegaishimasu ]
What else then?
Does the captain clean up trash they've left behind?
Shiraishi is nodding yes to that
[ Wants it to happen ]
As far as the show goes
if the members and the captain don't get on the same page
well that would be bad for the group
And with that
over there
[ Trap door ]
We've brought this one in again?
Its been awhile
I only see this thing on [Komakasugite] and on this show
And with that tonight
it'll be quiz questions about Captain Akimoto
These are easy questions the members should know
so if a majority of 8 or more members answer correctly
she'll escape the trap door
But these questions are so easy
Like "Her name is Aki____"
[ Super low level ]
Those level type of questions right
That would make for a boring tv show though
We can't help that part...this is supposed to be a celebration
Its not like we want to see her fall
You pretty much talk to everyone right?
That's right..I pretty much establish communication with everyone
so I get the idea that they all know about me
Because of that...make your way over there
I have to stay there?
Is this how you treat the captain?
You won't fall...it'll be fine
[ No need to worry ]
Akimoto is in her normal clothes
Here Akimoto moves into standby over the trap door
and right away the quiz will get started
Of course seeing her up there...that looks high up
But Akimoto herself doesn't look much different compared to sitting over here
[ Due to the size of her head ]
Now then here is Akimoto Quiz question #1
Himura-san..this question should be no problem
Akimoto Manatsu
what day is her birthday?
This one?
That should be no problem
As captain of course the members would know what her birthday is
Will a majority of them know the answer?
Well then...Hoshino has known her for so long...how about Hoshino shows us her answer?
August 17th...you're sure of this?
I'm sure of it...since I'm a 1st member
as a 1st member
There's a bunch of birthdays in August
That's true
Hori would you show us your answer?
August 26th...that's a little different
You remember her birthday as being August 26th?
yes...I have this image of celebrating her birthday around the end of summer
ahhh I see
celebration around the end of summer
She's making quite a face...I wonder what's going on
But like Yamashita...she joined the group later on
Would you show us your answer?
August 19th
So you're thinking that's your senpai's birthday?
yes there's no way you can get your senpai's birthday wrong
That's true
eh if you can get 8 overall
you'll be safe for this question
hai...understood
This is an easy one isn't it?
Its mega easy!
Why are you angry?
How about a newcomer like Kaki show us her answer?
What's this?
August 20th
You're sure of this?
yes I am
confident?
You memorized it or something?
She has the same birthday as Shiraishi-san
ah...because you memorized Shiraishi's birthday
[ only because she memorized Shiraishi's birthday ]
From what we see there's already 4 different answers
Does anyone have the correct answer?
ah Kaki had it right
Her birthday is August 20th
[ Answer: 8/20 ]
And that means 3 of them answered wrong
yes...they were totally wrong
Well they all had August correct
That's true
Fairly close
You can't have fairly close on a quiz show
Now then you'll need 7 more correct answers otherwise you'll fall
ehh? no! yada!
She going to be ok?
Everyone all at once...OPEN
I see all red
hai OK
[ 12 people answered correctly ]
Shiraishi wrote
arigatou
She wrote "same as mine"
yes same birthday
And Yoda
I got it right
August 20th
Once I heard the show was going to be a Manatsu-san Quiz
I studied the Nogizaka homepage
So if you didn't study up you wouldn't have known it
[ verbal blunder ]
Thank goodness she did
That's a safe
CLEAR
arigatou
You might not even fall today
hai
The questions are that easy
Akimoto Quiz Question #2
Captain Akimoto
what is it that she refuses to do?
There's something she'll never do then
Of course all talent-san has something
What is that one thing she refuses to do?
Can a majority answer correctly?
The members answers are....
Shinuchi if you would show us your answer
DON
yes please read it out loud
Wear clothes that cover the neck
She will never wear clothes that cover up her neck
Takayama would you show us your answer?
hai
Wear clothes that cover the neck
So is this something she's said often?
yes we're buddies...the "we refuse to wear clothes that touch the neck" buddies
ahhh
Could we see yours Yoda?
Yoda's answer is incredible
buzz cut
What does that mean?
You studied for this didn't you?
I did study but
I'm thinking she hates buzz cuts
in the back?
obviously I'd hate that!
So she'd refuse a buzz cut?
Even with Manatsu-san
Is there anyone that's actually ok with getting a buzz cut?
How about Sigourney Weaver?
[ Buzz cut OK ]
Its fine for Sigourney Weaver
I'm talking about people in Nogizaka
Hori would you show us your answer?
No eyebrows
no eyebrows?!
What's that about?
Since she's self-conscious about her eyebrows
without all the proper eyebrow makeup
I'm thinking she won't show her face to anyone
How about Asuka-chan?
Refuses to work without her bangs done
She's giving her a stare down...
no bangs
Excuse me Akimoto-san
your reactions are giving away the answer
What's your problem? I'm giving you a buzz cut
[ Punishment buzz cut ]
Has she mentioned her bangs before?
She's never talked about it but without bangs she'd look really weird
[ Super insulting ]
That was mean
Let's check if any of these current answers are correct
dozo
Hori
No eyebrows!
[ Refuses to perform without her eyebrows touched up ]
Akimoto you refuse to work without the eyebrows?
That's off limits
In certain places I'm ok without makeup or having my hair done
but I have to have my eyebrows filled in
eh? So you wouldn't say no to a buzz cut then
I've never had to consider a buzz cut before
nobody has requested it
I want to give her a buzz cut
But there was a match with clothes that cover your neck
When they said that I'm like "I agree"
that answer means that they know me very well
I've got a short neck so
clothes that go up the neck
make just my head look completely unnatural
[ Much like a Kokeshi doll ]
And with that
let's have everyone reveal their answers
OPEN
And with that
everyone reveal your answers at once
OPEN
What? ah Kitano answered correctly
arigatou Kii-chan
And that means
a majority of them did not answer correctly
unfortunately this will be her first fall
seriously just hold on a second
But we have to do this
I really hate the part where I know that I'm going to fall
wait!
But you could fall several times today
ah! I hate this part!
How would you like to do this?
For the first fall you can decide how its done
[ Getting toyed with ]
Should I just press it or give you an 8-count?
Which is better?
I'll take the countdown
Too long?
Here goes
you'll get 5 seconds
I really hate this part...what now
She's all white
HA HA HAAA~
Pretty good job of getting covered white
Am I supposed to keep doing this...
Next you'll fall in an egg bath and then finally into panko bread crumbs
[ Flour to eggs to bread crumbs for frying ]
Then into boiling hot oil
[ deep fried croquette ]
Every time Akimoto-san does this it highlights her laugh wrinkles and makes her look old
yes spread it out to make it a pretty white
hey Hori...as far as makeup goes...making wrinkles stick out is bad right
that's right...this is the complete opposite of what's currently trendy in makeup
[ Next week its the conclusion of "Celebrate the new Captain Akimoto" ]
Now then...she's fallen down 1 time
Will she be ok here on out?
Please don't allow your captain to fall anymore