We're a little late but
let's celebrate Akimoto Manatsu becoming the new captain!
With Sakurai having graduated Akimoto took over the duties of captain
It hasn't been fully covered on the show so
tonight its an episode to celebrate the occasion
We're giving out quiz questions about Captain Akimoto
the questions are so easy that the members should have no trouble answering so
if a majority of 8 people answer correctly
Akimoto can avoid falling down the trap door
On last weeks show
What's off limits for her?
We are "never wear clothes that go up the neck" buddies
What do you mean buzz cut?
On the 2nd question she quickly went down
this time how many times will Akimoto fall through the trap door?
Now then...she's fallen in 1 time
please don't allow your captain to fall anymore
hai
Akimoto Quiz...question #3
For the next question
either get 8 correct answers or
if Shiraishi answers correctly Akimoto will be safe
Just needs Shiraishi to answer correct then
Maiyan
Just need Shiraishi to get it right
This question has a special rule
since the question involves Akimoto and Shiraishi
even if less than 8 answer correctly
as long as Shiraishi answers correctly its a clear
Captain Akimoto
just like Shiraishi
have something unexpected in common...what is it?
in common?
just like Shiraishi
Could it be something recent?
Its already remarkable that you share the same birthday as Shiraishi
are you like the same person or something?
just about
[ Shiraishi just about equals Akimoto ]
Shall I give out a hint
I'd like one
But once I say this I'm not sure it'll help
You'll be like "do they really have that in common"
"maybe they're like twins or something?"
[ HINT: Would make you believe they're twins ]
But that is so true
you'll wonder if we're twins
eh I have no idea...
Shiraishi hasn't written anything
and she's the key player
Only Shiraishi has to answer correctly for her to be safe
You're very lucky
First lets take a look at Shinuchi's answer
there it is
Parents own the same model of car
ahhhh~
Their parents own the same type of car
That'll make you think they're twins
[ Just a car makes them twins ]
Same model of car...they're practically twins
Now then Ikuta
please read it aloud
They say "yoisho" to anything
YOISHO
yoisho!
yoisho
That's not it?
Manatsu has this habit where when she sits down
she'll say "yoisho"
She'll open something "yoisho"....its a habit she has
Unexpectedly Maiyan too
she'll also say "yoisho" for things
That makes them twins!
I see then...Hori
hai
They were born in the same hospital
ahh that one
since they have the same birthday
If they were born in the same hospital its like ehhhh
they must be twins
Now then Shiraishi
hai
Let's look...if Shiraishi answers correctly
That would be good
Wore the same clothes to the audition
You both wore the same clothes to the audition
eh Shiraishi..this something you remember?
Not sure if its Manatsu but I know someone wore the same clothes
[ vague recollection ]
She's unsure of whether it was Akimoto or not
But since we have the same birthday
and other things in common I thought I'd try writing this one
got it
so then
among these answers are any of them correct?
None among these
The rest of you then...open
red means correct answer
Nobody got it
[ NOT CLEAR - trap door ]
yes that would not be a clear
What is the answer then Akimoto?
The results of our medical checkup were the same
Shiraishi?
[ Does not remember! ]
Even hearing the answer she doesn't recall
You don't remember this?
Medical checkup results?
You mean the english one? yes!
Its like the detailed results were the same
You mean the one that tells you whats in bad shape?
yes yes yes yes yes
This is sad right now
The detailed results were the same
and for some reason
This is way too sad right here
[ one sided ]
I heard about it from manager-san
Its too sad...we have to drop you
Its sad...Shiraishi doesn't know what you're talking about
Shiraishi you don't know what she's talking about do you
And she thought this would make them twins
To be honest we both also use the same lip gloss
and then also
the bag...we also use a similar drawstring bag
[ Desperation ]
All this together in your mind makes you twins?
I'm wondering if we're twins...
So you use the same drawstring bag then Shiraishi?
That's cute
The same drawstring bag
The lip gloss...that's a recent one right?
I get that one
But that medical checkup one...not quite
eh? You knew about the drawstring bag though?
[ Terrifying levels of desperation ]
That's way too sad!
What drawstring bag?
What bag she says
The light green one...
ahh using it now?
I've always carried a light green bag with me
sorry about this...
Shiraishi over here...Shiraishi will press the button for us
[ Cruel executioner ]
Now with Shiraishi pressing it
And with that Shiraishi will be in charge of the trap door button
not yet! Maiyan
Maiyan...Maiyan
Maiyan Maiyan
here goes
Maiyan!
Manatsu gomen!
That was so sad
That was really sad
Having Shiraishi press the button
Shiraishi also teased her with the button
That was incredibly sad
gomen she says
She doesn't feel sorry though
Shiraishi please return to your seat
The first thing Shiraishi wrote was so different
Her first answer was "really good shooter"
[ From the 2019 Fall Fatal Four Way Battle ]
That's right we're both good shooters!
See...we have so much in common!
[ Horror movie level of terror ]
I feel bad for her
Feel bad for her
Feel so bad for her
Akimoto that's too bad
gomen gomen
We believed this question would be easy since it was part of a survey taken earlier
She said she'd answer right away so
we thought Shiraishi would know this one
Did we discuss this directly?
We talked!
[ Desperation ]
[ How many times will new Captain Akimoto fall today? ]
Akimoto Quiz Question #4
This question also has a special rule
Even if over 8 people don't answer correctly
as long as Ikuta answers correctly its a clear
Either Ikuta or 8 people get it and she's safe
Iku-chan will definitely get it
really?
Captain Akimoto
if she were to give Ikuta a nickname what would it be?
you see...its totally easy
Seems she could get this one
Do you normally call her this?
Hold on...you can't just start talking to her
I'll make you go up there
[ The in denial BBA ]
Seems like you can get this one
I have a lot of confidence for this one
oh...Ikuta just gave her an ok
Once you understand our relationship
Why are you talking right now?
Maybe we should drop her once for that
[ Already covered in flour but still doesn't want to fall ]
Please write your answers
Akimoto do you have any new gags lately?
gags?
Other than your ZUKKYUN and UFFUN
eh right now its those two
You're currently doing those two
I'd like to see you do three
really?
ZUKKYUN...UFFUN
Could you add one to that?
I'd also like to see
ZUKKYUN like this...UFFUN to the side...something else to the other side
Can you make something that fits in?
ZUKKYUN
UFFUN
and something else
Try just going with the flow
3...2...1
ZUKKYUN
UFFUN
ZUKKON
I like it!
[ zukkon! ]
Not sure what you're doing though
The sound doesn't match your movement though
You like zukkon then? Its good
First lets see...eh Hoshino
Musical
nickname Musical
OY Musical!
If its Iku-chan
like if you yelled "Musical!" seems like she'd yell "hai"
She truly is Musical
Good one...OY Musical!
[ Musical Ikuta ]
That's a cool nickname
That makes me happy
And then Kitano
Genius
sugoi....that's quite a nickname
How about Kubo? DON
Me too
Genius
How about Endo?
DON
Genius
How about Shiraishi?
DON
Genius
What's going on here?
[ Does not hate this ]
How about Hori then?
DON
Question monster
What's that mean?
Its like Iku-chan is aggressive with the questions
she's pretty much
"What if this were done like this"
or like "What happens to people when they die?"
I see..so she asks a lot of questions then
How about Asuka-chan?
DON
Monster
That's in a good way
in a good way
Monster Genius right
And Shinuchi?
Monster
ah what's that about?
I've witnessed how she picks on Manatsu
She the type to mess with people?
Its crazy
Ikuta does this to Akimoto
That's right...she'll rub on her head
It can be early morning or it doesn't matter when...she'll mess with my head
That indeed is a monster
ehh Tsutsui
oneechan
oneechan?! But I'm older than her
Is that a Takeshi-san thing? oneechan!
Why is she oneechan?
Why?
They're such good friends I'm thinking she's like an oneechan to her
That meaning of oneechan
I see..not looking good for getting 8 correct answers
yes..I need Iku-chan to get it right
Well then Ikuta would you show us your answer?
dozo
eh Gian
Gian
Stop giving away the answer with your facial expressions
[ The face don't lie ]
That's awful
She smiling and everything
I can't help it...I don't have a poker face
This one?
I don't understand it either but whatever happens she says "That's Gian"
She says Gian around me
so I figured that was the answer
I see
Now then...is that the correct answer
arigatou
And that means she's safe
Thank goodness...I knew they'd answer it for me
I haven't accepted Gian as a nickname
The reason I call her Gian
When we're in a car or a plane we're often sitting next to each other
The seats are really your designated personal space
Right here there's usually like an armrest
She'll take the armrest and push it to the back
She lifts it
yes and then
even with that line there she places her leg over the line
Then somehow she'll get her bags in there
When I'm using lipstick she'll say "I want some"
[ What's yours is mine ]
She's like that?
When I put on earrings she's like "give me"
You give it to her?
I never give stuff to her
That's why I think she's Gian
Why? You just like her stuff?
Stuff she's using
yes..I'll think "I want that"
[ I want it so hand it over ]
hey give that to me
Akimoto Quiz Question #5
Captain Akimoto Interview Quiz
What's the most verbally abusive insult Akimoto could say about Himura?
wah what would that be? That's a hard question...its Himura-san
He's such a good person
Saying this
it pains me to say anything
ehhh
Wait we're doing this one again?
The answer doesn't have to be exact...just needs to follow the same idea
Try saying something based on what you see
Why do we have to look at them slowly think of an answer?
[ Hidden insult fest ]
Why all the shots of them thinking hard?
What's the most verbally abusive insult Akimoto could say about Himura?
that's why they're trying to answer
Everyone's answers are...
Takayama
hai
slimy puddle frog
What do you mean slimy puddle frog?
Did you really think everyone would have that same answer?
Now how about Ume
cringe inducing physical appearance
cringe inducing physical appearance?
What does that mean?
"UWAH~" kind of like that?
[ Goosebumps grade physical appearance ]
How about Ikuta then? Ikuta
old man
oh shut up
[ Simple is best ]
old man!
old man! Quiet down with that
You'll be an old lady someday
How would Akimoto say that to him?
old man
Quiet down Musical
[ Counters using her nickname ]
I'm happy...I like that
How about Shiraishi?
Where's the chin?
shut up!
shut up
Its right here...the chin line is right here!
I would never say something like that normally so
if I had to say something that's just what came out
where's the chin
Asuka-chan
Some kind of slimy flesh ball
shut up!
shut up
I'm hearing lots of slimy today
[ Bad Asuka ]
Up to now Asuka-chan took time to write her answers but this one she wrote instantly
How about Hori?
Hori
repulsive fingers man
Can't help that...its my joints
Its not all finger the joints are a little darker
repulsive fingers man
Why are my fingers repulsive?
You'll never match answers with that
You thought 8 or more people would answer "repulsive fingers man"
Yamashita
Face is buried
These are normal insults
It is not buried
Yoda
buzz cut
[ Limited to buzz cuts ]
Now then the correct answer
wah~ this is so hard...its Himura-san
He's such a good person
Saying this pains me
ehh
Crappy chin man
The correct answer is crappy chin man
That was the dirtiest of them all
That was the dirtiest
I don't think that but I had to give an answer
When forced to answer you call him crappy then
Why is my chin crappy?
And with that anyone with a chin related answer will get marked correct
chin..maybe its just Shiraishi that got it
"face is buried" is pretty close
[ Facial contour issues ]
fine Yamashita also gets it correct
That's all of them right
Well you're nowhere near getting 8 people
Himura-san would you press it?
This isn't good...Himura-san onegaishimasu....I truly don't believe that
Call him crappy chin man to his face
I'm using my chin to press it
[ Crappy chin switch ]
That's a new one...tell him then Akimoto
hey crappy chin man
I watched crappy chin man hit the button and couldn't even see her fall
[ The downside to using the crappy chin switch ]
That kind of hurt
oh your hair is starting to look kind of cool
I really don't think that
eh? You don't think of him like that
Akimoto Quiz Question #6
So Akimoto
it doesn't matter what her answer is as long as 8 people answer the same
ohh
Question
Captain Akimoto..as a part of Nogizaka46
what does she mean to everyone?
New Captain Akimoto
what do the members think of her?
Rather than as part of Nogizaka46...
If the respect is there we should see a lot of answers that will make her happy
Shiraishi
may we see your answer
She's a person anyone would find lovable
uwah~
That's what you think of her?
She's a super hard worker and anybody that watches her
would take a liking to her
[ Cannot hide the joy ]
Takayama
She's someone that's loved by all
Same thoughts as Maiyan
Ikuta
She's someone that's reliable and lovable
That's 3 of them
Kitano
hai
Everyone's calming influence
calming influence
Yoda
A sexy beam of light
What's this? sexy
You got called sexy
Asuka-chan
Rule breaker
[ Sudden disrespect ]
Like how she exposes some skin
just those kind of rules
I also think she's lovable
Then why didn't you write that instead?
Everyone please show us your answers
DON
I see kind and reliable up there
I also see mother figure up there
So then
is there a correct answer?
They didn't have similar answers
none
eh but still
since I'm really happy can we just leave it at that?
[ Getting compliments more important than falling ]
The answer Akimoto wrote down
kawaii
[ Answer: kawaii ]
Nobody here answered "kawaii"
eh I didn't even get 1?
None
Got a sexy in there
I still fall after all these compliments?
That's right
But you're lovable and soothing
those types of compliments plus reliable
I am happy to see all that
I'm happy but
Please yell out "I'm so happy!" for us
please yell "so happy"
I'm so happy!
KYAAA
I was a little fast there...gomennasai
Still get surprised by it every time don't you
Its scary
Every time you lift yourself out of there I see the same thing
[ Expect a white Akimoto ]
I wasn't expecting to fall so much
Next its the last one
Last
Let's get this last one
Awhile back...during NogiDoko
Akimoto's 1st episode "10 questions with Akimoto Manatsu" remember it?
I remember
It was 7 years ago
For the last question we want Akimoto and all of you to answer the same
everyone?
7 years ago
Akimoto as a senbatsu member of the 4th single
this took place when she came back as a member
The everyone must answer the same quiz
When you think of a large animal its....
There's a lot of large animals
elephant elephant elephant elephant elephant-san
elephant elephant elephant elephant elephant elephant
elephant!
Now then
Akimoto...your answer...dozo!
Bear
Akimoto was the only person to write bear and it was a big fail
Because of that let's do that one again
[ Revenge match after 7 years ]
Akimoto Quiz Final Question
When you think of fall fruit its...
Its a simple question with limited choices
but here Takayama...
How about we agree on that fruit with the strong sense of freshness
Would that cause confusion?
Why not go with the fruit that doesn't have that freshness
Let's do the one without the strong sense of freshness
Based on Takayama's guidance
will they all be able to match their answers?
But its fruit we're talking about
Now then everybody all at once
OPEN
The final question
When you think of fall fruit its...
what did they answer?
Now then everybody all at once
OPEN
DON
persimmon persimmon persimmon persimmon persimmon persimmon
sugoi...they all had persimmon
Now then if Akimoto
wrote down persimmon
they clear...this is revenge for 7 years ago
Did they become one? Akimoto's flip card
onegaishimasu dozo
pear
pear!
no way? eh why?
[ revenge match is a fail ]
I'm shocked...what happened?
This is super creepy
The same result 7 years later
[ deja vu ]
You really think its persimmon?
[ Still in disbelief ]
Their answers did not match
But from now on...Captain keep working hard
ganbarimasu
So then...itterasshai
Shitara-san
Shitara-san...Shitara-san
no wait..really
hai~
It has to be persimmon there
sumimasen~
well those answers didn't match
Why did you write pear? Was that on purpose?
[ Akimoto Theater is underway? ]
Its the same bear pattern
If the bear one was on purpose that would be scary
How come?
I ate a pear yesterday
That's unrelated
[ It doesn't matter what you ate ]
Finally new Captain Akimoto will express her thoughts
Its better to spread out the flour evenly right?
This good? kawaii kawaii
no your nose...the nose
You've become crappy nose man
Please don't lump us together
She doesn't want to be lumped with you
What the hell
You shut up!
[ crappy nose vs crappy chin ]
crappy chin man
Your zukkon is stupid
That's a stupid looking gag
Akimoto are you ready? onegaishimasu
hai...I've been named new captain..I am Nogizaka46 Akimoto Manatsu
well perhaps
its possible you don't feel like cooperating with me but
I'll do my best to help everyone along so
everyone don't worry
it would be nice if you continue following us
everyone please look forward to seeing us
bye bye!