Nogizaka Video Clip Queen Championships!
woo hoo!
Things the members have wanted to do
they've made those things into self produced video clips
In this episode their finished creations will go up against each other
For the member that shines as the Video Clip Queen
they'll win the right to produce their own episode of the show
On last weeks show
we saw the 2 entries from Ikuta and Takayama
this week what kind of video clips will appear?
First we're starting with Hori Miona's creation
I'm personally into makeup
this time no matter what
I wanted to give a member my own personal makeup session
Not for yourself? Another member?
that's right
I'll be giving that girl a makeover
Because she's hopeless
[ Currently in need of help? ]
Were you thinking "this girl needs a makeover?"
Its someone that originally showed no interest
so to get them into fashion and makeup and such
I did this one
What is makeup according to Hori Miona?
Makeup is...
something a girl can't live without
Its your own personal pursuit to become the image of an ideal woman
It requires a kind of tuition...this is what best suits me
I'd like to continue pursuing makeup until the day I die
The charismatic beautician
Hori Miona
is here to support all women
Beauty Channel
Miona's Beauty Lesson
Its 3rd member Mukai Hazuki
Mukai?
The reasoning is...so normally
What's up with this picture?
you could say she's got her own unique style
Today too...she's got some unusual fashion
And now that she's 20
like femininity for example
to give her a different kind of mature look
using fashion and makeup...I'd like to show her some things
Without this stuff
I can't step out into the world
eh?
It makes that much difference?
It adds gloss and will tone up your skin
This makes your skin glossy
eh doesn't makeup-san do this for you? You do this yourself?
I do it myself
You do it yourself?
So this foundation
its super good...its by IPSA
ultimate foundation
Switch over to this stuff and its "you've become mega cute"
the fans will say this to you
As for powders...the white types
when you're adding color
the foundation is the base color
so it becomes meaningless
Now for the next step
to add some complexion
[ Apply lipstick to the base ]
You've mentioned that your bangs always have that soaking wet look right
I'll apply this powder to your hairline
technique
I'll add some to your hair
Doing this will help keep your bangs from getting dried out
I'll add highlights now...highlights are crucial
You have a high nose so you don't need so much
If I cover the entire area
it'll make your nose look stretched out
So just in this upper area
and just a dab to the tip of the nose
Mascara too
if you use a brown color
a black mascara would make everything look tight
Basically both the eyeliner and mascara should be brown colors
Feels moist right?
If its too moist
use tissue to clean it off
[ Lightly remove the foundation to apply lipstick directly ]
That's better for applying colors directly
rub your upper and lower lip together
What's wrong? What happened?
Its all spread out now
Did she spread it all over herself?
You smacked your lips a lot didn't you?
make-up
hairstyle
fashion
Hori Miona has taken care of it all
her biggest masterpiece Mukai Hazuki
is complete
eh~
First we have the trendy glossy skin look
and then the tone up
by applying the foundation
it makes her skin look bright
pink blush to the cheeks to make them look wider
went with a dull pink
for the mouth...with a small mouth like hers...to make it look wide
I mixed some orange and red
the mascara and eyeliner are brown colors
it brings out the girly side of her as well
under her eyes and on her eyelids
some reddish brown colors and glitter
I've tried to turn her into a sly and sparkly kind of girl
I see...you've given Mukai a makeover
But she does look cute
very nice
mature looking
Today Mukai
is the new Mukai here?
Lets bring her out here then
mega kawaii~
ah she's looking cute
She's also walking differently
Its like your nose is high
eh Mukai how was it doing this?
getting a makeup session
well...sorry my voice is all hoarse
[ At such an important moment ]
She actually didn't give her voice a makeover
The clothes too?
ah these are my clothes
Those are your clothes?
I feel bad for using my own clothes though
Is that so?
Why does she keep doing that?
This entire time...
What was that move?
For today I've kind of
asked her to try a new character
Its not her usual self...so she's acting more girly
What types of things does she say?
Would you buy this 1 million yen bag for me?
That's horrible!
[ The face she uses when she asks you to buy stuff ]
Would you buy this 1 million yen bag for me?
That's the message you're sending?
She's a sly calculating type
1 million yen bag?
well I'll have to think about it...
[ gullible oniisan ]
Can you tell who does makeup themselves and who goes to makeup-san?
Hori-chan has a huge makeup bag
She carries the makeup kits that stack up and expand
That's right
Is that so? She likes it then
While Takayama was talking
she's still looking at me like "Buy me this 1 million yen bag"
[ Fully gets into a role ]
Forget about the 1 million yen bag
Did Hori instruct you to target Himura to get the bag?
How many million yen bags?
How many millions are you going for?
She keeps looking over here
Face the cameras and ask for one
good...no that's good
That's good somehow
1 million yen bag
But she's usually had this wild type of image
her usual image is kind of like this
[ constantly preparing for battle ]
That's the only Mukai I know
shoulders drooping and looking up
Like something is about to drop on her
When we do games or something her eyes bulge out
[ The woman who takes things way too seriously ]
But when she looks like this
this is like having an actress from a drama make a guest appearance
She fits that image
We are seeing a different side of her
Stop making those faces!!
How many millions do you want?
The next entry
is a Shiraishi creation
This time I've done a comedy sketch
comedy sketch?
I'd like everyone to give it a watch
You did a comedy sketch?
hai
oh! eh~
This is Shiraishi Mai's...I want to do a comedy sketch
This time Shiraishi wanted to perform in a comedy sketch
so she gave these comedians an offer
Its these people...
Kanda has this great ramen place....let's go there
Hold on now...come over here
This is the place
Trying to be funny
Comedy sketch masters
Shiraishi gave an offer to
King of Conte 2014 Champions
Sissonne
So how come
you want to do a sketch with us?
Well recently we've worked together a lot
I've also gone to see your live show
from that I've totally gotten into your comedy
This time I definitely wanted to work with you
So you don't look at us like fresh new talent then
[ Shiraishi is tired of watching them ]
You're joining with us to make a comedy sketch
Today along with Sissonne-san
and myself Shiraishi
its a new unit
named Sironne
That sounds kind of delicious
Something you'd eat in Nagoya
And with that...to create a comedy sketch
they're having a meeting
What kind of sketch would you like to make?
What kind?
I like the out of control ones
out of control
out of control type
By the way...between setup man and straight man
which role do you prefer?
There aren't any girls who want the straight man role
I've never heard of such a thing
Put me in your sketch...I want to do the grunt work!
It could happen...I'll be in charge of moving the story along
I don't have much confidence with this
I'd prefer doing the setup
But with Shiraishi-san we could
I'd like to see you act all emotional
I don't get to do that much
You're in charge of doing cold stares right?
Its those cold stares right
[ The Nogizaka stare ]
Kind of like an oneesan presence
And then also
tell us what's off limits for you
off limit items?
Like "I absolutely will not do this"
my butt?
[ She will not expose her butt ]
She can't expose her butt then
Just the butt? Everything else is considered OK?
[ Afterwards.... ]
The script is all finished
The theme is based on [Shiroi Kyoto]
ah that's right
that's the hidden theme
human drama...human drama
Right away they started practicing the script from Sissonne
to hear papa was in an accident...
Could you make it more tragic sounding?
For the line "Its all my fault"?
Just what kind of comedy sketch did they create?
Now then
A new unit that's here just for today
please watch this comedy sketch by Sironne
Please god I beg you...please save his life
Is that Shiraishi?
Its not her
mama!
Mai!
How's papa?
He's in surgery
Can they save him?
I don't know
Why did papa have to get into an accident?
sensei!
my father...how is he?!
what's his condition?
Are you the daughter?
That's correct
Please calm down
calm down...you have to give him some space
sensei!
Did you save my father?
Please calm down
I did all I could for him
I'm unsure what condition he'll be in after this
It can't be
Its all my fault
papa...
I was going to take the dog out for a walk
he said to go to the supermarket to buy groceries for dinner
But since going to the supermarket would have been troublesome for me
I said I'm walking Jon the dog...papa should go get the groceries
So if I had actually gone shopping...
papa never would have had this accident
Don't cry...you did nothing wrong
What happened to Jon?
He's tied up in front of the hospital
The dog is out front then?
sensei! whoa whoa whoa....hai hai hai
Please save my father!
I already told you I did everything I could for him
Please let's all calm down
hey now...let's all calm down
calm down..hey its still attached to your wrist
sensei!
onegaishimasu!
Please just step back for a moment
just calm down...stay back..stay back!
young lady...young lady!
please wait there! why are you running away?
sensei why are you running from us?
please hold on a second
I understand...I'll listen
Let's talk...okaasan...ahhh
What are you hiding from us? There's nothing
I'm hiding nothing
You need to calm down...it'll be fine...calm down
Do you realize you're holding a bag of poop!
You're carrying poop
I'm telling you the surgery was a success
mama~
Its all my fault
okaasan...the poop is touching your face
She's getting a good sniff right now
Mai its not your fault
Mai you did nothing wrong
She's breathing it in deeply isn't she
So today
I made up my mind not to do anything
I stayed in bed till 5
Its mama's fault...mama did this
Mama did nothing wrong!
people have days where they stay in bed
yes they do!
I don't want a mama like that
Could you take care of that bag first?
please god
You're in a hospital
please save him!
save him!
Its rude to pray with a poop bag
That's rude to pray to god with a bag of poop
okaasan please stop using the bag of poop as a religious offering
Your father has regained consciousness!
papa!  papa!
papa!
Please leave that here
Get rid of the poop please
I'm bringing Jon!
Don't bring in the dog
Jon! ah
ah okaasan did you just wet yourself?
sugoi
You did a complete comedy sketch with Sissonne
yes I'm incredibly thankful
Was that real dog poop in there?
For the poop visual we used fried red bean buns
[ a delicious substitute ]
To make it look realistic
It really did look real
it looked so realistic...sugoi
Towards the end she did this one
So was that difficult?
hmmm...it unexpectedly required a lot of physical endurance
sugoi...wish we could have seen that performed live in studio
Now if something happens to Sissonne you can fill in
As long as its wrapped around here
[ As long as there's poop ]
The next entry is an Akimoto creation
In Nogizaka a lot of things are off limits
in particular anything thats sexy
The sexy stuff is definitely off limits
So you can't do nude scenes?
[ Absolutely not ]
Showing a lot of skin is off limits
You have a clean image
We have to preserve that clean image but
since today's show is about things we really want to do
nude scene!?
Its not a nude scene but Konno-san
I went to him directly to persuade him to give me permission
Asked him in person?
I got his permission so
I made this video that's similar to TV Asahi's [Hitou Roman]
hot springs?
It was something I wanted to try
I made a video that has that same feel
hot springs shoot!?
ah...is that Akimoto over there
ah there's Akimoto
[ Manatsu's Steamy Travel Show ]
ah...steamy travel
The place where perfectly clear autumn skies welcome you...
the place everyone knows about...this popular hot spring location is....
Atami
Right away I'm going to where I'll be spending the night
or at least that's what I thought
The smell of delicious food invites me...
so its a quick detour through the shopping district
ah!
eh~
I've stopped to visit
a place where you can get freshly fried food items on a stick
Maruten
For example this piping hot cheese stick
itadakimasu
What's going on here?
mmm~
oishii
This gourmet food that you can savor as you walk around
its a great way to enjoy the hot spring area
Now she's done it
Staff: Akimoto-san...there's cheese on your face
really?
ah...using the tongue
Are you stupid or something?
[ messing with the audience ]
They don't make tv shows like this
Its 10 minutes by car from Atami Station
I've arrived at my lodging for the night
konnichiwa
[ Owner: Uzawa Tomomi-san ]
Taking care of me
its retained the look of the Showa era
this historic ryokan has been in business for 120 years
Shin Kado Ya
In my room I change into a yukata
and the first stop is the large bathing area
Himura-san has been laughing the entire time
[ Himura can't stop laughing ]
ahh its one of these scenes...there's the neck shot
oh? what's this?
finally...finally the undressing scene
oh my
OY
This isn't very Nogizaka like is it
now that's something
Why does there have to be a bath towel?
[ Was waiting for the nude scene ]
They take pride in their bountiful spring water
the charm of having their own private source of spring water
its their own special ryokan hot spring water
Their special water with trace amounts of alkaline
has a reputation for being gentle on the skin
Its true...you can't participate in shoots like this
nerve damage as well as sensitivity to cold
and physical recovery...its effective for all types of ailments
This spacious indoor bath area
soothes all the stress of a busy day
Its like watching an early morning tv show
so hot~
what's this?
What's the deal with these cut in shots?
[ The setup is inexplicable ]
Following a short rest
in my room I receive my traditional meal to fully enjoy the autumn season
Right now I'd like to enjoy
this claypot matsutake mushroom dish
another neck shot
What's going on here?
seriously? The camera stays here?
the perfect chewiness
and the aroma
Show us shots of you eating!
[ matsutake less important than neck shots ]
The ingredients are all local and in season
my food appetite doesn't seem to want to stop
You're just like Okubo-san right now!
[ Taking the comedian approach ]
That's the kind of work Okubo-san takes
With the fresh ingredients
as I enjoy the tastes of the season
next its the pride of the ryokan...the outdoor hot spring
She's going in again?
[ Persistent entering the bath scenes ]
Located on the rooftop
the open air hot spring
You can get a complete view of the town of Atami here
its what you'd call a scenic view
With the sense of freedom and Atami's scenery
without a doubt this will soothe both your body and spirit
yada~
There it is
I'd like to get video of some cheese stuck here...will that be ok?
ah maybe like this
How about if I wring out the bottom of the towel so you can capture the water trickling down
Maybe in this area...get that sweaty look
like put in an uncut scene
Could you film me from behind while I'm eating?
sugoi...all members trying to fake a smile
[ A creation that causes fake smiles ]
Was that not good?
Those shots of how you eat....
ah I had to give out a lot of direction to staff-san for those
[ Added her special touch ]
It was that soggy eggplant scene right
Up to now Nogizaka hasn't been able to show stuff like that so
personally as captain
and with being oneesan age I wanted to create something like that
Shinuchi your thoughts?
Were you thinking that's an accurate oneesan image?
simply embarrassing
[ Even as the oldest..she found it unbearable ]
Watching that you didn't know how to react?
There's a 15 year old next to me...I had to cover her eyes a lot
With 15 year olds sure
there's no reason to be going to baths like that is there
Its too soon...
[ The overprotective BBA ]
I saw Kitano laugh a lot though
Its like her body was so beautiful...that was mega ero
But really
that made my pulse rate go up
It was stimulating then?
That's what I was going for!
That was my goal
That was your goal...hai
Is that so...what's going on then
you trying to become a sexy actress?
no no...that's not right
If so I would have fast forwarded through that
[ The unwanted plot development ]
So it was pretty much get the shot from this angle...get me like this
you had a lot of instructions
The wringing of the towel
the camera happened to be stopped
while they were doing setup
I was hot and squeezed the towel and saw the water dripping and thought
ah! I want them to get a shot of this
[ A Director Akimoto original ]
With Akimoto whenever she says I want to make this type of video
you really seem like you want to do it
I want to do it!
My desire....cannot be contained
sexual desire?
[ bold statement ]
It can't be stopped
That's exactly what it is
Hoshino what did you think of that?
I think the fans will probably be happy
It was a fresh new look
All of you being forced to watch this...must be horrible
[ Seemed like they all wanted to get away ]
Having to sit and watch that
you probably have no idea how to react to that
really?
But the highlight of all this
the biggest one was the neck shots
The neck scenes lasted pretty long
The scenes with me eating
it was crucial there too...more important than the food
enjoying the nape of my neck was the theme of this trip
So while I ate they shot it from the back
One time...while you're eating the Matsutake
you should have put it behind your neck so we could see it
You wouldn't show us what you were eating