DON!
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
We are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And they are Nogizaka-chan
woo hoo
we're gonna....we're gonna get a picture of you~
And what's this?
Since they're taking a picture
So Himura-san
hai
Tell them what's on the show today...onegaishimasu
Nogizaka Video Clip Queen Championships
woo hoo~
This time its some things the members have wanted to do
they self-produced and created some video clips
Their finished products will be judged against each other
And then for the winning member...
This is amazing...the prize for this
the winner gets 1 episode of Nogizaka Under Construction all to themselves
[ Prize is getting to produce an episode ]
That's not something you want to just give out
So the winner of this
can do an episode of whatever they want
[ Whatever you want ]
You'll get full backup support from us
we'll be dragged into whatever you want to do
That's for 1 episode right
The first entry is Ikuta's creation
Anything you want us to pay special attention to here?
special attention...I see
A couple of the members cooperated with me for this
but some of the members didn't notice what was happening
When you watch this video
its sort of like
Some of them will suddenly appear in it or something?
hai
Is this hidden camera stuff? You said they didn't notice
That's correct
eh? Is that Ikuta?
This is Ikuta Erika's....watch me blend into that background!
blend in?
hai
And with that starting now
I am going to blend in with the ceiling
members will come in...and without them noticing
I'll have some challenges setup for myself
The set I'm using...much more than expected
a lot of preparation has gone into it
[ Steel frame ceiling setup ]
This time 10 people from the art and props department
took about 3 hours
in order to setup this fake ceiling setup in the waiting room
The equipment was installed
to allow Ikuta to be suspended in the air by wire
and blend right into the gray ceiling
And then...as part of a fake episode where they record comments
the members will get called in
Did members really not notice all this?
She's blending right into the ceiling behind the members
Then she'll experiment with what she can get away with without being noticed
eh this is scary though...what now...
The first person to record comments for the fake show is Kitano
The first critical point is when they enter the room
so will Ikuta
be able to blend into the ceiling?!
You stay hanging like that?
ah that's right
She's coming in
[ Kitano ]
She didn't notice anything did she
sumimasen
She won't notice at all then until she exits maybe
She has entered the room without noticing Ceiling Ikuta
Ikuta Erika
blend into that background!!
OY Kitano!
[ Just now realizing ]
Kitano doesn't notice anything
she didn't even notice Himura-san at Jingu
And then
as Kitano has a meeting with staff what will the first experiment in the background be?
party glasses
She's going to put them on and fool around to see if she gets caught
[ party girl hanging from the ceiling ]
Its going to be so scary for them when they see her
You'll get noticed like that
Ikuta is blending right in
there's no signs of her being discovered
Next its a mikan
hanging up in the ceiling she'll try eating one
She won't notice that
ah but if she looks slightly in that direction she'll be visible
Why would Ikuta want to do this?!
[ From the earth to the ceiling...I am the chosen one ]
We said you could do whatever you wanted
There's no signs at all of her getting discovered
and that's when Ceiling Ikuta tried this
What's she about to do?
[ Landed 40 cm behind her ]
Amazingly she takes the mikan peel and gives it a toss
but Kitano didn't notice anything
Right here the fake show is finished
Will she notice Ceiling Ikuta as she leaves the room?
That's messed up
Somehow didn't notice her there
[ Completely ignored ]
I was able to blend in completely!
As she was leaving
well somehow
I wasn't sure if I'd be able to fool her
but it seems that people leaving never take a look at the ceiling
But this is all going pretty well
But here an unforeseen accident takes place
onegaishimasu
Turned off the camera
An unbelievable blunder by the staff
the next target Umezawa
walked in while Ikuta was still recording her comments
She suddenly came inside then
onegaishimasu
That's some awkward use of the camera
uwah she didn't notice it
Nice move by technical staff-san right there
[ Retreats calmly ]
The staff panicked however
Umezawa without noticing anything takes a seat
[ Practical joke cameraman ]
The cameraman that essentially has no business being there
now has nowhere to go
and randomly retreats to a corner of the room however
Umezawa doesn't seem to suspect anything about this comment shoot
staff and Ikuta make eye contact and signal to continue the mission
First..it has a plastic wrapper and seaweed which make it super loud
she's going to eat this konbini onigiri
That's going to make some noise
[ crunch crunch crunch crunch ]
what? somehow she didn't notice that one
There's suspicious noises coming from the ceiling
but there's no signs of her getting detected
and then...
What is she doing?
Even with the crunch sounds there's zero indication that she'll get detected
Next Ikuta
her mission will be to open up a folding umbrella
Those make sounds...she'll have to notice something is up
She'll see that in the background
What is she doing?
ahhh still didn't notice
Still doesn't know
She even moved the umbrella around boldly
and still did not get detected
And then to close the umbrella
once again she'll fold it up
She noticed!
She's been discovered!
[ Panics and then pretends she's a ceiling ]
blend in! blend in!
Here Umezawa noticed the sound from the umbrella
this mission is a fail
What are you doing?
ah...I'm blending into the ceiling
The next target is Kubo
Its a nervous moment each time someone walks in however
Does seem like nobody looks up as they walk in
Ikuta has blended in completely and is not detected
And with that Kubo also starts her comments for the fake show
The next challenge for the blended in Ikuta is?
Behind Kubo she'll stretch out a long straw
the mission is to drink the juice 3m below her
She lowers the tube trying to hit the cup
the target is hard to hit
She can't seem to get it in
And then finally...
[ Juice currently ascending upwards ]
ahh grape juice?
ah she's drinking it
The difficult ceiling straw mission
she was not detected and its a success
Right here hanging from the background ceiling
Kubo not knowing that Ikuta is listening
brings up this subject...
Its one sided but I'm often involved
well Ikuta Erika-san
she'll go along with whatever I ask from her
[ Sudden Ikuta information ]
So you like Ikuta?
I respect her
Look at what the person you respect is doing
[ Admires this ceiling person ]
Whatever it may be
with all her power she makes it clear what she wants to do
[ And what she wants....is to hang from a ceiling ]
She made it pretty clear
Ikuta Erika-san
the way she lives her life...that's what I like about her
[ Good opinions of her are skyrocketing ]
That's how she lives her life
Even when busy she never shows anyone she's exhausted...that part of her is so cool
[ This ceiling never gets tired ]
Right here the fake recording is finished
She's exiting
Can Ceiling Ikuta complete this one without getting noticed?
ehhh~
[ What's the next bold move that Ceiling Ikuta will attempt? ]
I wasn't detected was I
I'm so happy
She said those nice things about me all on her own
The next target is 4th member Kanagawa
[ Kanagawa ]
Ikuta has overwhelming confidence as she blends into the ceiling
And Kanagawa suspects nothing as the fake show recording starts
Ceiling Ikuta has become even bolder and this time has a hanging scroll
Is she going to unroll it?
Ikuta watches intently as she calculates the timing to drop the scroll
They're really funny people
I'm really into them
[ Ikuta Erika was here ]
Why does noone notice?!
Bold move
She timed the opening of the scroll to their laughter
and with the perfect timing
its this look of self satisfaction
Ikuta Erika...keep blending into that background!
After she quietly rolls the scroll back up
its on to the final mission
This is a pop up tent that opens itself up in one move
she's going to open it in midair
That'll make a loud noise
She moves to standby while trying to remain undetected
That's going to be loud
Will she be successful?
That was impossible
The tent created a huge sound and this mission is a fail
And then the abruptness of the situation caused Kanagawa to freeze
From these experiments
even if someone is hanging from a ceiling somehow nobody notices
that theory has now been verified
With that said that was pretty funny
Somehow went undetected
Nobody discovered you
Kitano didn't notice anything at all
I didn't notice her doing any of that
I did feel an instant burst of citrus though
She did throw mikan peel right behind you
And then Ikuta is hanging up so close to that door
That was fairly close distance
Its a good thing Kubo said she respected Ikuta
if she had badmouthed her there
that would have been awful
I have a hard time dealing with Ikuta-san
[ Awkward moments waiting at ceiling standby ]
But in the past...I think I've told this story before
when you're talking to management about work
on the table there's always an ashtray and a tissue box
but this time I saw something that looked like a mic
ah! The mic means its a hidden camera practical joke
Speedwagon's Itoda and I think Himura-san were also there
I thought this is getting filmed...I better be funny
But it kept going and there was no kind of reveal
Nobody was saying anything about a practical joke
what's going on right now..then I take a look
it was a screw
[ Manipulated by a screw ]
This black screw was facing my direction
Looked like it was being hidden
That screw had me freaking out the entire time
The next entry is Takayama's creation
And Takayama..
So I really like Zun's Iio-san
I wanted to do a location shoot with Iio-san
I had to find a way like
could I become Iio-san's partner somehow?
That's Yasu-san
[ Currently working as his partner ]
They're both Zun
So did you ask Iio-san?
That's right Iio-san went on location with me
really? This is our 2nd time today watching a video of Iio-san on location
[ Can't believe we're doubling up on Iio-san ]
On Thursdays we get Iio-san on NON STOP!
Think you can invade NON STOP! then?
[ In charge of Thursdays? ]
I've always thought about how I want to shoot on location with Iio-san
Iio-san
sitting next to him
kind of like a business partner
It would be like a dream if that were to come true
And with that how can she get Iio-san to take a liking to her
Regarding Iio the joke setup machine
there won't be the usual wisecracks
we're looking for a new kind of chemistry between them
What happens if she sets up the joke
this experimental location shoot will be carried out
In the end Takayama
Iio's best partner
can she become Zun's Kazu?
Kazumi and Kazuki's
[Kazu Kazu Sanpo]
Going back to the glasses
perfect 45 degree bow...Zun's Iio Kazuki
I now have 1.2 eyesight
[ Sudden boost ]
I was wondering what kind of glasses you'd go with today
But its hard to respond to those jokes
That's true
Today on [Kazu Kazu Sanpo]
Takayama walks around town checking out places she'd like to see with Iio however
The opening segment won't end because
Takayama acts natural and keeps setting him up for jokes
Let's go...you sure about this Kazu Kazu Sanpo?
This opening segment has already gone about 15 minutes
[ No walking on the show about walking ]
You suddenly turned your back to me
I thought everybody was leaving
You don't meet on location to just split up right
ah! This is the place
That was quick!
I guess this spot works
[ The 1st spot required no walking ]
Its this place
The first spot they're visiting
is a Taiwan Cafe where the tapioca drinks are popular
Chun shui tang
Here Takayama
recommends the Tieguanyin milk tea to Iio however
understood...sure then
I'll have the matcha milk tea
How come!
[ Fitting in perfectly ]
Is that ok?
I'll have the Tieguanyin milk tea
but without any tapioca
beep beep beep beep beep
[ Shocking drink order ]
Unbelievably this order was not to setup a joke
it was what Takayama really wanted to drink
Quickly among all the chaos
its time to report on the flavor
Its going to be really delicious
understood...guess I'll have some
Getting to see Iio-san drink some of that tapioca
I'll be happy to see that part
Go to heaven! oishii
I went to heaven just now
In one sip Iio was sent to heaven
what will happen to Takayama?
You called it "go to heaven"
go to heaven
Still going!
[ Taking up a lot of camera time ]
That's really amazing
ah...its nice
nice?!
Is there alcohol in there?
[ Lousy comment ]
So like this one...when you drink
you're feeling relaxed right
How are you supposed to end this segment?
[ simple question ]
This is about Kazu-chan's corner isn't it
That's right
For those I'm not sure
maybe chug the whole drink and leave it empty...
[ The finish the meal strategy ]
Or maybe start rock climbing this wall
you could say "let's go to the next one"
What is this!
This is awful! What is this?
Shitara-kun and Himura-kun are watching in studio?
ah hai...Iio-san
What's your relationship with them?
We're in the same business
[ We know this ]
So then Shitara-kun
when our jokes bomb his main job is to clean up after us
He's part of the cleanup
Next for the two of them
it launched in Denmark as a fun lifestyle goods brand
they'll stop by flying tiger for some shopping
How about these guitars over here?
Aren't these nice?
ah these are nice
Play them together
Its ok! Its ok!
Bananaman will say something to get huge laughs from this
[ dropping bombs ]
There's no way
I can't clean that one up
This will be a tough challenge for them
Guitar suspect A
I'll be suspect B
ah guitar suspect B
[ Immediately catches on ]
Acoustic guitars
those are made of wood
[ worthless information ]
Inside a store with lots of small items
the number of prop jokes get paced up
Cases for glasses...the cases are cute
What is it? Bee? Moth?
Maybe its a fly or something
Its got style
really?
Anybody over 40 might know...
its Silence of the Lambs
Hear of that movie?
Never heard of it right? Look it up!
She's laughing...that'll make you laugh
[ joke meant for the Showa era folks ]
What if I told you to make a joke using this?
eh? This pink one...the pink one
What would I do with this...
ah just put it on top of your head
on my head
For example...maybe like this
Super low budget Lion King
[ Abundant knowledge to use in such emergencies ]
The 2 of them bought several items that caught their interest
after these few words its on to the next spot
This will leave behind some good memories of shopping
and then something else I'd like to leave behind
ninja power
glasses left behind
You left me behind too...
Next..she wants to see Iio move around
the spot Takayama has selected
is a place where you can enjoy all kinds of activities
with all kinds of athletic facilities
TONDEMI
So Bananaman-san
they had a location shoot here before
I watched them and it looked so fun
So we're repeating location spots now?
[ Normally something you'd want to avoid ]
First the 2 of them
will use a trampoline to jump
and land in the jump pit
You want ojisan to go first?
He's really jumping
augh!
ojisan...ojisan is working hard
Laughing hard isn't she
[ Laughing hysterically ]
Before I knew it all I saw was darkness
Much like this at TONDEMI
both Kazuki and Kazumi enjoyed simply having a fun time
How about a janken gag
hai...janken gag?
And then finally
They've built up enough trust to where he'll teach her a janken gag
For the end of this location shoot
how do you wrap this up?
[ So full of questions ]
That stuff is really difficult
I have this hunch that something eventually will come to me
But that's how I ended up with ninja power..glasses left behind
well...so today
left behind some fun memories of Kazu-chan
but what else should we leave behind
That's it! Ninja power
Iio left behind
I'm just an old man left behind
I saw it for the first time...
I've had enough! Camera-san!
yah sugoi
What's truly amazing is I don't remember anything they did
[ As a news information show its a zero ]
That's really bad
Takayama what's the deal?
You wanted to do an Iio-san type of location shoot?
When I watch him he has a comforting type of humor
I was a fan
So then to meet him and make a formal introduction
its something I've wanted to do
Go join Asai Kikaku Talent then!
[ Your prescription is to change talent agencies ]
But the janken gag
what did he teach you?
He gave you a gag didn't he?
Iio-san knows a bunch of janken gags
You got one?
I got one
Could you do it? I'd like to know it
ah well...let's all play janken everyone
saisho wa....fairy tale movies
are mostly fiction
That's supposed to be fairy tale stories!
That's a modern version
all right...today let's all watch a fairy tale movie
sumimasen
Pretty much everyone has their own janken gag
That's actually true
Himura-san has his too
I did this a lot in my former profession
Those times when you janken for something
this is the one he always did
Let's try it then
Everyone wants to play janken right
Say "saisho wa gu" with me
saisho no kiss
is on the 15th spring
[ Back again after almost 20 years ]
That takes me back
So that one...do that for us
[ Next week its more of the video clip queen championships! ]
saisho no kiss is on the 15th spring
I'm feeling kind of embarassed