DON
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
we are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And they are Nogizaka-chan
what's this?
what's going on here?
How do you say December in english?
What she say?
winter
So Himura-san
hai
tell them what's on today's show....onegaishimasu
here it goes
Nogizaka Class-B News Awards 2019
In 2019 all kinds of news became public
Nogizaka46
Among that there's little bits of news you may not know that we'd like to share
Sprinkled in throughout 2019
Nogizaka46 News
First...these items made news worldwide...the Class-A news
In January they held their first live concert in Taiwan
ni hao Taipei
Nogizaka46
held their first concert in Taiwan
They fascinated an audience of about 10,000
Following that class-A type news
its stuff nobody anywhere talked about
Nogizaka class-B news
January...Mukai
Mukai decided it was time to create a lot of class-B news
January...Higuchi
Higuchi removed 4 wisdom teeth all at once and underwent a transformation
January....Shiraishi
Shiraishi got into mahjong
January...Terada
Terada got into green tea highballs
January...Umezawa
Umezawa got into Shiitake horoscopes
That's all...this was Nogizaka class-B news for January 2019
well sure...as far as worldwide news
there's that type of news and
now we've seen what class-B news looks like
Lots of those sounded class-B
I didn't understand the very first one
Mukai decided it was time to create a bunch of class-B news
Is it because of this?
We did this episode last year too right
For that I only had extremely boring stories prepared
So this year I'll have some class-B
news that I'll feel comfortable talking about...started it this year
But we're about to see what you came up with
You've set the bar high for yourself
[ Mukai will have to dig herself out of this one ]
And then the next one was Higuchi
Wisdom teeth removal makes good class-B news
All 4 removed simultaneously is something
eh? all 4 at once?
ah all 4 at the same time
That's amazing...just removing 1 gets pretty bad
I figured it was better to endure the pain just one time
How was your face after that?
I was thinking I'd never make it back to normal
I looked like a monster
[ Higuchi right after wisdom teeth removal ]
Is this some kind of app filter?
This is cute...there's no monsters like this
[ All puffed up ]
eh there was this much swelling?
It hurt so much that I cried through the night
But everything swelled up so evenly
[ symmetrical swelling ]
That's incredibly cute
You went to work like this?
yes I did
4~5 days after I'd go to work
If staff-san called for Higuchi and this showed up....
[ Who are you? ]
People might think I gained some weight
Anyone else here get their wisdom teeth out?
ah you did? Did you swell up?
So I heard about what happened to Higuchi
I was told 3 weeks of swelling with 3 months for a full recovery
that sounded too scary
I asked my dentist to remove 2 of them
uppers?
uppers
For work I thought the swelling would be better if I took out both uppers
but her story scared me so much
I removed them 1 at a time
it came out and stopped bleeding after 1 minute
and I had no swelling at all
[ Some people are just fine after the operation ]
star dentist!
Is that because of a good dentist or just how your teeth grew in?
But my dentist was very good
Nogizaka-chan....we have a hospital we go to
That's good right
When I got scared from hearing Higuchi's story
I asked the members if they knew a good dentist
that's when Shinuchi-san
told me about this dentist I went to
That Shinuchi knows something about everything
[ Hospital master ]
This dentist did such a good job of removing my wisdom teeth
eh you didn't use that dentist?
I did
[ Only Higuchi developed serious issues ]
Well then it really is about how your teeth are positioned
I think it depends on how your teeth grow in
Well my wisdom teeth were very large
So big that they had to be completely cut
I get it...I also had all mine removed by one place
my teeth were like this
In the morning I called up the closest dentist
and the wisdom teeth were removed but the anesthesia wasn't working for me
In the chair I'm practically like "OW"
[ pain and suffering ]
Just felt like they were getting pulled out
After that I had some Bufferin and got drowsy
[ pain medicine causes drowsiness ]
After that well since I was young I didn't have any job or anything
so I slept and woke up to find my pillow covered in blood
[ wakes up in a pool of blood ]
It was a disturbing amount of blood
But it seems some people had their wisdom teeth in a certain position that didn't hurt at all
so for anyone who will need their wisdom teeth removed...it'll hurt but you'll be fine
I got mine removed from the same place
I had to get 3 teeth removed...at once?
hai
But I only had 1 vacation day
but hearing about HinaChima and her swelling they gave me 5 days off
got some extra days
hai
So when they took out the 3 teeth
I didn't swell up at all
I have a picture of it
This is right after my wisdom teeth were removed
eh? soon after
The morning of the next day
ehh?
Are those your teeth you're holding up?
[ teeth are spheres? ]
Those teeth are crazy
eh? That's the following day?
not swollen at all
eh but right here...sorry
because this area is so big nothing looks swollen?
[ Taking advantage of an optical illusion? ]
They're a very good dentist
From now on...lots of you still haven't had the wisdom teeth removed right
Its lots of you right
It hurts like hell
But for some people it doesn't hurt...didn't hurt for you right?
Mine didn't hurt
Matsumura too right
I went out for yakiniku the day they were taken out
[ Goes right for the kalbi post operation ]
next
Shiraishi
you got into mahjong
hai
you play mahjong?
Like around last year or the end of the year before that
staff-san told me that Nakada had recently
started playing mahjong and that I should get into it too
You appear on a tv show right?
Every now and then I make an appearance
From that conversation
"I bet Shiraishi could learn the game really quick!"
I felt halfway forced to learn it
so I downloaded an app for my phone
From there starting this year I'd play it in my spare time between jobs
So is there a mahjong table in the Nogizaka dressing room?
[ Dressing room turned into a mahjong game room ]
Didn't do that?
Haven't done that
But if Shiraishi started playing the mahjong world would get pretty excited
just like they did for Nakada
Nakada helped the game expand
I'm happy about that...its hard finding 4 people to play
so I'd be happy if more people played
But those mahjong jobs....
She'd take those jobs from you!
[ Fighting over the mahjong character ]
You didn't need to say that
She won't take your jobs
After this airs I'm nervous to see what happens
Get more people playing
and make your own show
ah I'd like to do that
Didn't Kitano play?
hai
Was it with the family?
its with the family...we play every Saturday
[ Weekend mahjong player ]
eh? that's amazing
My room was taken over
and now there's a game table in there
I play against my sister brother and father
Since I'm a very lucky player
I don't even have to use calls for discarded tiles
and it'll all line up for me
[ Kitano doesn't need your tiles ]
ah then you only need 1 more for the members to play
[ Waiting for 1 more so the tournament can start ]
need 1 more
But you haven't played mahjong with them yet?
no but we just discussed this yesterday like "Let's go play some mahjong"
[ Formation of the mahjong club? ]
What does let's go play some mahjong mean exactly?
Does that mean you'd go to a mahjong parlor?
really?
Wait...what's it called
you don't play against strangers...you play as a set
ah so you don't barge into some stranger's mahjong game?
[ mahjong parlors also considered Free&Easy? ]
Those old men would take it very seriously
next we have
January...Terada
hai
You got into green tea highballs?
Rather than into it...I'd say I tried it for the first time
First time drinking it was last January
and since then
Miona...Hori Miona and I would go out to eat soba
she'd take me out
we'd drink together
Its like the Nogizaka drinkers...I usually picture Eto
I can't picture Terada drinking green tea highballs
How many do you drink?
Normally I'll have 5
That's a normal amount though
But going out for soba and drinking alcohol sounds so working class
[ Can't help but get soba and a drink ]
So its like oneechan taught me this
Hori drinks there too?
I went with friends to a soba place
and I had a soba tea highball
to go along with eating soba
They're really drinking soba tea highballs
But there's so many cuter drinks out there
I don't drink those
Soba highballs are for people like us
[ ojisan defending his territory ]
Goes totally against your image
But all the 2nd members this year reached adulthood...Watanabe too
we're all 20 now
so with that its like
Junna too....
I bet she drinks
I drink heavily
[ Hard drinking Junna ]
She recognizes
She looks like a drinker
Fits her image...so you drink?
What do you like?
I'm also into green highballs
[ Heavy drinkers call them green highballs ]
You had a green highball phase?
Then I moved on to just highballs
Those are still trendy
Then the highball phase
finished and lately
I've been drinking beer
In the end its beer
But this can be expected for your age
Still doesn't match your image though
I pictured you drinking cute cocktails
Those are too sweet
They are sweet
Sweet drinks ain't real alcohol~
[ The preachy ojisan ]
Are you the strongest drinker?
I'm not weak
Sounds right
Do you often order 3 drinks for yourself at once?
[ rocket start ]
Those people who drink strong right at the start
green tea highballs...I recall you had a nickname for tea
what was it? was it chassu?
its a chassu highball then?
chassu high sounds good
That's right...chassu high
chassu high
She wants green high
She calls it green high
She gradually increases the amount of shochu in it
[ To the top of the ice ]
And next...Umezawa
Ume
This one...isn't the Shiitake horoscope famous
Shiitake horoscope
I think everyone has heard of it
It was recommended to me
and I decided to test out last year's horoscope
So it tells you your lucky months
mine was April June and August
So in April
to about 2 months after
I got offers to do 4 theater plays
In August that was my first senbatsu
it was pretty accurate
so I got further into it
Since it predicted yours
When that happens you believe it more
That's right...there's also a weekly horoscope
I've brought both your horoscopes
I did some research
yabai...are you going to call Himura-san a Shiitake?
[ Diagnosed as a mushroom? ]
Bananaman are both Tauruses so she'll announce their horoscope for this week
Currently there's something red you don't want to get bothered by
I don't know what that means
so what that means
This week all Taurus people will get easily angered
It means you'll be sensitive
you're trying to concentrate so getting bothered would be trouble
you'll be put into delicate mode
This week you should avoid acquaintances and find a safe space
a park bench or a distant cafe would work well for you
So we should go sit on a park bench...
[ dazed and confused on a bench ]
Don't bother me! Don't bother me!
I should do something like that?
That's messed up...since Ume believes in this I should find a park bench and space out
I do believe in it
But there's a cure
ah there's a cure
how to overcome this
You need to laugh every now and then
You mean like a sudden "heh-heh"
heh-heh
[ suspicious character in the park ]
Then say "ahh..I'm gonna laugh"
doing that and laughing will brighten your mood
That's a disturbed individual
ahhh~ I'm gonna laugh
hee hee hee
[ needs drug testing ]
yabai...just from this week nobody will want to hang out with me
[ zero friends ]
But this is for all Tauruses...won't that park get full?
[ Taurus traffic jam ]
Its all Tauruses
ahh~ I'm gonna laugh
HA HA HA HA
[ Everyone talking to themselves ]
Fortune Nakada
didn't you predict good things for Iwamoto?
Like she'd be unstoppable
What happened to that?
She's Under Center
[ emphasizing her achievements ]
But I still haven't really felt all that good fortune yet..
[ Not getting all the good fortune that was promised! ]
But my fortune was really accurate I think
Fortune Nakada-sensei is sure of it
I'm thinking there was no doubt
hai...arigatou gozaimasu
[ play time is over ]
Next for 2019
its February and March class-A news
February...Nishino Nanase
had her graduation concert
In Nogizaka46
she centered 7 times....Nishino's graduation concert
was held in Osaka
Several news tv shows and newspapers covered it
it received worldwide attention
In February and March there were some items nobody knew about
as fara as Nogizaka class-B news
February....Yoda
Yoda's pet goat was castrated
Now that's class-B
February....Kubo
Kubo's older sister won her school beauty pageant
February...Sasaki
Sasaki got her drivers license using a stick shift
March...Mukai
Mukai from Mukai is Mukai
March...Seimiya
Seimiya delivers the commencement speech at her school graduation
That's all...this was the Nogizaka class-B news for February and March 2019
What was Yoda's about?
It seems Gonzo was castrated
so this is your pet goat?
One day I get this picture from my mother
"Guess what this is" she wrote
It looked like internal organs
hold on now...your mother informed you in quiz format?
[ What are these round things? Quiz ]
You mean the part that was castrated
she sent as a picture?
She sent me a picture of that
I answered "Is it some kind of edible organ meat?"
She responds "Gonzo-kun has been castrated"
eh...was that meant as the answer?
When I asked if it was organ meat
She said "wrong answer"
"Aren't they cute"
[ okaasan is into gross humor ]
Wouldn't there be blood all over them?
It was bloody...there was a towel
sitting between them
Like "Guess what this is"
[ crazy mama ]
seriously? okaasan seems totally aggressive
That was funny
next its Kubo
hai
oneechan
well yes...she's currently a college student
the school she attends...they have a beauty pageant
and I knew that she had entered it
She sent me a picture in January
like "I won the grand prix"
grand prix
I have a picture
We don't look alike at all
[ Kubo's sister from when she won the beauty contest ]
ah its true
I wouldn't say you don't look alike
but she's got a beauty look
Kubo is more towards the kawaii look
oneesan is more beauty
Is oneechan interested in joining show business?
I don't believe so
She said to stop her if she ever thinks about doing it
how come?
Doesn't it seem terrible?
Even though you decided to do it?
Its the beauty sisters
Next..this is February
Sasaki
manual
You got your license?
Using a stick shift
Lately everything has been automatics only licenses
The driving instructor-san also told me its rare for a girl to drive stick shift
So how come the stick shift?
There's a character I like in an anime
the character drives a manual transmission sports car
That's the only real reason
Which anime is this?
Its Conan
this character named Furuya Rei
Is this great detective Conan or future boy Conan?
[ wrong Conan ]
Are you planning to drive a car with a stick shift from now on?
My parents own an automatic so
Of course they do
I'll never drive another one...it was just for driving school
How about you buy one?
manual transmission
I think a stick shift car would fit you pretty well
ahhh...well then...eh
I'm not buying one
[ Rejection in top gear ]
We weren't looking for a tease there
This isn't [Ariyoshi Seminar]
I will...not buy it
You have no interest in driving your own manual transmission car?
Since I learned how to drive one
I've acquired the skill so
You're satisfied with that
Don't want to drive one?
eh..automatics are so convenient
[ Graduated from stick shifts ]
You should have just taken the test for automatics then
But you're wasting those skills
So you're not looking to go out and buy the same car as the character you like
They would have it used right
I'm pretty sure
Will you buy it? Will you not buy it?
I will....
not
[ Not in gear ]
And next
here it is...Mukai
Mukai was determined to create some class-B news
Mukai from Mukai is Mukai
can we start off with the picture?
picture
ahhhh~
This was a recording for another tv show
Once I went inside my dressing room
across from me was Mukai-san's dressing room
So I took a picture for class-B news
Panther Mukai
ah that's right
now I get it
Across from Mukai there's another Mukai
That's my class-B news
That is B grade
60 points
[ Score is also B grade ]
After that...there's an after that?
Did you get confused and go in his dressing room?
After that
about a week later
I met Mukai-san on another tv show
so I told him this story
He had a super confused reaction to it
[ Panther Mukai is normal ]
Got a fake smile
Well my name was completely different but
for a certain show I always got
the 2nd floor corner dressing room
In TMC Studios we always get the same dressing room but
one day we were 2 doors down
The usual room
at that time
Chono-san...it was Chono-san
Pro wrestler Chono-san
it was his dressing room
We did what we always do
and barged right in
I made a mistake and charged into his dressing room
Plus you never knock to go in your own room
Doing that I see him sitting on a chair in the tatami area
It was just like that
yes Himura-san also barged into the dressing room just like that
[ screwed up as a combo ]
Chono-san's was right in this area
That's why I thought that was the right room
But he was super nice
I was just about to take off my shoes I was so far in
I barged in...OHHH Chono-san sumimasen
[ Terrifying mistake ]
I got that close to him
That's the real Chono-san
And next we have
the commencement speech
You gave the speech
hai
I brought it today
That's the one you read?
yes..I used this one
Giving out the commencement speech is really something
Student council president?
ah I was student president
Is that so? sugoi
About how long is this speech?
Its really long
So you graduated this year
Hold on now
eh you write in that much detail
You read the whole thing?
Isn't that long?
eh no way
eh so how did the speech go?
While I was reading it from behind me
I could practically hear the crying from the other parents
everyone cried...
They were moved?
from your speech
So how does the speech start off?
The start
I want it to sound like a speech
The speech that reminds her of graduating
representing the graduates...Seimiya Rei
Would you?
Commencement speech
Spring visited us early this year
already the cherry blossom petals are expanding
and even now they've started blooming
With dreams in our hearts we're about to go down the path we've selected for ourselves
it almost feels like a celebration
This is kind of nice
He's already crying
[ obasan moved to tears ]
ojisan...the ojisan
very nice
My favorite part
there's a part that made everyone cry
onegaishimasu
And now...as I calmly reflect back
what brought us to this day
was all the hardships
In troubled times they always watched over us
they were always there to help us...starting with school principal
all the different senseis...friends..and family
Even when we couldn't tell them everything
they would always embrace us with their affection
its because our families watched over us that we felt reassurance and could progress
sorry about this
ojisan over here isn't crying at all
[ Got tired of it? ]
He cried last time but the ojisan is not crying at all anymore
Did you write this yourself?
hai
seriously?
[ Next week is more 2019 class-B news ]
That...that's not class-B
A-grade
A-grade!