Here's what I'm doing given about 1 month of time
Everyone's goals tournament press conference!
I messed that up
Goals tournament?
Continuing on from last week
they all learned a new skill during the summer
and now they're holding a conference to present the results of everything they learned
However if they're unable to clear their challenge...they get a punishment game
So the next one
its Seimiya on the trampoline
We've got a camera out on location where she's at so
Trampoline training center?
huh? Its someone I've never seen before
[ Remember me? ]
Shinuchi...you went out there then?
I have Rei-chan next to me
I'm Seimiya Rei
domo domo
ah...everything is setup behind you then
That's right...the trampolines are sitting right behind us
Nervous?
yes...really since practice
On a scale of 1 to 3 with 3 being normal where would you say you're at?
If 10 was perfectly normal?
3...he said 3 is normal
Out of 1 to 3
I'm a 3
[ Normal ]
Giving Seimiya guidance
part of Japan's Gymnastics Association as the General Manager of Judges in trampoline
Muto-san
First we'll check on the abilities of Seimiya who has previous gymnastics experience
You've done a fair amount of gymnastics haven't you?
Those aren't the moves of someone who tried it briefly
Seeing that sensei made a change to her goals
Rather than just the trampoline basics...if possible
I'd like to teach her some trampoline competition level skills
Sensei saw Seimiya's moves and decided
she wouldn't get the beginners course
Following trampoline competition rules
he's asking her to level up her goals by doing 10 tricks consecutively
Shitara asked for it so here we'll ask sensei if she's ready to do flips
Staff: In 1 month
we were hoping to see somersaults
That is not something I recommend
Staff: How long does it take to learn?
For quick learners
it takes 3 months
There's a lot of risk involved
Of course the somersaults are at a high difficulty level
so to reach her goals
its 2 months of intense practice
Coming up...its the same as the trampoline competitions
she'll perform 10 tricks consecutively
Can she do it without making a mistake?
And then...will she show us some somersaults?
And with that she's going to attempt 10 tricks
since its a trampoline she'll just keep doing a new move on each jump
yes understood
Plus she only gets 1 shot
no mistakes
complete all the tricks and she passes
These are the rules however
you ok with that?
hai
I'm actually feeling brave so
ganbarimasu
ganbare!
She only gets 1 chance and mistakes will not be tolerated
Can Seimiya do the 10 consecutive tricks?
onegaishimasu
uwah...this is making me nervous
She's starting...
oh! Started off with a back somersault....2
She quickly turned it around...#4
Was that 5?
whoa she did a flip
Did she do all of them?
She did it right?
Seimiya has been practicing for this day
Her first trick started off with a back somersault
then she went to the straddle jump
Then back to back she did
a seated landing and another with a half twist
then she regained her form and stood up
And then another seated landing with a half twist
she stood back upright and then a tuck jump
followed by a straddle jump
then she finished off the routine with a back somersault
some of the landings were a little off but
she completed all 10 of her tricks
Seimiya...those somersaults
he said it would be risky to learn those in that little time
but you just did 2 of them
I wanted to get those into the routine no matter what
so at the start and the end
I stuck them in
I'd like to ask sensei about that
sensei...she did that in a short amount of practice time...isn't that something
If she went into a competition
she could practically use that exact same routine
For her to do all that was incredibly impressive
I'm thinking she's ready for competitions
She has natural talent
If you could tell us if she passed or failed...
we're not experts and can't make a proper judgement
when you're ready to determine if its a pass or fail
This time its...
pass
[ 10 consecutive tricks on a trampoline - CLEAR ]
You've cleared your goals....omedetou
So then actually
Rei-chan has additional skills she's learned
She'd like to perform it right here
An additional skill she's learned?
Actually other than trampoline
floor trampoline...floor tumbling
It starts with a roundoff
and goes into a backflip...its a move I've practiced
hai
seriously?
And with that she needs some time to get in standby so
I'll send it back to you for a moment
If so we'd like to see Shinuchi on the trampoline
That's right I'd like to see Shinuchi do it
trampoline!
Do the one where you land on your butt
The one where you sit and stand back up
No that's not it
That's not what we asked for
That's just an old lady sitting down
Its not just the trampoline
Seimiya has also been practicing floor tumbling
will she be successful?
And here is Rei-chan's extra skill
she'll go from a roundoff into a back somersault
Its time!
onegaishimasu
That was scary to watch
What happened just now?
There's the results of hard practice
the back somersault with good elevation was a success
What? That was amazing
I couldn't do it at all during practice
being able to do it
since I practically lost count of all the failed attempts
I was really worried about the performance but
I didn't give in to the nervousness...ganbarimashita!
And Hoshino what are your thoughts?
She was so good that it looked like
I didn't do any practice for mine....
[ The difference in experience ]
She had base experience
Since she was already good to begin with I'm thinking she's very athletic
But that was amazing....wonderful!
omedetou
omedetou! otsukare!
The next to present their results are Endo and Kaki
What they presented
would be a combination of both sleight of hand and illusion
their goal was to put on a successful magic show
Giving these 2 guidance this time
Female Magician Alice
Alice-sensei
All the way from high level stage magic to card magic
she specializes in a wide variety of magic
she's the female illusionist
First its the foundation of magic
they'll practice working with cards
wah~ that's so hard
Kaki is good with her hands
and she manages to clear each of sensei's objectives however
Endo who has never even cut a deck of cards before
That's not how to cut a deck
On the 24th single
as center and as a front member
it was a very active summer for the both of them
During any break time they could find
they did intense magic practice
In the end how much were they able to learn in about 2 months?
A magic show filled with anxiousness
its just about to start
Watching that video now you've got me worried about your hands
That's true
I'm really clumsy so...
it turned into a struggle for me
Being clumsy plus having such a short time to prepare...there's no way
The anxiety filled magic show
in front of the members can they make it a success?
Kaki and...
Sakura's
Miracle Magic Show!
First I Kaki Haruka will start off with some card magic
here it goes
ganbare!
[ Passionate fans ]
These cards have not been altered
I have this deck of cards
There's an ojisan being loud right now
First of all I'll give these a shuffle
this is a midair riffle shuffle
That's a big deal
sugoh
Now then
I'd like 1 person to draw a card for me so
Himura-san
who me?
Would you draw a card for me?
Please pick any card you like
Any of them?
You can pick any card you want
I think I'll go with this area
hai
hai...hai
yes so the both of us won't look and we'll close our eyes
so please show the card to everyone
here goes....right here
yes...I've shown it to them
Now then
I'm going to shuffle these cards
so just tell me when to stop
then please return your card
here goes
STOP
hai
place it right here
please return the card
Now I'll cut the deck
yes...now then
I'd like to guess the card Himura-san drew
Would you picture the color of your card in your mind for me?
yabee
His face got all messed up
[ The side effects of telepathy ]
I've read your mind..I've got it
The card Himura-san drew
it is not a black card
its also not a red card
blue
I picked up the color blue from your mind
Don't be sending her weird messages!
[ Mind flooded with wicked thoughts? ]
I read the color blue...so the blue card
I'll now look for the blue card
There were no blue cards
ah!
Himura-san....there was a blue card
There was? What?
My card was blue?
Please tell us the number and suit of the card you drew
I can say it? hai dozo
5 of clubs
eh?
What? Don't freak me out like that!
[ Worried about Himura's memory ]
It was the 5 of clubs
yes...the card that Himura-san drew
hai
She got it! She got my card
Its a.....miracle!
It wasn't blue before was it?
It was not blue
It turned blue
However the card magic
is still not finished
The card Himura-san drew earlier...the 5 of clubs
I'll place it right here
And then Shitara-san
would you help me?
I'm not a shadow magicians assistant!
I'm going to shuffle the deck
tell me to stop whenever you like
The card that I'll show you
please remember it
here goes
STOP
yes...now then
please remember this card
got it
I'll return the card
Would you shuffle the deck?
You want me to shuffle then?
You sure?
Cut the deck
eh? You're letting him do it
wah sugoi
High rollers do this all the time
He really shuffled that deck though
arigatou gozaimasu
Now I'd like to guess the card Shitara-san drew
would you picture the color of your card in your head?
ah...I've read your mind
The card that Shitara-san drew
it was not a red card
it was also not a black card
blue...blue!
I had red in my mind the entire time
I picked up blue from reading your mind so I'll now find the blue card
no way...no way!
He just shuffled all those cards
There are no blue cards...no blue
what? no blue cards
the blue card from earlier...
That's the only blue card here
The card Himura-san drew earlier...the 5 of clubs
wouldn't it be something if it was now the card Shitara-san drew
sugoi
There's no way
The suit and number of your card?
King of diamonds
If you'd flip the card over for us
No way...that's the 5 of clubs
That's the 5 of clubs
here goes
sugee
Its a....miracle!
When did it get changed?
So far these 2 have been pretty good
next up it'll be Endo performing her illusion magic
Starting now this will be chopping a body into pieces magic
I'd like to cut Kaki up into a bunch of pieces
I call this "The dismembering of Kaki"
YAAY~
[ Cruel naming ]
grotesque sounding title
Kaki please go inside
going in
You're going to be dismembered
you ok?
I'll close the box now
eh...this is really something right here
yes...starting now
I'd like to insert these iron plates
yes....starting from the top
here goes
You're going to cut up Kaki
you ok?
ah it went in
Kaki just pushed it back out
you ok over there?
one more plate
I'll insert this into the bottom
Could we put a stop to this
At that short distance...I don't know
What's happening?
went right in
The plates are in
And now Kaki's body has been cut up into pieces so
I'll pull this out
I will scatter her body even more
here goes
Kaki!
eh? how?
Kaki has been dismembered
She's all scattered
Her feet are sticking out
What's going on here?
eh? what is this?
I feel bad for Kaki so I'm going to hurry up and close this
hai....3...2...1
Now I'll remove these
eh? how come?
Is Kaki back to normal?
open
uwah~ she's ok
Its a....miracle!
That kind of amazed me...I'm stunned
That was you in the box then? That was me
For the illusion magic it was Kaki
that's right
Since I can't do the card magic
The card magic was really good
I read your mind and it was blue
so I made the card blue
well there you go
ah sensei...sense will give out their grade
card magic techniques...in that short an amount of time
must be really difficult
That's right. Kaki-chan put in a lot of practice time
At first the card color was white
she was able to darken it
yes because of all her practice
So then sensei
you're holding the pass or fail sign
please hold it up for us
onegaishimasu
Pass!
[ Putting on a 2 person magic show - CLEAR ]
The next to present her results
Umezawa Minami
Her presentation was on
giving a VR art performance live in studio
First to get Umezawa accustomed to VR
she'll experience some of the VR world
sugoi!
This 360 degrees of space will be your canvas so
Now that she's experienced what its like
right away she'll start practicing
wah!
In the virtual space...first she'll get a feel for using her virtual brushes
However in VR art
its not just about drawing a picture in VR
Giving guidance for this one...Sekiguchi-sensei
its rare to find worldwide
her specialty is in live performances of VR art
And with that the details of her challenge
Umezawa picked the song
[Influencer] and she'll time her art to the song
Her goal is to finish her drawing
while doing a live performance
Its not just the accuracy of the painting
this challenge will also require some speed
In the end will Umezawa
make her performance of the very difficult VR art a success?
What's this?
You're not just simply drawing
along with [Influencer]
That's correct
Its about a 4 minute song so you have to finish in that time
So this is presented as a performance?
Its been packaged together as a live performance
You're doing it but how do you think it'll go?
All the girls I've seen so far have been really amazing
I'd like to ride their momentum and give it my best shot
She'll have a time limit of around 4 minutes
what will Umezawa draw in her virtual space?
eh what's this?
What is that?
horse..its a horse
horse? Doesn't it look like a horse?
ah it does resemble a horse
eh what's going on right now
How's she doing this?
You can look over there and see Umezawa drawing it
Here come the legs
looks like a horse
like a horse
ah she's changing colors
ah...brush change too?
That's a real horse
Its the mane
ohhh...the tail
She's changing the background
Looks like outer space
She made it white...its a white horse
eh sugee...how come
green
Its like a dream world
what's this?
ahhh its pegasus
uwah~ sugee~
sugoi~
It lets you do all this
uwah~ adding wings
what is this?
this is really something
what now
looks like clouds
Its an aurora!
Its pegasus flying through an aurora
uwah~ I'm in it!
The other side of the moon...how long were we there?
ah she's putting you there
sugee~  I'm riding the horse
I'm riding it
You're running out of time! Hurry!
hurry
watch out!
This is amazing
what is all this? sugee
Umezawa!
hai~
How was it?
I was so nervous...my hands are shaking
Did you finish everything?
I finished it!
you finished?
Those pictures of us were drawn earlier weren't they?
That's perfectly fine
[ mean spirited fault finding ]
I did properly draw it!
Those?
You did?
sugee...didn't you find her art style mesmerizing
[ incredible finishing touches ]
sensei
this sensei is amazing
[ Sekiguchi Aimi-sensei ]
Umezawa-san...sugoi
she was incredible
She really was
So I've taught this in like 10 different countries
but among them all she was probably the fastest to pick it up
[ setting a world standard ]
Do you have to be a good artist to get started?
That actually makes no difference
Nobody here has really drawn in a virtual 3d space before right
So the people that have spent their lives drawing on flat paper
when they try it they're like "What do I do here?"
and some are unable to do it and also
how she operated the interface...she never lost her way
I'm thinking she spent a lot of time practicing at home
You can practice this at home?
There's a simpler version of this setup she took home with her
If sensei calls this a fail that would be pretty funny
[ Extreme hardcore coaching ]
So then sensei
onegaishimasu
Well of course
[ Live studio performance of VR art - CLEAR ]
Umezawa achieved her goal...omedetou