Nogizaka class-B news awards 2019
In 2019 all kinds of different news went public
Nogizaka46
Among that some smaller news items among the members also happened
Spinkled throughout 2019
Nogizaka46 news
First its things that made news worldwide
the class-A news
April...Ikuta Erika
Ikuta won the Kikuta Kazuo Theatre Award
Nogizaka46 Ikuta Erika
she was recognized for her excellence in theater
the 44th annual
presentation of the Kikuta Kazuo Award
together with a group of distinguished actors
she was awarded the Theatre Award
June...Hori Miona
the Shanghai International Film Festival...the award for Best Actress
Nogizaka46 Hori Miona
in her starring role for [Hot Gimmick]
in the Asia Newcomer Category
she took the award for Best Actress
In June...for the first half of the year
they took 1st place in artist total sales
1st?
For the 1st half of the year according to Oricon
for artist total sales
when including all music software
they totaled 4.42 billion yen
Nogizaka46
for 2 years in a row they took 1st place in total sales
Following that class-A news
the things nobody talked about
here is the Nogizaka class-B news
April...Iwamoto
Iwamoto became a high school student
April...Akimoto
Akimoto's credit card has some random charges on it
May...Ozono
Ozono sees another cat staring at her
June...Ito Junna
Ito becomes watermelon peel
June...Tamura
Tamura's father goes hardcore into crane games
June....Wada
Wada fails the level 4 english proficiency exam
That's all...in 2019
this was the April to June class-B news
next
this was Iwamoto
ah you became a high school student
You entered high school
I started high school
You joined as a 2nd year middle schooler
1st year...I was 12
Well? Feel different?
Have you become an adult?
ah I cut my hair
[ subtle change ]
So do you still have to tell someone if you're doing a hairstyle change?
Probably if its a major change
Need to ask to see if you'll get permission
What if someone wanted to go with a shaved head....
[ Shocking image change ]
Like Takayama's new hairstyle
ah...how is it different...
Your hair is totally like it has some green to it
there's some silver in there
ah!
Don't say "ah" to that
Its not like that
[ randomly playing dumb ]
It looks different now
It has some ashy color
So actually....
actually? Does that mean you have a reason?
nope
during summer vacation
for the first time
I got my hair bleached one time
it was a secret
So right now...over the bleached hair
I've dyed it black a couple times
So my hair color has changed a little
It was only for summer break?
That's correct
You wanted to do it right
I've always wanted to do it
But this year when I cut my hair short
obviously I was nervous about NogiChuu
I worried if Shitara-san and Himura-san would notice
so for you to notice the small change to my hair makes me incredibly happy
That's not a small change...that's noticeable
Its enough to make you think about how it'll effect work
You think its that different?
eh? If that's so people will get mad at me....
A lot of time has already passed since the change
eh!?
Its looked different for a long time now
seriously?
Why do you keep yelling out "eh"
[ What's so shocking? ]
You've looked like this for like 3 months now
But for the 4th members have you thought about a hairstyle change but worried about what would happen
Like cutting my bangs
I had to tell someone first but
the day before yesterday
I had level bangs that I didn't like so I wanted to thin it out
since I cut the bangs with kitchen scissors
[ kitchen hairstyling ]
cut them yourself?
You used kitchen scissors?
The moment I cut them my bangs stuck up
There's a lot of girls that its almost a life or death situation if their bangs aren't sitting just right
[ The bangs are their life ]
Looks totally cute
I was really embarrassed knowing that a tv recording was coming
Miria-chan you had green hair at one point didn't you?
Its not because I wanted green hair
It was green then
I wanted ash gray
But it looked green
looked like you admired Shrek...
[ Once again its Shrek ]
Say "I ain't Shrek"
I ain't Shrek!
We've had this conversation before
But since you said that..at the handshakes
even with this normal hair color
people would call me Shrek
That happened?
[ Shrek nickname stuck ]
sorry I did that to you
Please use Shrek in a good way everyone
[ onegaishimasu ]
There's no using Shrek in a good way
hair color...Hoshino's hair turned brown
I was always told I couldn't change it
Hoshino ever since her rebellious phase its been like this
nope...because I was rebelling I told nobody
and dyed it
somehow someone told me it looked nice
I thought "I told you so...its a good thing I tried it"
[ Good girls don't copy what she did ]
And then
isn't this one crazy
Akimoto
hai
What happened to your credit card?
Suddenly my phone rang while I was out
it was an unknown number and I'm like "what's going on"
This ALOHA?
[ Call from Hawaii? ]
This means phone
The credit card that you've been using
we believe there's been some unauthorized charges
please confirm these purchases
The credit card company? It was my credit card company
When I heard the charges I panicked
on such and such a date
"Did you make a 200 yen purchase to buy in game items?
I don't play games that much and don't pay for in game items
I said "I don't think I bought that"
3 days later there was a 500 yen charge for an in game item
no...I didn't buy that
There were several charges on my card for in game purchases
I thought that sounded strange
I said I didn't make any of those purchases
ah this is probably credit card fraud
also "Did you win an auction for some Nakamori Akina-san goods?"
"Yes I purchased that one"
[ Akina fan? ]
I definitely did not place any bids
You didn't?
eh kowah
I have no memory of doing that...this is really strange I thought
I said probably none of those charges were from me
Well we think these are all fraudulent charges so we'll refund you
The total amount was 120,000 yen
ehhh
Your card info was used a lot
There were also charges for overseas airline tickets
How did you get into this mess?
I do a lot of overseas internet shopping
I probably went to a fake site
and they stole my credit card information
That lets them buy stuff with your card?
Seems so
Those small charges for in game purchases are something you won't notice
Like if I were in your situation
It seems like they were able to stop those charges in advance for me
then they disabled my credit card
and sent me a new credit card...it was a lot of hassle
In my mind it was a minor incident
That's an incident
yes its an incident...that's...
eh incident
[ copyright Abe reporter ]
next...there it is
Ozono
There's a cat staring at you
Didn't this happen last year?
[ 2 years in a row ]
Last year too...I was walking down this road
I felt something staring at me
I looked and saw it was a cat on the window of a house...
like this?
That's right
Much like an old man peeking at you
So you can sense that?
Yes I can...you don't often sense something staring at your from above right
but still I was able to sense this one
I always look up and see a cat
eh? so this year too
I have a picture
[ Cats that stare at Ozono...2019 version ]
But if its a cat...that's normal
Staring at you again
Giving you a mega mega stare down
What? So this only happens once a year?
That's right...last year it only happened once
This year too its only been that one time
Once a year you get a death stare from a cat
[ Cat day ]
Its a different cat each year then?
always a different one
Just stares right? Doesn't come near you right?
ah but still
I was about to take a picture and moved closer
but the cat moved towards me
It kept its eyes on me
That made it easy to get a picture
That's pure class-B news
[ Definitely B grade ]
On to the next one
Ito Junna
what's this? you are now watermelon peel
So Suika
there's that Suika unit right
Suika had 5 members
I've noticed I'm the last one
[ Realized she's been left all alone ]
Last December Kawago graduated
since then its been hectic
Nana...Yuuri...Karin
You're right
I realized its just me now
That's why you're the watermelon peel
You were the peel?
[ In charge of the peel ]
not the watermelon seed?
[ Junna does the Suika pose alone ]
Up to now all of us would get together and drink
I realized I'm alone
You realized you were drinking by yourself
huh?!
[ The woman left behind ]
The others are still there
is Tulip still doing ok?
ah Tulip is fine...we have 4 members
Myself...Maaya...Iku-chan...Himura-san
So I'm still in the unit
[ Himura, an active member ]
That's funny to suddenly hear Himura-san
I occasionally hear that I'm in this unit
And next for the month of June
Tamura
Your father got hardcore into crane games
What's that about?
Its like in my family
when our days off line up we'll often go out together
Since then we've lost some of the places we usually go to
but the final destination would be the crane games
My father got so into them
he won 2 Switch systems
What's a Switch?
the game console
eh? He's that good at crane games?
He's also won tickets for Disney twice
They don't just have plushies these days
How much a play?
100 yen
ehhh
And he wins stuff?
He wins
Those special prizes are setup to be impossible to grab
yes those are difficult
He grabs a key
and drops it and then uses the key to open the prize box
He plays those cranes
So its a crane game where you only grab a key
You have a picture?
hai
Isn't this crazy?
Who? Who? Who is this?
This is your father?
otousan?
eh so this is otousan
That's my father
Your father is super young
He's all funky
Funky?
Don't want to get close to him when he's playing
Look at that stance
That right hand is incredible
How old is your father?
Like 45
or something
I believe he's around that age
So young
I'm 46...he's 58
[ The age gap comedy duo ]
That makes me senpai
But lately he's been winning too much
so they've increased the difficulty level
[ Counter measures for the Tamura family ]
Like "oh no here he comes"
The sweatpants are coming...The sweatpants are coming
[ Beware of this man ]
The store made it harder?
That's why we haven't been going there
What's the deal with his stance?
That's probably when he just misses
[ Tamura's father feeling the sting of a loss? ]
Now then...also in June we have Wada
This is messed up Wada
It's pretty bad
Isn't the level 4 english proficiency test taken by middle school kids?
Its the level for up to 2nd year middle school students
The test site
only had kids there
[ Meant for kids ]
You went to take that test?
Since I'm doing a learning english tv show
It was for the show
I have to get level 2 proficiency
That's the goal
yes...I took the level 4 test but failed it
I thought there would be a clock there
I thought there'd be a clock at the test site
but there was no clock
plus I forgot to wear a watch
I didn't know how much time I had left
I was still answering problems at the start of the test when they said time up
You took that much time?
I could not answer the questions at all...it was hard
Haven't you been doing this show for awhile now?
yes its my 5th year
[ The results of 5 years of studying ]
Is it all fails?
ah but when I took the test in October....
wait...you said October weird
juugatsu
juugatsu?
[ There's no way it sounds like that ]
finally...ah juugatsu
juugatsu
I don't get it
inoshishi
Why did you say inoshishi just now?
[ Sudden inoshishi ]
juugatsu
In October
you took it?
yes I took level 4 and level 3
I finally passed level 4
ah you failed level 3?
ah level 3 didn't go well...
got a little greedy there
The other day when we all went to Shanghai
at airport customs
they spoke to us in english
at immigration
But since she likely didn't even know right or left
she was the only person they took for questioning
[ Take the baka for questioning ]
They took her away
So why did they do a check on you?
why? Its like
Because the members are there you could say you were with them
no...well
right before the fingerprint scanning
I burned up my RE and MI fingers
wait...excuse me a second
[ confusion in the audience ]
That's not how I usually name my fingers
RE and MI?
RE and MI
Its DO-RE-MI-FA-SO
Nobody is going to understand you
So you remember them by DO and RE and MI
That's how you remember?
So its your RE and MI fingers
I burned my RE and MI fingers such that it messed up the fingerprint
You burned them?
So the fingerprint reader couldn't pick them up
I heard a lot of english about that part
But I couldn't understand
Like "Why can't we read your fingerprints?"
You probably talked about RE and MI and they thought "This girl is crazy"
[ Take her in for a drug test ]
What happened with the fingerprints?
They couldn't use the fingerprints but the picture of my face matched
so they let me pass
That's really really interesting
Now I want to know how you burned yourself
Were you pressing down on something that would burn you
There was this fish grilling machine
I went to press the lid closed
the door was really hot
and I sizzled myself
That broiler under the gas range?
hai
That's where you burned yourself?
Like here's the handle and then here's the glass part
So I didn't use the handle and just used my RE and MI fingers to shut it
[ Uses RE and MI for pushing ]
Normal people would yell "HOT" and take the hand right off
That way they don't burn themselves so much that it removes their fingerprints
Are you like "HOT~" while still pressing
[ Too much faith in RE and MI ]
Somehow my reaction to it was delayed
RE and MI
This was not talked about anywhere
August 2019 class-B news is...
August....Seimiya
Seimiya scored a 46 on her midterm exam
August....Mukai
Mukai buys a new glove
August....Shiraishi
Shiraishi's birthday cake incident
First its Seimiya
So on a test
In Math part A
I scored a 46
You have a picture
46 points
100 is max right
hai
What's this about?
I'm not good at math
But since I scored over 30
I passed...or at least there's no makeup exam
ahh no makeup exam
But why? Because 46?
That's right!
[ That's the sole reason ]
ah that's why you liked it
I took a memorial picture
But this looks bad for your future math tests
Someone please teach me...
Anyone here good at math?
ahhh Ozono says she can do math
I'm not too smart but
I do really well in math
In other subjects I'll get like 20s and 30s but
just for the math part I'll score a 94
[ science and computing Ozono ]
She can teach you..will you let her tutor you?
hai
Teach her
I don't want to
You don't?
[ Has a hard time teaching ]
Just teach her a little
hai
Amazing that she gets 20s in other subjects
And next? Mukai
hai
What's this about?
well in elementary school I played softball
since then my glove got pretty worn out
So I bought a new glove
That's good class-B news
You hear this from boys mostly
Seems like its rare to hear this from a girl
I also like going out and watching baseball games
For watching games you bring the glove to try and catch a foul ball right
[ That is not common knowledge ]
I get it...so you bring the glove to baseball games
That's right
ah you brought it?
This is the new glove I bought
I still haven't broken it in yet
Would you hold it up and show us?
hai hai hai...she's a southpaw
left handed then
Its cute so I bought it
You take the glove to the baseball stadium?
I bring it
You watch the game with the glove on?
Watch with the glove on
Ever caught one?
I haven't...I noticed the foul balls fly to places I don't want to sit
And also
I have noone to play with
Nobody to play catch with
ah catch
So there's nobody to play catch with
on the weekdays at the park
if I go around 3 or 4 there's usually elementary school kids
so I'll play catch with them
You play with children?
children you don't know?
I target children I don't know...
[ That statement could lead to a misunderstanding ]
kowai kowai
I go after elementary school kids going home from school
to start a game of catch
eh?
Here Mukai and Bananaman will recreate
how she gets kids to play catch with her
So pretend we're kids playing catch
YAAY!
You just barge in?!
[ Sudden infiltration ]
kowah
really?
But they will catch it for me
obviously they'd catch it...
I'd dash straight home if that happened
What do they say? "oneechan what's this?"
Let's play together!
I don't want to...wait why
we're already playing
toss it here
[ forced start ]
really?
They'll be like "There's a weird oneechan here today"
[ Go tell mama ]
But the place they usually play catch
it never changes so
They remember me
like "ah you're back"
like "its that old lady"
[ Being insulted ]
You've turned into the town's crazy old lady
That old lady is back
Like the old lady with the glove is back
Is this really happening?
That's right
That old lady is here!
[ The heart is strong ]
You're fine with "here comes that old lady"
What position did you play for softball?
I was on the bench
[ Left out of the game ]
That's why you want to play so badly
What are you future plans for the glove?
maybe some sandlot baseball
I'd like to do that
Are there any womens sandlot baseball teams?
We had pinch hitters and called strikeouts
its like
since I've now worked to remember all the rules
I want to play the game
What do you mean you remember all the rules
You know all the baseball rules
really? So you're thinking of joining a game with those kids?
Get a picture with your phone
ah you mean me?
[ She's been assigned a follow up report ]
That'll work
Thank you. This time together was enjoyable
[ She's a good kid ]
she's very polite
Shiraishi
hai
The birthday cake incident
So Manatsu and I
share the same birthday
so we celebrate together every year
They'll bring out 2 birthday cakes
So all the way up to last year
they'd bring me a bigger cake
cake size?
yes the size
The cakes are different sizes?
I'm a year older than her
I think that's why my cake is bigger
It could be the difference in rank
[ Accepts the difference in rank ]
You'd understand why her cake is bigger
It was like that but this year
when they brought out the cakes
put together my cake looked a little smaller
what's this? just like that?
that's why
I'm like "eh?"
[ Can't believe this could happen ]
You have pictures
[ This years cakes ]
This is from this year?
They look about the same but
Once you take a real close look....
Manatsu-san's cake is sort of...
You have last years pictures?
I also have the pictures from last year
Its true
Last year Shiraishi's cake was bigger
You can tell just from looking
[ The 2014 birthday cakes ]
So this is unforgivable
Well its something I haven't accepted...
[ On the verge of Kuroishi-san ]
But for Akimoto you've finally gotten to the same size cake
yes for me my cake has always been smaller
it really bothered me
obviously when they bring out both cakes like that
mine is clearly smaller but
when you have a small and big cake next to each other
you have to look at the plate
Both of us look right for the plates to see whose cake it is
Doing that...the big cake always says Maiyan
the smaller cake will say Manatsu
I thought it would be the same this year
but when they brought out the cakes
they looked about the same size
They look close
things were starting to look good
I looked and thought "eh?"
My cake is bigger
You saw you had the bigger cake
I thought "All my hard work has finally paid off"
[ The peak of Nogizaka46 ]
Like I had finally surpassed everything I said I'd do
I was so happy
This year was a very happy year
So Shiraishi had an unhappy year
Also something else that annoyed me
sometimes we'll get the same cake and they'll make a large cake
That sounds good
And that's totally fine...but every time
it says Maiyan and Manatsu...Maiyan always comes first
[ Detailed complaint ]
But here Maiyan comes first
[ Because of her rank ]
I think you understand
But I wanted to surpass her
The pissed off Akimoto is much more powerful
[ years of accumulated bitterness ]
Its been a good year for me
That's interesting...can't wait to see next year
What will happen to next years cakes?
I wonder what the person in charge of cakes will do
[ Torturing the staff ]