Again tonight
the goal was to learn a new skill during the summer
and now they're going to present the results of all their practice
And next its Sakaguchi's frisbee dog
We've got a camera on location
eh frisbee dog training center?
hai~
Himura-san...Shitara-san....everyone in Nogizaka46
konnichiwa
domo domo...sorry to keep you waiting
eh Sakaguchi-san how are you feeling?
Sakaguchi-san is feeling nervous
You're nervous then
Well its raining here
Is it a downpour?
[ Curious to know if its a downpour ]
It is not a downpour
So its raining pretty hard
will that make it more difficult for you?
With the wind and rain....the wind will really affect the frisbee
The wind is really strong
Well Sakaguchi herself said she wanted to acquire a bunch of new skills
hai
I really regret saying that
[ That was a reckless comment ]
But that's what you said
Taking care of Sakaguchi this time
He's won many awards in frisbee catching dog competitions
Dog trainer Nishida-san
And then this time
paired up with Sakaguchi for practice its....
oh wow~
Its Border Collies Beck and Uno
uwah~
wait...
sugoi
Completely different from my dog...
yes
Sakaguchi's pet
is a mini Dachshund named Tiffany-chan
Sakaguchi seems a bit intimidated by Beck's intensity but
the most important part of making her show a success
is a relationship of mutual trust
The dog fetches it for her
To give a performance where they're both in sync
within their limited amount of practice time
she must concentrate on bonding with Beck
Furthermore she's at step 1 as far as throwing the frisbee
Once she tries to throw one...
[ Direct assault on the staff! ]
This part was unexpected...ehhh~
To get to where she can throw it straight
for some people it takes several years to learn...its a fierce struggle
Even with self-practice
she cannot get it to fly straight
Even for the Nationwide Tour she brought along frisbees
and she continued the self-practice but
Sakaguchi has got herself into big trouble
will she be able to put on a performance with Beck?
Sakaguchi!
Your frisbee throws don't go straight
That's correct...no matter how many times I throw it....it'll go off in the wrong direction
You're not so good at frisbee
I'm not so sure about that...
[ Not going to accept it ]
I'm pretty certain
How's your compatibility with Beck?
Its looking good!
really?
We've become real close
How's the wind right now?
While we watched that video
the rain got even stronger
So is it a downpour?
[ Has to know if its a downpour ]
It is not a downpour
But you'll still be in bad shape
This time Sakaguchi
along with a 90 second song
it'll be a beautiful performance with girl and dog
a type of competition called the free flight
her goal is for the dog to make 8 catches of the frisbee
During the show...to be successful she needs 8 or more catches
with those rules she only gets one shot at it
Are you fine with these rules?
Its fine...
Its fine? Why are you talking like that?
[ Your majesty enters ]
Beck!
She only gets 1 shot at this dog show
can she get the dog to make 8 or more catches?
onegaishimasu
ganbare!
ganbare
beg
stay
come through
through
spin
stay...over
through
spin
stand....hand
catch
Beck
That's one
catch
Beck
over
catch
[ Incomplete pass ]
come come come
[ Beck is on the loose ]
Beck!
[ Completely out of control ]
Beck! Come on
Beck! Beck!
Beck!
through!
through
circle
catch
Beck
through
Beck stay
stay
Beck up!
What's going on? Is it over? Sakaguchi
Are you done Sakaguchi?
Its finished
How was it?
It was incredible but your goal
that's a fail
[ Did not make 8 catches ]
Did you count along?
well Beck-kun seemed nervous
so there were 5 catches...got really close
yes so 8 catches
Please give me another chance....
Shitara-san could we give her 1 more shot?
No we won't
[ She only had 1 shot at it ]
How come?
Sakaguchi...hurts doesn't it?
no really....that was so different from practice...
We totally get that
yes...but that's still no good
eh Shitara-san!
hai hai
For real...she worked hard for an entire 2 months
I know this but sorry....that's no good
[ Adheres strictly to the rules ]
Those are the rules
Want another shot don't you?
Let's do 1 more!
That's not happening
[ Not going to let her do it ]
Why not?
Unfortunately Sakaguchi could not accomplish her goals so its a punishment game
Since she's on location her punishment will happen on site
yes and with that
eh right here we have....liquid Propolis
[ Special version of Ikuta's Propolis ]
So the one Ikuta brought to the studio
we've made an even stronger version
Sakaguchi
but its supposed to be great for your throat
ah it smells!
why does it smell?
Sakaguchi please drink up
Its gross!
[ Propolis as an insult to injury ]
Sakaguchi...is it gross?
augh~ its so gross
Its supposed to be good for your throat
Next we have Kitagawa
woo hoo!
woooo~
Previously Kitagawa presented her flipbook manga on the show
Combining elements with flipbook manga
she'll take on pop-up manga
And with that this time
she'll become the pupil of Honda-sensei
First of all to learn the basics of pop-up manga
she'll give a simple picture some movement
using a tracing table
the essentials of flipbook manga
she attempts to draw something frame by frame
With Kitagawa-san's finger...try to make the picture move
ah~
Once you tap it...you'll make the sphere move
then that sphere
will go in the opposite direction
give that a try
yes lke that
well right now its not going to move
[ Please draw that part ]
Now that Kitagawa World has been unleashed
on the tablet she draws it out frame by frame and takes pictures
And then right here
she's about to take a picture of her own finger however
Is it ok to do this with my finger in a band-aid?
Its ok
I'm unable to get used to writing with mechanical pencils...
That's from a mechanical pencil!?
Are those blisters?
You know those mechanical pencils that are easier to grip
with those I'll fall asleep
so I bought mechanical pencils that have a rough grip
mechanical pencils with a rough grip?
ah...maybe your fingertips are sensitive
[ Can follow any conversation ]
That's a great sensei
He listens to everything
The part that flies out is also drawn on the tablet
once they're connected...
Even the hard to handle mechanical pencils...you'd still fall asleep
ohh~
ahh
Kitagawa trying pop-up manga for the first time
what is the original story that she came up with?
I'd like to do a heartwarming story
one that will make people cry
and then...
These cicadas are incredible
It is summer time...
In the end what will Kitagawa's heartwarming pop-up manga look like?
Kitagawa
But for this one...its really going to take up a lot of time
plus you're trying to create an emotional story
It might make you cry....
really
For us even on [Unbelievable] nothing makes us cry
[ Powerful enemy ]
I saw you light a match in that video
Did you burn everything down?
For the first time in life
I struck a match
You've never lit a match?
Never and that's why sensei looked like he'd get burnt
[ Each part sounds crazy ]
But still for Kitagawa
this isn't much of a pass or fail situation for you
It would have to come out incredibly bad for you to fail
If there's crying
You sure you want to make it that hard for yourself?
It made me cry
Let's try that then
really?
If anyone here cries you'll get the ok
But if nobody cries it'll be a fail
Maybe it'll be Himura-san that ends up sobbing
Now then here is Kitagawa's
original pop-up manga so please watch along
My friend.
Its summer vacation and yet there's nothing on my schedule
ah they have stuff like this
she crying?
ah its her tears
what?
sugee
You're a round one aren't you
Let's be friends from now on
wah~
its a watermelon
ok then
ah!
sorry...I hit the wrong one
Drew a nice picture
Its name is Maru then
Today we're going bug catching
What's that?
Its Himura-san and Shitara-san
konnichiwa
They were both so pretty
Don't we look creepy there?
ah! There's a festival
Maru...let's go together
its the 31st
Well? Anything here that you want?
You want a mask?
hmmm~ but you're round
wah~ What pretty balloons
ah!
Maru....so you wanted to be one of those balloons
The fireworks are starting...lets watch
Maru...
these are called fireworks
They're pretty so watch carefully
This was a fun summer vacation
[ Yuri-chan...see you next time ]
see you next time...is it over?
sugoi
Who cried?
Anyone in the back? No crying?
Your creation was very nice but
nobody here cried
And that means...eh
you fail
[ Make someone cry with your original pop-up manga - NOT CLEAR ]
It was very nice...enjoyable
It disappeared at the end
Disappeared at the end
It wanted to become a balloon
it wanted to be perfectly round like the balloons
So Maru was kind of an oval shape
no...it was always cute but
it wanted to be perfect
Maru did....gomen gomen
It was not an oval then
OY! Somebody please help me out here!
[ A girl that makes you give up ]
And with that sensei called her manga a pass but
Kitagawa will still be doing a punishment game later
The next to present her results
Saito Asuka
Saito Asuka was going to attempt
the mask change
In studio
using a mask she did the routine where she actually didn't change masks much
[ No change ]
That happens in the authentic version
Once she tried to impersonate the art form by watching the video
She really did some of it...Asuka-chan was good
[ The Mask Change ]
The mask change is all about...
its got over 300 years of history behind it
a traditional chinese performance art
It's considered state top secret
and is passed down from generation to generation while protecting its secrets
Teaching the art of the mask change this time is
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
My name is Cho
I'm Chinese
yes..we do not have permission to get Cho-sensei on camera
Sensei has been a part of passing this mask change art form down each generation
and this time she'll be teaching it for us
This time her costume will be fully custom made
however you'll have to wait until her performance to see it
Staff: Your thoughts after putting it on?
eh this is really incredible
I'm starting to get a little excited
And then right away its time to start practice
or so we thought
We couldn't get any video of her practice
After practice
eh this is so hard
its kind of crushing my spirit
when I'm in the middle of it...
Up to now all the work in Nogizaka
for the future I've never ever thought of what I'd do as a step up but
maybe its all led up to this
Once I graduate maybe I'll become a mask change master
Unable to capture training video
Saito Asuka underwent lots of intense training
Did she become a mask change master?
Now then...its all a complete mystery...Saito Asuka's mask change show
its showtime
Is that Asuka-chan?
Is it Asuka-chan?
sugee
Its awesome but I really can't tell if that's Asuka-chan
Is that really Asuka-chan in there?
Is that Asuka-chan?
How does she do that?
That's amazing
Is that really Asuka-chan in there?
You wouldn't be able to tell if it was someone else
Another mask change
ah that's a panda mask
well is it a panda mask?
ahh panda
what it change to?
monkey...that's a monkey mask
ah monkey
monkey...that's monkey
a woman's mask?
that was fast
How many mask changes has she done here?
eh she's coming up close
Why? Wrong one?
She the wrong one?
[ wrong person ]
Why? What's wrong?
She's picking someone
What's going on? oh me?
Me then
Are you really Asuka-chan?
she changed it
That was Asuka-chan
That was Asuka-chan?
nothing changed...no change...no freaking change!
No freaking change!
[ No change ]
no freaking change
ah its Asuka-chan
There she is
what?
Its Asuka-chan
Thank goodness....the entire time we were thinking "I don't think thats Asuka-chan"
sugee! otsukare!
From the start I couldn't tell if it was you doing that
That was me!
Verified it at the end though
Was it difficult?
mega difficult!
very difficult
But you know how to do it now...you can do it for the rest of your life
Of course with mask changing
there's no sort of trickery about it but
there are levels of it from beginner to expert
there's much higher level versions of it
I was told "You're not ready for the pros yet"
[ That was beginner level ]
How many mask changes today?
It was about 10 changes
about 10 mask changes then
You even stuck in a "no change...no freaking change"
[ Their favorite part of the show ]
We can't get sensei on camera then
But she's here with us?
ah its her hand
ah sensei
She can't show her identity however
does Asuka-chan have good sense for this?
yes she did very good
very intelligent
Lets hear sensei's judgement then...onegaishimasu
[ Mask Change Show - CLEAR ]
The challenge is a success
Takayama...she got up real close to you though
Once you change the mask can you use it again?
Since those aren't really masks
[ dumb question ]
Can you go back to an older face?
It is possible to go back
After showing my real face once
it would have been possible to change to another face
That's a really high level technique
Anything you can do to stop the mask from moving when you breathe?
You saw it move?
Around this area you can see it moving in and out
eh I had no idea that was happening
[ No idea what you're talking about ]
And here...for Kitagawa who could not accomplish her goal its a punishment game
Electric shock Russian roulette
One of these is going to give you a shock
feel bad for her being all alone right
This is painful
I feel bad for her~
will you do it?
How many cups do we have?
How many? ah
How about all the people who feel bad for her come up
That would be Takayama and...
Akimoto and...
Who just said they felt bad for her?
Mukai and Nakada too
Unbelievably its now 5 people in this punishment game
only 1 cup will cause a shock
who will fall victim to electrocution?
Now then...will Kitagawa avoid punishment?
electric shock Russian roulette
3...2...1
dozo!
wah! gomen!
wait! how come?
ah sorry...looks like only 1 person was safe
[ We were mistaken ]
That's not what you told them
So only 1 person was safe from all that
I can't believe this...
That was too cruel...
sumimasen...
This is all my fault...
[ Begging for forgiveness shootout ]
"ah its mine" and then everyone around you goes down
[ Double the surprise ]
The manga was very nice
ah...sumimasen
[ Didn't hear that ]
[ By the way they gave Sakaguchi another chance...she failed again ]
What now? Another version? How about shooting it this time?
hai dozo
ah its gross