DON!
akemashite omedetou gozaimasu
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And we're underway
Nogizaka Under Construction 2020
ehh we are your hosts Bananaman
And this is the Shitara Unit
YAAY
Shitara Unit?
Where did Shitara Unit come from again?
What was that Shitara Unit used for?
Himura-san please tell them what's on today's show
onegaishimasu
Shitara Unit
The reward blowout shopping spree tour!
Now I get it
Its from almost exactly 1 year ago
we went down that path...road!
[ Copyright THE TRABRYU ]
That's not my go to song
You always say road
Sure I have sung it in the past
You're singing as the next Takahashi-san
[ Road Shitara ]
It was a year ago..the show you all did in kimonos
On that episode it was Himura Unit vs Shitara Unit
and my unit won
The prize money they won from that
was never used up to now
That's why today it'll be a shopping spree
[ Shopping extravaganza ]
You did win that one
We needed to get this done quickly
like before Inoue graduates
[ She's leaving us ]
For the graduates that are watching this
those who haven't collected their Himura Award..its coming soon
[ Please rest assured you'll get yours ]
And with that this time
The Shitara Unit members...using their prize money
will simply buy items they like
on this reward location shoot tour
eh today we have arrived at this place
eh Bic Camera
We are at their store located at Shinjuku Nishiguchi
But this is a running business
so talk in a whisper...
Its probably fine
up to this point I've been talking nonstop
[ From here on out its whispering ]
The Bic Camera employees are awesome so don't worry
Talking like this is boring
[ Can't get fired up ]
But the people here are awesome
But its been Shiraishi
Shiraishi is known for buying appliances on this show
She's practically got a full collection
she bought a washing machine
washing machine and rice cooker
Do you use them?
I use them
It makes mega delicious rice for me
And the washing machine is good?
Its awesome
Its a good one then
But there's still more appliances you want?
There's still more
[ Unending desire for appliances ]
This time
they'll split into 3 groups and walk around the store
The members will decide what sort of items they want
And then
an appliance pro will answer any product questions they may have
The members will find the item they truly want and buy it
its a can't fail buying system
First up it'll be these four..time to start shopping
What appliances are they looking to buy?
First group
Today you're all in your personal clothes?
Today its our clothes
Isn't that outfit too sexy?
[ sexy Higuchi ]
I usually dress like this
That's how you normally dress
So on this team
several people wanted this...remember what it was?
A humidifier
Who else wanted a humidifier?
ohh lots of people
I'm looking for a mixer
ahh mixer
space heater
ah a heater...that's a good one
We've entered the humidifier zone
That's a cute one
So you aren't currently using a humidifier?
I'm not
I want one too...you aren't using one
I didn't really believe that humidifiers did anything
Its better to have some humidity
I used one at a hotel and woke up feeling completely different
I thought I should own one
Since nobody I knew owned a humidifier
I heard people would spray water on their carpets and spread it around
Some people would do that
Is that so? I don't do that
They'd save their bath water
But we're talking hotels
hotels too
Better to use a humidifier
Could we end this? Nobody here does that
[ zero sympathy ]
But I think you should consider where you'll place it
Are you putting it in your living room or bedroom
living room
Is it a big apartment?
[ somewhat rude question ]
What was that? The way he asked that was funny
That sounded like a scary ojisan
Himura-san isn't asking about how much your apartment is...he just wants the square footage
What color are your curtains?
[ Interrogation ]
Now he's asking about the color of your furniture so they'll match
Don't look at him like a crazy old man
I think a white one would be good
white? white then
Next we have the Dainichi series
Dainichi is famous for their humidifiers
The worst part of humidifiers is the maintenance but they've made it easy
This hybrid model provides quick humidity and has energy saver features
they say its #1 in terms of quietness
Quiet operation is very important
There's also this one
kawaii~
This is by Balmuda
eh that's kind of stylish
vase type
They make those toasters
This thing toasts bread?
This does not toast bread
huh? Does it toast bread?
You can use it as a toaster
It can't make toast
[ Appliance writer Fujiyama Tetsuhito-san ]
It is made by that same company
I thought it would toast bread
Its really fancy
This Balmuda...you fill it with water from above
It doesn't have any needless buttons on it
simple to use then? Its simple
Its just that the price...well it is what it is
But today since you're not paying with your own money
There's a couple more to look at
ah these are some tiny ones
Are small ones ok?
For the bedroom?
You want one for the night stand
This is a nice one
This one won't get your room soggy
This one produces a really fine mist
I want one on my night stand...when I sleep
I pass out from drinking and wake up with dry tongue
[ That's Shitara's tongue ]
I'm completely dried out
If that's so you could carry this around with you
You can carry it around while it charges via USB
They have rechargeable ones
For live shows or other jobs you could walk around like this all day
That one is really nice
I want one too
I want to take it to the hotel
Well lets take a look at the mixers and you can change your mind if you'd like
ah really
This looks good
But yours is going in the living room
But I need one for the night stand...when I wake up my eyes hurt
You get dry eyes?
My eyes will hurt so much
How do your eyes dry up while sleeping?
I actually sleep with my eyes wide open
Your eyes stay wide open?
When you sleep your eyes stay open?
All facial orifices are wide open
[ The all open girl ]
Then you really need to get this one
You need to go see a doctor for that
My face opens up so much when I sleep that the members will comment on it
She looks awake...people will try to talk to her
People will try to talk to me
Like this
That's her asleep
you lie!
[ Disturbing way to sleep ]
My mother will even talk to me while I'm asleep
she thinks I'm awake since my eyes are so open
Could we set this one aside
[ Legitimately wants one ]
Its a cute one
Next its on to the electric space heater section
Who wanted a heater? It was Hazuki
eh? It'll warm up the apartment...
Obviously these will warm up your apartment
How about that big one?
Check this one out
eh? They make tiny ones
What's going on here? They make them like this too
That couldn't warm up an apartment
What type are you looking for?
For when I'm eating...
That's the living room then
Electric heaters haven't changed much have they
If you're looking for one that warms up a room real fast that's the Alladin
It'll warm up in 0.2 seconds
So even during cold winters
you don't have to wait for it to get warm
0.2 seconds is instant
How about a small one? How's this size
This is good and light
There's not much room in my apartment for it
ah is that so
A compact heater would be good
compact
Well then this one is good
I would say that is compact
[ The irresponsible group ]
If you're looking for compact this is the one
What do you do normally?
To keep warm
I take a bunch of blankets and wrap them around myself
[ Primitive way of staying warm ]
That's a sad way of going through life...curling up in blankets like that
There's one more
ah what's this one? kawaii
So this one
This one looks like a fireplace
That's right...this one will warm up your body and your soul
Micro Stove
It lights up like charcoal
And the warm air comes from here
Its a cute heater
Also you can turn off the heater and have it on just for display
display
There's a white one too
ah you like the white one
This kind of white
Since my apartment is white
Its kind of expensive...
Its not expensive
Overall there's a ton of money for you to spend here
The mixer? Are you always making blended drinks?
yes like I'll have a morning smoothie
I'll have one every now and then but
I bought the cheapest mixer I could find at an appliance store
and I've used it for so long
I'm thinking about getting one with more features
That's for juicing right
This one is incredible
It could take a light bulb and grind it into dust
or your cell phone
That would be a problem
You can put cold vegetables in here and get warm soup
Can you make shaved ice with it?
shaved ice?
[ why? ]
ah but it can do crushed ice
For shaved ice they sell shaved ice makers
[ Don't use a mixer for that ]
Around here is the recommended Healsio Green Presso
Its that one
It makes juice without destroying all the fiber and nutrients
yes since there's no heat it preserves all the vitamin C
So if you want the pure juice you should go with something like this
I want one that can do more than juice
ah she wants more uses
So this one?
That's the vacuum mixer
It removes the air inside and then does the mixing
that way there's no oxidation
This time
they'll be able to test out the products inside the store
First up
its juice from Sharp's Green Presso which uses a slow speed process
How will this juice taste?
Everyone say "renaissance"
YAAY
oishii...sugoi
Its got a gentle flavor
eh oishii
its freaking delicious
These leafy greens are in there too right
I'd like this put in some shochu
or with some vodka
Seriously if you added this to some champagne or vodka it would be a cocktail
You could even add in a horrible champagne...
[ That's just champagne ]
Next up
they'll try out the Tescom vacuum mixer
here goes
ah it has to stay pressed?
I didn't keep it pressed
Is it creating a vacuum right now?
eh sugoi...kowai kowai kowai
everything is getting squeezed in
eh kowai kowai kowai
Since it can also crush ice
it is now a cold smoothie
In the end how will it taste?
renaissance~ renaissance!
Try some
I wonder how it will be different
ah..so this one is more about raw ingredients
But this one
is like a smoothie
they would sell at a restaurant
Please have a drink
Know what I mean?
Its good
huh? This is completely different
That one has its own deliciousness but
ahh well either of them are fine
This is really good...it really is
And with that have you decided what item you want?
hai
Feel free to change your mind from what you said earlier
You can also pick out any item we didn't go into detail over...anything you're interested in
Now lets see who wins the drawing
eh?
We don't all get something?
ehh? seriously?
no way!
gomen gomen...did you think everyone was getting to buy something?
You didn't tell them that part...I didn't?
You're such an imbecile
[ Baka Shitara ]
ehh~ no way!
The prize money arrangement
is that a set number of people from each group will get what they want
This time there will be 2 winners
After this and you return to the others if you would keep this a secret...
[ Repeating this with the next group ]
We're going to do this to all the groups
So there's one ball per person in there
the white ball is a miss and red is a winner
[ Order determined by janken:  Higuchi - Mukai - Iwamoto - Terada ]
What item do you want?
That humidifier by Balmuda
ah! She's going for that one
The round one
It would look cute in my home
just as expected...
She went for the expensive item...
[ legit choice ]
ok here goes...red means winner
Now then
will she draw a winner?
dozo
white!
She got a white ball
ehhhhh~
white
But it'll be fine
even if you draw a losing ball
Even with a losing ball you still get a prize
Himura-san onegaishimasu
omedetou gozaimasu
The consolation prize
kowai kowai kowai..this could be something scary
ah! Its batteries!
[ consolation prize ]
You must be happy...those are real AA batteries
You can never find batteries when you really need them
Now then...after that there's 2 winning balls and 1 miss
Its better to draw your ball later
Now Mukai
hai...may I
In the end which item did you pick out?
The thin space heater
The Alladin heater and the humidifier
[ Wants 2 things ]
The humidifier that was like 5000 yen
I walked by it
You walked by a humidifier that was around 5000 yen
That's fine by me
Mukai is requesting a humidifier she saw when the cameras weren't on
since the cost of both items together is still cheap we'll allow it
ganbare
If she gets the white one then you 2 win
So that's the situation
Now then here goes...Mukai
dozo
sugoi!
Red! That's a winner
You've done it
This is my happiest moment of the year!
[ We're only 5 days into the year ]
There's a chance we won't even get to Terada's turn
no...its come down to this
eh what do you want?
The humidifier I can put on a night stand
The thin one then
That's a good one
I can bring it with me to the hotel
We should ask her now what she wants
So I want...
It doesn't have to be the mixer
So its not the mixer
its an air purifier and
there was there humidifier thing attached to it
That one on the other side...
[ Another item that wasn't put on camera ]
This area that was away from the cameras...ah that's what I want
Even after we were all over here drinking smoothies
[ The abandoned mixers ]
Even after all that?
That's what Bic Camera does to people
[ Makes you impulse buy ]
There's only 1 winning ball left
Who will get it? Will it be Iwamoto or Terada?
Now then let's get started
I'll give it a spin
Which one is it?
Red~
She got it
And with that our first group
Mukai and Iwamoto get the items they wanted
After this could you hide the batteries
[ Keep it a secret ]
Next up
these 6 people will go shopping
Thanks for waiting
Let's get going then
I believe all of you were asked what items you wanted...what did you say?
I said robot vacuum
You bought a vacuum before didn't you
yes I did
You're really focused on vacuuming
But this time its an automatic
I'd like for it to vacuum automatically when I'm not home
Seems like that's mostly what the vacuum robots get used for
eh..what did you pick?
rice cooker and toaster
So a rice cooker and toaster
They'll have some good ones here
I want a good rice cooker
eh Inoue what did you ask for?
I mentioned a lot of items
Like almost an entire home appliances collection
almost an entire collection?
And what did you say?
What was yours?
A vacuum
vacuum? hai
What did you say?
vacuum for me too
I also said vacuum
Let's start with the vacuums then
They're really wanting to do some vacuuming
ah you like a clean home
But the vacuum Matsumura bought in studio last time was really nice
That's a really good vacuum
The battery would come off for recharging
I loved the vacuum and then my mother loved it
so my parents bought one too
That was wise...wasn't that style of vacuum in this area?
We might as well
do some research to find the good ones
and here is our expert
onegaishimasu
Torneo..this Toshiba vacuum is the most balanced in capabilities
Its balanced between the weight and power and battery life
ah the batteries are important in these lightweight models
For those who own a pet
I highly recommend this Toshiba
I'm a pet owner!
Pet hair will not get tangled inside
But girls with long hair...this would help them
yes it would
How heavy is it?
Its light
Its light...so women can carry it everywhere with them
The lightest vacuum would be this one
Sharp..ah its light
This is extremely lightweight
Even lighter?
mega light
Its the weight of 2.5 mic stands
About 2.5 mic stands
If that's so I could just about carry it and sing into it
I can hold it up with my pinky
This does make using it around the house much easier
Could you sing into it?
Light enough to sing into?
Would you sing for us?
Any song is fine
Romantic...ah
[ Instant regret ]
Well? Can you sing into it?
Junna can you sing?
sing something
House~
[ Entering the humiliation zone ]
Couldn't sing much there?
[ Don't come over here ]
You can do that for us right?
Is it better if I hold it?
eh its still...
Lift it up to see how light it is
sugoi
Can you sing with it then?
Sing a little bit
Curtain no naka~
[ *Verifying that its lightweight ]
Everyone's singing old songs
Inoue...how is it?
Could you sing with it?
yes I think I could
[ Casually sends it back ]
Would you sing for us?
oide shampoo~
[ Unclear if there's a correct answer ]
Himura-san you hold it
It really is the weight of a mic
Himura-san could you do [Denen]?
ishi koroke tobashi~
taiyou ni naita boku~
[ copyright Tamaki Koji ]
This is totally doable
I could totally sing [Denen] with this!
After that...the show recommends this one
eh? what is this?
Shark
Evopower...what's this one?
eh this is a vacuum?
I like this one
That's an entire vacuum?
Vacuum like this?
Is it a hand vac?
There's attachments
This is a good one
Can you sing with it?
[ Once you touch it you're done for ]
ah these 2 haven't done it yet
So how is it?
Its mega lightweight...this is great
Could you sing for us?
This is so nice
hashire! Bi...
[ Immediately gives up ]
You're embarrassed singing your own songs
I think I might have insulted the song a little
Think you can sing with it?
Its so light...eh?
This vacuum is mega lightweight
Can you do it?
toki no nagare ni mi wo makase~
[ This time its Teresa Teng ]
I want to check the suction
sugoi~ I can't pull away
Can't pull away can you
That would make your heart race...that "I can't pull away"
what? Tamaki-san?
[ *Still checking the suction ]
Are you trying to turn me into Tamaki-san with that?
Is this really Tamaki-san?
[ Random character ]
I can't see it but its likely not him
But this one is 20,000 yen
It all goes in here?
How do you empty the dirt?
With this you could drop the dirt right into a trash can
That's mega convenient
Way too easy
Next the group
is moving into the robot vacuum section
They have this many models of robot vacuums?
There's a bunch of them but
some of them can be really loud
The ones that go WHRRNNG
ah you know this?
Recently it seems like Shiraishi Mai-chan has a robot vacuum
but its so loud it makes you wonder if its worth it
I want the type that shoots out water
That's over there
But I think those just wipe the floor
Those are mopping robots
But if you find yourself mopping everyday then its fine
I have a mopping robot at home
I see...then its these over here
About 32,000 yen
It uses a crazy amount of vibration where it mops
It rolls along and leaves everything shiny
I want to try it
Everything turns shiny
So shiny you can see your reflection in the floor
If that's so..since its so cheap get one of those along with the Shark
If you get them together that's just around 50,000
That would work out well
Can I do that?
Of course...its your reward location shoot
This is all for Shitara Team
If you're looking for a combination mop and vacuum
What's this one?
This one mops and vacuums
It does both?
This is the best then...so they make these
They make them
Could you show us the bottom?
This is the towel part
With just one machine
it'll do the vacuuming and mopping for you
eh sugoi
For pet owners
ah sugoi
With other robot vacuums
if your pet happens to poop on the floor
the robot will spread the poop everywhere
I've heard that happens...it'll come into your bedroom like that
This model can detect for it
What does it do then?
It will avoid it
It'll avoid it
Can it tell you whose poop it is?
[ Poop identification? ]
Does it work for people poop too?