DON
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
we are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And they are Nogizaka-chan
kawaii
Accept this!
Himura-san
hai
Please tell them whats on todays show
Here it goes
Romance Fantasies Grand Prix 2020!
With Valentine's Day coming up
the fantasies of the members just get more wild
So right here
among all of their fantasies
they've written their ideal Valentine's Day into a script for us
Leading role...director
the casting of the love interest
all of it was left to the members
and they will act out their ideal Valentine's Day for us
eh this time we've got 6 entries
The members in the back are playing the leading male role for this
So is this the image of their ideal boyfriends then?
Has to be...its the boyfriend role in their fantasy
so that's why they would offer them the role
Seems like everyone has bigger hair now
First its a Valentines fantasy drama from Director Tamura
Ready
start!
Even with it being Valentine's day
I'm working overtime all alone
The one I admire...Shiraishi-senpai
I was planning to give him my homemade chocolate
but I just can't seem to finish these presentation slides
ahh~
What am I doing right now!
[ Shiraishi-senpai returns from a business meeting ]
ah!
Tamura
You're still here working?
ah.....hai
[ He hands out a bottle of milk tea to Tamura ]
Here...
maybe you should have a drink
How about a little break?
senpai....
How did you know I love milk tea?
When it comes to a cute coworker like you
I'll know everything about her
eh!?
heh~
The new project
are these the presentation slides?
hai...
But I'm having a hard time making the graphs
What do we have here....
[ Shiraishi gets up real close to Tamura ]
So right here
just by changing the color doesn't the chart become easier to read
See...its really simple!
arigatou gozaimasu
senpai is so amazing
For me
I've been doing this for hours and I'm still nowhere near finished
[ Spins the chair around ]
It'll be fine
As long as your work at it
someday you'll get good at it
But for me
I really can't do anything right
I'm slow at getting work done
I can't come up with good ideas...
my personality is all dark
I'm clumsy...and foolish...and ugly
SHHHH!
[ Places pointer finger on her mouth ]
Don't criticize yourself any further
Lets put an end to you hurting yourself any further
Tamura's hard work
there's someone next to you that's been watching all your hard work
eh!?
By the way
I'd consider myself to be that person
senpai
please don't look at me like that
[ Box of chocolate falls on the floor ]
And this is?
well.....that's....
a box of chocolates
I was going to give that chocolate to senpai later...
I was planning to properly give it to you....
no...
what am I doing right now...
SHHHH!
[ Places pointer finger on her mouth ]
That happens twice?
She won't let her talk at all
arigatou
Your feelings have been completely accepted
senpai!
[ Tamura goes to Shiraishi for an embrace ]
[ OH MY LITTLE GIRL / Yutaka Ozaki ]
This is an Ozaki song
hai CUT
You did a good job of playing an office worker
[ Convincing in her role ]
That's great
In terms of age
I'd be about the same age as an office worker
About how much older is your senpai here?
26 years old
[ Office love with a 26 year old senpai ]
Close to reality then
kakkoii...
kakkoii?
very handsome
But that finger shushing was pretty good
[ Killer move...the finger shush ]
I definitely wanted to do something that wasn't at all realistic
so I suggested that one
Anything happens....SHHH~
[ Not letting you say anything ]
But you could mess up and stick it right up there
[ Dangerous play ]
What happens afterwards?
Do they start dating?
At work our relationship is kept a secret from everybody
[ They say nothing to their coworkers while their relationship grows ]
I thought that was incredible
That was well done wasn't it
That posture after she spun her chair around
[ Maintaining the lean over stance ]
Next is a Valentine fantasy drama from Director Hayakawa
There's a boy I'm interested in
Ever since middle school we've been classmates
He's incredibly smart
so I was sure he'd go to a different high school but
by some coincidence we're going to the same high school
This boy
I wonder if he knows what day it is today?
How does he feel about me?
Love that Kansai dialect
[ Matsumura leaving school ]
Matsumura!
huh?
Wait for me!
What's this...oh its Hayakawa
hey Matsumura
do you know what day today is?
Today?
no I don't
That so?
But everyones in a good mood today
ahh...is it Valentine's Day
Well everybody from class would be happy but
that stuff has nothing to do with me
How come?
Maybe it does involve you
Matsumura
have you received any chocolate?
hmph........no I have not
good one
Wait a second
[ Hayakawa hands over the chocolate ]
here
eh!?
What's this?
Its chocolate
so...the other day
you let me read your notes
that's why
in appreciation
What? A thank you gift for letting you see my notes?
well....arigatou
hey Matsumura
I've always wanted to ask you this but
I know that Matsumura is super smart
So then why did you decide to go to this school?
Why did I decide to go to school here?
well that's because
the reason for that is...
well there's all kinds of reasons
eh what do you mean all kinds of reasons?
well yes...
ehhh
of course...
What is it?
Because of you
because you said you were applying to this high school
eh!?
That means...
I've had enough!
I'm just going to say it
So I
have a crush on you
Because of you...
since I have a crush on Hayakawa
I applied for this school
For you to say this now is going to cause problems!
[ Matsumura looks confused after his confession appears rejected ]
Well allow me to say this then
this chocolate
I said it was a thank you gift but
its a true valentine
[ Osaka LOVER/ DREAMS COME TRUE ]
baka!
what was that for?
hai CUT
So using the Kansai dialect like that
it sounded natural
[ Kansai dialect = PASS ]
Plus your song was Osaka Lover by Dreams Come True
Osaka Lover
I thought a little about
what happens to them after this
After this?
The image I have in my mind
is that he goes to a high academics level college far away from me
I'm kind of foreshadowing
a painful future for them by using that song
sounds sad
Hayakawa doesn't study her hardest to get into the same college?
hmmm...
ganbaru
[ Back in fantasy world ]
I'll study real hard
Matsumura you can't leave her to go to that college for smart people
In my mind I would never drop myself down a level
[ Keeps it real ]
Why are you like this!
Director Umezawa presents her true wishes in this Christmas fantasy drama
ready
ahhh~ start!
I've been dating my boyfriend who's older than me for about a year
I'm waiting alone at his house and he's late coming home from work
Even though today is Christmas
I'm not into making a big deal out of anniversaries and such
but I'm feeling a little motivated
guess I'll make dinner and wait for him to come home
Christmas?
[ Umezawa brings out dinner ]
ok then
now the preparations are OK
They're already dating then
Even with that its getting really late...
What's he doing right now?
[ Lies down on the sofa ]
ah she's going to fall asleep
ah...yabai
got tired of waiting
ahh...definitely going to fall asleep
She fell asleep
[ Shot of the clock displaying 11:45pm ]
tadaima~
What's this?
Minami fell asleep
Can't do much about that
what?
We bought the same cake
On top of that what an amazing dinner
Minami sure put some energy into this
tadaima
[ Minami wakes up ]
ah!
What? Did I wake you up?
okaeri
Just in time to say Merry Christmas
ah...that's right
So today
I found this fancy chopsticks store
and I bought these
Me too
you kidding me...does that ever happen?
During lunch I bought these at a fancy chopsticks store
As I thought the 2 of us
we think the same
come over here
This episode is right before Valentine's Day though
But Christmas
is so nice
Its like during a normal day I want it to become just a little special
[ Not too over the top adult love fantasy ]
That's why I didn't add in any kyun stuff and kept it natural
You purposely kept it from being like "here's the moment"
Plus you had a man play the role of boyfriend
[ Actor-san? ]
That's not an actor?
My name is Ito Junna
ah so that was Ito Junna
So Ito Junna was voted leading male role #1
[ Boyfriend role candidate #1 ]
Since I heard she was that popular
I'm super happy to do that scene with Junna-san
Why does this sound like a business?
[ Full control of NO. 1 ]
Next up
Director Kaki's Valentines fantasy drama
ready
start
Even with today being my birthday
I'm sitting all alone in my room
to have such a lonely birthday like this
instead maybe if someone would come take me away from here....
Feel bad for her
sigh~
my birthday is about over
[ Sound of the window opening ]
eh?
eh?!
Who's there?
Kazu-senpai! What are you....
SHHHH!
What is going on here?
If you scream everyone will hear you
What are you doing at this time of night?
Today
its Haruka's birthday isn't it?
Would you like to come outside?
But look how late it is...
If you exit through the window it'll be fine
Actually there's something I want to show Haruka
Something to show me?
It'll be fine! Hurry up!
Before your birthday is over
Now then!
hai
[ Grabs her hand and leads her out of the window ]
Kazu-senpai suddenly appeared late at night
He says there's something he wants to show me
At this hour to take me out somewhere
where exactly is he taking me?
Where exactly are we going Kazu-senpai?
Have a seat here
Kazu-senpai seems out of control
Haruka
congratulations on your birthday
So how do you like it?
My present for you
present?
Its so dark I can't see anything
Haruka is still a child
I guess you can't see it then?
hey now Kazu-senpai! Please stop fooling around!
Then for Haruka
I'll make it so that you can see it too
here goes
[ Christmas lights light up ]
eh sugoi!
Haruka
happy birthday
congratulations on your 18th birthday
eh?
arigatou gozaimasu
But when did you do all this...
I just barely set this up in time but
somehow it made you happy
thank goodness
Haruka....
would you be my princess?
That's crazy
hai
if you're ok with me
arigatou
[ Suki / Nishino Kana ]
[ Kaki sneezes ]
You'll catch a cold
So this one....obviously
Kazu-senpai is way out of control
[ Character way too strong ]
What's Kazu-senpai all about?
He's a senpai at school
1 or 2 grades above you?
2 grades higher
He's only 2 grades higher with all this?
But didn't she totally
capture a girls thoughts with Kazu-senpai
[ Still in pajamas ]
She didn't let her change or anything....just dragged her outside
then she snaps and says "How you like that?"
[ Super laid back ]
You just do everything on a whim
That's true
That part was added in
What happens to you after that?
He's super popular so
if we're discovered all the girls
will turn into my enemies so
its kept secret
But there's no way to keep a relationship with Kazu-senpai a secret
ah we'd boldly walk around as a couple starting tomorrow then
You'd walk around like that....that's no good
everyone would look
Even if they look...he'd come and protect me
yes...I protect!
[ The Kazu-senpai shield ]
I protect
I'd like to see Kazu-sensei appear in more scenes
We should have Kazu-sensei come out in a series of scenes
[ Hopes to start a series ]
OY! Let's go!
[ This is how he'll enter every scene ]
Why can't you use a door like normal
Why do you always come in through the window!
Next its Director Tsutsui's Valentine's fantasy drama
ready
I have a classmate that works as a librarian named Ren-kun
Whenever there's a break
you'll always see him reading a book
Watching him read like that is a secret pleasure of mine
But I'm sure there must be
something other than books that he's interested in...
She watches him
ah...is this a book return?
hai
[ Removes the bookmark from the last page of the book ]
sigh~
so....
are there any books that you've read recently you could recommend?
My recommendation?
Since Ren-kun is always reading
I'm thinking you'd be an expert
[ Pulls 1 book from off the shelf ]
This is by an author that's gaining attention lately
I believe its an easy read
arigatou
[ Takes the book and puts the bookmark on the last page ]
huh? What's the matter?
Tsutsui-san
do you not use the bookmark?
I tend to read all the way to the end in one sitting
I put the bookmark in the back....I don't use it
I see
However...
this bookmark has a cute flower pattern doesn't it?
[ Turns over the bookmark to see the words "I like you" ]
just like that?
Ren-kun?
gomen
its like
I couldn't tell you directly
gomennasai
ah wait a second
I'm happy
arigatou
What's going on?
Thank goodness
ah! Its time for the next class to start
Let's go together
just like that then
[ Baby I Love You / TEE ]
So the bookmark is setup like that each time show borrows a book?
yes even though
I always write on the back of it
since she doesn't use the bookmark she never sees the message
Now I get it
Each time brings sadness
But once she finally turned over the bookmark
she sees what you wrote
From out of nowhere
And then after she says "Let's go"
was holding him by 1 finger on purpose?
hai
ah that was part of your directing?
Since the boy is a bashful type
holding his entire hand from the very start
would seem too embarrassing
You haven't gotten that close yet
What's it called...
its like having a pure white kind of love among us
As for me...
Your love has already become totally stained
[ The stained adult ]
But I never experienced anything as pure as that
It was all just so cute
Finally its Director Kubo's Valentines fantasy drama
ready
AUGH!
Ever since elementary school
I've always gone to the same school as Yamashita-kun
We've always been good friends
so at school there'd be rumors about us
but up to this point we've never discussed our true feelings
We seem to understand how we feel about each other
surely its mutual....
Also which one of us will confess to the other?
It was just the timing of it all
That the shoe locker?
[ Yamashita carries his letter to the shoe locker ]
That's the childhood friend then
sigh
Its a letter
[ To Shiori ]
ah it went in!
huh?
just now?
Isn't that the wrong locker?
That's a major mistake
ah it was a different locker
[ Kubo changes shoes and leaves ]
Major mistake
[ He put the letter in Yakubo's locker instead of Kubo's by mistake ]
A month later it was Valentine's Day
Yamashita-kun was on the way home from club practice
and he was with me at the bus stop
I summoned up the courage to tell him my feelings
Shiori
ahh...ah Yama...
ah did you have club practice today?
ahhh...our tournament is coming up
there's no time to rest
How about you?
I also have a tournament in March
But its nothing like Yama's tournament
I see
[ The conversation stops and there's silence ]
Seems awkward
I should tell you...
ah gomen
go ahead
You go ahead
No go ahead
I said you could talk first
So actually
I have something I'd like to tell Shiori
What is it?
So I....
I have a girlfriend now
eh?
I asked out Yoda from Class-5
Since we've known each other for so long I thought I should tell you
All because of that misplaced letter
heh~
I see
I understand
That's good to hear
I'll support you
I see
arigatou
ah!
I think I left my gym clothes in the classroom
I'm going back there to get my clothes...go on without me
well then...
ok then
The tournament
give it your best
hold on now
[ Betsu no hito no kanojo ni natta yo / wacci ]
It ends like this?
Why? Your fantasy is this sad story?
[ Can't believe its a fantasy of lost love ]
This one really...like what happened at the beginning
his letter
he makes a mistake and puts it in the wrong locker
Then that letter
he waits forever for a proper reply
That's right...Yamashita has to wait
That letter had your love confession on it right?
The names looked similar
I put it in the wrong locker
Saying it went in the wrong locker
doesn't that seem too sad
It ends with Yakubo then?
So he ended up dating Yoda
Who? You ended up with Yoda?
Yoda-chan from Class-5
[ The 3rd woman ]
I confessed my feelings to her
but I never got a response
I guess I'll ask out Yoda then
[ Settles for Yoda ]
Was Yamashita supposed to be this type of guy?
I easily get over things
Shiraishi
Does Yamashita's behavior sound wrong to you?
100% Yamashita is the bad person here!
That sounds right
What would Kazu-senpai do in this situation?
[ Kazu-senpai! ]
Painful isn't it
If that were me
that night...
right through the window
[ The window is the only option ]
The award for Best Fantasy
Tsutsui's
library scene
[ Director Tsutsui wins the award for Best Fantasy ]
So my favorite part of that one
it was the overall feeling of gentleness
the moments with no dialogue...it was the dramatic pauses
I really felt the emotions from it
it clutched at my heart
omedetou gozaimasu