DON
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
we are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And they are Nogizaka-chan
ah there's a lot of them
ahh there's so many
There's so many of them
YAAY~
yay?
With so many people here Himura-san tell them what's on the show
onegaishimasu
Here it goes
Entering into year #9
Right now there are family members that have something they want to say 2020!
Its coming up on 9 years since the debut
Nogizaka46
Since there's more new members
things only their family would know
a side of the members we still don't know about
we asked for stories of that nature in a secret family survey
Up first
Something only the family would know...can't miss stories
So these stories are guaranteed to get laughs
I see
[ Terrifying bits of dirt about the members ]
Almost like why haven't you mentioned this one
The families were confident that these stories were a sure hit and gave them to us
ah sumimasen
First is a scoop from Watanabe's mama
Back when my daughter was little
When you were a little kid
We went to a department store to buy clothes
Does this remind you of anything so far?
Don't remember this so far
eh your mother went into the fitting room
she was trying on clothes and started changing
that's when Miria-chan
she saw her mother undressing and mistakenly thought it was bath time
She got fully undressed
then ran out of the fitting room and within the department store
she ran around naked
[ On the loose and completely naked ]
kawaii~
That sounds cute though
It appears that this really happened
Don't remember?
You must have heard this story at home before
My sister went shopping with us too that time
My older sister has mentioned that I ran around the store completely naked
That kind of stuff is so cute though
But how old were you to run naked like that? Were you around 12 years old?
[ Not a laughing matter for a 6th grader ]
How long are you going to mistake that for bath time?
The next inside scoop
its a can't miss episode about Wada
We got this one from your mother
When she moved to Tokyo...the letter I immediately got from my daughter
came in an envelope used at funerals
[ Letter to heaven ]
You did that to her?
That's a can't miss story right there
That is quite a story
hai
This is an absolutely true story then
yes that's right
That's incredible misfortune to put a regular letter in that envelope
I had no idea
that it was a letter of great misfortune
That doesn't make it a letter of great misfortune
[ Haunted goods? ]
So that's
an envelope used for funeral offerings
I bought it at a konbini
and wrote my letter and sent it off
I simply wanted to put it in an envelope
and this envelope looked so fancy so
ahh so that's what happened
But there should have been congratulation envelopes on sale next to it
For whatever reason I chose the funeral envelope
Was it to write the address?
ah I wrote the address
That's going to freak out whoever receives that letter
Why on earth am I receiving this?
[ Giving your mother the chills ]
Wada....that girl truly is crazy
Well other girls have come along but noone can top Wada
The next scoop is from 4th member Kanagawa's mama
From when you were in 1st grade
you scored a zero on a national language test
zero points
zero
Then you happily ran up and said "mama! Saya got a 0!"
She said this as if she got a perfect test score
That's really cute
In addition to that your mother
she wrote things her daughter is unsatisfactory at
eh knowledge
Starting off there is pretty amazing
That pretty much means everything right there
vocabulary skills
slurred speech
There's too many words she doesn't understand
there they are
Do you remember scoring a 0 on a test?
I totally remember it
You do
I filled in all the blanks and got a zero
[ All wrong answers ]
I get it...you filled it as best you could and still got a 0
I was feeling both shocked
yet also kind of happy
Why would there be feelings of happiness from that?
I thought it was kind of rare
Any members recall a moment when they thought Kanagawa has problems
any stories like this one
She'll say something is nothing special when she meant to call it short and stocky
That's Himura-san
[ #1 guy in the short and stocky world ]
Himura-san didn't hear you and asked what you said...she said short and stocky
You should remember that word by image
Either image or the sound of it
How would you describe me?
short and stocky
yes yes yes...I am short and stocky
[ Visual reminder of that vocabulary word ]
eh remember anything else?
So corn flakes
here it comes...something involving corn flakes
[ Its also a gag by Milkboy ]
She confuses the word cornflakes with frankfurt
completely different
[ No logic behind this one ]
I ate a parfait
parfait...that's a parfait
Those have cornflakes
Saya comes up and says "I love frankfurters"
[ parfait with bonus intestines? ]
Is there any way to confuse those 2 words?
Maybe she remembers on sound alone?
Do those sound the same?
The fu in flake and in frankfurt
She mistook flake for frank?
Not sure how this happened
I wonder how this happened
How? I'm trying to help you out right now
[ Not on the same page with Himura ]
So you go to a konbini and will ask for cornflakes?
Instead of asking for a frankfurter?
It should work in reverse too
I never do that
never you say
She only treats me coldly
[ Say NO to Himura ]
Just now even though Himura-san was trying to cover up for you
I tried to...
[ Refuses to accept Himura's helping hand ]
Its because you're short and stocky
That part she can say clearly
So do you understand the meaning of song lyrics?
ah I have no idea
[ Agrees wholeheartedly ]
That was noble
This will make Akimoto-sensei fall right out of his chair
[ You're killing the guy that writes the lyrics ]
Akimoto-sensei I don't understand this at all
Have you heard some recent lyrics and wondered what they mean?
ahhhh
poppi pappapa
so poppi pappapa....nobody knows what that means
[ Meaning unknown is the correct answer ]
Anybody know what it means?
There's no real meaning is there?
If you search for meaning in those words you'll die
[ Going deep into philosophy ]
You're not supposed to think about what poppi pappapa means
Next its a can't miss story from Kitagawa's mama
Back when you went shopping with your mother
Thinking back there were many times when you'd stand by the entrance and open the door
That's a good girl
So when you went inside you kept the door open for others
That's very admirable
But then more customers would come in
and she'd be stuck holding the door
That became her job
She became the doorman
So then the other day
there was this old lady she didn't know
She asked "What floor is women's clothing?"
This was recent?
They thought you worked at the department store?
It happens when you hold open a door right
you open it and say "dozo dozo"
and that part caused a misunderstanding
I'm not good at making my way inside
When you go in you're supposed to exit out of there right
When I open a door
[ Can't get away from the door ]
baka!
Once its open you have to go straight
why would you follow the door around?
[ The behavior of someone who works there ]
That's why people think you're the doorman
This spinning around is no good
That makes you the doorman
[ Turns are banned ]
Do you press the buttons for people on the elevator?
on the elevator
I've never ever pressed the door close button
[ no door close button pressing experience ]
I don't press the button on my own
When you're annoyed you mash that button don't you?
like close close close don't you
Even if someone is walking up...close close close
[ door close button masher ]
Feel bad about doing it but
Don't come in! Don't come in!
I've let the door close just in time
[ Heartless door closing ]
Next is a scoop from the Tamura family
Previously
you had a location shoot out at FujiQ
the day before that
Do you know what this is about yet?
eh? What could this be?
You hate riding roller coasters so much that
remember now?
that at home you did some serious sobbing
Unless its something very unusual she's not a girl that cries very much
so she must really hate roller coasters
But if you cry because you hate roller coasters
doesn't that make you a girl that cries a lot
You really must have hated it then
We have video
eh? They made a video?
hai
dozo
[ Tamura's dad recording ]
Seriously what am I going to do?
Don't overthink this
if you hate it there's nothing you can do about it
But everyone has to ride it
Consider yourself lucky...the roller coaster lovers will be like
the roller coaster lovers...
What do you think you're doing!
[ Mom gets angry at dad ]
ah I get it
I don't get this...don't cry
heh heh heh heh
And then here's what happened on the roller coaster
Thank god I"m alive....
So your father filmed that
of you crying
Its likely my father filmed that
And while laughing
heh heh heh heh
He got this close
[ Papa laughs uncontrollably at your tears ]
That's a nice family
The father laughs while filming
was it him? the master of crane games?
That's him
Its that same otousan!
[ The papa with intense character ]
That's a great dad
great dad
Its that same otousan
That's how he can film so close while his daughter cries
[ Fighting stance allows him to get close ]
Next...recommended by the family
Our kid is amazing at this
First the Matsumura family brags about their daughter
Where's Matsumura at? There she is
There's really nothing I'm amazing at
Our daughter is amazing at
her skin is white
Her butt and arms are the same color white
kawaii
I have not actually seen her butt
please check out her photobook to verify...from dad
otousan!
That's her freaking dad right there
[ Papa loves her daughter ]
Otousan is asking people to look at her photobook?
Its a casual promo for the photobook
Well he is pushing the photobook
otousan does make it sound like that
But in my family
there's a lot of compliments passed around
ah that's good
Like in the group chats among the family
when I appear on tv
Sayuri-chan you're on tv! You're the cutest in the world!
When I appear on a music tv show
Sayuri-chan is about to perform...everybody gather around the tv
hai! I'm watching you
Next Yakubo mama brags about her daughter
Since she has a round head
makeup-san said "You look like Anpanman and Doraemon"
makeup-san talks to you like that?
[ Straight up makeup-san ]
That's mean
When she was told that
Yakubo
much like Anpanman and Doraemon
the both of them
I'll do what I can to become as popular nationally as those 2
that was her answer
"What a great girl" I thought
You said that?
That's a mega good reply
Since I was so happy
Since I was happy
You were happy?
Even though having a round head isn't really a good thing
But Anpanman and Doraemon have round heads
But both of them
are cute looking so
Those two
[ Both of them would be senpais however.... ]
Referring to Anpanman and Doraemon as those 2 sounds out of place
[ We'd like you to tell us how you count them up ]
Today you look very much like Doraemon
[ Short and stocky and in light blue ]
I was thinking I looked much like Doraemon today
You do look like Doraemon
[ Distant relative? ]
The next to brag about their daughter is the Mukai family
Her strong luck at prize drawings
This is what our daughter is amazing at
luck at prize drawings
There was a prize drawing at the konbini for a Rilakkuma
she went there and spent enough money for 2 entries
Mukai
On the way home
she had a 1st prize Rilakkuma
there was one in each hand
[ 2 times 1st place prize ]
She won 2?
With the money to enter twice
she played twice and won two 1st place Rilakkuma
We have a picture
Mukai
[ Unable to relax ]
Is that Mukai in the middle?
This is so cute right here
What's going on here?
She won those?
sugoi...those things are almost as big as Mukai
Mukai do you remember this?
I remember it
You paid for 2 entries and won twice
yes...I really loved Rilakkuma
please let me enter this
Doing that I won twice
sugee
They were so amazingly huge
They are...I mean which one is Mukai
[ 3 siblings? ]
Its the one on the far right
The brown one is Mukai?
That brown one is Mukai
I used to go to Sensoji for the New Year's shrine visit
That place is famous for drawing a bad fortune
But even there
I went on a streak of drawing excellent luck
Year after year?
Your new year's shrine visits were always excellent luck
It was
But since joining Nogizaka
that was my last time drawing good fortune
[ Hit rock bottom after joining? ]
Since then its been all bad fortunes
ah you mean at Sensoji
Next...its a family selection
Our daughter sparkled in this best scene from the show
First its Shiraishi mama's selection for best scene
Shiraishi
Nogizaka Under Construction Blu-ray
this is from Akimoto Under Construction
Rid yourself of weakness....aim to be the perfect idol
Using hypnotism to have them conquer their fears
the images of my daughter who hates snakes
were her best scenes
Seriously? She picked that one?
hai...let's take a look back at the scene she's talking about
here it is
I don't really want to watch this
dozo
wah wah wah! I saw it! I saw it!
what what what? what did you see?
KYAA
yada! yada! yada! yada! yada! yada!
Take a look...the closer you get to it
the cuter it'll seem to you
look
Its amazing
Shiraishi stuck in an awkward position
[ Jumps right in to touch it ]
The both of them are having no problems at all
This is incredible
wah sugoi...wah sugoi
wah this creeps me out
wah wah wah~
eh she's holding it
Could you break the hypnotism?
hypnotism off
What happened? What happened?
Looking back..that hypnotism stuff is incredible
Its scary
You hated snakes that much but then had no problems holding one
That's interesting stuff
Maybe if there's another chance...someday
ah..there's no need
You're hesitating but you'll be hypnotized so its all ok
[ The strongest case for hypnotism ]
Next its a selection from the Umezawa family
During the 3rd member proxy battle
there was a balloon sumo contest
Watching it you could feel her strong desire to protect her beloved Shiraishi
it didn't matter whether the show was entertaining
the sight of her fighting to protect someone was so cool
that it moved me from the bottom of my heart
yada
You cannot allow Shiraishi's face to get hit with a pie...
do you realize how many photobooks she's sold?
[ A battle she cannot afford to lose ]
You can't allow Shiraishi to get hit with a pie
HAKKEYOI
NOKOTTA!
oh what do we have here
Mukai is eliminated
[ Himura a victim of friendly fire ]
Himura-san took a hit
And they're running out of endurance
ah they're both out
both of them went out
I won~
wah sugoi
[ Tearful declaration of victory ]
Shiraishi
she's emotional from seeing her fight
[ Senpai also has tears in her eyes ]
Saved her from taking a pie
There were no thoughts of losing
I absolutely...
I absolutely knew I would win
[ Thinks like an athlete ]
That's a good thing
But seeing you go all out for that battle
the people watching on tv
like your family were so moved by that performance
so embarrassing
Next its a selection from Shinuchi mama
The fantasy romance awards...for best kyun in the drama category
There it is!
The creation of Director Shinuchi
Line of Ginkgo Trees
As my daughter and director and actress
I thought she worked so hard on it
The trophy she won from that episode is on display at home
ah is that so
Every time I walk by a line of Ginkgo trees I think of her video
The trophy is currently still on display
It is then
Its on the tv stand
ah...on the tv stand?
hai
That's a good place to put your trophy
Next to my Cable Music Awards medal
is that trophy
[ Lifetime achievement ]
The next theme
what the family hopes for
Its things the family wants their daughter to do in the future
First its the hopes of Hoshino papa
After graduating...I would assume from Nogizaka
if she'd train at golf...
Why!?
I hate that idea...is he stupid or something?
[ Proposal rejected within seconds ]
What is he talking about?
I'd like her to be the first Nogizaka46 graduate
to become a womens pro golfer
Why does he want that?
I have no idea what he's talking about
He's telling you to go become a golfer
She's actually quite athletic...he continues to say
eh? Do you play golf then?
My father is into golf and now my mother has recently started playing
I've never ever mentioned anything about wanting to play
Since you're athletic you could do this couldn't you
But why..stupid...its just so stupid
Since its her father's dream...lets check her current golf swing
Swing like you're really trying to hit a ball
eh kowai...what if I damage the floor?
Don't worry about the floor...if that's the worst that could happen
What now? Himura-san
how about you lie down?
[ On The Himura ]
Your father's dream
dozo
kowai!
What's the proper technique then?
Keep your hands close together
This really makes no difference...I'm not doing it!
[ She don't need your lessons ]
What are you talking about
Then you move like this
ah like that
yes yes..yes yes...just like that
That'll give you a better swing
I've had enough...can we end this?
[ Graduates from golf ]
What? You'll never become a women's pro golfer like this
Why are you taking my dad's side on this?
Because its your father's dream
Who cares about that...this is so truly embarrassing right now
Hey I'm telling you...you've got good athletic skills
[ Make papa's dream come true! ]
Next its the hopes of Yamashita mama
This is from okaasan
I'd like us to go together on an extended vacation
Sometimes we'll do 1 night trips
we look for a nice hotel and make reservations
the pictures and such fill me with excitement on the days leading up
when the day comes to pick her up for the trip
Yamashita sleeps in till almost noon
by the time I meet my daughter its far too late for departure
all the tourist spots I had researched beforehand
I've never gotten a chance to actually check them out
The outdoor bath with the magnificent views
by the time we took our bath it was pitch dark
I couldn't see anything!
If she can make time into her schedule I'd like us to have a nice relaxing trip
now I understand
That's what she says
hai....
So this....
[ Not my problem? ]
Don't just say "hai" to that
But they give you some vacation over New Years don't they?
I guess so
How much time is your mother asking for?
Maybe she's asking you to take a year off to go around the world
[ Full on backpacker? ]
Do you have talks about where you'd like to travel?
She really enjoys travel
ever since I was little
she'd take me to all kinds of places
But since joining Nogizaka
days off are maybe only 1 or 2 days
so we don't travel much anymore
I'll work really hard in Nogizaka
and give her a present
That's right
nice story
Next its the hopes of the Akimoto family
eh Akimoto
hai
Its from your little brother
My brother?
Ever since I was little
I've wanted to start a business with her
start a business?
hai
I've been thinking about wanting to work with her
Plus he's thought about it since he was little
Together with my sister that I've always loved
my dream is to put in the hard effort as we work side by side
eh mega kowai
I haven't mentioned this yet to my sister so
I'm not sure whether she'll like the idea or not
If this dream were to come true I wouldn't need anything else in the world
ehhh~
kawaii
Please come and work with me
What is this?
However...
I would be company president
I think he slipped a joke in there
That sounds super cute
You sure that's my brother?
Age?
He's 23
Then he's serious about this
eh but still
Ever have this conversation before?
Not even once
But he wrote about wanting this since he was little
Since he was little? That's got to be a lie
no no
That's not the little brother that I know
He wrote "my dream is to put in the hard effort as we work side by side"
heh?
What's he talking about...
Why are you blushing? Its a good thing
That can't be....did my brother really say this?
He really loves his big sister
You're the sister he's always loved
uwah...that reeks of lies
no no...he even wrote it down for us
What's your brother doing now?
Right now this is his first year with a real job
Perhaps he hates his job?
[ Low job satisfaction? ]
Forget this job...I'd rather work with my sister