DON!
And Nogizaka Under Construction is underway
we are your hosts Bananaman
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
And they are Nogizaka-chan
hai kawaii
hai kawaii....hai kawaii kawaii kawaii
We're not losing
weak
So weak
And with that
Right away please announce whats on the show
Generation Gap Battle
That's right
We've got them all sitting by age generation today
Nogizaka46
in order to be loved across several generations
tonight using trivia that varies from generation to generation
they'll play a quiz game for us
This will allow them to interact with any generation
the final goal is to become all generation idols
This time you've been split into 3 teams
The teenager team
ah good one....fresh
fresh
In the middle team
So these are the members stuck in the middle then
eh Veteran Team
well this is just as expected
Shinuchi is 28 isn't she
Are you the oldest then?
yes I'm 28
Shinuchi's sense of composure is quite amazing
[ senior type of presence ]
This happened when I reached my late 20s
when I hear my age its like..."ah I'm really getting up there"
That's right...for us
its just like that
Well the 2 of us are seriously crappy old men now
The crap really goes flying
[ crap juices ]
Himura-san can't see anything close up or far away
Himura-san...like with his phone
he doesn't squint his eyes...Himura-san
he's the type to bulge out his eyes
Its really messed up...it looks like this
[ The staredown ]
So when he eats a parfait he can't see the inside of it
Yet he still wants to eat parfaits
The parfaits...I just want to see what's inside
When you're old you can't see the inside of a parfait
Also for this one we'll be playing too
We're playing?
We've got our own button
We're going to be the age 40+ team
Nobody with ages in between?
I wouldn't say that
[  As long as you're here ]
Himura-san explain what we're doing
onegaishimasu
Generation Gap
Name that tune quiz
The different generations
have been separated according to difficulty and points
and they'll play the Name That Tune Quiz
By the way to give everyone a chance
there's a Nogizaka46 category that is limited to just 10 points
Some of you here likely know how strong we are at naming Nogizaka songs
Its just that in our case
we don't know several of the song titles
much like last time...as long as we can sing it we'll pass
That's a special rule for us
sorry to have to do that
The members will occasionally sub out
right away lets get the Generation Gap name that tune quiz started
Which girls are strong at name that tune?
Kubo is powerful at naming Nogizaka songs right?
That's right...doesn't feel like I can lose
Didn't you win this last time?
I won
You sure we didn't win that?
So that was completely unfair!
What part was unfair?
I can't let that slide
At the time I had the lead
then suddenly we get BO0WY's B-Blue song
[ The B-Blue incident ]
Everyone answered assuming it was a Nogizaka song
Even though it was a Nogizaka song category
But still everyone knows B-Blue
[ A song that spans all generations ]
You're being silly
But with the 90s
huh? Were some of you born in the 90s?
That's right
But you'd have been very little
right...didn't hear any 90s songs
But that team wasn't born yet?
ah the teenagers were born after 2000
sugoi
90s songs would be old time classic songs for them
Well lets have the teenager team pick the first category
So then
for the 1st one
songs of the 2010s
for 10 points
Starting now its serious competition
Let's get started
Question...onegaishimasu
Please name this song
What?! It didn't get through
Zen Zen Zense
[ Zen Zen Zense / Radwimps (2016) ]
You totally knew that one
[ Totally easy ]
Everyone pressed the button?
I'm sure I was faster
Saw the movie too?
I did see the movie
ahh I wanted to answer that one
You answered correctly so pick again
The teenager team
How about the 90s songs?
But Saku-chan knows a lot of musical artists
90s songs for 10 points
Good one...I'm thankful...90s songs
question....onegaishimasu
Please name the song
eh? But I pressed the button
Why can't we get through
Why can't we answer?
You've got this
If time runs out we move to a different team
You know its that song
Running out of time
its...its...
There is a time limit!
So for this...
I have to say the title?
You have to tell us the song title
Asuka-chan hurry!
The moment their time runs out
this should go on to another team
YES!
May I?
Mr. Children right
Mr. Children's
Innocent....Tomorrow...
[ Can't believe they messed up ]
Which song?
Wait a second...wait
what? what? what? what? what?
Mr. Children-san's Tomorrow Never Knows
They stole it from us!
[ Painful miss ]
gomen...I thought it was [Innocent World]
Good answer...who knew that one?
ahh...so you didn't know the title at first
I didn't know...that's correct
ah you did well...we basically told you the answer
I messed that up
Next its songs of the 2000s for 10 points
Please name this song
[ Can't seem to think of the title ]
Can't quite remember the title right now
hey the button pressing is too loud
[ Everybody just relax ]
Hurry! Hurry!
Yes I do have a nice watch
[ connoisseur of high quality watches ]
ok..ok...here goes....I'll answer
This is Kobukuro's
Sakura!
[ Sakura / Kobukuro (2005) ]
Sakura
You really got that from the intro?
Of course!
We truly love Name that tune Quizzes
[ Name that tune oniisans ]
We got 1
Here Bananaman selects the Nogizaka46 category
That's your line!
ah I'm supposed to say that
I have to move this forward...
[ Absorbed in the quiz ]
Now then the question.....onegaishimasu
Please name this song
Could have got that one
I know that one...could have had it
Offshore Girl
[ Offshore Girl (2016/15th) ]
That's a Shiraishi song
hai
You knew it
Now its all tied up
All tied up then? ok I see
Here there's a member change
Next its songs from the 2000s for 20 points
This is a super short intro quiz
Please name the song
Get it wrong! Get it wrong! Get it wrong!
eh here it goes
Orange Range's
Hana
[ Hana / Orange Range (2004) ]
I'm so happy
so happy
[ All serious ]
Next they pick
songs from the 2010s for 20 points
This is a super short intro quiz
Please name the song
ah as expected the teenager team got it first
Lemon
[ Lemon / Yonezu Kenshi (2018) ]
Did you know it instantly?
How does the rest go?
ah just from the singing you can figure it out
ah now I get it
I could have answered with this
The middle team is all fired up...what's the matter?
ah well...
It was super funny when Chidori-san sang this
[ Her review of TV Chidori ]
That has nothing to do with this
Here the teenagers selected
the Nogizaka category
Please name the song
AHHH!
We got it!
TEN TEN TEN TE TE TEN~
Its that song
I know the name of this song
Nogizaka46's
Synchronicity
That's wrong?
wait what? Hold on
We were wrong?
Its not TEN TEN TEN~
That sounds like it...it matches?
Matches the singing
DA DA DAH DAH DAH right?
[ That's the A verse ]
So its not Synchronicity
That's wrong...gomennasai
Is it the Kaerimichi song?
[ That's wrong too ]
ah Veteran Team....dozo
Yoakemade Tsuyogaranakutemoii
[ Yoakemade Tsuyogaranakutemoii (2019/24th) ]
That's right...the recent one
yes...DE RE RE RE TEN right
I'm just pretending I didn't know it
[ That would be upsetting ]
Our answer was good enough...didn't have to say the title
[ Arrogantly answered incorrectly ]
Coming up they'll try the 30 point questions
and the name that tune quiz will instantly heat up
How will this super competitive generation battle turn out?
Hori...you're already 23 then?
hai
The way she said "hai" just now sounded very ladylike
How old were you Hori when we first met?
ah you were age 8?
I was 16
Here the Veteran Team
selected the very first 30 point question
So its a 30 point question
Here comes a mic
Are we singing?
Question....onegaishimasu
This is a sing it out quiz
Sing it out quiz
Listen to the intro...the team that presses the button first
must come up front
and sing the intro using the correct lyrics to get the points
And now the question
Totally got this one
I can't...I don't know this one
kimi yo zutto shiawase ni~
kaze ni sotto utau yo~
ooooh yeah~
[ Sakura Zaka / Fukuyama Masaharu (2000) ]
Sakura Zaka
That's pretty scary going up there
Mess up the lyrics and its a wrong answer
That song was from the 2000s then?
Sakura Zaka
[Mirai Nikki]
[Mirai Nikki] brings back memories
Now then
what now? How about 90s songs for 30?
We'll definitely get this one
Yes we're doing this to win
[ Legit choice ]
question....onegaishimasu
This is a sing it out quiz
And now...the question
Love this one!
[ Yuzu != Banana ]
chuushajou no neko wa~
akubi wo shinagara~
[ Natsuiro / Yuzu (1998) ]
Yuzu Yuzu
Wasn't that their debut song?
YAAY!
We got both those 30 point questions pretty easy
Check it out...we got a huge lead
eh the 40+ team has 90 points right now
Here Bananaman selects the Nogizaka category
Please name the song
ahhhh...hai dozo
Nandome no Aozora ka?
[ Nandome no Aozora ka? (2014/10th ) ]
So that came out in 2014?
The one where you climbed Mt. Fuji
Here there's another member change
Next its a song from the 2000s for 30
This is a sing it out quiz
And now...the question
Now then please sing along with the song
When does the singing part start?
Definitely could have got this one
I've got it!
ah I want to sing this one
sure chigau toki no naka de~
ah the song Everything
What happened just now?
I was wrong...that was close
I nearly humiliated myself...
That was close....you thought it was something different didn't you?
I did...I was thinking about singing it passionately
nee doushite sugoku~
Dreams Come True..you thought it was them
[ Love Love Love ]
That's why when she started singing
you mashed that button
[ Only created a nuisance ]
Middle team...
A song from the 2010s
for 30
Song from the 2010s for 30
This is a sing it out quiz
and now...the question
ah they got it
Veteran Team
eh what is this song?
ahh I've heard this song
What was it?
"arigatou" ~tte tsutaetakute~
anata wo~
[ arigatou / Ikimonogakari (2010) ]
No doubt about that one
Himura-san knew that one
All of you knew then
Your button didn't get through
You didn't make it
It didn't get through
It works
[ Lost faith in the button ]
When you think "does this button work" it always works
Want to try 90s songs for 30?
90s songs for 30!
This is a sing it out quiz
And now the question
Please let us have this! Let us have this!
please! please! please!
This is his song!
Its his go to song
You better hurry up
please! please! please!
Please let us have this one!
Please let us have it
That's his song!
Himura-san they have to go up front...
That's his song
nandemonai youna~
please! please!
We lost? This can't be
Please let us have this one
choudo ichinen mae ni~
ano michi wo totta yoru~
What did you sing just now?
choudo ichinen mae ni~
ah which one was it?
[ Can't get through ]
OY! Hand it over!
OY! Hand it over
Give this to us!
Why is this?
choudo ichinen mae ni~
ano michi no~
Got it!
[ Persistence ]
Its the real thing
This is your song...
Shitara-san this is your song
This is not my song...I just sing this regularly at karaoke
Sing it good for us
choudo ichinen mae ni~
kono michi wo totta yoru~
[ Road / THE Tra-Bryu (1993) ]
The lyrics are "kono michi"
ok then
I really don't know this song
That's a tricky one
I'm exhausted
so tired
Lets do a Nogizaka song for 10 real quick
[ Take a rest with some Nogizaka ]
Now then the question.....onegaishimasu
Please name the song
That was fast!
DAH DAH DAH DAH DAH DADDAH DADDAH~
sugoi
[ Taiyou ni Kudokarete (2016/2nd album) ]
I know the song
You liked this one didn't you
Not sure what you're singing though
What's the title?
Taiyou ni Kudokarete
Taiyou ni Kudokarete then
sugoi~
It sure is
I think I know all of them
[ That's what makes them the official oniichans ]
Bananaman has all the momentum and are running away with it
can the members make a comeback?
Once again the members will substitute out
Next its songs from the 2000s for 20
This is a super short intro quiz
Please name the song
The middle team got it
ah its the middle team
now then...dozo
Chocolate Disco
[ Chocolate Disco / Perfume (2007) ]
Wish they answered with [Polyrhythm]
Here the middle team
once again go for songs from the 2000s for 30
This is a sing it out quiz
And now the question
ah could have got this one
Could have got this one
ashita kyou yori mo suki ni nareru~
[ Kiseki / GReeeeN (2008) ]
Correct answer...its GReeeeN
GReeeeN's Kiseki
Matsumura you don't know this one?
I really
for some reason
my student years were way too dark and I never heard these kind of popular songs
seriously? what did you listen to?
Back then all I listened to were anime songs
never heard Kiseki-san's GReeeeN
That's GReeeeN's Kiseki
[ miraculously reversed them ]
Why'd you add san to a song title?
Its GReeeN-san's Kiseki
Reversed!
What will you choose?
To win you need a 30
Can you do THE Tra-Bryu songs?
Toryaburyu~
For 30?
songs from the 2010s for 30
2010 songs for 30
This is a sing it out quiz
And now the question
Get it wrong! Get it wrong!
Get it wrong
Sing it wrong!
hitonami no~
itonami no~
[ Koi / Hoshino Gen (2016) ]
The 1st answer was wrong because they said hitonami
I was wondering what part was wrong
It was itonami!
It was itonami
And this is the final question
the teenager team selects...
What will it be?  Nogizaka for 10?
[ Get to the end...go for 10 ]
Songs from the 2010s
for 30 points
ok....OK!
Have to try for 30
That's fine...that's fine
[ Desperate attack? ]
Guess the right song here and I'll give you 100
[ Big chance ]
The last one is a sing it out question
which team will win it?
And the question.....onegaishimasu
This is a sing it out quiz
And now the question
ganbare!
ganbare! You can do this
doushite~
kimi ga naku no~
[ Himawari no Yakusoku / Motohiro Hata (2014) ]
From the Doraemon movie
From Hata-san right
ah they were too fast
And that means...ah!
champions
the 40+ team...Bananaman...YAAY
That was entertaining~ she says
Name that tune quizzes are pretty entertaining
I could do that all day
I could do just that for 24 hours
That's basically [DO-RE-MI-FA-DON!]