DON!
Okay, we've started, we're the hosts of Nogizaka Under Construction, Bananaman.
And here are Nogizaka-chan!
Alright then, Himura-san.
Yes.
Please announce our activity for today!
We want tell Hashimoto Nanami about this! The Nogizaka Unfortunate Stories Grand Prix!
As stated, this time, we have here someone who loves unfortunate stories even more than her daily three meals.
In the past, when Ikuta suffered a broken bone and couldn't participate in their hit campaign prayer...
Hashimoto, who loves unfortunate stories, was found heartily laughing by herself.
Well, I do actually find these stories funny...
But I also think that precisely because it's unfortunate, if nobody laughs about these stories,
then they really become unfortunate... Right?
Ah, I see.
So it's laughter that wells up from kindness.
Really now?
Really, really!
So, then, today...
We'll have members share their own unfortunate stories themselves.
And Hashimoto-sensei will judge whether or not these stories are to her liking.
Unfortunate Stories GP Judging Committee Chairperson
Hashimoto Nanami
I see.
Unfortunate
Funny
Not Funny
(Off-putting)
Not Unfortunate
Judging Committee Chairperson Hashimoto will judge whether or not an unfortunate story is funny using this chart...
And at the end, the funniest misfortune will be chosen as the MVF!
So the best one would be here, right?
Unfortunate and funny.
That's right, unfortunate and funny.
And the worst scenario would be that a story is both unfunny and not unfortunate.
Normal story.
So that would be a boring, normal story, huh.
That's the worst.
That's seriously the worst.
So what's important here is that... Your story should not put off Hashimoto-sensei even if it's unfortunate.
Like if it's just too unfortunate.
A merry story would be best.
So you'd prefer merry.
Yes.
Unfortunate Stories Grand Prix. Our top batter is Wada.
The title of her story is: Presents from Guam.
We went to Guam in March, right?
So then I got home and I thought I'd take out the things I bought and opened my luggage bag.
And then, I was surprised to find that my bag had become pure white.
I thought something must have gotten spilled.
When you opened it?
Yes. I thought "Scary~ Scary~".
Ghost story?
Huh?
Huh? Hm?
Was that Inagawa-san just now?
Then when I looked for what got spilled, it was the body cream I bought for myself.
There was really little left of it.
I wondered why... But then I thought I did want to try it, so one day, I looked at it. I wanted to know what it smelled like and all.
And then when I looked at it...
Tester. It was labeled "Tester".
So you ended up buying the tester.
I made a mistake and did I buy the tester?
Ah, wrong words.
Why a question?
"Did I buy it?" What happened?
That's funny.
Once in the middle of your story... Was that Inagawa-san? Inakawa Junji-san.
You said "Scary~", right?
Not "Scary~" but "Scary~ Scary~". You said it twice, right?
That's Inagawa-san's trademark line though.
I did it unconsciously...
Unconsciously, I see.
You alright?
Yes.
An unfortunate story from Guam... How will Hashimoto-sensei rate it?
Between funny and not, it would be on the funny side.
Around here...
Oh! That's kind of good, right?
Pretty good.
Yeah, this is a funny misfortune.
Unfortunate Stories Grand Prix. Next up is Ikuta.
The title is: Skating Lesson Tragedy.
This is a story from when I was in my second grade of elementary school.
At the time, the figure skater Asada Mao-chan was very popular.
I was little then and I admired her.
And then, with all that, there happened to be a poster in my hometown that said "Taking applications for skating classes".
So then I thought I wanted to try this and was going to do so with a friend.
So on the first day, my father was going to be taking me to that class on his bicycle.
So it was close?
Yes.
But I was really, really excited.
I was just so fired up and hyper.
The main focus would be this foot of mine here.
Focus on the foot.
Yes. So as I rode on the bike, I was going "I'm so excited~" and going like this excitedly on our way there.
And this foot here got pulled in with the wheel...
Ow, ow, ow!
She's laughing. She's laughing.
Good rating ❤
She's laughing alright.
Is this the funny part?
And I then broke a bone in my foot.
Again?
Yes.
Broken bone again?
Not so much again as that was the original.
Ah, yes, I see.
She's laughing really hard.
Yes. So then, of course, I couldn't go attend the skating class.
And, from then on, well, I... I've never skated even once.
You've never skated since then.
Never.
It's pretty amazing to break your foot on your way to class.
Yes!
The more recent one where you dropped the detergent was your foot as well, right?
Oh, that one was toe.
And for this time... I mean for the original incident, it was my ankle.
Ankle Fracture
Which ankle?
The left one.
Was it a comminuted fracture for your left ankle?
It wasn't comminuted, but it somehow got broken...
Sounds painful, right?
Sounds terrible.
And you're laughing, right?
She's laughing.
In contrast, Nishino has been trying not to listen anymore.
I'm really bad with stories that involve pain.
So you're bad with painful stories.
It's hard to listen to, right?
Hashimoto-sensei, though, was laughing a lot.
She was already laughing even during the part where Ikuta was waving her legs.
Premonition of fracture
Like "Ah, she's gonna break her bone..."
How long did it take to heal?
Around one year.
I couldn't move freely for that long.
It took a year to heal.
So your foot got caught in a bike and it took a year to heal.
That long? It took that long?
Second grade is a time where kids want to move around a lot too. It was sad, wasn't it?
And what's more... My ankle broke into two pieces then.
Yes. So even now...
And maybe for the rest of my life, I'll have to live with 3 ankles.
3 ankles?
Hole IN one.
What? How can you have 3 ankles?
What do you mean by 3 ankles?
So, I have 2 ankles on my left and then 1 on my right.
Oh, that's what you meant.
Even though the normal total number of ankles is 2...
Ikuta-san, you have 3, right?
I have 3.
There are inner ankle bones too, though.
Oh, yeah.
True!
So... So then totaling them...
I have 5!
5 ankle bones!
Right.
Ikuta's unfortunate story. How will Hashimoto-sensei rate it?
It was really funny... So around here?
Oh, this is quite high!
Amazing.
But according to Hashimoto-sensei, there's still quite a way to go in terms of misfortune.
Not yet that unfortunate.
Not yet.
That's bad. Like how unfortunate would be the max?
Right?
The manager of Konjakuan was there.
POJI-PEACE
( ￣o￣ )
m 0 0 b -2 0 -4 0 -6 0 b -7 0 -8 0 -8 -2 b -8 -2 -8 -2 -8 -2 b -8 -3 -8 -4 -6 -4 b -4 -4 -2 -4 0 -4 b 2 -4 4 -4 6 -4 b 6 -5 6 -7 6 -8 b 6 -8 6 -8 6 -8 b 7 -10 9 -10 10 -9 b 10 -7 10 -7 10 -6 b 12 -4 13 -3 13 -2 b 13 6 13 4 13 7 b 12 8 10 8 8 8 b 7 8 6 8 5 8 b 4 8 3 8 1 7 b 0 5 0 3 0 2
Why is it black? Why is it big?
I'd get asked that.
And why is the one asking stupid?
I got one that's even older.
Unfortunate stories grand prix. The third story is from Wakatsuki.
The title is: Rather Worn Out.
When you have siblings... You usually, well, get their stuff... Like hand-me-downs.
Yes, that happens.
I think most of us has some experience like that... However, my sister happens to be 8 years older.
So then, I get stuff from my sister who is 8 years older.
In elementary school, we use recorders right?
Normally, these recorders are black and white, right?
Yeah.
The one I had was pure white.
So then everyone else had a black and white one and only I had a pure white one.
That's a bad age to be different from everyone else, huh?
People around me would ask, "What happened to the black part?".
That's kind of stupid as well, though, there was never any black in the first place.
"What happened to the black part?"
"Is there no black part?" - It starts with those questions.
Next, back in elementary school, we had those arithmetic sets, didn't we?
Oh yeah, I remember!
Like a tool box of sorts.
Mine was a hand-me-down as well.
And, well, it was 8 years old...
So there were these sticks used for counting.
And we used these sticks to form shapes and stuff.
So, everyone else's was new, of course.
So their sticks could be put together, attached to each other...
But mine could only be lined up.
8-year gap.
They can't be attached.
Yes.
Then, of course, the teacher had the newest model as well.
"Alright everyone, why don't we take these sticks and form a 3-dimensional figure?"
A cruel question.
So 3D, huh?
They can't be attached to each other. They can't form 3D.
So I told the teacher that I could only do flat figures, and I ended up being the only one behind in class.
You should've just taped them together.
Yeah, that was my only choice. So, there was that.
Kind of heartbreaking.
She's reacting. Hashimoto-san's reacting.
She's laughing hard.
"That girl's stuck with flat figures!"
So aside from those, we had a sewing kit in elementary right?
My sewing scissors were clearly bigger than others.
It was all rusted and kind of black too.
And on top of that, it didn't match the size of my sewing kit so it would protrude out of the box.
It wouldn't fit.
So then, I got questions again. "Why is that black? Why is it big?".
And why is the one asking stupid?
What's with that person?
I replied "Ah, I don't know, but somehow it's big and black..."
But I thought the worst one was the Melodion one.
Melodion?
Oh, I guess that's not what it's usually called... I meant the key harmonica.
Oh... Ah, you mean pianica.
You call that melodion?
Yes, we call it melodion.
Seriously?
What the heck's a melodion?
Amazing, huh?
Yes, melodion.
Melodion.
You play it like this, right?
Yes. For the melodion, I probably got the one from my brother.
So, it had his name written at the back in large characters.
And when I looked at it more closely, the the part you put in your mouth had bite marks.
Ah! Inoue's making a face!
He was a guy, so I guess he bit it.
It had lots of bite marks.
I was quite troubled, and in the end, I did get a new one bought for me... Just the part here.
Limited to replacement parts.
Oh, so just that part? What about the main body?
Oh, well, the main part was still usable so I was told to just keep using it.
So then I became a middle school student. I went to the same middle school as my older sister.
So I wore my sister's uniform...
Eh? Your school uniform too?
Yes.
Well, 8 years have passed, so it was a bit different.
So during the opening ceremony, someone asked me... "Hey, the cloth of your uniform... Isn't it kinda' thin?"
The Nasty Classmate
That... That friend kinda keeps hitting the marks... What's up with him?
Is that the same person?
An awful person keeps appearing.
"Your buttons... Aren't they kinda' big?" - things like that.
So there were small changes?
Yeah, there were small changes, like whether there was a lining or not and all.
There were changes like that, and I kept getting asked about it.
You kept getting hand-me-downs huh.
So it's like that.
I guess that happens often when you have older siblings.
Yeah.
Back in elementary school, I also suddenly got a hand-me-down for my bag.
I didn't like it!
Everyone else had shiny new ones and only I got a used one.
I really didn't like it. So, even though I was a child, I cut this part here...
Cause, well, if it got damaged then I could get a new one, right?
And then I got an even older one from a relative!
Failed strategy.
Well, that's unfortunate!
It is.
That one just now is around here, right?
Here, right?
When I think about it now, it's really no big deal, but at that time, I just hated it.
Yeah.
Hand-me-downs.
Wakatsuki's unfortunate story. How will Hashimoto-sensei rate it?
Then...
So this is full... Is it higher?
A bit.
So a little bit higher than Ikuta? Oh, you did it.
The funny factor was really high.
Really high.
There are six years in elementary school, right?
There are teachers who are around for those entire six years, right?
Yes.
I guess there could've been teachers who kept seeing Wakatsuki from first grade...
And probably thought... "That girl's things are always old huh..."
There's an 8-year gap, after all.
"That girl keeps getting weird things."
Like that...
That's bad huh.
Teachers won't be thinking that, would they?
That teacher's the worst. Like, "That girl's things are always old."
"In various situations, there's always just this one girl who has a different thing."
That's some amazing laughter right there.
And it's quite old to boot.
That was funny.
Unfortunate stories grand prix. Next up is Takayama.
The title is: The Swing Incident.
Back in elementary... I think I was also in second grade at that time...
I was also? Ah...
Just like other members, around second grade.
Yes.
This is a story around that time. So, I was playing on the swings with my friend.
And there was another friend with us, just watching. There were only 2 swings.
So, just playing on the swings were kinda' not enough for us...
So, it has those rings, right? So, those rings...
The ones here?
Yes, those.
The links, you mean?
So we kinda' crumpled those links together, then let go.
Yeah, we did that too.
We did that!
It's like you roll them up.
Yeah.
Sure, we did that.
So we did that, crumpling them and letting go. And we had fun.
So then, somehow, only my swing went back to normal, and my friend's just stayed like that.
So we thought it would just get fixed and we went home, leaving it like that.
The next morning, during the morning assembly...
A teacher said "Everyone, I have something to talk about with you. Yesterday, the swing got broken."
"Did someone here do it?"
So then I thought "This is bad..."
You guys did it right?
I thought that was us, so, for the time being, I stood up.
Oh, how impressive.
So I stood up. So we were asked "Who broke it?"
It wasn't exactly me...
True.
I was thinking my friend should just say it, and fess up.
Then my friend got up...
"Kazumi-chan did it!"
The Unexpected Betrayal
You got betrayed.
Yeah she said it. Quite strongly too.
And I thought, "Seriously...?"
But, well, I thought I'd tell the truth and said "No, no, no, she did it."
Oh, so you said so? You talked back?
I did, I did.
Then, that friend said, "No! Kazumi-chan did it!"
So it became pointing battle.
Yeah.
You were kids, after all, huh.
After that, our teacher asked the other friend who was with us "Someone-kun, who did it?"
Oh no. Then it'll be that kid's testimony.
Yes. So then, that guy said, "I also saw Kazumi-chan do it!"
Innocent Crime
Why??
Why?
He said that!
Why would he say that?
Why would that boy... I mean he was watching, right?
Probably... I think he lost to that girl's intensity? Her intensity saying she absolutely didn't do it.
Then the teacher also said, "Kazumi-chan, you did it, didn't you?"
So, then, everyone was your enemy?
Yes. That's right.
I thought there was nothing else I could do, so I said, "I'm sorry, I did do it."
That's so sad...
So, back in elementary school, I thought, ah, this is how people who get false charges feel...
A victim of false charges?
You wouldn't really think that at that age...
Well...
Thinking about false charges at that age... pretty amazing.
Did you still get along with your friend after that?
Oh yeah, we get along very well.
Why?
We're really good friends.
Well, we've been together for many years, so our friendship couldn't really get broken over just a swing...
But she completely sold you out.
Well, I guess so...
Takayama's unfortunate story. How will it be rated?
Around here?
Oh, that's quite...?
Pretty high?
Pretty high, I guess?
Yes, yes.
Well, it was quite unfortunate.
Yes. To have experience a mini trial at second grade is quite something.
And everyone ended up becoming her enemy. Depending on the person, it could cause someone to lose trust in others.
I was really glad to hear that you still get along even now.
The manager of Konjakuan was there.
Coming up. Everyone breaks out in laughter while listening to Higuchi's unfortunate story.
Unfortunate Stories Grand Prix. Next up is Kawago.
The title is: "My Alma Matter"
Four years ago, my middle school got closed down.
Oh, so it's gone.
And in February this year, my elementary school got closed down.
Oh?
The end.
End.
So they're gone.
Yes, they're gone.
But, well, I guess the number of schools are decreasing right now.
Yes...
That's sad, huh?
It is.
Sad, huh?
Your alma matter full of memories...
And my kindergarten as well, it's planned to close down in the near future.
What's with that?
What will it be turned to?
I think it'll be a park or something like that.
So the building will be gone, huh?
Are there few children?
Yes. There really were only a few. I think there were seventeen of us.
Seventeen students for the entire elementary school.
For the entire school?
Yes, seventeen for the entire school.
Still. There are lots of other places with even less.
I guess that's a little early?
I guess it's a little early. Middle and elementary school, huh?
Oh, but, my hometown is really out in the sticks, it's Chichibu, Saitama.
So in our high school, students come from all over, and there was...
There was this guy from really deep in the mountains.
While we were in school, he said they would be moving and I asked "Why are you moving?" and he said "Ah, but I'll still be going to school."
He said, "My house is going to sink to the bottom of a dam."
Well, that does happen.
Yes, it does!
Right?
My mother's relative's house got sunk too.
So before it gets sunken, we usually go there to visit graves.
That's quite amazing, right? It's like, the entire place ends up at the bottom of the water.
It disappears.
Yes, from schools to graves.
Even graves?
Yes, the entire village, or entire town... Well, maybe not town...
The entire village is destroyed.
Kawago's sad unfortunate story. How will it be rated?
Around here, I guess.
I see, I see.
You were trying to put it on the other way.
It's not that unfortunate.
It's like Nagasaki is walking towards the future.
Well, it's indeed sad, but putting in feelings of wanting to move forward as well, that's where it is.
Oh. I see.
Unfortunate stories grand prix. The last entry is from Higuchi.
The title is: "Breaking Away from Loneliness"
This happened after a recording of Nogizaka Under Construction.
Oh, so this happened after recording.
Yes. I don't remember what we recorded that day.
But for me, I felt like I wasn't able to do it properly and got quite depressed.
I talked to the manager about it and everyone was going home.
What, something like that happened? What was that time?
So then, when we go home, we ride on a microbus and go home together.
So everyone else went down ahead of me.
I was talking to the manager and finally got my feelings in order and said thank you.
Then she said, "Well then, everyone's waiting for you so why don't you go home."
The manager was going to stay behind so I ran down the stairs alone.
And then, the moment I opened the door...
There was silence and it was totally empty.
Empty?
Well, it seems no one noticed that I wasn't on the bus and it left.
Got left behind.
Wait!
Ah...
So they left, and I thought "Ah, I got left behind..."
It was... just... tears started flowing out. The recording didn't go well too, and now I got left behind by the bus.
You were just so sad.
It feels terrible to get left behind by the bus.
I thought "What a day..."
"What a day!"
Really, I just thought from the bottom of my being "What a day." and so I was crying, and...
So you cried right there?
Yes, but no one was there to help.
That's at the entrance of this studio right? So you cried there?
I did. Then from behind me, I heard a voice asking "What's wrong, Hina?"
Oh, who was it?
When I looked behind me...
The manager of Konjakuan was there.
Studio Restaurant
Konjakuan's Manager
Oh, that guy. That guy's very kind.
Thank goodness.
The manager appears.
So he talked to you.
He asked while smiling what happened and why I was crying so much.
I said while crying that today, the recording didn't go well for me and I got left behind by the bus.
He got angry for me saying, "Really, why would they go and leave you?"
And he stayed and waited for the bus to come around again with me.
So then he stayed with me and saying "It's alright" and gave me 10 pieces of mitarashi dango.
The manager's kindness
That's great, right?
Mitarashi dango?
So he gave you some.
Yes. So that's my unfortunate story.
At the last part, it was a happy ending, right?
So funny!
So the bus came back, right?
Yes.
Higuchi's unfortunate story.
How will Hashimoto-sensei rate it?
Here.
Oh, there?
Oh so the misfortune factor is quite...
Oh, it's quite high?
The funny rating is quite high as well.
Members all have experiences of feeling down over recording sessions.
Oh. So like after these sessions?
During a time like that, being forgotten and getting left behind by everyone would really be quite a blow.
For sure.
That's just sad.
So who will shine with the laurel of the MVF?
Nogizaka Unfortunate Stories Grand Prix. All the entry unfortunate stories have been told.
The funniest unfortunate story... Who will shine as the MVF?
Nogizaka unfortunate stories grand prix's MVF is...
With the story "Rather Worn Out," it's Wakatsuki Yumi!
Wakatsuki. This is just as the chart indicated.
I could kind of feel that Wakatsuki spending her childhood always having to use old hand-me-downs kind of connects to how she is now...
It was really funny.
And being able to talk about it lightheartedly now is good, right?
Yes.
Right?
And, well, listening just now... All of the members' unfortunate stories are things I've experienced as well.
Oh so you could relate?
Iku-chan's too.
There was a time I was really excited after finishing preparations going "Swimming class starts tomorrow!"
On my way there, I got overly excited and raised one of my hands while riding and ended up doing a barrel roll.
And I broke this part here, and half of the bone went on top of the other half.
And I was told I couldn't go anymore the next time.
Oh, you broke your bone...
Because of that I just remembered now...
Back in kindergarten I got overly excited thinking that the next day was going to be our sports festival, and as I pedaled on my bike...
I ran into a light pole and fell over.
And I got hurt on this part here.
You got a cut?
It was more of a scratch.
So the next day, our class won, but in all of our photos I had this short mustache-like mark...
That's funny.
Himura-san, you broke your arm here right before your school trip right?
Uh, the day before my elementary school trip, I played tag with my friends, and well a kid named Oda-chan was it.
And that kid rubbed his nose like this and chased me doing a nasal mucus beam, and getting chased, I ran up to the top of the slide.
And Oda-chan kept chasing me doing this and I got scared, so I fell off from the slide.
And bang! And this part here got broken like this, and I got a cast like this...
And in all the photos where we did the peace sign I was like this.
All. All of my photos were like this.
It got recorded as memories.
POJI-PEACE
( ￣o￣ )
m 0 0 b -2 0 -4 0 -6 0 b -7 0 -8 0 -8 -2 b -8 -2 -8 -2 -8 -2 b -8 -3 -8 -4 -6 -4 b -4 -4 -2 -4 0 -4 b 2 -4 4 -4 6 -4 b 6 -5 6 -7 6 -8 b 6 -8 6 -8 6 -8 b 7 -10 9 -10 10 -9 b 10 -7 10 -7 10 -6 b 12 -4 13 -3 13 -2 b 13 6 13 4 13 7 b 12 8 10 8 8 8 b 7 8 6 8 5 8 b 4 8 3 8 1 7 b 0 5 0 3 0 2