TechiNeru46.blogspot.com
TL+Timing: TechiNeru46
Translated to English: Yuuki
Checker: TomoParu
Uploader: MonakaRisao
Let us show our efforts
Nogizaka46 has been established for 4 years
Outside of their views ..
What do they see?
There is no great burden for Nogizaka,
and certainly builds better responsibilities
Thinking seriously
about the future
Nogizaka46
Thinking about how to make Nogizaka more famous in the country
With the entry of the second generation
does this have a positive impact?
I'm not entirely confident
NOGIBINGO! 5
This is the last episode of NOGIBINGO 5
So far we have done a lot of fun
Today we planned a serious episode
Today, we hope Nogizaka46
Thinking about the future seriously and carefully
The first theme is
How is the growth of this Nogizaka46 group?
Ikoma Rina said from the bottom of heart
I think we need to go back to the beginning of the heart
and think of many things from ourselves
Experiencing many failures
If we can expand the field that we can do, I think it's very good
We need to go back to the heart and think of many things from ourselves
What does it mean?
Yes, this group has been standing for four years
Form some kind of "habit"
I can do that things, I'm not good do that things.
Habits like this come out by itself
But that is not good on things that are much more challenging
Always explore your own desires
The whole summer tour should be attended but not a word spoken yet
Although it allows everyone to speak
But not heading in the right direction
I think we should add an opportunity like this
In front of everyone, some can not say their own views
LIVE's opinion was also presented by Ikoma
I often express opinions
My own words can not be expressed in my heart and mind
Even if I want to say it now.
that makes me more hestitate to say it
Really?
Like, I can't comment on LIVE
Must speak in front of many people
Of course. I want to make an opinion that have a positive impact
Every thought is always hidden
The most important is to let your voice out
I was thinking of building Nogizaka at the top level
For example, when LIVE is underway
What needs to be improved and more
Therefore I must express this views
So for me
There is no great burden for Nogizaka, and certainly builds better responsibilities
If you can not express your opinion
You should be able to assume this responsibility
So true
Before expressing their opinions, they tend to hide in the corner
As expected, everyone thought, ah-there must be someone expressing their opinion  so I think it's okay
Ideas such as these always arise
I hope we have a sense of crisis
Contribute our strength to make Nogizaka better
I want to share and think about how to make Nogizaka become more famous in this country
Now we have more opportunities to work outside
For the group, we must bring these outside work experience
And share this experience with members
Ikomachan is very good at expressing his opinion
So we often ask her to convey our thoughts
I really think I should learn to express my own thoughts
Sounds good
Minami grew up a bit
She had a lot of ideas and then told me about it
Already growing
The next theme is about LIVE from Nogizaka46
Overflowing performances
Nogizaka 46 should sweat more drips
Dancing with annoying bangs
Trying hard to keep singing
Hopefully our performance can make the song Nogizaka46 resonate in the hearts of everyone
As expected, for idol, LIVE is very important
I would appreciate as a group if you attend LIVE
In the summer of this year
Dance with the dance teacher, starting from the beginning of the stretch
Also ask the teacher to sing with me, to correct it
Trying to strengthen these basic skills
We have to start this summer
(So) current strength is not enough
I used to be very concerned with my bangs
Even at LIVE
Like how to keep my bangs so it do not become a mess when dancing
Really? - Yes it is
I have the same thoughts with Himetan, when Under LIVE
Everyone breaks a lot of sweat
Fans is also very excited
I also feel it's cool
But of course, I know it's different
Next is about the relationship of first and second generation Nogizaka46
First generation, Akimoto Manatsu gave advice to the second generation
Nogizaka has a harmonious impression
We have some mistakes too
If the first gen remains the same, the second gen will be disrupted and this is a danger
A lot of feelings that arise
So second gen is more highlighted, it's okay
I always say it
That's right, what do you think Karin?
When the announcement of senbatsu for the next single, none of the second generation is selected
The second generation has been able to match the first generation
With the entry of the second generation
does this have a positive impact?
It feels the power of today is still very weak
She said if there were no direct competition
There is no such feelings like "Restraining Yourself"
This becomes a question
There must still be a tenuous relationship between first generation and second generation
Ikuta, What's there that you want to say?
That's right, when the second generation comes in, there's a gap between us
But, it is certain that I am older than Karin and Mai, immediately call me Ikuchan
And not just in front of everyone
Personally how to get rid of these tenseness is very important
And thoughts like this are out of their own accord
So I think we should talk more with second generation
Recently (second generation) told a lot of story too
Who has just recently told the story?
Recently it is Miria-chan
When we sat together in bus, we talk a lot
I'm thinking "ah we really can talk to each other"
Hashimoto, have you ever talked to or talked about something with second generation?
I have spoken to all second generations, except Ayane
Ayane is the type of person who you can talk to but does not reply to it
I understand, I understand
-Maybe she's nervous
She was very tense so when she try to reply, her voice did not come out
But Miria and Ranze often talked
with me and came to me
When I have some free time too
I happen to be in between first generation and second generation
I did not get into three singles at the time
Straight into the fourth single
In my heart I always feel like 1.5 generation
So when the second generation comes in
My mind always says, I do not want them in
Recently I have forgotten this gradually
Now I remember it again
As the only 1.5 generation, I want to create a relaxed atmosphere
Finally, a very important person sends a shocking message
After this, tears can not stop
I will try
All members of Nogizaka46
This from a very important person, has sent a voice message
First voice message from Akimoto Manatsu's mother
When Manatsu says she wants to go to Nogizaka46
Mother is very worried
Worried that the world of entertainment is a terrible place
It would be very quiet without Manatsu
Plus I want Manatsu to be a happy ordinary person
But looking at your enthusiasm
So we decided to support you
Manatsu is very grateful to fans who always support you right?
Then you ask "Really?"
She said, "If I do not think about myself then it means nothing"
This is from the depths of your heart
I am very proud of Manatsu
If you already feel reach your limits
Make sure you go back home
If something goes wrong, you can tell anything to mother
What Manatsu wants to do, do as you wish
Do your best, Manatsu!
It's from your mother right? - I was surprised
My mother said it well
Next message from Ikoma Rina's father
To Rina
Looking at your situation now
That you work so hard from the bottom of your heart, that surprised me
After entering high school, there happened to be auditions of Nogizaka46
And I tell you to just try it
Now, if I think about it again ..
I brought you there
I feel a little sorry for you
After entering Nogizaka46
You cry desperately while organizing
activities
Your mother listened to your complaints
I accept this fact
You invited us to the concert
Until then, you show us your great leadership
Dad is very grateful
Rina should go to explore things that Rina wants
And then find what you really want
I hope you can make every effort to achieve that goal
I will always support you, do your best!
That was a message from Ikomachan's father
Message from Eto Misa's mother
Misa always hope that Nogizaka46 can be a big and great group
Misa always says "I will always try hard in Nogizaka"
Feelings like that I like it very much
I feel Misachan
She wants to make
In order for Nogizaka46 to be a famous group and known by everyone in japan
Please always support Misa and Nogizaka46
A message from Nishino's father
Nana did not have any confidence
So that Nana can have a will in facing a challenge
Papa and Mama suggested to audition for Nogizaka46, but
Nana initially seemed not interested
But, for a long time you want to enter
Papa is very happy
When you were elected, we were all very surprised
But Papa has a feeling you will definitely get through
After entering, every day back and forth from Osaka-Tokyo with Papa
Though difficult, we strive to survive
It has been four years since that time
Nana accumulated a lot of experience
Recently, slowly you gain some self-confidence
Nana's growth goes far beyond Papa's imagination, Papa is very proud of you
In the future, please show us a smile as you go
I will always support you
Message from Takayama's best friend
Takayama told me that she passed the final audition
I think that "it really happened."
Recently my friend said "I know Kazumin"
It makes me happy
While at LIVE, fans is holding a Takayama oshimen towel
It really makes me feel so happy
Although we do not always discuss about Nogizaka
But I think it's good that Takayama can do what you want to do
Do your best, I will always support you
Very grateful, I was very surprised
Message from Sakurai Reika's mother
Reika told me that she wanted to audition for Nogizaka46
Honestly I am surprised
Now Reika is the captain of Nogizaka46
But being a captain is not an easy thing
I know that her character makes her unable to be a "captain's leader"
4 years, find out how to be a good captain and worry about others too
Often cry
However Reika spent four years to
build the image of a captain who has a unique style
Captain like that, I feel is a very good captain
You also become stronger than ever
You are working very hard, aren't you
From now on I hope you as "captain of Nogizaka46 Sakurai Reika"
I want you to keep up the spirit
So that's it
Sakurai-san
How is the voice message from your mother?
Shocked no matter what
I'm not entirely confident
This group is growing continuously
(Captain) can not always lead the whole group in order to progress
Captain should become more reliable
But I have no way to be a captain that everyone imagines
It is sometimes difficult to discuss with members
So sometimes I approach Mom and cry and tell her
Isn't it good to be confident?
I will try hard
Staff NOGIBINGO! From now on will continue to support Captain Nogizaka46 Sakurai
NOGIROOM!
TechiNeru46.blogspot.com
Sorry, No Sub For NogiRoom
The letter this time was unexpected from that person
It's from Ijirisan
For Nogizaka46. Thank you for your hard work at NOGIBINGO! 5
Letter from Official Grandpa? And a message of gratitude from Ikoma Rina can be seen in Hulu
NOGIBINGO!6 We will definitely do it
The 2016 Nogizaka46 Blu-ray and DVD has been determined