When I saw people wearing black, I got the feeling that we were all heading towards the same place
It was a strange yet familiar feeling
It's like being a kid inside a bus while heading to the public pool,
feeling that everyone around me is also going to the pool.
That sensation
Ari no Koto
I was part of a 5-member idol group
The group's name was Udagawa White Bears
It was often teased for sounding like a boys baseball team
It's been a year since disbandment
We weren't really that popular anyways
Our center's withdrawal decided our fate
Us that were left behind tried our best to continue for a while,
but the final live went in shambles and ended miserably.
Ari!
It's been awhile! Doing well?
Yeah! Looks like Sumi took the same train
I made a mistake and just rushed in the train
Me too
Somehow you look like an adult now
Really?
I haven't changed at all though
Maybe it's because you're wearing black
So are you!
That's true
It's been awhile!
It's been awhile
Sorry for being late
It's fine. It's nice to see you both of you
Have you been well?
Do you have a safety pin?
Her blazer got a rip on the back
Unbelievable right? It's been so long and she tears her clothes
How did this even happen?
I don't know, I just rode the train as usual though
I brought one with me
Really? Nice!
So Samu lived in this kind of area
But it's way off where you'd expect Samu to live right?
That's true
Thanks
Let's ride a taxi?
I say that but there seems to be none
It looks like we can walk it though
-Really?
I searched it up awhile ago and it's around 15 minutes away
As expected of you
It seems to be that way
Then let's head that way
-Let's go
It's just pitch black
There's nothing in sight at all
It's already late after all
The names we go may be weird to others
But they come from parts of our names
My name is Arimoto, hence Ari
Sumi is Hasumi
Kimu is Kimura
Momo is Momoko
But Samu is the only exception
Even though the name Ito Chika does not contain "samu" anywhere
but for some reason, we called her Samu
That Samu, 2 days ago
on the way home from buying something
got hit by a truck and passed away
We were lucky we found a taxi.
Who would've known that we were going the wrong way
Seriously
What happens again in funerals?
It's a wake, not a funeral
I don't know either way
First light an incense, and then give the family your condolences
What exactly do I have to say?
We learned of her death only last night
So everyone looked for clothes in a rush,
not having any mourning dresses at hand, it was really rude
Isn't the cabinet smell bad?
Really?
I just borrowed this from my mom
There's a big shoulder pad inside
Are you Hirano Nora?
But actually my clothes aren't even black, just navy blue
Will it be noticed?
It's night so it should be fine
Ari's clothes look cute right?
I bought it for when my relative had a wedding
I wonder if this is too flashy
Isn't that fine? It shows your grievance for the family
There's a loose thread at the back of your stockings though
Really? Oh no!
Why are your clothes so easy to tear?
How much will you put in the goshugi?
TL note: goshugi is an envelope with money, given as gifts in weddings
okoden is the proper term for condolence money
It's not goshugi. it's okoden
I'm giving 20,000
I only put in 10,000
Also it's bad to have the first number be divisible by 2
That's goshugi
Actually, recently having it at 2 is like saying "Best of wishes to the both of you"
I already told you, that's for goshugi
We won't be accepting any offerings
But....even if you say that
Your thoughts and feelings are enough
I'll guide you inside
It's like we've earned something
Why don't you use it to repair your phone's screen
I wonder if Komiyama-san came by
I don't think so
I mean for a manager, Komiyama-san is a no-show when he's needed
I'll be calling them over, so please wait here
Onii-san, it looks like Chika's friends are here to see her
Thank you for coming all the way out here today on such a short notice
Please go ahead and light some incense
Samu's wake is empty
We probably came too late that's why everyone's already gone but,
even though we are lamenting the death of Samu,
the emptiness just doesn't feel right.
You're all from Udagawa White Bears right?
Yes
Thank you for coming despite your busy schedules
Please go take a look at her face
Samu's.....already dead
I want to put something for her to be buried with, is it fine?
As long as it is something that can be burned
Samu liked this after all
No wait a moment
Samu liked Takenoko no Sato, you got it wrong
TL note: bamboo shoot-shaped and mushroom-shaped chocolate by Meiji
takenoko = bamboo shoot | kinoko = mushroom
It was Kinoko no Yama
I heard it was Choco Baby though
TL note: other Meiji chocolate products
No, it's Apollo
Any will do
It's not like she'll really be able to eat it
She might be able to in heaven
If it's heaven, then everything's there
There's no reason to specially take anything with her going there
I can get anything in heaven?
That's what heaven is after all, you can eat and drink anything
Wait, heaven is above the clouds
There's no way food would be there
Above the clouds?
My grandmother told me the people above that have nothing there just watch us, the ones below
Always?
While snickering, they watch our daily lives
All day long?
Rather than a day, more like year-long?
I wouldnt be able to do that if that was me
Isn't that just hell then?
Those kinds of feelings would disappear, if you're in heaven
Like being paralyzed?
Yeah, like being given anesthesia
Anesthesia?
Somehow, heaven feels scary
Please help yourselves to the food
Thank you very much
-Take your time
I kinda feel sorry for looking like we came here to eat
But not eating would be rude too
We really are hungry after all
Well then
Sorry, I won't be drinking
Sumi, could you pass the orange juice?
I didn't know alcohol was a no-go for you
Was the person awhile ago Samu's brother?
Probably
Wasn't he kinda cool?
I thought so too
A handsome guy with defined features
Seems like a beard would fit him right?
-Definitely
Like Mouri Kogoro
A moustache?
-I was thinking more of on the chin
Like (Daisuke) Jigen's?
No, shorter than that
Then, (Vinsmoke) Sanji's?
It's the one where it's connected from side to chin
Like Heidi's grandpa
That's a big beard, plus his hair's white
Like that but black
You must like those types a lot Ari
I get what you mean
Ari's always been attracted by looks alone
I like those that have really big beards
If I were to tell the truth,
I don't have an interest in boys
Keep your hands in sync
Then, I'll be checking on each one of you
Keeping up?
Let's try it again?
It's hard isn't it?
-Yeah, it is
Nice and easy okay?
I'd find myself looking at girls ever since I was a kid
My romantic delusions also involved girls
I thought to myself that it was weird, so I kept it a secret from others
Then let's proceed to the next cut
- Got it
Then for the next cut, hold on to Samu who will be in the middle,
and then Kimu to Momo,
and Ari to Sumi, hug your partner from behind
Ari go to your position too
Get closer
Hold on tight
What's wrong?
Is it fine if we switch places?
I don't really mind
There
Sorry
It's fine. I might sweat a lot
What's wrong?
Sumi's feeling sick
She's getting feverish
You should get some rest
How is she? I brought a fever pad
Still sleeping
She looks like she's in pain
Yeah
Looking at her closely, Sumi really is pretty right?
Her face is small, and her eyelashes are long after all
Is that so?
Komiyama-san still can't come
He's always away when he's needed
Is she okay?
I thought "So Samu was the same"
I also kept that as a secret
Hey, could we talk for a moment?
What is it?
Come over here
So you know...
is what happened awhile ago like that?
By that you mean..?
What you did to Sumi
The kiss
I did kiss her
Are you like that too?
Like that..?
You like women..?
Do I have to answer?
If possible, I'd like you to
Then I'll tell you
Not at all
The LGBT give off a fashionable sense right?
I thought it would've been better if I was
It's impossible
My heart doesn't go crazy for girls
I have always worried that I am weird
That being found out spelled the end for me
And here she goes talking about fashion sense
Is that all? Let's go back
About this...
Don't tell anyone about it
What was that for?
It really is impossible
I don't feel anything at all
More than a sauce face, shouldn't it be a ketchup face?
TL note: sauce face = western(/sharp/defined) facial features
ketchup face = a little less defined than sauce faces
Sauce in this case is worcestershire, and ketchup is strong but still milder in taste than worcestershire, hence the analogy
Ketchup?
It's strong like sauce, but a little more refreshing
Ketchup isn't really refreshing though
She really was a mysterious girl
Kissing others for no reason
Not thinking about the trouble her strange reasons may cause to the people around her
At the time of her death, disappearing by the truck's light
Samu was weird right?
Always doing weird things
I thought she was pretty cold to us
I mean, Samu can come from samui(cold)
I did say that before
She will be cremated tomorrow right?
Don't remind me
I mean isn't being burned horrible?
Being burned directly in a big incinerator
Then what do you prefer we do? A burial?
A burial is kinda scary as well, with the feeling of slowly rotting
Then, a wind funeral?
Wind funeral?
Let the body be taken by the water, in the end to be eaten by birds and other animals
What? That sounds really scary!
Excuse me
Mitsuhishita san wake up, you'll catch a cold
Take a rest upstairs
Sorry about that
Not at all
Thank you for coming, even at this late of a time
I'm Chika's brother
This was...
a very unfortunate passing
It is at this time and going forward
Was there an accident?
Yes but actually there are still things to look into
The case is still under police investigation, with regards to it being an accident
What are they still loking into?
The truck driver is saying
that Chika committed suicide
Suicide?
Samu no Koto