The first annual
Quiz
Sasaki and Suzuki
Nogizaka's two most bizarre members
Sasaki Kotoko and
Suzuki Ayane
What was it like doing that just now?
What do you mean just now?
Acting as a cat
This time
these 2 using a quiz format
we'll thoroughly inspect their behavior
The way these 2 live life
will be revealed!
Let's have today's main characters come out
Sasaki Kotoko-san and
Suzuki Ayane-san
This is amazing right here
The most lavish thing we've had on NOGIBINGO!
That's right
Today
these 2 are our main characters
Suzuki-san.  Tell us your thoughts.
ganbarimasu
Did the mic pick that up?  Are we good?
How about you Sasaki-san?
ganbarimasu
ganbarimasu she says
Wait a moment.  Today
are you more motivated for this today Sasaki-san?
huh?
See you next week!
[ Show over? ]
So let's quickly get into this
would the 2 of you introduce your clip
onegaishimasu
Ready, set
Quiz
Sasaki and Suzuki
and we're off to the location of the 1st quiz question
on the way to the site, when we take some hidden footage
No conversation
much like the driver
she's focused on the road in front of her
Suzuki Ayane
The 1st idea
is a sports test
They're unknown athletic abilities will be examined
This should be good
Possibly a sign of things to come on this episode
its raining
Quickly, lets try asking them their feelings on this
ganbarimasu
That's right.  ganbarimasu
Making them run in the rain
and possibly angering them
thats all they have to say about their feelings
Using radio calisthenics to carefully loosen up their bodies
Its onto the inspection
This time they'll be competing in the 50m dash
We'll have them run a short distance
to measure how fast they are
Its hard to picture these 2 running so
what will happen?
Just to be sure
lets ask again how they're feeling about this
ganbarimasu
After getting that feeling of deja vu
Sasaki starts
but ended up with a poor time of
10.33 seconds
And now its Suzuki Ayane's turn
she's never shown us full-on motivation before
what will her running look like?
It is now Suzuki Ayane's turn
And she's started
A beautiful running form
gradually increasing speed
Suzuki showing this kind of will to win
has never been seen on NOGIBINGO! before
She's at the finish
Let's take a look back on her run
Watch as she switches instantly to her racing stance
And then something you wouldn't imagine from Suzuki
Just what kind of time did she get?
And here is Suzuki-san's time
8.73 seconds
That's fast
Actually
this begins our quiz question
What happens when we have Sasaki hear this voice...
Ko~toko!
Its Kakki
Did you give your all?
Its me.  You know me
If this is Kotoko
I wonder if she'll figure out who I am?
Its Kakki!
What do I do!
Actually this voice
is from a popular voice actor
Kakihara Tetsuya-san
Kotoko
I know you're tired from running
but knowing Kotoko
I just know you'll beat your last time
ganbare Kotoko
What do I do! What do I do!
NOGIBINGO is freaking awesome!
I want this recording!
What is this?  Its really Kakki
yabai
And this is Quiz
Sasaki and Suzuki
Getting cheered on by her favorite voice actor Kakihara Tetsuya
Sasaki's 50m time
Will it decrease?
Or not?
Ikoma-chan, Matsumura.  What's the matter?
You got Kakki!
He didn't say Kotoko
He said Ko~toko to her!
[ Anime lovers losing their minds ]
So like TA~RARA sounds good then
I~koma!
Why am I hearing this from Ijiri-san?!
So then.  Answers
All at once
open
Won't decrease
It decreased
Decrease
And with that
the ones who say her time won't improve
is Matsumura's team
Why is that?
Your body and your heart are different things
we all felt it won't make her faster
Nishino-san team says she'll be faster
It seemed like she could run faster
and I wouldn't think the 1st question is a trick question
so because of that
she should just run faster
Too much analysis for a variety show
[ Over thinking ]
So then for the correct answer, Eto-san
hai
Let's take a look
Please introduce the clip
Ready, set
Quiz
Sasaki and
Suzuki
This is Sasaki Kotoko's 2nd attempt
Can she break her previous time of 10.33 seconds?
Now the start
And she reaches the finish
Did she break her previous record of 10.33 seconds?
The time we're all waiting on is
Sasaki-san's time
9.62 seconds
And with that
the correct answer is her time decreased
The answer was a faster time
The teams that answered correctly get 10 points
Matsumura team
your team was incorrect
And now back to Sasaki-san
you got a better time didn't you?
That's right
That's not a "waratte iitomo" moment
[ Studio audience? ]
By the way
stories about Sasaki-san
Saito Asuka do you have any stories?
Myself
Nakada Kana and
then Kotoko
I've been telling them for a while "Let's have a party"
and I was looking forward to a party
but before I knew it
it seems they were having parties without me
Was your party fun?
Yes, our party was fun
[ Sounds like some fun parties ]
On to the next question then
Would you two introduce the next clip please
The intros
since we don't say anything after the Sasaki and Suzuki part
can we just keep using that intro?
But perhaps they'll give us a different pattern
for the intro
Really?
Both of you go ahead then
Ready, set
Quiz
Sasaki and
Suzuki
Nothing changed!
Quiz
Sasaki and Suzuki
Once again lets check in on them while they're being transported
Tired as we expected
Suzuki is dozing off
Sasaki
the message she got from the voice actor
she's listening to it over and over while grinning
The next idea
100 questions with Sasaki and Suzuki
We'll investigate what's going on inside their heads
By the way, if we were to ask them their thoughts for the 3rd time
ganbarimasu
Question 1
Sasaki and Suzuki's favorite food is?
[ Sasaki - Hamburg, ice cream ]  [ Suzuki - Rice, ice cream ]
I eat ice cream everyday
I eat ice cream almost everyday
Both of them wrote down ice cream
oddly enough, its something they have in common
Question 5
Sasaki and Suzuki's hobbies are?
[ Sasaki - voice actors, anime ] [ Suzuki - nothing really ]
Do you have a favorite anime then?
Right now I like Bungo Stray Dogs
Things that don't
happen in reality take place
and then everybody's cool
Question 32
Sasaki and Suzuki
What do you do on your days off?
[ Sasaki - Wake up, anime, sleep ] [ Suzuki - Sit at home ]
I sleep in
and when I wake up
I watch anime
and go to sleep when I get tired
Do you take even one step out of the house?
I don't go out
Don't go out
On the other side Suzuki
I stay at home
I take a bath
The whole time?  Yeah
Is that enjoyable?
Yes, its fun
heh~~~~
Question 51
Sasaki and Suzuki's strengths are?
[ Sasaki - Hair smells good ]
So, Suzuki-san
I can always predict the worst possible outcomes
What does that mean?
Like this film shoot for example
there's a good chance
it might get dumped or something
those kinds of predictions
If this were to get cut
would you be emotionally damaged?
But that's just it
since I predicted it, there's practically no damage
And after that Sasaki and Suzuki continued
answering questions
And then
finally we're at the last question.  [ Draw yourself ]
Question 100
Sasaki and Suzuki
which 1st class member do they look up to?
[ Suzuki - All of them ]
And this is Quiz Sasaki and Suzuki
Which 1st class member did Sasaki write down?
So then all at once, answers
open
Matsumura-san
Nakada Kana-san
Kana-san
Who picked out Nakada-san from her team?
hai
Yourself
She asks me all the time
to take her out to eat
That's why I have a feeling that she likes me
She's after your money
She's the Nakada ATM
[ Merely a source of revenue ]
Higuchi-san, are you able to
have respect for Nakada-san?
Sure....sure I can
[ Doesn't appear that way ]
Let's make this into Sasaki and Suzuki and Higuchi
Lets take a look at the correct answer
One more time.  Hey, this is killing our cameraman!
So then
go ahead
Ready, set
Quiz
Sasaki and
Suzuki
And the correct answer is
Sasaki-san
Nakada Kana
Why?
I thought it would make her happy if I wrote this
Is there something about her you admire?
You mean Nakada-san?
Nothing in particular
And with that
the correct answer was Nakada Kana
So the correct answer is Nakada Kana
those teams will each get 10 points
But her reason?
Her reason...
What was the reason again?
I sit by her in the dressing room a lot
you always come up and sit next to me right?
Well that's the only seat available
[ Misunderstanding ]
Lets hear a story about Suzuki-san
Matsumura-san, do you have a story?
During filming
when she sits to my side
she's grabbed my hand before
this girl
I thought maybe she likes me or something
Is that so?
That's not it at all
[ Misunderstanding #2 ]
So then lets get to the next question
Are we doing that?
Eto-san, are we?
The last couple times they've added a "ready, set" for us
Is that so?
So then
onegaishimasu
Go ahead
Ready, set
Quiz
Sasaki and
Suzuki
Quiz Sasaki and Suzuki
we're getting around to the last question
Where they've arrived
Pasela Resort
Ikebukuro Nishiguchi Location
Having never gone out with each other for karaoke
we've got cameras setup today
to inspect their behavior
Between them, who will sing first?
Right away
Sasaki and Suzuki order food and drinks
Which one of them will be first to grab the mic?
And neither of them sang....
The odd competition to see who can hold out the longest continued
30 minutes pass
Suddenly
possibly because they could no longer endure the boredom
they try to pick out a song
Will someone finally sing?
They don't have 3D here yet
Lately everybody's got 3D
They punch in an anime song
but don't sing and just watch the video
30 more minutes go by
Pizza itadakimasu
They watch the karaoke demo video while continuing to eat
Sasaki and Suzuki
And then
30 more minutes go by
They continue to focus
on the karaoke demo screen
In danger of this continuing all the way to the end
appearing to only want to watch the demo screen
Sasaki and Suzuki
At this point the staff
requests that either one of them
picks out one song
to sing
onegaishimasu
Suddenly both of them start drinking
And here's our Quiz question
Sasaki and Suzuki
who will read the situation
and voluntarily sing first?
So then
answers
open
Sing together
Suzuki-san
If Sasaki-san sings first, then everyone has the wrong answer
What's the reason you picked Suzuki-san?
Since she has the power to predict the worst outcome
obviously Ayane can read the situation and pick a song
Lets see the answer.  This is the last time
Change it up a little bit right?
onegaishimasu
Ready, set
Quiz
Sasaki and
Suzuki
Read the situation
and be the first to sing karaoke
Will it be Sasaki or Suzuki?
The 2 of them came to karaoke
and an hour and a half has now passed
Sasaki still focused in
on the reliable demo screen
What's this?
And now Suzuki has her eyes on the demo screen
and then how come
the 2 of them refuse to make eye contact
Will it be Sasaki Kotoko the anime lover
or the one who can forsee the worst possible outcome
Suzuki Ayane
Now they're starting
they've switched their focus from the demo screen
and they've started the song selection
Will they sing?
Looks like someone's singing
The mic is now in someones hands
The one holding the mic is Suzuki Ayane
Is she going to sing?
This is Nogizaka46's
[ Koko Janai Doko Ka ]
And now Sasaki is going to sing
And there you have it
the correct answer was Suzuki Ayane
Suzuki-san was the first to sing
Ikoma-chan Team and the 2nd class team get 10 points
All the questions are done
Ikoma team and the 2nd class team got all the answers right
so then
Sasaki and Suzuki will consult each other
and decide the winning team
Time to announce the winning team
onegaishimasu
Ikoma-san team
Ikoma-chan team is the champion
and will get an extravagant reward from Suzuki-san
onegaishimasu
What could it be?
Suzuki-chan.  Open!
[ HGUC 1/144 scale - RX-78-2 Gundam ]
Could you give us an explanation?
Its gunpla
Plastic Gundam then
Yes.  This is
Aya-chan made this one
Who's taking this home?
Got to be Higuchi-san right?
Since it became Sasaki and Suzuki and Higuchi
From Suzuki to Higuchi
arigatou gozaimasu
Higuchi-san, how do you like the gunpla?
Ah, she worked so hard
In addition to the gunpla, on the display
we'll put a picture of her start pose
[ Bonus gift ]