That legendary program has returned!
In the first installment, they gave us laughs...
In the second installment, they delivered passion to the audience.
Nogizaka46 has truly grown as idols.
And in September, 2014....
With production confirmed, NOGIBINGO! 3 seems to be turning into the show of a National Idol group. However...
What is this?!
A man watching over the waiting room has become angry.
No way! Don't give me this crap! Seriously!
Hashimoto is...
Yawning! She yawned!!
She’s way too relaxed!
What’s wrong? Nishino!
Ready to fall asleep?
Nonononono! Nonononononono!
Really, there's no sense of tension here.
Even though they are about to perform,
the girls show no "sense of tension"
No "sense of tension"
Ikoma-chan is playing around too much!
Okay, that’s it. I can’t hold back any longer. I have to go there. Let’s go! Let’s just go.
Angrily towards the waiting room!
HEY!!!
Surprise!!!
Cut it out, all of you!
Even though you lot are trying to become true national idols,
looking at you now, your sense of tension is lacking.
Hashimoto-san. You didn’t try to talk to anyone.
I was thinking about that when you yawned!
And Nishino-san.
I was very surprised by your expression.
Are you tired or do you hate being here? Which?
Ready to fall asleep
Had I given you any more time you would have fallen asleep.
Judging you as a whole, I conclude that your sense of tension is lacking.
Having done NOGIBINGO 1, 2 and now 3, have you guys let your guard down?
No, no, no, no.
Don’t you think you’re only putting in the minimal effort?
-No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, you’ve all gotten pretty good at being “audience celebrities” with your hand-waving. That’s good.
Just like audience celebrities
Okay. So, listen up, girls.
From today, we are going to overcome your weaknesses!
The theme of NOGIBINGO! 3 is “Overcoming Weaknesses!”
In the first episode, the girls will try to overcome their lacking sense of tension.
They will challenge a “no NG’s allowed” episode!
Translation: kanjo & Fukagawa Highway
Timing: Pervies & Fukagawa Highway
Typeset: Michael Soares
QC: CurlyUdon
Ready, and...
NOGIBINGO! 3
No NG’s allowed! Title call in one take!
From here we will be tackling Nogizaka’s weakness, your "sense of tension."
To solve your lack of a sense of tension,
we will have you travel from this area, through various obstacles, toward the studio.
However, if any of you receive an “NG”, we will retake the scene from the very start.
Ehhhhh?
Well then, let's go over the course!
To travel from the start area to the studio, the girls will have to pass 8 challenges.
First, one girl will countdown to “start”.
Then, she'll remove her hairband...
And three girls will pass it through the first area using only their glasses in a “hairband relay”!
Two girls will receive the hair band then drink milk together while giving us an idol smile.
Then, they will encounter the announcer with a common knowledge quiz.
The three girls will have answer the question in harmony.
Next, two girls will carry a ping-pong ball on two pieces of string...
Through a 20 meter corridor without dropping it!
Then, in front of the building, after they perform an “1-shot gag”...
Three girls has to act out, without mistakes, a conversation with long lines!
The longest line is this: the full title of AKB48’s song with a very long name!
From then, three groups will take turns tossing grapefruits and catching them with forks!
Finally, the girls will work together to make the show’s title with letters!
Please enjoy this segment along with Nogizaka46’s new single, "Nandome no Aozora ka?"
I will now announce the group assignments!
For the "3, 2, 1, go!" at the start we have Sakurai!
Oh.. yeah! Yay!
Even though you're the captain you’ve got no sense of responsibility.
Here are the rest of the group assignments…
And the group who will be in charge of the long speech is…
I’m sure you’re used to this by now… Hashimoto group!
Nanamin! Go, Nanamin!
You can do it easily. You’re an actress, after all!
Hashimoto is an experienced actress
Actually, I haven’t even been in one this year!
So this is your first, then?
First acting of the year
As long as you have a sense of tension, you should be able to get through this!
If for whatever reason we can’t do this in one episode...
We will continue with the same concept for episodes two and three until you get it!
-Ehhh? No way!
The members immediately get into their groups and practice before the real thing.
Will the girls be able to pull off the introductory title call?
Now, it’s time for take 1!
Ready?
And… action!
3... 2... 1... start!
First, rest the hair band on her glasses.
Their ability to work together and their concentration is being tested.
-Ah, they’re getting close!
-Now, Akimoto will pass the hair band baton to Eto.
-Just a little more! Be patient! Be patient!
Do it! You’re lifting her gl- AH!
Failure
Hold on, this is difficult!
-Sorry everyone! Sorry!
Akimoto tried to place the hair band on Eto’s glasses.
However, she caught Eto’s glasses and the band fell!
Manatsu-san! The objective isn’t to lift her glasses!
Sorry!
Don't mind!
After gathering their spirits, it's time for take 2!
Ready… and, action!
3... 2... 1... start!
-Good.
Concentrate, concentrate.
Captain Sakurai passes the hair band to Akimoto!
Having learned from their previous miss, Akimoto tries passing the hair band down to Eto from above.
-Oh, looking good!
-Great! You got it!
A marvelous success!
Now, Eto will try to pass to Fukagawa!
Ah, very close!
Looking good.
Failure
What happened?
Fukagawa tries to accept the hair band from Eto, but Eto instead leans in for a kiss.
Eto's kissy face ♥
Without a hope of success, the hair band falls tragically.
-I thought I’d try snatch a kiss while I had chance but I messed up.
-No, I messed up, because I was so surprised.
Fukagawa discomforted
-Feel free to have fun, but please remember to have a sense of tension.
-Ah, I'm sorry!
Take 3!
Action!
3... 2... 1... Start!
Good so far. Here will be fine.
Having received the band from Sakurai, Akimoto tries passing the hair band down to Eto from above.
Don't move your glasses.
Eto-chan.. Eto-san. You're close to getting it. Doing good!
Just a little bit more and it'll fall.
-Good, good. It fell, it fell!
-So far, so good, Eto's turn now.
Okay, on to Fukagawa next!
-Ah, no! Not Maimai! You’re too cute! Too cute!
-I’m blushing…
This time, she was able to put her feelings for Fukagawa aside, and the transfer was a success!
On to the next stage! Fukagawa heads to the Milk pair-straw group!
In this rough barrier, failure means having to drink an indefinite number of glasses of milk!
Next, we have milk, right?
Itadakimasu!
They begin drinking with their “idol smiles.”
What’s this? We don’t mind if you spill milk out your nose.
Shiraishi moved away from the straw. It appears something hit the spot and she can no longer drink.
And so…
Because she could not stop laughing, the challenge failed.
Failure
What happened? Why were you laughing?
Her face was a lot closer than I thought it would be…
I got nervous and laughed!!
I’m sorry!
Ah, sorry!
The group suffers after missing their once in a lifetime opportunity.
Failure
They make consecutive misses, and cannot manage to leave the sound room.
Consecutive Failures
Because of this, the Grapefruit Team has made an appearance in front of Ijiri Okada.
Ah, what’s wrong, Grapefruit Team?
It’s not coming around to us
I noticed. Have you been practicing?
Yeah, we did.
We practiced too much, and now we’re running out of grapefruits!
Be careful! Use your grapefruits carefully.
Can you can finish it in one take when it's your turn?
Definitely!
Brimming with confidence
I think it’ll come soon, so please be ready.
Sorry, you had to be last.
In order for the Grapefruit Team to also get some time on air, work on your “sense of tension!” Take 6!
And… action!
From the opener, Sakurai, through the hairband relay has been successful so far.
Itadakimasu!
The baton has passed to the Milk Pair Drinking team.
Nice! Keep looking at the camera, Matsumura-kun! That’s great, both of you!
You can look at each other, too!
The two finished the 300mL of milk with a smile. Exactly what you would expect from idols!
Delicious!!
Having the milk finished, Matsumura passes the question card out to the Quiz Team!
The three must answer the question together! Will they be able to?
Question: In what year will the Tokyo Olympics be held?
3... 2... 1...
2020!
Well done! Great, now go, go!!
Now the group will bring the ping-pong ball to the pair who are waiting with strings to hold it!
What is important here is matching the rhythm of their breath and their balance.
Facing this challenge is the Ikoma-Kawago pair.
Do your best!
Ah, good! Follow Nagashima’s directions!
With the ping-pong ball finally stable on the string...
Ready… tan.. tan.. tan
Eh, what's with this cheer?
A strange cheer
"Pan pan"?
Nakamoto uses a strange cheer and the pair moves toward the goal: outside.
Surreal!
Paying attention to detail, they're fine tuning their balance.
Ah, the window is open! Wind is getting in!
The window's open and wind is getting in! Look out!
Look out.
A little more!
What kind of trap is this?
Just 5 meters until the goal!
Ikoma’s expression shows an unbelievable transformation from the beginning of the show.
Serious mode
You’re doing fine!
Concentrating hard, they took four minutes to finally reach the goal.
Then…
Has Kawago left yet? Are you outside?
Eh, did it fall?
The ball fell
We’re... we're outside… safe?
It fell after they reached the goal so they’re clear!
Next is the long speech team!
Nogibingo! 3 Amazing! AMAZING!
Remind me, what was the song we were going to record today?
It’s Nogizaka46’s new single, “Nandome no Aozora ka?” to be released on October 8th.
As well as a cover of AKB48’s single
"Suzukake no ki no michi de, kimi no hohoemi wo 'yume ni miru' to itte shimattara
bokutachi no kankei ga dou kawatte shimau no ka,
boku nari ni nan nichi ka kangaete mita ue de no
yayakihazukashii ketsuron no you na mono". Those two songs!
Why didn't y- eh?
Failure
You just said, “kangaete mita ue de”, right?
It's “kangaeta ue de no,” but you said, “kangaete mita ue de no”
-No way!
You said it, didn't you?
I did?
You did…
I think…
I may have said it…
From the start!!
-I’m sorry!
From the start!
It's a tough segment.
With a line mistake, we're back to the start.
Time to wrap it up! Take 7!
Ready, and… action!
From Sakurai to the hairbands… no misses. Clear!
Next is their third glass of milk but they drink it all up with idol smiles! Time for the quiz!
Question: What is “mokuyoubi” in English?
3... 2... 1...
Thurs^$@£
What did you say?
“Mokuyoubi”?
We just made a pronunciation error…
What is “mokuyoubi” in English?
3... 2... 1...
Thursssde.
Say it once each. Nakamoto. No, Hori-san! Ready...
Thursday!
Nakamoto-san!
-Thursday!
“Ready” then together…
R-Ready…
Thursday!
Correct!
With Ijiri’s intervention, they’re through!
Next is Ikoma and Kawago’s super tense “ping-pong ball carrying”
If they think it’s unsafe, even for a little, they stop moving.
Ready…
Tan tan.. careful!
Ah ah ah ah ah ah.. Keep going!
Drop a little
Ready....
Everything is for the members who are waiting to play their part.
They move step by step closer to their goal, and then…
If Kawago-san stops out you’re clear… 5cm left!
Are you out? You are! You did it! Clear!
Ping-pong ball success
Next is the long speech area!
This time, can the actress Hashimoto pass the test?
Nogibingo! 3 Amazing! AMAZING!
Remind me, what was the song we were going to record today?
Don’t you know? It’s our new single, “Nandome no Aozora ka?” to be released on October 8th.
As well as a cover of AKB48’s single,
"Suzukake no ki no michi de, kimi no hohoemi wo 'yume ni miru' to itte shimattara,
bokutachi no kankei ga dou kawatte shimau no ka,
boku nari ni nan nichi ka kangaeta ue de no
yayakihazukashii ketsuron no you na mono". Those two songs!
Why didn't you say it sooner!
Actress Hashimoto, clear
In a big improvement, the actress Hashimoto perfected the long speech!
Now they move to the team who has practiced more than any other,
the Grapefruit Team will be attempting
three successive tosses and catches!
Hey, do your best!
Go for it!
Ready?
Can they make it?
Nogibingo 2 DVD is on sale!!
Over 60 minutes of Making of, Deleted Scenes, and Recap Party footage!
See the official site for more info!
A kiss would be fine too~
In order to overcome their weakness...
Nogizaka46 attempts the miraculous 1-cut challenge!
After various failures, they finally get to the grapefruit stage!
Can they succeed at three catches in a row!?
Here it comes!
Do your best!
We begin with the first toss!
Here I go!
Nice! Nice!
- Next one!
One more, come on!
- Third toss!
Nice!!
A grand success!
Next up is 20-man text formation!
If they fail here, it would all have been for nothing!
Go for it! Go!
Here we go! Come on!
Don't mess up!
Get to your positions!
Focus!
Here we go!
Starting!
Ready, set!
Nogibingo 3 is starting!
Awesome! Awesome! Awesome awesome awesome!
So... those grapefruits!
Amazing!
This one...
This one was performed with 100% success rate! You've done it!
Amazing~
Did you keep practicing while you waited?
We thought, everyone's made it this far...
There was only one stage left. We weren't allowed to fail!
We would keep practicing until our hands became grapefruits!
And before that, that long title of Suzukake...!
How'd you feel when you failed the first time?
I thought, "I messed up..."
I said it in my own words. Really...
That's pretty disrespectful to Akimoto-sensei, who created the title.
You thought "tried to consider" sounded better than "considered".
Top batter, Captain Sakurai!
Captain~
You did it with no misses!
That's right, no misses!
What was your line?
3! 2! 1! Q!
That's it.
And then you let your hair down.
Being the captain, don't you think this job was a bit too easy?
Had it easy despite being the captain?
Why is life like this?
The staff probably thought she was the least capable one...
Ponkotsu character?
Ah~ you serious?
- That's probably right.
But, honestly! Honestly, watching everyone...
I thought I didn't really do anything...
Even though it was great to scream "Wah~" at the end...
Accomplishment: zero
Like...
"Why is this?" I thought...
What do you think you would've been able to do?
The grapefruit one.
We have a grapefruit prepared!
Can you catch it?
If you succeed at this, you'll feel accomplished, right?
Feel accomplished during the first episode of Nogibingo 3!
With the captain representating, everyone should feel the tension!
Do your best!
Here we go! The tension! Will captain succeed? Let's go!
Can captain Sakurai Reika catch the grapefruit!?
Here is a notice from the show!
Surprisingly, Nogibingo 3 will provide special footage online!
Hulu and NTV will provide online streaming after the show airs!
See the official site for more info!
Emergency challenge! Captain Sakurai's Grapefruit Catch!
The tension! Will captain succeed? Let's go!
You got it, you got it...
She did it!
This is great...
Captain, you've done it!
Yes!
Everyone, from now on, let's keep on overcoming our weaknesses!
Yes sir!
Be more lively when you say "Yes sir"!
Let's overcome it!
Yes sir!
After this, having finished watching tonight's episode...
Nogi members have a girls' talk in their best pajamas!
At home, I'm a nudist. Like, I would just have panties on.
Shiraishi Mai's slightly sexy secret is revealed!
Tonight's on-air recap is Nogi member's Pajama Girls' Talk corner!
Also known as... NogiRoom!
After Nogibingo 3 finishes...
It's over! First episode...
Time flew by so quickly!
Everyone's in pajamas today.
Yeah.
- We have pajamas on!
We match!
- That's right!
In different colors...
- You're right!
Different colors...
So cute...
Doesn't Maiyan prefer to be nude?
Eh? Nude?
At home, I'm a nudist...
Like...
- What would you wear exactly?
Just the panties pretty much...
- Seriously?
With a t-shirt on...
- Right?
I said "right?" but I don't really know...
We haven't lived together!
When the episode ends, Hulu will air the complete NogiRoom!
Never-before-seen girls' talk will be shown!
Also, we'll reveal Nogi members' love letters, full of thankful words!
Giving you a glimpse into the girls' world: NogiRoom!
I like you!
For more info, click on the home page!
And now, next week's episode-
Nogibingo is joined by the ultimate helper!
That is... Matsui Rena!
A test to see Matsui Rena's relationship with Nogi members!
But...
This is really starting to get weird.
- That's true...
What should I do?
- In addition!
What? What? Eh eh!
A mysterious being greets Matsui Rena!
Stay away... it's scary...