We're going to conquer your weaknesses!
Do your b-- Ahh!
We had them work on their teamwork,
Please stay with me forever.
The feminine skills needed to develop as a woman.
Puffing my cheeks in anger!
They even worked on their acting abilities
to get used to multiple situations.
In order to become national-level idols, they have overcome their weaknesses. This is Nogizaka46.
The theme of tonight, the final episode, is...
Dreams.
Translation: kanjo & AESub
Timing: OM
Typeset: AESub & Michael Soares
QC: Curly Udon
Nogibingo! 3!
These girls run full speed toward their dreams.
When they debuted as idols,
they had many troubles and worries.
They bring together their various treasures filled with these feelings,
and begin their girls' party.
To join Nogizaka46, that was your first dream.
What feelings did the girls hold in their hearts...
when they began to walk this path?
Let us return to this time and find out what they felt when they began the journey toward their dreams.
Let us begin with this treasure...
I brought a treasure with me.
A letter that I got from my mom when I moved to Tokyo.
To Takayama who moved away and began living alone.
What does this letter from her Mom say?
It's too embarrassing to read it myself so I'd like Ikuchan to read it.
- Okay!
Uwah! Such an important thing...
Dear Kazumi,
The hardest work bears fruit,
take advantage of the great opportunities.
You're working in the entertainment world which everybody admires.
I'm very proud to have a daughter like you.
It's finally time for you to become independent...
To me, your presence is huge.
Thank you for always being with me.
I will work hard too.
I'll always pray for your success and happiness.
I'll always be watching over you.
Please rely on me.
From Mom.
Chiichan's crying!
Chiichan, why?
Saito Chiharu is crying before Takayama
Chiichan, cheer up!
Why so much?
Chiichan!
You live at home, right?
She isn't separated, but just the topic...
I would be so happy...
Y-yeah! When I moved I was really upset but...
I have this... and I look at it when it gets hard.
That's something to be happy about.
But... but, like... how to say it...
Well, people who are living with their families
Can you think of anything your parents told you that made you happy?
After we had senbatsu announcements,
when I called my parents
they never said "that's too bad" or "do your best next time,"
or even "that's good." They always said "have fun."
Ah!
She didn't say either.
Anything is fine, just have fun!
Ah! That's nice!
And that has always helped me.
Wow, that's so nice...
I'm happy about something they avoid saying...
When we were doing principal, it was really rough and I often say "I wanna go back to Osaka!"
My mom came all the way to Tokyo,
she was crying a lot when she saw me cry.
It was the first time I saw my mom cry
but she never said "come on back to Osaka."
She just told me "do you best here" while crying...
and that was... ah, even now when I think about it...
Back then, my mom had it rough but...
she was still supporting me. That made me very happy.
People who came to Tokyo, how was it?
Lonely...
I thought so many times I want to go home, but I have a dream...
That's why I came here. I feel like I can't go back until it comes true.
I understand!
I came to Tokyo before I met everyone
so I felt less lonely after I met everyone.
Until then I was always alone...
I see...
There's a part of me that's working hard because other members are here. We're all supporting each other. So I understand that.
The next treasure is a photo Shiraishi took before their debut.
From the beginning...
Like, just after we passed the auditions
and we just had our first week of our lessons.
The "adult members"... around five of us... took a purikura photo together.
I wanna see it!
No way! Wait, how old were we here?!
- You were around 19?
- Yeah, around 19.
19 years old? So young!
We went for yakiniku, right?
Yeah! We had yakiniku and then took our first purikura together.
Nanami went in with her lesson clothes.
It was a hassle to change so I got on the train in my lesson clothes...
had the lesson and then went home with the same clothes.
A jersey and t-shirt.
That's all I had.
Ah, but that's Kotoko's usual outfit.
- Your usual?
- Ah!!
Yeah, but you're very cute today!
Today's good!
Last night, I was talking to Karin-chan on LINE and I had her pick my outfit!
Ehh?! They're so cute!
It was so tough! Everything she showed me was so ugly!
Where do you buy clothes?
Back home in places I don't really know well...
Back home?
Can I show my treasure as well?
This is my treasure!
- Ah! Kazumin?
- Kazumi-chan!
When I got promoted to a full member this year, she gave me this photo which says
"congratulations on your promotion, let's work hard together!"
I was so happy. I treasure it.
Since I have this chance,
there's one thing I wanted to ask...
Would you like to have dinner together sometime?
- You're asking now?
- Let's go, let's go!
If it's not now, I'd be too nervous I wouldn't be able ask.
No way.. let's go!
Awesome! I can't wait!
Me too! Wow, I should take out some cash!
Don't say it that way!
Next, we have Ikuta's treasure.
What might this object, said to bring back memories of the early days, be?
It's something I received back at the beginning, a video of the "Nogizaka no Uta" choreography.
I don't think any of you have seen it before.
The reason I have it is
It was the day before my high school entrance exams so I couldn't go.
So I had a staff member take a rough video and send it to me.
I wanna see it.
- You have it?
I have it.
Scary!
That's not a treasure!
- It is treasure!
- No, it's trash!
In our lesson clothes, right?
- Yup!
No! You can't! I'm not wearing make-up!
Let us take a look!
Here is the 3 year old choreography video from their pre-debut days.
No way! No!
Stop it!
Stop! Stop!
No way!
Please... just...
Wait! Wait!
What were you thinking showing this?!
I thought Ikoma-chan was so cute in it!
I'm hideous!!
That's too much!
You're very expressive about that!
This is terrible!
What are we all holding?
Wooden chopsticks!
Dancing with wooden chopsticks
You watch this?
When I was cleaning, I found it and I felt like watching it.
But you shouldn't have brought it here!
Ah, but if you look back at the early days, don't you feel like working hard again?
I mean, back then, weren't we so frantic!?
We were so unfashionable... what about now?
Ah.. I wonder...
You're not unfashionable anymore. Look at this sharp looking necklace!
Trying harder because you're in AKB?
Matsui Rena-san joined recently, right?
What was your first impression of her?
- Rena-san?
- When I first saw her I was like
"Ah! It's really her!" That memory really stands out.
But of course, we weren't thinking that Rena-san would join us...
When her concurrency began, we were all very nervous.
But she eased our nervousness for us...
And now we really fit together.
I'm really grateful that she's so considerate.
Was there any member you found difficult to talk to?
Someone that you get along with now.
During lessons, Ami was always late.
That happened every time!
You were late all the time.
She always took her time eating cold noodles.
- Cold noodles?
- Really slowly!
You were late but you were still eating cold noodles!
- I remember thinking she must be a real big shot...
- A big shot?!
Well then, let's move on to the next event.
But... before that...
It's already Christmas, huh?
Yeah, one year just flew by.
What is Ikoma-chan wishing for this year?
It's a secret.
A secret? Why? Tell me! I want to know!
What about Ikuchan?
- Then mine's a secret as well.
- Eh, why?
Well then, let's both wish for Santa to come.
- Alright, let's wish for that!
Ready, set...
Santa, please come to our place as well!
Merry Christmas!
Ikuta Erika's first dokkiri is a huge success!
Dokkiri huge success
I came over because you called!
I'm Santa after all!
Wait... this is my first time!
Eh? What is?
I was shocked!
- I was really surprised.
- You were?
Well, since I came to fulfill everyone's dreams...
- Really?
- Let's go together. It's over there.
I'll fulfill them over there. Let's go!
The event of fulfilling the members' wishes starts now!
Merry Christmas!
- Merry Christmas!
How nice. Has everyone made wishes to Santa this year as well?
Yes!
Those wishes have been received by Ijiri-Santa!
Rising expectations ♥
From now on, each and everyone's dream presents...
I'll be giving them to you!
Ijiri-Santa has prepared Christmas presents which the members honestly wished for.
However, only the members whose names are written on the balls in the bag will receive it.
So, what kind of presents did the members wish for?
Everyone was serious about it?
Really serious!
Here I go!
Starting off... The first Santa present is for...
Hori-san!
Eh? How nice...
- Hori-san, go ahead!
Alright!
- Go!
- So nice...
The presents will be received in this separate room.
What did the 2nd gen Hori Miona wish from Santa?
Without further ado, open the present!
Here goes!
Contained in a formidable box, the contents are...?
What is it?
Eh, what is that?
Very happy!!
What is it?
Yay!
I haven't heard her with that kind of excitement before.
Hori-san! Right, what is this?
This is... I asked for the tastiest meat in Japan.
How much was it?
- This is...
- 10,000 yen!
That's expensive!
- 10,000 yen...
- That looks amazing!
Please do it with your best smile, it's 10,000 yen after all.
- Yes, itadakimasu!
Shivering in delight
So cute!
- Cute!
- It looks delicious!
Immediately rice
Since you're young, you go to the rice right away.
Though adults don't go for the rice,
you went for it right away!
Hori Miona-san, Merry Christmas!
The next member to receive a present is...?
This person!
Merry... ah! Ikoma-chan!
Really?!
Please go to the next room.
What did Ikoma-san wish from Santa?
Let's open the present!
I'd hate it if it's a jack-in-the-box.
Huh? Wait...
Alarm clock
Really? Really?
This alarm clock has a certain gimmick...
Lady Rina...
It's time to wake up.
Huge scream!!!
What?
Is she happy?
- Thank you very much!!!
Her reaction's the best.
Well then, please report that joy to the other members...
Did you want a clock that badly?
It's the inside of the clock ♥
- The contents.
- What's in it?
A voice ♥
Ono Daisuke, a famous voice actor best known as Sebastian Michaels from the anime Kuroshitsuji
- Whose voice...?
- Ono-D!
Attention
That's dangerous!
- Eh? What is it?
- Ono-D is dangerous!
There's a voice actor here!
Wailing!?
Kotoko is crying!
Ah, I thought you were talking about Ono the director.
- That's not the one!
Ono director = Wrong
Did this do it?
- Ah, I'm sorry...
- Please let me hear it later...
What's in it? Let us hear?
I love you.
Rina, do your best!
He said "I love you!"
Just before he said he loves you, he said your name, right?
Huge scream #2
Ikoma Rina-san, Merry Christmas!
After this, the presents continue to be delivered.
For captain Sakurai...
It's a Santa Claus cosplay outfit.
Santa Husband & Wife?
It's weird!
For Hashimoto, facial equipment with a real purpose.
A steamer...
Well then, let's continue.
And the next member elected is...
Sasaki!
It's not the time to cry!
What did 2nd gen Sasaki, who just cried over Ikoma's present, request from Santa?
Eh? You're kidding me!
Wait... It can't be!?
This...
Ticket for a signed autograph from Mashima Hiro-sensei
Wailing once again
What's written on it...
Thank you very much...
What's wrong?
You're in tears!
You were really wailing when you opened it...
She smiled.
With Ikoma-chan's turn, you were so envious that you cried, but now...
Seeing you cry like this, something better must have come along. What was it?
A ticket for an autograph from Mashima Hiro-sensei.
- That's wonderful!
- He's the mangaka of Fairy Tail and Rave Master...
His drawings are really good, and it's always been my dream to meet him.
Passionate
Really... I'll save it as an heirloom.
Right.
After this, she comes face to face with her admired Mashima-sensei.
I'm really happy...
Geinin 3, DVD & Blu-ray sales have been decided!
It's impossible!
Fully packed with making-of footage and bonus content!
Me too...
I love you!
To fulfill Sasaki Kotoko's dream,
we head to where Mashima-sensei is.
Good day...
Hello!
How is it?
Wailing 5 seconds in
It's really him...
To Sasaki who cries within 5 seconds of meeting him,
Mashima-sensei presents his autograph.
I intended to draw Sasaki Kotoko-chan...
With this surprise caricature, Sasaki's reaction is..?
Wailing
I keep crying...
I heard you were a fan of Gray, so I drew him...
And this is Musica from one of my previous works...
I heard you also like him.
Please accept my gift.
Thank you very much.
Mashima-sensei, thank you for your cooperation!
Sasaki Kotoko-san, Merry Christmas!
So, this will be the last present. Who will be drawn?
Akimoto.
After this, a huge panic because of Akimoto's unthinkable Christmas present?
Come on!
Eh? What is it?
What exactly made an appearance?
Here's an announcement from the program!
Nogibingo!3 will be available for streaming on Hulu and NTV after the broadcast!
For more details, go to the program's homepage!
The present Akimoto requested from Santa...
Will be unveiled!
Present, come on!
Eh? What is it?
A snake appears!?
What did you want to do with this?
I wanted to wear a snake on my neck.
You wrote something like that?
Is it okay like that?
Well then, please.
Ah, that's nice.
Staff!
Attention
A snake's skirt-flip?
It's a perverted snake!
Akimoto Manatsu-san, Merry Christmas!
By the way, Saito Yuuri-san...
What did you write?
I want a Nogibingo! 4!
I think this is everyone's wish, so pray for another chance like this to come...
Well then, let's meet again when the time comes!
Bye bye!
Thank you!
Did you come here by yourselft@$%#?
After this, a sneak peek of the 46 minute special version of Nogiroom.
A love letter has arrived.
It's from Ijiri-san!
Oh my!
NOGIROOM!
First off, the backstage talk that wasn't aired.
Kazumin, you had that thing that wasn't aired, right?
- What was it again?
- A mousou request...
From the 2nd episode...
Ah, the hostess club one...
- She did wear...
- I don't know about this?
- Your voice was amazing, right?
- Good evening, I'm Kazumi♥
Good evening, I'm Kazumi♥
Did you come here by yourselft@$%#?
That part!
I could never say it!
I understand!
Uh oh!
Tissue, tissue!
Drool! She drooled!
The photography contest...
Since Takayama was so particular about taking it, the water got cold.
Right! Sorry about that!
You really were in the water?
Eh? So from this part down?
From here is... well, it's a secret ♥
A love letter has arrived.
It's addressed to Nogizaka46.
Who would it be?
It's from Ijiri-san!
Oh my!
The continuation of Ijiri's letter with overflowing love will be shown on Hulu after the episode broadcast!
He's not an Ero-Kappa at all.
Come see us in our pajama outfits!
Click here!
NOGIBINGO! 3! Blu-ray & DVD sales have been decided!