21 August 2011, from a nationwide audition which saw 38,934 auditionees,
33 girls were selected to form Nogizaka46
Just right after their formation, their namesake show was decided
After continuous lessons, the girls need to quickly become 1st rate idols
Last week was the 2nd episode ..
Nogizaka46's front members, the Shichifukujin are decided!
These 7 members are the shichifukujin!
but this lineup may change any given time so please work hard
So then, the content of this episode is!
The number 1 idolmaster in the media world, Yoiko's Arino would thoroughly assess the 18 non-senbatsu members
Among here, I feel there's no girl that would sell-out and get a big break
Ehhhh?!
Brought to you by IkomaSubs
Translated & Timed by Jiaemi
Visit www.Facebook.com/IkomaSubs for updates!
After this, beautiful girls which would not lose out to the senbatsu members would make their appearance!
DON ~!
Nogizaka tte doko has begun!
I'll introduce the guest
He is this person!
I'm Yoiko's Arino!
DON~ !
Arino-san you're famous for loving idols right?
I love idols
I heard this, it's weird when Arino-san pinpoints someone
and says that this girl would be able to pull it off, it really worked out well
Seems like it
ahh, yes it has occurred before
who did you said about before?
Erm, recently it was Nagasawa Masami
How long before she became popular did you feel she would have a big break?
Around 15 years old
Before she was the focus of the world, I was already observing her
like her photoshoots and felt that it's coming (her big break)
Wow that's amazing
Yes, that's why on BOMB magazine I wrote Nagasawa Masami
Ehhh?! Amazing!
So did any members catch hold of Arino's interests?
Here comes the 1st senbatsu members, please!
Arino-san, wave at Arino-san
Arino-san is focusing on them
can I have a handshake?
How are they? They are quite similar to SKE48?
Since you've had a TV program with them it would seems like it right?
I had a look at their profiles
I looked at them all, I don't think there's a girl that would become a big hit
Ehhhhh~?!
You See!
I read it right here right now
Ohh! There it is!
What is this person?
He's amazing!
Who is this person?!
I wanted to try this
What did you wanted to do?
Someone who stood up and said "wait a min" is someone who would not become an idol
Ahhh! It's someone who would not become an idol!
lucky not one of you stood up
So they all passed this test?
They all passed
Everyone passed
After Arino's thorough check ended, we shall announce tonight's plan
Himura, if you would!
Here I go!
Nogizaka46 non-senbatsu member introduction!
With that said, please watch the PR videos of the non-senbatsu members
Hi, nice to meet you, from Hokkaido 18 years old, Hashimoto Nanami
My rival is Sashihara Rino
I have recently acquired a one-shot gag, I would like to perform it
A mimicry of the automated hand dryer in department store toilets
here I go!
she has to look at the person's face
She has a cool face and composure
For an idol to do this is rare
yes it is
Idol lovers would use this mini-episode as a base for fantasies
Ahhh I see!
The fans would think "she has just recently mastered it, maybe shes been to a department store"
They would imagine "what kind of girl is she"
She has to think about many things just from a word
There would be people going to a department store and camping near the girl's toilet just to meet her
Ahh I see, that's disgusting
Nakada what's so amusing?
These people are those that support you idols
That's true
That's right, so you shouldn't laugh at them
What do you mean by no laughing
Hello everyone! I'm 148cm, 15 years old, 1st year of high school, Ito Nene
Mame = bean
Because I'm tiny, members call me mame-chan or mameyan
My favorite item is the smell of brown paper bags
That's good, fans would give paper bags to you along with the presents
Oh i see!
My talent is backflip and the recently popular doyagao
doyagao = face after doing something triumphant
So she's going to do them together right?
She's going to show a doyagao also right? Woah fast
and then .. the doyagao
and she's confirming the staff are there
should you have said that?
the doyagao was directed at the staff
a backflip would be good right?
Yes, it can be used in dances
From Tokyo, 3rd year High school, Saito Yuri
Members and friends call me Yuutan
my recent my-boom is mimicking stitch from disney
the quality is not that good but I'll give it a shot!
I'm stitch!
that's it, thank you very much!
to keep continuing things like this is important right?
yes, it should be, mmm..
At lives, when the MC is saying something
and says mimic stitch!
She'll go "Ehhh?" or do it while being embarrassed
That would be cute
Hi, nice to meet you, from Osaka, I'm Kawamura Mahiro, 16 years old, 1st year of high school
The members call me Lotti, so please call me that
I don't usually play sports, my body is flexible
can anyone do the bridge?
ahh you can do it?
can you do it?
yes i can
can you bend back?
I can, but I'm not wearing shorts
ahhhh, you're not wearing shorts below
but it cant be seen
then you better not
or alternatively everyone strips, your decision
ehh ~ lets strip ~
that would be a problem!
from Osaka Sayurin aka Matsumura Sayuri
Foods I like are strawberries, peaches and fried chicken
To be honest, I have no talents whatsoever
so I stole a gag from Nanamin
I'll mimic the sound of an F1 car
sound series
Slow! Isn't it slow for an F1 car?
another one is the voice of a lamb
that's horrible!
do lambs sound like this?
don't they go "mehhh"?
"mehhh" is for goats
mehhh is for goats right?
your gag is sheep or goat?
mine is the mimicry of a sheep
show us?
this is it! teach them
teach it to them
is there anyone who can do this too?
ahhh everyone is able to do it
from Hiroshima, the youngest in Nogizaka46, Wada Maaya
I think of Oshima Yuko as a rival
my talent is karate
she stammered!
that's amazing
this is good
she has long arms and legs
from Nagasaki
2nd year of middle school, 13 years old, Kawago Hina
I love natto
even though people say I look cool
the fact is that I'm an otaku
I love idols, anime and cosplaying
karate
what's your talent?
a lot of girls know karate
did she really demonstrated karate?
what was that just now? "yaaaa"
the "yaaa" sounded constant monotone
I wish to work more with 48 related groups
does anyone here do anything other than karate?
oh there is
I have been constantly practicing kendo
Takayama all the while learning kendo, how's her skill like?
you went out of the screen!
maybe if she had a sparring partner
sparring partner? I guess I'll go
begin!
she got a point
Nakamoto Himeka, 3rd year of middle school, 15 years old
please call me himetan
I come from Hiroshima
I can do the dance of Perfume's
I'm sorry
kawaii
Hi everyone, i am Noujou Ami, i love the Dwarf Encyclopedia
2nd year of high school, 16 years old
I love acting, Oshima Yuko is my rival because of her acting skills
my talent is the mimicry of a rabbit
this is good
ah this is amusing
this is interesting
I see
she has completed her role
Himura can you mimic a rabbit too?
Yes I can
Oh I see
can you show us?
Sugoiii
You look like one of Ubertone's art pieces
Nice to meet you, I am Ito Marika
I am from Osaka, brought up in Kanagawa and I am 15 years old
I think of Itano Tomomi as a rival because she is a fashion leader
food I like are green peas, nassu, plums, ginger, and beef jerky
That's too many!
I could only remember beef jerky!
my talent is classic ballet
woah, flexible
Y shaped balance?
V goes like this
ow ow ow!
it's been awhile since I have done this, it hurts here, sorry
what she did at the last part was cute too
you were looking at that place?
i do look at those spots too
I do look there
I could learn from this
it would be better if she could narrow down her favorite foods
Hi, I come from Osaka, 2nd year of high school, Nishino Nanase
ever since I got into Nogizaka46, people have been telling me I have become more elder-sister like
but, I am not elder-sister like at all
instead, I'm the little sister
I love drawing pictures the most
she won't draw for us
this is awesome
I'm sure she has a sketchbook
she could quickly draw something
she could draw something simple so we could witness her skills
it could be like "I drew Akimoto-san"
Have you all met Akimoto-san before?
only twice
can you draw him?
are you good at drawing?
just do it simply
you've only met him twice so I don't think you'll remember his looks
thank you
that was good, did you see?
see what?
when she took something from the staff, she said thank you
yes we saw
there are a lot of idols that don't say that
Ehhhhh?!
So that means she has good manners
are you done drawing?
this is interesting
this is Akimoto-san
who is this?
From Saitama, 16 years old, 2nd year of high school, Inoue Sayuri
I like sweet and furry things
oh she loves transforming objects and she has twintails
there are 2 sayuri in Nogizaka46
the members have given me the nickname Sayunyan
I would be happy if you all could call me that too
people would want to call her Sayunyan
hmm.. I see
they would want to get it out of their mouths
as for my talent, since I love sentai heroes ..
sentai heroes = power rangers
i'll mimic them with a transformation
please transform~
can she do it?
she didn't tell us what kind of transformation
she seems to like sentai hero or things related to it
otaku people would probably like her
ahhh .. the moe type of idol
yes, the little sister type of idol
I see, its true
when these fans meet her she is able to hold a conversation about these stuff
besides looks being important, her hobbies would also have significant importance as well right?
yes
she probably like them from the beginning
yes it probably is, as shes willing to even do transformation poses
it's a talent you know ~
Hi everyone, Kashiwa Yukina, 2nd year of high school, 17 years old
I was a member of Momoiro Clover previously
I want to make use of the dance and vocal skills I acquired while I was a member of Momoiro Clover
please support me
my recent favorite food is something like fried pasta
oh she's experienced as an idol
oh I see
that's scary
Hi everyone, I'm from Oita, 18 years old, Eto Misa
please call me misamisa
since i was in the volleyball club in middle school
I was a relay runner in elementary through high school
I am a sporty girl and I have confidence in my ability in sports
I'll demonstrate my talent, jump rope
that was an amazing demonstration
not everyone can do that
I'll challenge the 30-jump which in middle school I could jump 10 times
I jumped once, applause please
hi everyone, in my 2nd year of middle school, 13 years old, I'm Higuchi Hina
from now on, I'll work hard to not to look back and regret
my talent is body percussion
but I saw her profile
there was a question "what is AKB48 to you"
most girls answered "an existence we look up to"
or "an existence we must become better than"
here, I wished for them to try and use words to destroy AKB
what did she write then?
to us, AKB is our parent group, and has an existence akin to a mother bird
ahh I see
she wrote this so I thought she would be interesting
from Saitama, 3rd year of middle school, 14 years old, I am Saito Chiharu
members and friends call me chii-chan
I would like you to call me that too
my talent is .. even though I'm not really good at it
I can move my lower lip without moving my upper lip
what the hell is that?
I wanna see that!
oh she meant that!
thank you
from Oita, 15 years old, 1st year of high school, I am Hatanaka Seira
Itano Tomomi is my rival because I see her as a respectable figure
even though I am from Oita
because Oita is famous for its Kabosu Limes
I'll work hard using Kabosu power
the term kabosu power does not ring a bell ..
my hobby is erm .. I love eating very much
my talent is that I eat more than a normal person
that last part was weak ..
what is this? she eats more than a normal person?
I wonder how much more
with no gauge we cant tell
what's this
in Nogizaka46 there's 3 Seiras
but please call the 2nd year of high school's Nagashima Seira, Seirarin
my 3 life virtues are Eat, Sleep and Talk
Hi everyone, always delivering to your heart, the place of smiles and energy, from Aichi
2nd year of high school, Seirarin aka Nagashima Seira
I don't have a talent so I'll do the "GETS!" gag with all my might
wow shes already done her catchphrase
she seems like she already has a catchphrase
she seems to already have decided on one
she couldn't remember her lines so she was like "Erm erm"
she went like this "erm erm"
she was nervous right
but it's good that she's cheerful
the girls who are not present sure do get teased a lot
but there's still a lot of cute girls
yeah
Arino-san, after today's filming
if you were to choose a favorite member, who would it be?
you can choose from either the senbatsu members here or any other members
he would choose but
is there anyone who wants to do an appeal before he chooses?
ahh there's one!
then, if you would, please
I'll sing a song
instantly raising her hand, Ikuta will sing a song
here I go
What song?
thank you very much
wow that's amazing
she sung a genre of a song we didn't expect
what song is that?
it's called "Think of Me", it's an opera song
ohhh, Think of Me?
Ehh? you've sung something amazing
that's AKB's new song right?
ahh that's not it
anyone else wants to appeal?
ahh here she comes!
go for it!
it's really plain though
ahh since it's plain, then it's okay I guess~
it's okay it's okay~
what could be sorry-looking Wakatsuki's seemingly plain talent?
ahh it's okay
I can do this to my thumb
it's like this right
i'll bend it back like this
ehh? you're kidding!
like this?
can you even do that?
did you dislocate your joints?!
what the hell did you do?!
I dislocate it once first
why did you do it?
wow! show it to the camera!
I did it
no no that's not it, look at the real version
you didn't do it
I did it!
I tell you, you didn't do it
you could sing along while doing it
Think of me~
after all these appeals, he would definitely be able to choose
for sure
ehh ~ what should I do
after this, idolmaster Arino's oshimen is decided!
Hi, we are Nogizaka46!
have you already checked our official site?
profiles are of course about members this-and-that >w
many different information are up!
please check the official website!
we'll be waiting for you at the official website~
Arino's word of appeal would be very beneficial
if you would please do the honors
thats ..
you can write that on your profile too
I'm oshimen-ed by Arino-san
Who would get chosen as Arino's oshimen?
ermm .. then
Wakatsuki-san I guess?
finger!
you did it!
since when did you bend it backwards again!
you did it
with that done, please "set fire" to the girls again
the girls are growing day-by-day
"set fire"?
ahh I see, the lineup may change again
yes thats it, please treat us well
ahh, if the lineup may change, I want to see Inoue-san soon
ahh, the transformation girl
from Saitama, 16 years, 2nd year high school, I am Inoue Sayuri
since I love sentai heroes
I'll mimic their transformation
Inoue is your oshimen right?
I think so
if that happens, what would happen to Wakatsuki-san?
it would become troublesome right?
it would be shocking right?
yes it is
please choose 1 then
next episode, Nogizak46 surprise sports aptitude test!
Nogizaka46's first handshake event
the first Nogizaka46 meet-and-greet session has been decided!
23 and 24 October 2011, the event would be held at these venues for 2 days
Even though the members are still new, please come and see the girls characters which are you have not seen on TV
detailed information at Nogizaka46 official website, we await your warm response
Hi everyone, from Akita, Ikoma Rina, 15 years old