Located in the south of Tokyo, Nogizaka.
Many people come here for pursuing their dream to become a star.
And the idol group that pursuing their dream now is AKB48 official rival, Nogizaka46.
August 21th 2011, audition all over Japan held.
There were 38,934 applicants, 36 people chosen, and now has 33 people.
Then, Nogizaka46 itself, what kind of idol group they actually are?
And how is their concept? Producer Akimoto Yasushi speak directly.
The concept of Nogizaka46 is "No Concept".
The difference is, let's say in AKB48 there is an election and janken tournament one times a year.
But in Nogizaka46, the members change will be faster based on fan's votes right at the moment.
That means, the 5 years journey of AKB48 in the last 5 years must be approached by Nogizaka46 in only 5 months.
So thats why, hard training is their everyday menu.
In a very short time, there will be member changes etc.
It has just begin, but they already have a new test.
From 33 members, 15 will be choosen as senbatsu member.
From the lesson result, also from the fans comment in the official site, Nogizaka46's staff choosing the senbatsu.
Then, who will success this time?
- Shiraishi Mai.
- Yes.
The first choosen is 19 years old Shiraishi Mai.
- Ikuta Erika.
- Yes.
And next, 14 years old Ikuta Erika.
Then, 17 years old Sakurai Reika.
- Takayama Kazumi.
- Yes.
The fourth, also 17 years old, Takayama Kazumi.
And next, all choosen member got their name called one by one.
For them, senbatsu member is their first test.
After formed, they must do a hard practice everyday to become senbatsu member.
And because their hardwork has paid off, now they all cried happily.
- Last person is..
- And finally, the last choosen member name will be called, they all look nervous.
Ikoma Rina.
And the last choosen member is 15 years old Ikoma Rina.
Tears of joy arises, and they express their happiness to each other for being choosen as senbatsu member.
For them, this is a very happy moment.
And for those who were not chosen, the battle has just begin, there are still a lot of chances for them to replace the current choosen member.
Translator & QA: Part2gee & Rustyhand
Timer & QA: Koala13th & Herrysis
English Translation by Archykun & Jejedeath
Visit www.nogizakanouta.blogspot.com for more!
NOGIZAKATTE DOKO!
This is a free fansub. Please do not reupload, sell, or stream.
DON!
- It is finally started.
- Yeah it's finally started.
- Nogizakatte Doko MC, Bananaman.
Starting August 2011, this is Nogizaka46's main TV show.
- They already have their own TV show, so lucky..
- Yeah, nothing like this one before.
And for celebrating our first episode, our guest now are..
are these people, please..
Good night..
So it's Ungirls..
- Why, you have a problem?
- Yes.
Your face makes me want to puke.
1 human, 3 monsters.
And now we gonna ask the Ungirls, who's their AKB48 oshimen?
- Do you have one?
- Me..Um..Mayuyu and Yukirin..Ah I slip my tongue.
- Because black hair is pretty.
- So you like black hair.
- Because you're a thin haired skinny guy.
- Hey what's your problem!?
- Himura also have one.
- Me, Oshima Yuko..
I even bought Yuko's photobook.
He said he have his favourite part (in the photobook). If he likes something,
he'll always impersonating it.
The one where she peek from the pipe, and come out to the outside.
- You don't have to say it, have you ever seen a photobook where the person come out from the pipe?
- Basically, in that part.. Let's practice it.
So bad..
Official rival (AKB48)
Official rival? Wait we still don't know anything, did they have their own theater like AKB48 too?
Well, there is no theater.
Ee..Nogizaka46 doesn't have a theater..
AKB have one..their sister group also have..
They all have their own theater.
And when you think Nogizaka46 have a theater,
that's a big mistake! There isn't!
So they are "Idol that you can't meet".
- Why?
- There is no other way.
What is the reason?
So they're not the idol that depend on the theater.
After this Nogizaka46 members will show up. Please take a look at these fully talented members.
And..Please come in..!!
How is it? So pretty..
And they came in while waving their hand to us.
So happy..
Now is the time for introduction, so their name and face will be remembered.
Viewers, prepare your notes.
Impersonate gesture of anyone, or anything. And if they say
you're stupid because of that, nevermind because that is the point.
- Ok, let's start from here.
- No, no.
- Give me the example.
- Okay, Yamane.
- Eeeh..
- Do it, show us the example first, how long have you become a comedian ?
Umm, 11 years..
My name is Yamane Yoshiaki,
My specialty is impersonating gesture of Kappa.
Then do it.
Kiiiii ~~~
- Ok.
- Ok, thank you.
Please introduce yourself.
From ShÅnan, kid full of spirit, 18 years old Ando Mikumo.
3rd grade high school, I like to eat tsubuan (red bean paste).
Please be kind to me.
Wow, already made up.
- Ikuta Erika, call me Ikuchan.
- Ikuchan.
Yes, my specialty is piano and I can name the capital
of the whole provinces in Japan, please be kind to me.
- Tanaka can also do that.
- I can do that.
- Do you really can do it?
- What's the capital of Mie?
Mie is..hmm..now I can't remember ^^
If not now, then when?
- It's Tsushi..
- She told her..
- So it's you who can name it.
- Maybe you can also say all of it..
Come from Akita, Ikoma Rina, call me Ikomachan.
At first, maybe you think I'm cool, but actually I'm a monster..
Please be kind to me.
Everyone here are monsters too.
I will not lose.
She say "I will not lose" although this is not a war.
Grade 1 high school, 15 years old, Ichiki Rena..call me Renarin.
I have been into 10 kind of dance schools, I dance to relieve stress.
- Can you practice it now?
- Ok, I will do samba.
- That's a 'can see' pants right?
- Nevermind.
- Oh, so it's the 'can see' one.
The eldest in Nogizaka46, from Saitama, 21 years old, Yuminee or Iwase Yumiko. My hobby is playing game, please be kind to me.
- The youngest in Nogizaka46, Grade 1 junior high, 13 years old, Saito Asuka.
- Grade 1 junior high?!
I love strawberry milk, I can impersonate
the voice of Donald Duck from Disney.
Ok, do it.
- But it's so bad.
- Then we will not ask you to do it.
- You say you can do it just now..
- Ok, ok, I'll do it.
- Why facing that way? Oh, impersonating the sound?
- Yes.
- While facing the back?
- No..
- Then what?
- Ok, I'll do it now...
Not really bad.
- Nice to meet you, my name is Sakurai Reika. This is the 14th year I'm studying in all girls school.
- Eh?
14th year in all girls school.
- Eh, what does that mean?
- From kindergarten to high school, I always in all girls school.
- Oh, I see.
- There are all girls kindergarten too?
- No actually it's public..
Wait, wait..That's different.
No, I'm not lying. There are only one class for boy, so I had never been with male classmate.
- Ah, so you're never in same class with a boy, so it's always only girl classmate.
- Yep, it's like that.
- So you never talked to a boy, or..
- Yeah, actually I'm so nervous right now.
- Wow, any ideal type of man that you like?
I know where this is going. As I thought.
(It's progressing quickly! Reika-chan will choosing a boyfriend!)
From this 4 people.
- Eh, from this 4 people?
- Yes.
- Actually I kinda like Itao-san (Itsuji Itao, another japanese comedian)
- Itao-san!?
So, it's not from this 4 people..
Look like junior high student but actually I'm in 2nd grade high school, Wakatsuki Yumi, call me Myumyu.
Im good at Loli-goe (impersonating loli's voices), and can added ra-ri-ru-re-ro in every words.
What do you mean?
For example, hello I am Warakaratsurukiriyurumiri.
- Ah, I see..
- Yes.
- Can you do it to every words?
- Really?
Nogizaka Forty Six.
Rara-poruto?
Can't do it.
Sorry.
2nd grade high school, loves tomato very much, I'm Yamatomato, Yamato Rina..
I will work hard, please support me.
Will work hard? Seems legit..
- So you love tomato very much.
- Yes.
- But AKB48 Maeda, Acchan, always said that she loves tomato too.
- Wow, really?
- Yeah, hey what if the fans will just give you tomato as present?
- It's okay. I'll be happy.
- What did you say just now? Yama..
- Yamatomato.
My name is Yamato Rina, Yamatomato.
I added it to my name.
What do you mean the tomato?
- This is the tomato, Yamatomato
- Oh, I see..
- So, Yamato is..
- Enough!
Let's continue..
Japanese and France descent, Miyazawa Seira.
- Eh, mixed?
- Yes.
Call me Seira. My specialty is classic ballet which I'd learned it
for 14 years. Please be kind to me.
- Wait, practice it.
- Can I dance now?
- Yes, please.
- Maybe there will be a solo part dance later..
- Definitely.
- But I don't think they will have a song that use a classic music..
- They will have one!
- 2nd grade junior high, 13 years old, Hoshino Minami.
- Wow, so young.
I love sweet food, and lately I often doing
"Hayakuchi Kotoba" (Fast-saying word game).
Lately I addicted to it.
- What is the most popular word now? Try it.
- Eeeeh, now?
- 'Eeeeh' it's not included in Hayakuchi Kotoba.
- The most popular word this day, there is one, right?
Ok, so if I ask you one word, yo can do it?
Just an easy one.. bo-ku-bo-bu.
Say it fast 3 times. Come on.
Bokubouboububu.
- You can't do it..
- One more time please..
Alright, go on.
Bokubobubo..
What if I told you, Bokubobu is very hard one actually!
Bokuboku.
There, you say bokuboku..You should say it faster..Come on.
Bokubobuboku..
Already master one word?
How about amamuginamagomenamatamago?
Namimumemago..namagomago
Bokubobu?
3 times..Come on.
You're just addicted to it, not good at it. Am I right?
So what's your favourite word?
Akamakigami, Aomakigami, Kimakigami.
Why you like those words..
Nice to meet you, my name is Fukagawa Mai, call me Maimai..I always hungry, so give me food. I can draw a person face in 10 seconds.
10 seconds?
People always told me that I don't have any special physical character.
- Ok 10 seconds, let's count it together.
- Wish me luck.
One..Two..Three..
It's okay girls, just shut up, you're too noisy.
They told me to shut up.
- 3 people..
- Just tell us when you're done.
- She didn't see me at all.
Ok done.
- Eh, you finished? She didn't see me at all.
You don't have to see Himura-san..Oh it's done! Look!
- Eh, you really can do it..
- Yes!
- However, there is a part..
- What? Are you saying that it's bad?!
2nd grade high school, read from up or down, Nakada Kana..
Idol otaku who become an idol.Please be kind to me.
Oh, an Idol-otaku idol.
- Nakada, right?
- Yes, Nakada kana.
- What is this? Your parents were getting high when decided the name?
- I'm afraid so.
Oh look, read from up or down, still Nakada Kana !!
Maybe that is your parents purpose.
Hello, I am 17 years old, from Chiba, Takayama Kazumi. I want to become a great idol like Yamaguchi Momoe-san. Please be kind to me.
Can you sing one of Yamaguchi Momoe-san song, "Kisetsu" ?
- Yes. I can sing all of her song.
- Wow!
- Then sing it.
- Ok, I'll try.
- You know Yamaguchi Momoe-san have a very awesome glare. So please, give some emotion to it.
- Hey! She did some emotion just now.
Yamane, give some emotion too..
Ok, now!
Wow!
- In the "Don't fool me" part..
- What's the title?
Zettaizetsumei.
Nice to meet you, I come from the 4th dimension, Mayora planet, 19 years old, Shiraishi Mai. Call me Maiyan, I will work hard, please support me.
- This one come from the 4th dimension..
- Yes..
Then, how did you get here?
- 4th dimension is inside the Doraemon's pocket.
- Tell me how did you get here?
- From the sky.
- The sky?
- Sky is 3rd dimension..
- Okay, okay, I come from Doraemon's pocket.
So you're one of Doraemon's tool..Shiraishi Mai !!
Yeah, it's like that.
- If that's your concept, it is still not perfect..
- You still can do better.
- You're so different in the photo.
- Yeah, she has cool and sexy image.
- Her image is like Kojiharu.
- Yeah! You wrote it, you're Kojiharu's rival right?
Yes!
- Hmm..Mayora?
- Yep, Mayora.
- You love mayonaise, right?
- Yeah, really love it.
What food you usually eat with mayonaise?
- Yakisoba.
- So, you can always eat mayonaise?
- It's not like that..
So it's not Mayora..You're not always eat mayonaise.
Next time when we give mayonaise..you will be like..
Thank you.
And during this time, important things happen!
Attention!
Actually, we have an important announcement.
- I bet all of you have heard about Kami7.
- From AKB48..
Nogizaka46 didn't use the Kami7, but..
Nogizaka 7fukujin.
Nogizaka 7fukujin are the center of Nogizaka46, 7 people.
- And who are they? We will announce it now.
- Eeeh!
Already decided?
- Ok,  I will call the name.
- Nervous.
Are you ready...Yes, this is the 7fukujin election.
The first one is...
Finally, Nogizaka 7fukujin election, members crying, and the choosen is..