Tonight's Nogidoko, members take a test to check their idol aptitude!!
Scary, scary, scary!!
Members uproar! Innovative answers galore!
What did you just say?
And an unexpected past of a member surfaces
Will anyone unsuited to be an idol surface!?
DON~!
Nogidoko has began, we're your hosts Bananaman!
We will be in your care!
And for today's guests .. there is none present today ..
We are present! We are here!
A significant number of us are right here!
They have appeared
Er .. you all are Bokunchi right?
A play on this comedian trio's group name
We are Wagaya!!
They are Wagaya!
It seems like the members has changed yet again
Last week around 5 new girls appeared on the show but ..
This week the lineup has changed again
Those who have switched in please raise your hand
The lineup has changed alright
The senbatsu lineup would change frequently
The lineup changes every week
First of all, a self introduction for the 4 girls who has been selected for the 1st time
Born and raised in Osaka, 2nd year of high school, I'm Nishino Nanase
Since I love drawing, erm ..
If there is a request, I can draw almost anything on the spot
You must have done something for this moment?
I didnt ..
It seems like a trend to say you didn't do anything when asked if you did something
It happens often
From Hokkaido, 18 years old, I'm Hashimoto Nanami
Lately I have started growing leeks
I will try my best with all I've got. I'll be in your care
You don't seem to have any spirit on you ...
I've recently came from Oita prefecture
Leaving that aside, I love eating
I'll do my best! I'll be in your care!
Hakata dialect
Oh! Ganbaru-ken!
You didn't mention your name at all ..
All you did was self-appeal!
Hello! From Hiroshima, 13 years old, 1st year of middle school, I'm Wada Maaya!
I have yet receive a cute nickname like the others so please give me a nickname!
Bye ~
Are you learning english?
No I'm not!
And this time, to check how suited are the members as idols
All 33 members take on an idol aptitude test!!
The results would be announced in the studio!
The 1st section of the idol aptitude test is this!
General Knowledge Test!
An idol needs to have a certain amount of general knowledge
How much general knowledge they have
And also to witness the birth of "innovative" answers!
1st of all, the general knowledge test!
Of course if you can answer the question its great
But when you can't answer it, it would fall on how you answer it to make it good for variety
We are also looking for that
Also find out the baka of the group right?
For that part, please make sure you guys prepare for that later okay?
Didn't I say so? For the sake of variety
The right way to answer a question wrongly .. there might be a chance later
You guys should get ready
Then, shall we get going?
If you tell me at this point of time, I'll get nervous ..
What you have just said didn't enter my ears
1st of all, the announcement of the member who got the best score in the test!
Nakamoto
Thank you very much
You weren't stellar at sports
You are better at intellectual stuff right?
Thats right!
Shes the brainy type
Shall we take a look at the questions? First things first, the 1st question is this
泥臭い can also be intepreted as Unrefined
Answer: 'Soil' Prime Minister
Prime Minister Noda who was elected this September, what has he been called that is similar to the odor of mud?
It just happened recently right
What was he called?
First up, Matsumura
This is Matsumura's answer
Correct!
You knew this?
Yes, I heard it from the news
Ahh, thats good to hear
Then, lets go with Wada next
Nattou is fermented soybeans
Nattou
Nattou Prime Minister?!
But if you consider stickiness of the nattou into account with the question ..
Is that what you meant?
I didn't know how to read the kanji of 泥臭い
泥臭い: Unrefined
I didn't read the Kanji of Doro (Mud) and only read the Kanji of Kusai (Smelly)
And I thought the answer would be nattou
Well, you couldn't read the Kanji right?
Ah, you haven't been taught the Kanji for Mud since you're still in year 1 of middle school
Yeahs, I haven't learnt it
Etou
here
Etou's answer
Dustcloth Prime Minister
Well, the answer was derived from dirtiness
The odor of mud .. the dirtiness of mud
Its the odor of mud
They have different meanings!
Because that was the only hint available
Using that as a hint right?
I was thinking of writing the base of the shoe or dustcloth as the answer
Yeahs the base of shoes stink of mud!
Is that so? It differs from people to people!
-Shiraishi
-here
Shiraishi's answer, here
The base of a shoe
Maybe you both were thinking the same thing
I see
Shiraishi do your shoes stink of mud?
Nonononono
Its smelly!
Is it smelly?
I'm just joking ~
Forget it ..
You were a little disappointed back there
Shiraishi whats the smell of your own shoe?
I have never smelt it
She went like "I have never smelt it"
Next question, which famous person said this phrase "The earth is blue"?
The answer is Yuri Gagarin, an astronaut, but ..
Lets look at Shiraishi's answer
Kanpei Hazama-san
He ran the marathon right?
The earth is blue
I thought the person circled the globe, and I thought the person was looking at planet Earth
Miyazawa Seira's answer
Oda Yuji-san
An actor and singer
It was bluee!!
He said "Its awesome that I was born on this Earth"
Well then, shall you guys attempt this question?
But the answer has already been flashed!
Well then only Tsubokura will attempt this question
You don't necessarily have to be comical, if you know the correct answer you can just say it
Now then, who was the person who said this phrase?
Kosuerin
Kosuerin-chan??
Wrong wrong
Gagarin
Ahh! Gaga .. I only remembered rin
You got the rin part correct
Ahh .. I see!
The CEO of Apple Inc, Steve _____?
Answer: Steve Jobs
Next question, the CEO of Apple Inc, Steve who?
The correct answer is Steve Jobs but ..
First up, Ikoma
Here is her answer
Steve Jobs, correct answer!
I got it correct!
For this question out of all 33 members, only Ikoma got it correct
Ikoma you did it!
This can't be!
You can't do sports, maybe you are the study type?
That might be true ~
Rola is a Vivi model known for her unique way of speaking
She spoked like Rola
Here is Hatanaka's answer
Err .. Steve Lemon!
Steve Lemon!
Was it due to the company being named Apple?
Yes thats it, erm
Apple in japanese is Ringo right?
And apple belongs to the fruits family
when I thought of fruits, Lemon came to my mind
So I wrote Lemon down
So you wrote Steve Lemon as the answer right?
Next, Nishino
Nishino's answer, here it is
Stevenson
Ahh .. answers like these are good for variety
This answer is awesome
This is? Stevenson?
Such a person exists right?
Well, if we searched, we would probably find someone called Stevenson
No one comes to mind when I think of the name Stevenson
Because I didn't know who was Stevenson ..
Because you didn't know who was he, you wrote him down as the answer? Opposite style of answering?
Lets move on, Takayama
Takayama's answer, here!
Steven Spielberg
You went and ended the name with 'n'
You added an 'n' consonant into the answer?
In comparison, Nakada's answer, here
Stevenberg
Stevenberg?!
Were you intending to write Steven Spielberg or someone that name contains 'Berg'?
I wanted to write Steven Spielberg but ..
I didn't know how, so I just wrote what I think it was spelled as and it ended up as Stevenberg
You just renamed Steven Spielberg
Everyone just added a 'n' consonant at the end eh?
Well there aren't really many Steves ..
They probably thought the answer wouldn't start with Steve
They definitely thought the 'n' consonant needed to be included
They thought the answer would definitely not contain 'Steve'
Answers also went all the way to 'Steven'
Now, Himura-san
Yes?
But the answer already appeared
Who is the CEO of Apple Inc? Steve what?
Steve .. Williams!
Hes a pro wrestler!
Terry Gordy's tag team partner
Oh thats Terry Gordy!
You made that up right?
Well we don't know about that right?
You whispered to me asking me if it went alright
It went alright, thank you
Well then, Tsubokura
Ehhh?!
Well of course you should answer it
The CEO of Apple Inc, is Steve who?
Steve Fuon
You know, you're interesting!
No, Himura-san you're the interesting one!
You're amazing!
Next! Lets move on to the next question
Next question, Kato Cha, who married a lady 45 years his junior
Sakai Maasaki who married a lady 22 years his junior
This style of marriage, which recently became popular, is called 'Toshi no Sakon'
Toshi no Sakon: When the age difference between couples is larger than the age of the lady herself
Matsumura!
Matsumura's answer, here
Yabakon
What did you mean by this answer?
Due to the vast gap between the couple's ages, they might go 'Thats bad!' .. I guess?
I meant it in a good way
Like 'Thats bad' ~
Thats bad eh?
This buzzword is popular
So I capitalized on it
Hashimoto's answer
Care (Nursing)
This is a little over the top ..
This is a little disrespectful
The way you answered this question
Hes in the pink of health
Then, Tsubokura
Yes?
You're good at this
You're blessed by the stars today eh?
You're someone who belongs to this kind of variety
What do you call someone who marries a lady way below his age? What Kon?
Someone-who-captures-young-ladies-kon
Which is the incorrect answer
That isn't the correct answer right?
Yatabe
Yatabe has the right answer
What do you call a person who marries a lady way below his age?
"Tea Ceremony of the Year"
Construct a sentence using the following phrase. The phrase is: To trip someone up
The habit some people have of grabbing onto small mistakes made by another person and correcting them, a nitpicker
Lets take a look at Ikoma's answer
Sorry, but could you pass me that plate that has the fried squid? I want to eat that.
You wanted to eat that right?
The last part was cute
This is hilarious!
The last part about you wanting to eat the fried squid was cute
This is almost totally correct right?
In another context this is correct
The next question is this
Make a sentence using the phrase "A piece of cake"
Oh, a piece of cake huh
Shiraishi
A piece of cake, grandma out in the fields with a scythe collecting the tea leafs
This is funny!
This is interesting!
What do you mean by this sentence?
I thought it was a grandma growing tea leafs out in the fields
And she uses the scythe to harvest the tea leafs .. I don't know ..
You meant the collection action of the tea leafs?
Ahh so thats what it meant
Oh, collecting the tea leafs, I see what you meant
This isn't something to cheer about!
You've got it wrong you know, even though you Yay-ed
Next is the test of imagination!
Complete the Senryu which starts with "The truth is"
Nagashima
The truth is, it would be bad if I do not slim down. But I still ate.
But you continued to eat despite that!
Instead of "But I want to eat" you said "Thats why I ate"
But you still ate!
To be fat is really unsightful you know
You are not one to talk!
But its the truth, if you're fat, there isn't any good outcomes
Next up is the test of the member's expressiveness
The girls have to draw something based on the given topic to express themselves, only relying on what they remember of it
For the first theme, this is the task
A kangaroo!
They need to hold back while drawing this
No one shouldn't draw this wrongly
Well then, first up, Nishino
Nishino you are good at art right?
Nishino's drawing, here
You're good!
The drawing is good and cute too!
This is really good!
Whats the noticing point of this drawing?
Its large legs
She also drew the baby in the mother Kangaroo's pouch
In the pocket right?
You're good at this, really
It looks cute too
Next up, Hashimoto
Hashimoto, you seem like you are good at art
You seem like you are able to calmly observe objects
Well then lets take a look, here
What is this?!
What is this!
Where does it's legs bend at?
Scary scary scary scary!!
It looks like its carrying its child in a bucket!?
Actually, I study in an arts university
Say what?
What did you say?!
I study in an arts university
ARTS UNIVERSITY?!
Please stop going!
You're kidding me right?
You study in an arts university?!
What do you study in university?
Spatial Design
You don't seem to be capturing any spatial design in this
If I have a design template
So if you have a template, you're good at it?
Well, average ..
So your drawing becomes like that if you don't have a template
This would be good as a T-Shirt design
Next up, Ikoma!
Ikoma's kangaroo, lets take a look!
It looks like its talking
Its saying something
What is it saying?
Its saying "Teriku Teriku"
Teriku teriku?
It has an adam's apple
When you zoom out and look at the entire picture
It seems like theres a nest
Inside the nest, it seems like
there are 2 baby kangaroos that look the same as the father kangaroo
They are similar as the father kangaroo, crying out Teriku teriku
Is it the kangaroo's children?
They are the kangaroo's children
They are the kangaroo's children right?
Yes they are
But the one in the father kangaroo's pouch is different!
Its a rabbit!
Its cute!
-This is different from the others right?
-This is a rabbit stuffed toy
Stuffed toy?!
Why did you draw a stuffed toy inside the kangaroo's pouch?
I wanted to draw it's child but ended up drawing a rabbit
I see
You wanted to draw the child but ended up drawing a rabbit right ~ ?
The task to draw a kangaroo turned out like this, lets move on to the next task
The next task is this!
Ahh .. well this is difficult I guess, who knows?
Would they know about this?
First up, Nishino!
First of all, lets take a look at Nishino's Sphinx
Here it is!
Wow its good!
Its a little scary
Its face looks a little manly but you've managed to capture the main features of the Sphinx
I can tell its the Sphinx
You're good at drawing
Next, shall we look at art student Hashimoto's drawing?
Well, you do belong to an arts university
Please draw this well
Hashimoto's sphinx, here
What is this?!
This looks like it has been drawing by a little boy
Next up is .. Ikuta
Ikuta's Sphinx
Ikuta seems to be able to pull this off
Lets take a look, here
Whats the blobby thing at the bottom?!
I wonder whats that disgusting thing
What the hell is this!
I thought my drawing was good so I added the legs below
Ughhh .. this is disgusting!!
This Sphinx looks like it could walk at a very fast speed!
It seems like this Sphinx has traveled from that distant pyramid in the picture
But this picture is still considered acceptable
EHHH?!
Lets take a look at Eto's picture
Here it is!
This is the Merlion right!?
The Sphinx went to Singapore!
Its the Merlion right?
I thought the Merlion was the Sphinx
-I thought it was something of that structure
-But you know what a pyramid is
I know that the Sphinx is from Egypt
Still .. But still this can be considered as the Sphinx
Nononono, its completely out!
Next, Shiraishi's Sphinx is this!
What what what is this?!
What is this!?
This looks like the ghost of Nami Hie
What is this!
Its a ghost ~
What is its state of position?
This position
Its turned around with its back facing the front?
Even the eyes are totally white, what does it stand for?
Because I was in a rush
In a rush?
Its unfair for you to say that!
Its unfair to say that! You shouldn't be rushing!
Rushing through a test?
Theres no such thing as that
Only you took a long time to complete the test?
This design can also be turned into a T-Shirt
But .. this is still considered good
Nonono, it can't be!
Wada Maaya
Lets look at Wada Maaya's picture
You're kidding me
The Sphinx, here it is
What the hell is this?!
You crossed the border! WOAHHH!
You totally ditched the topic
You ditched the topic totally
This isn't like those history observers studying about the Sphinx right?
This is supposed to be the Sphinx right?
This is Sphinx's older brother perhaps?
You did a good job looking at it
Look at the bottom part of this picture of the "Sphinx"
This person is reading a book
Neapolitan is written on the cover of the book
Carbonara is also written on the cover
This person looks like he's really studying about pasta
But the book's title is "Sphinx"
Is the book about Sphinx or what?!
What is this about? I really want to hear what is this all about
What is this? Does this persons have any relations to pasta?
He is the person who created pasta
The person who created pasta, Sphinx-san?
This is amazing ..
Interesting drawing right?
I would love it if everyone's drawings were turned into an animation
Ahh that? We didn't do that!
Perhaps I said too much?
Sugiyama
Next topic is an ideal pet to have
The members think of a pet they wish to keep and express it in through a drawing
For this topic, we will also start off with Nishino
Nishino's ideal pet, here!
Wow .. amazing!
Seriously you're good at this!
It looks like its actually moving
What is this? There are some petals swirling around it
When you go near it, it would emit a nice smell
Ahh I get it ..
This pet is not a dog or something similar to it?
Its closer to a deer or something like that?
Yes
In the future, I'm not sure what but when Nogizaka46 is having live tours, you could design the tour T-Shirts
Do it, you have the talent for it
Wada
Woah, erm .. is this Hirano Remi!?
Hirano Remi is an actress
Ahh! This looks like Hirano Remi!
Its this small
Oh, this pet is miniature in size
What is its size? Around 10cm?
Its 5cm tall
Ohh, how does its voice sound like?
Its voice is very low pitched
Low?! Shouldn't its voice be high pitched instead?
It seems like it would have a high pitched voice
The topmost button seems like its ..
The topmost button is attached onto its skin
Ehhh 8metres tall!?
Right after this, a shocking piece of work makes its appearance!?
Theres still more
EHHH!?
Takayama's drawing, here it is
This doesn't come through ..
Its 8 metres!?
EHHH 8 METRES!?
I really wanted to keep a toy poodle, but
I now live at my hometown
Its quite tedious traveling to Tokyo
I wanted a vehicle for traveling so I mixed them together
You will ride this 8m toy poodle to work?
Yes, I'll come to work in this
Is the current color of its fur okay?
Yes, something blueish
Something blueish ~
Last up, Hashimoto!
-Well, she should not disappoint us here
-You are from an arts university after all
Right after this, finally the unveiling of art student Hashimoto's atrocious pet!?
Last up, Hashimoto
-Well, she should not disappoint us here
-You are from an arts university after all
Here it is
What is this? Do you want an old man that looks like that?
No, its size is miniature
Ahh, the size is miniature right?
Would it be able to talk?
It would just stay in one corner
Its a pet that would just do its own thing without talking?
It already looks like that ..
In the next episode, the events that unfolded at Nogizaka's Meet-And-Greet Session would be revealed!
We are Nogizaka46! Have you already checked our official website?
The profiles are of course, about member's this-and-that, a variety of information are up!!