21 August 2011, from a nationwide audition which saw 38,934 auditionees, 33 girls were selected to form Nogizaka46
Compared to AKB48 and their annual senbatsu elections
girls can be switched anytime from senbatsu to ensure the group grows
And on the 4th broadcast a sudden change!
On the top lane, did some of the members sitting there change?
They have changed!
They have sure changed!
Finally the member switching has commenced!
Tonight, the new senbatsu members are introduced!
Furthermore, in the surprise sports test, the sports aptitude of all 33 members are tested!
DON ~!! Nogizaka tte doko has begun .. and lets introduce our guest for this time!
He's Hosokawa Shigeki-san
Hosokawa-san you have established an image that you are knowledgeable about Kaden
Kaden = Japanese tattoo and kanji art
What about idols?
I like idol kaden
What is idol kaden?
Idol kaden is like BOOM it blossoms and it's like flower buds
The recently switched senbatsu members are present in the studio
So they can be changed just like that?
It's not that the program has changed
Due to certain circumstances the senbatsu members change frequently
Oh that concept has already began?
Ever since the start, I do not really understand the switching
Some members present in the previous episode are not here now
Oh is that so?
Since they're here, lets give the new senbatsu members a chance to introduce themselves
Oh yes
Please come forward
Please give me your heart, nice to meet you
from Saitama, 16 years old, Sayunyan aka Inoue Sayuri
About the VTR in the previous episode that we saw
You mimicked the sentai .. something
I love sentai heroes
sentai heroes = power rangers
May I?
I'll go with my favorite transforming sentai, Goseiger
Transform! o.O''
Here she comes
You're a rider right?
Yes I am, I want to scout her
I want to open the pink box
My marble-like eyes are my charm point
I come from Oita, 18 years old, Eto Misa
Please call me Misa Misa, I'm in your care
Always delivering something to your heart, the place of smiles and energy, from Aichi
2nd year of high school, I'm Seirarin aka Nagashima Seira
I'm always giving my all so please cheer me on!
It's your own catchphrase but you seemed lost
I was a little nervous
And I blundered
You're somewhat cheerful
You're like "Heyyyy"
Nice to meet you, I'm Nakamoto Himeka, 3rd year of middle school, 15 years old
Nogizaka46's #1 pampered child, a little lonely, please call me Himetan
Sayurin Sayurin Sayurin-rin
Sayurin Sayurin Sayurin-Go
I love anime and manga, I am Nogizaka46's 2D world representative
I'm Sayurin aka Matsumura Sayuri, I'll be in your care
2D representative doesn't really have any meaning to it, what do you mean?
My dream is .. erm, because I really love 2D stuff like anime and manga
I want to become a citizen of an anime world
There we have it!
What's the anime or manga you recently took a liking to?
As for recently
I'm watching anime currently
the anime "Boku wa tomodachi sukunai*"
* I have little friends
I have little friends, are you talking about Himura?
No you've mistaken!
After introducing the new senbatsu members
The surprise sports test for every member is up next!
The sports aptitude of the members gets totally exposed!
For this sports test, you were told to come in attire that would be easy to move about in right?
Your own clothes right?
There might be some with really lame clothes
Fans would be interested in these things
They would observe you all and be like "oh so this is her fashion sense"
It's something to look forward to right?
First up its the 50m dash for the High Schoolers
I was pretty fast when I was in elementary school
I have confidence
but recently my weight increased
My body might have become heavier
But I'll do my best!
She's fast!
She has good form
Matching her confidence, her time is 7.88 seconds
Since this is a sports test
Because I wore this, I'll work hard not to lose to this
Shirt words = Gold Dragon
She seems fast
Woah she's fast!!
But she reached the goal
Even though she fell before the goal, she still reached the goal
And also a high record of 8.06secs
Since I gave it all I got, I'm satisfied
I am at an age where my body can't keep up with my feelings
In order not to show this, I'll do my best and run
She looks like the sporty type
Halfway through unglamorous moments kept surfacing
A miracle mistake happened, both of her shoes came off
With a timing of 9.47 secs, she dragged down the average timing
Please let me try once more!
I am aware that I am lousy at sports
In order to run faster
I'll discard my cuteness and give it all I've got!
Look at the way she runs
Nostalgic way of running
What's my timing?
10.19secs
Eh?! 10.19secs?!
I actually ran for real
I was shocked at this timing
I've never run with all I've got before
I'll put my best effort today
Almost off to a false start, she seems to be jogging
Her timing, the worst out of everyone, 10.71secs
Sakurai you're fast
Fast!
7secs!
Do you have any past experience?
I don't have any sports experience
But I was good at running since I was little
Good?
My personal best is 7.04secs
You're the only one that ran within 7secs range, you're the fastest
I was shocked about those that had timings of more than 10secs
You didn't ran in the last part right?
She seemed as if she was going to buy groceries
The next test is the 3-tier jump
Since it was the first time for most of the members to challenge this
The rule was changed to "free jump after 3 steps"
It's my first time doing this
and I'm a little nervous but I'll give it my best!
Sayunyan: I don't wanna see this!
Uwahhh she did it!
It was clear that there were more than 3 jumps
Of course only 3 steps were counted so her record is 4m 10cm
I skipped :X
I think it's difficult, but I'll aim to jump around 6m
6m is gonna be hard to reach
You're kidding me right?
Suddenly forgetting how to jump, Ikoma's record is lower than Inoue at 3m40cm
Just jump like that
Ehh? That jump became a record?
I totally can't jump at all
What a slow approach
You're kidding me, you're kidding me right
A total flop, her record is of course the worst 3m30cm
Isn't this awesome?
What the hell are you doing?
I want to flutter like a butterfly
I'll use tomato power to give it my best shot
Totally betraying her portrayed character
Her record is the best so far at 7m20cm
I ate tomatoes
Perhaps it's because of my tomato power
Next is the newly added senbatsu member Eto Misa
Showing her good athletic ability with a record of 7m15cm
Please look at this! One of my foot is further front
They measure the back leg
I'll do my best! Without tripping over!
She's amazing
That pile of sand is too shallow!
You keep falling
But I did my best
Ikoma-chan you did quite bad
At first you said you wanted to go for 6-7metres
I thought I would 'fly' normally
Ahh you don't have any athletic ability
You don't know your surroundings
When you move you don't know your surroundings
I'm sorry
Wakatsuki-san, you trip and fall at the end
I frequently trip over
But you did well
In TV they want those kind of scenes
How would she be expressed in Kaden?
Ahh let me think
Washing machine I guess ~?
She tries her best
Next is high-jump
Firstly, 90cm which a middle-schooler would be able to clear, Ikoma challenges this
Stop the video :x
She faces the bar head-on, an unprecedented failure
There was only footage of you falling
This is interesting
and then, shichifukujin Nakada Kana
Once more
Sorry, but I can't jump
The height of the bar - 100cm
Even though its 100cm I'll give it my best shot
Ouch it hurts, I fell from the mat
Yea it hurts
The speediest of the members Sakurai
Jumping upwards Miyazawa
and including Noujou, these 3 cleared 110cm
Only 1 of the members challenged 115cm
I have experience in ballet so I'm counting on my flexible legs
Oooo amazing
I've jumped over
Most of you can't jump
Most of you jumped forward, this is the first time I've seen a frontal high-jump
This is rare
It's a miracle, the way you didn't touch the pole when you jump
It's a new style of jumping, the way to jump without touching the bar
Definitely not touching the bar
You can't do that next
I jumped but ..
I tried to jump, but there was the pole there ..
The pole is there for you to jump over, that has been decided internationally for high-jump
Following, the sport which the members should all be able to do, but an unexpected twist occurs
Firstly, Shichifukujin Ikuta challenges this
You can't do it?
I can do "Clothes hung out to dry"
I'm Ichiki Rena
Oh Ichiki-chan
If it's "Swallow" I can do it
Why does everyone has weird techniques
That's a swallow?
I'm Saito Asuka
Show us what you're made of
She looks like she can pull it off
Oh she can't do it
I would like to challenge "Roasted Whole-pig"
Why roasted pig?
I did it!
Why does everyone have a weird technique
I'm Ando Mikumo
I'm counting on you to show us
I can do Daruma spinning, can I?
Here I go
They're horrible
Too many of you can't do it
Everyone did something weird
It's like you can't do the actual thing so do something else
Ikuta you did the "Clothes hung out to dry"
Most of us who couldn't do it were hanging like that during our break time
Oh I see
Those member that couldn't do it?
Do that it's fun ~ it's super fun, something like this?
Doing the "Clothes hanging out to dry" would only make your abdomen hurt
Indispensable to dance, a flexible body is needed
Firstly, shichifukujin Takayama
You're too stiff
Next, thanks to daily strict dance lessons, Hashimoto got a record of 64cm at 3rd
Shichifukujin Nakada, which unexpectedly retired at high-jump, scored 2nd position with a record of 65cm
And the top is Miyazawa with ballet experience, she got a score of 69cm
It's amazing, there's lots of flexible girls
Takayama .. 22cm is ..
You didn't even stretch right?
When I looked at the footage I was also surprised
It's like shes looking at the alarm clock in the morning
Can you stretch forward?
Forward is okay
Why can't you bend backwards?
Backwards .. I can only bend like this at best
If I bend my knees I can go like this
What happens if in dances you have to bend backwards like this, you be like that
That's a crocodile!
Next is holding ones breath underwater after exercise, this can test member's staminas
The correct method is to jog on the spot for 1min and proceed to hold your breath underwater for as long as possible but
This time, to further see their character, there will be a camera to observe their faces
The average for girls in their 10s is 16secs
Firstly, shichifukujin Shiraishi challenges this station
Ahh something amazing came out
that's bubbles!
I haven't got 1st in any of the tests
Since this is the last, I thought it would be great if I got 1st
Hope she would give it her all
She's gasping
She seemed to have came up too fast
How did she do?
ahh!
Ahhh , only better than the average by a little
Suffocating
Next, she got demoted from senbatsu, Ando Mikumo, can she show us her resolve?
Wow amazing! 51secs?!
The stamina I gained from basketball has shown itself
Soft-bodied Nakada, what about her stamina?
her eyes are open~
It's very scary you know~
She only lasted 8secs
The most problematic at sports, Ikoma challenges this
What the hell are you doing?!
Her record is a mere 1.81secs
Whats up with you?
It was tough
Yeah!
Whats with you Ikoma-chan?
Ikoma-chan you are lousy at all sports!
You can't do it?
I thought I could do it, but I went ughh and thought it was bad so I surfaced for air
Was it bad?
What would happen if you didnt surface?
I would have died!
Died?!
And Nakada, she opened her eyes while holding her breath under water?
Why did you open your eyes?
I thought I was supposed to open my eyes
If that was the case it would have been bad!
From now on, you all would have lives and have to sing multiple songs back-to-back
After 3 songs everyone would be out of breath
You have to train!
During training how is Ikoma? Does she do it right?
She can hold her breath for long during training, she goes ahhh for a very long time
Oh shes able to do that
How about we have an ahhh competition now
With that said, an ahhh competition to see who is the best at holding her breath
Who would be the winner?
here we go
Start!
Isn't that too fast?
20secs have passed
Oh Ikoma-chan .. She's done?!
How unexpected
Go for it!
She's still going!
Inoue 48secs
Even though i couldn't excel in the sports test .. wow amazing
This is their talent or weakness, everyone seems to understand themselves, this could help for their dances
Those that weren't good at sports left a deep impression but
On average, you all are above average for your sports aptitude
As a whole, you all are people that are good in sports
As a whole yea, there still are people pulling down the average
Here the guest announces his oshimen after observing them upfront!
Who will get chosen?!
Among these girls, please choose 1 oshimen
Based on who left the deepest impression this time ..
Wakatsuki Yumi I guess, because of her Tshirt
Thank you very much
That's good right?
She did well in the 3-step jump right?
I shall write this on my profile, washing machine
For an example, you're a washing machine right?
Today, it's Ikoma-chan's mission to say the ending
All of a sudden, Ikoma is tasked to do the ending, what would she do?
Please say the ending for this episode
Erm, Nogizaka46's ..
Hi we're nogizaka46
Have you checked our website?
Profiles are of course about member's this-and-that
A lot of info are on display
Please check Nogizaka46, please come and see us!
We would be waiting for you at the official site!
If you would please, Ikoma-chan
The one who pulled down Nogizaka46's sports aptitude average, Ikoma Rina, from here on please support Nogizaka46
~Bye Bye~