Today on Nogizaka Doko,
members' personal clothes fashion check!
From just one quick look, Miyazawa doesn't look very good.
The outcome of their everyday lessons will be revealed for the first time.
Nogizakatte Doko?
Their fashion sense shocked Bananaman.
Nogizaka personal clothes fashion check!!
Translation: NeruestSub
Don!
We are Nogizaka Doko's MC, Bananaman.
Here are the Nogizaka46 members for today.
-They're cute. -Of course they're cute.
Our guest for today is Ogi-san!
"Ogi Hiroaki" Japanese Comedian.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Ogi-san, are you currently doing a variety show with AKB?
Yes, on CS.
-On CS? -Yes.
Do you guys even go for oversea shooting?
-We went to Australia for two days. -With AKB? -Yes.
So if everyone work hard, you guys might have the same opportunity.
Lets go together!
Wanna go, wanna go, wanna go...
Arent they currently your "rival"?
Well...from just a quick glance over everyone
you realized that AKB48 is more prettier.
You said something like this even that you have a show with them?
It's because we have a show together, that's why I have the confident to say that.
AKB's proportion are really yabai.
That's really bad. That statement.
Today we have Saito Chiharu and Higuchi Hina.
This is the first time they appeared on this show.
Also, today's plan for the show is...
Umm...Who should read the plan this time?
-Himura-san! -Of course its me!
Who's has the most fashion sense within Nogizaka46,
personal clothes check!!
You sound like you're on All Night Fuji.
All Night Fuji (A popular Japanese TV show in the mid-1980s.)
Nogizaka personal clothes fashion check.
The judge will be the main editor of a fashion magazine called SEDA.
Every year the magazine has to review thousands of models
by the main editor Oyamada-san.
Today my fashion image is based on nostalgic doll style.
-Kawaii. -Aint that kawaii?
The one-pieces dress fit very well with her cute aura.
I think this is really good,
and the stocks are lovely.
But the heels shoes is in red color.
If she matched them with a simpler color like brown or black color,
the overall feeling could've been more outstanding.
What score should I give? Let me think.
65 points.
Next up, its Miyazawa Seira's with the cool and sexy style clothes combination.
-So Miyazawa like this style huh? -Not bad, Miyazawa.
-Where's Miyazawa? -Over there.
She wore a very conspicuous stripe,
it really fit well with her mature aura.
I'll give 90 points.
-Fukagawa. -Fukagawawa~~~
My main fashion focus for today is about this small jacket that I don't usually wear.
So to not make it look too tight, I wore a loose T-shirt inside to balance them.
And actually, I sewed this small jacket all by myself.
That jacket? Really?
The lower part is a little bit off.
But the jacket's really hard to make, its hard to believe someone actually made that alone.
The skirt fit really good, like a balance between them.
The only problem is that why did she picked that shoes.
That is the only problem.
If she had a grey or monotone outfit, it would be better if the shoes were black.
75 points for her.
Next up is Sakurai Reika, who wore a simple one-piece dress.
A outfit with black and white color only.
What will the main editor comment on this dress?
The dress is very modern and simple, really good fashionable.
But why did I get an old women aura from her?
You just got burned, girl.
For advice, if the overall color is simple like only black and white color,
to avoid that it looks like a dress you would've wear when you're going to a funeral,
she can wear a long stockings, or add clothes with a little bit of colors on it.
It will become better, please try it next time.
I'm really sorry, but 40 points.
Really!!?
Next up, Hashimoto Nanami with a long white blouse and a colorful shawl on her.
-Its colorful. -Her legs are long.
A slender body coordinated with a colorful shawl.
The main point will be the colorful shawl.
Oh... Very nice!
The shawl looks very nice, and she's really suitable for a short hairstyle.
Her fashion sense is very good.
90 points.
Next up, Nakada Kana with a black shawl which has the opposite of Hashimoto's style.
She has a different image than the usual her, very mature.
-very fashionable. -This is Nakada?
The main editor gave 80 points.
Next up, Iwase Yumiko.
A dress with a short jacket, a nostalgic style.
Every pieces she picked is very good if wore seperately,
but it kinda felt weird when she wore them all together.
First of all, the length of the coat and the dress did not match well together.
I don't understand them.
For the legs part, its bad too.
Maybe it will become better if she wore a black shoes.
40 points.
I'm Ikoma Rina. Today's fashion style is based on a French boyish style.
Basically I bought all of them from Uniqlo.
Uniqlo (Famous Japanese casual wear designer, manufacturer and retailer.)
Only the necktie cost a little more, guess how much did it cost?
3000 yen.
(Around $27.00 USD)
Its very boyish, as everyone from earlier wore feminine style clothes, it's very interesting.
85 points.
Miyazawa and Hashimoto got the highest point, 90 points. -Sugoi.
For me, I like Miyazawa's style the most.
I'm so happy.
But Miyazawa doesn't look very good over here.
What do you mean?
-But...but when I saw her personal clothes. -That kind of feeling...
That kind of Miyazawa was the cutest.
Next up, personal clothes check part two.
First up, Wakatsuki Yumi.
The knee high socks and the Middle East style shawl are her main focus.
-She looks sexy. -Her face.
Simple clothes, and the shawl has that conspicuous stripes again.
It's a mashup style, a very good mashup.
80 points.
Today's fashion point is the popular cloak coat I'm currently wearing.
The main point is the popular cloak coat.
She's able to fit a double-breasted coat with other clothes well, she's a very fashionable.
And that red color bowtie, using bowtie as accessories are really popular right now.
If the bowtie was this big, and the fact that she wore it at the side of her hair make her looks good.
-What about her legs? -The overall was very fashionable.
Only 17 years old and she already has this kind of fashion sense,
she would probably become a top fashion leader in a few years time.
90 points.
Ahh....I'll give 95 points.
Next up is Takayama Kazumi.
-That's cute. -Her legs are pretty. -She's pretty.
Dark green color stocking will leave a deep impression on everyone.
The use of dark green color means that she has a good taste in fashion too.
90 points.
I'm Shiraishi Mai.
Today's fashion point is this white knitwear.
and inside that is a dress.
A dress inside a white knitwear, that kind of fashion style.
Wearing grey stockings, and a spectacle in front of her knitwear.
-Not bad. -Yes, I agree.
She did not pick a black stocking but one with the grey color.
That makes her look more fashionable.
80 points.
Next up, Ito Marika. Combining a boot with leopard stripes, the rocker style.
And the use of hoodie and a pleated skirt works as they bring out the contrast between two styles.
The scary part is that she's only 15 years old.
The boot fits well with the purple stocking and the leopard stripes.
75 points.
Nishino.
Nishino's 95 points are the highest points so far.
Nishino is not here with us today.
-Is she not present? -Too bad.
-Is she here? Oh, Nishino is here.
Come over here Nishino.
-Did you wear your personal clothes on today too? -Yes.
-Kawai.
This style is totally different than the one shown in the video.
Little girl, open up your button, let me be happy. -No no no, no way.
If someone in the group does not have any fashion sense, you'll teach them, right?
Since you're a fashion leader.
Himura-san who do you think looks good?
Takayama, not bad.
-Kawaii. -Thank you very much.
90 points.
And you have a good figure too.
-Did you wear a dark green stocking? -Yes, that's it.
-You got a good rating. -I'm honored.
I'm actually very cautious when it comes to money, and I usually buy according to their price, not their appearance.
-You know how to pick your stuff. -Thank you.
That's fashion. Even if you did not have much you can still look fashionable.
Right... Ogi-san you and your partner were really fashionable right?
Yes...What do you mean yes!?
Shitara-san, you're the real fashionable person.
Himura-san, were you always this rustic?
WHAT ARE U TALKIN ABOUT!?
It felt like we're on an American comedy show.
Ogi-san, actually there's one more plan for today.
Ummm, who should read the title out this time?
Please use a funny way to read the title out ok?
Ogi-san!!!
What should I say?
The title of the next plan. Please make it funny. -What do you mean funny!?
Who's the best dancer in Nogizaka46!? Nogizaka Dance Skill Check!!
Nogizaka46 Dance Skill Check.
The verification dance class started 3 months ago.
Only seven best dancers among them can show their dance skill in the studio.
The seven-person who can present their dance beautifully will be able to perform in the studio.
They had to use one hour to memorize a 30 seconds dance move.
Everyone began at the same point. They'll have to learn from their teacher and adept the dance moves.
Everyone's hardworking.
Hand... leg... one...
Although its only a 30 seconds move, the moves are not easy to learn.
They'll need to mashup every moves to form a complete dance.
It will be hard for them since they only started their lessons 3 months ago.
One hour has passed.
They managed to learn all of the dance moves and were currently doing last rehearsal.
Although they only had limited time,
the members managed to digest everything their teacher had taught them.
Right before the filming start...
Ah, that's how they were during their classes.
Rekai is in the shot.
I'm excited so I decided to wear this.
-Michael Jackson. -I get that a lot.
Like you're actually performing...
Just like Michel Jackson.
Ahhh~~~~~~~♥
The test will be divided into three groups.
Who will be the one to be crowned as the skilled dancer?
Now for the second group.
They all look nervous.
-Those are some big dance moves. -Not bad.
And here's the last group.
They all learned this at the same time.
They were all smiling.
Yeah, that's good.
Finally, who will be the only seven members to perform in the studio?
Firstly, Ikoma.
Nakada.
Ikuta.
Kawamura.
Sakurai.
Asuka.
Inoue.
Everyone, good luck!
The seven members that were picked were moved to tears.
They are going to perform in the studio shortly!
Ikoma, that's right. You did well on dancing but you're kinda bad at sport?
I do not have the ability to do sports at all.
But I can dance very well.
-Sakurai, you cried too right? -"Michael".
-Yeah, I wore the jacket. -Not bad.
I tried my best, and I think I did my best.
But well, that didn't count as a failure as well.
Even if you forgot your line during a live performance, it's ok.
"The guy has a funny looking face," or maybe
"I'd never seen such things before,"
Nobody would ever say that.
Yes, they're talking about you Himura-san.
Yes, we're talking about you Himura-san.
That's why the audience is hooked, because of your face.
like "WHAT DA HELL IS THIS?"
"What the hell is this!?"
YOU SHUT UP!
The next person is Inoue. -Are you surprised?(That she was selected.)
I think so too myself.
-Even you look capable? -Yeah, you look capable.
Everyone thought I'm a capable person but actually, I'm very bad.
-No no no.
I didn't have dance lessons before this.
During the first lesson, everyone danced so well
and I thought the situation was bad for me.
That's what all this about, three months ago all of you know nothing.
But as the time progress with your continuous efforts, you grew up.
So in other words, those who Inoue had overtaken have to be really careful in the future.
If you do not start working hard...
-You're really something else Ogi-san! -It's only your first meeting with them...
-Who're you to judge them. -No no no.
So do not be overtaken.
You have to have the mentality of surpassing other people.
It will be over for you if you gave up just because you did not get picked.
Got it!?
You guys better keep up the good work.
When we saw Kawamura, we were discussing her too.
Your dance movements look good.
Did anyone ever tell you that you are a very energetic person?
What????
Very energetic indeed.
-Nobody told me that before. -Your movements are very big.
Because I love to d-d-d-dance the most.
So you like to d-d-d-dance.
I learned how to dance before.
The seven dance sichifukujin will begin their performance after the commercial break.
What? If there's a mistake its ok. Don't worry.
-You guys did well -Very good.
After this, who's the one that stole Ogi-san's heart?
Ogi-san, from what you saw today, please pick your oshimen*.
Oshimen ( 推しメン ) is a term used to describe a fan's #1 favorite member in a group.
Well...until the end, the one that stole my heart is,
my oshimen, Kawamura!
That's good.
Announcing a urgent news about Nogizaka46 here.
Shiraishi Mai's first magazine cover photoshoot!
Good morning. Onegaishimasu.
The magazine she will be featured on is "FLASH".
Usually, we(members) had a photo shoot together, but today it's only me.
I kinda felt lonely.
-Onegaishimasu. -Onegaishimasu.
Although she's very nervous, she did not forget to put a smile on her face.
And her photographer is the famous "Pervert Briefs-Man" Nozawa Hirobu-san.
Nozawa Hirobu (Famous photographer, appeared on different shows occasionally.)
Yes, yes. That's right. That's right.
Shiraishi Mai's first cover magazine will be on 26th November edition of "FLASH".
We're Nogizaka46. We'll be visiting your hometown to meet with you!
For more information, please go onto the Nogizaka46 official website!
Next Week, the quiz about Tokyo will be filled with weird and funny answers!
Konichiwa, we're Nogizaka46.
Have you checked out our official website yet?
Other than members profile, the website has everything you need to know about us.
Please do check out Nogizaka46!
And please come and see us!
We're waiting for you at our official website!