In tonight's Nogidoko, the members try out acting for the first time!
Their enthusiasm goes beyond expectations!
It's okay if you don't listen to the adults!
A sea of criticism comes out from Katsumata's mouth!
And miraculous scenes will show themselves!
What is that!
Himura goes amok in the studio!
Brought to you by IkomaSubs
For more subs visit www.Facebook.com/IkomaSubs
Translated by Jiaemi
Timed by @laNdeFalco
QC by ramenrider
DON!!
Nogidoko has begun, we're your hosts Bananaman!
And here are the members of Nogizaka46!
Yay!
These 3 members make their appearance on Nogidoko for the 1st time
And today's guest is Katsumata!
I'll be in your care! BAM!
You know, Katsumata in this world of showbiz, is known as "The Planner"
Remember this!
When they decide the members of a meeting ..
He's always included!
Because he's the person who came up with that plan
That's right!
This is true!
Is this amount of praising your accolades enough?
Thank you very much!
No problem!
But it's true, honestly!
Whatever is said or done, Katsumata has a hand in it!
It would be okay!
So today's plan for welcoming Katsumata is this!
Nogizaka46 1st acting experience!
From now on, there would definitely be drama opportunities for you all
The opportunities would definitely come very soon
For this time, the situation would be decided beforehand
There wasn't any script right?
Wow, that's awesome
They had to ad lib?
I'm looking forward to this
The first situation is this
「 Shouting towards the sea to snap out of a broken heart 」
The ending would be the best scene for this topic right?
That's true
The last part is going to be anticipated right?
First up, what kind of acting would she show us?
Wow, nice!
Oh! This somehow looks good!
Cute~!
Why?
Oh, the scene has started
You said that you would only love me!
Oh! This is good!
I won't fall in love ever again!
Your lines weren't decided for this?
Yes
That's amazing!
Next up is Inoue's first acting experience!
You have to think of your own lines right?
Don't leave me alone!
Ah?
Not bad
You said we would be together forever!
Is she crying?
You promised me that right here!
Stupid!
What would Ikoma from Akita's first acting be like?
She seems cool and composed
This is good
I wonder what's in her pocket
What's that?
What is that?
A sweet wrapper?
What did she throw?
What did you throw?
Goodbye
I want to know too
She looked at the camera
You looked at the camera!
I wonder what did she throw into the ocean
Matsumura from Osaka, what would she say while facing the sea?
Matsumura
Why did you leave me?
What's wrong with being an otaku?
It's obvious I love you more than anime!
Why won't you understand?
On a whole, they are pretty good at acting!
They composed themselves well
I was surprised!
I thought you all would be super lousy at acting
Not bad!
Not bad at all!
What is this? Amazing!
Isn't Shiraishi darn good?
You're good!
Really? Thank you very much!
You didn't have a script right? What you said was at the spur of the moment right?
Yes
That's amazing!
And Inoue
You were good
Ah, Really?
You were very good
You kicked the sand right?
Was it your plan to kick the sand or did it happen because your emotion level went higher?
Honestly, I wanted to jump into the ocean
THAT'S IT!
I thought that if there was a girl that did that, it would be amazing!
If she went into the ocean right?
It's just a small segment, but if there was a girl that would do that, she's a STAR!
I see!
I was thinking "GO FOR IT!"
I know someone who is like that, he overreacts to a small matter and blows things up in a freestyle way
And then, he once licked an amateur grandpa comedian's shoes all over
I thought that there would be no one able to win him in this area, and this person is Himura
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT ME!
THAT'S ME!
But it's about things like this right?
You had the feeling to do the same thing right?
Yes
Why did you decide not to?
I didn't want to get my uniform wet and our standing positions were decided beforehand ..
You can just push aside and not care about what the adults decide!!
There's a comedian duo called Fusoto No. 55, and in the past, the camera's angle was limited
The norm was to suit the camera's angle, but they performed their skits out of the camera's view!
Oh! I see
But they thought that they would be scolded for that so they ran away, but the producer chased them
And told them "Your skit is interesting so please come back and perform it once more"
EHHHH~
And from then on they became regulars on the show
In that context, it was good that we didn't know what Ikoma-chan threw
But .. what did you throw?
It was a pebble I picked from the ground
You threw a pebble you found on the ground?
I saw the pebble on the ground, and I thought to myself "Yay!"
So I thought it would be great if I used the pebble for the acting scene
Oh, I see!
You didn't show us the pebble, but you made eye contact with the camera right?
I merely glanced momentarily at the camera
Did you watch the last part?
Making eye contact with the camera is the thing you should not do!
Making eye contact with the camera is a no-no!
Please watch the replay of the problem-scene
Goodbye
This scene is good too as the lines were short and sweet
Wait a moment, shes looking into the camera
Totally looking at the camera
You looked directly into the camera once
It was obvious from that, that I didn't look at the camera isn't it?
No, there was once that you definitely looked into the camera
What did you look at?
EHH?!
They told me to look towards the ocean so I did as I was told
There was a camera there
So you're saying that it's the camera's fault for being there?
That's right~
The next situation is this
「 Bidding your long-time pet farewell 」
This is quite difficult right?
Isn't this tough?
Saito Chiharu's turn to portray her acting skills
Oh they used a real dog
Oh the dog is still alive
What kind of farewell is this?
Hey
Don't get angry at me
Oh? She's really ..
Thank you for all you've done
Bye bye!
This is tear-jerking
Next up, Itou Marika would challenge this scene!
Tomorrow I'll not be here anymore
That's why Momo you must
You will be adopted by a relative of mine
No, anything but this!
Ahhh~
These boots are expensive!
You were troubled by it
This has got to be a joke!
Unexpectedly, she retires halfway through!
Next up is Hashimoto Nanami, what kind of acting would she show us?
You've worked hard
It's good that you were energetic till the end
Byebye! (Laughs)
Didn't she just laughed?
Oh! What's wrong?
Wait wait! Don't do that!
Okay I get it! I'll stay longer with you
UWAHHHH!
It's the dog's fault right?
Bite her shoes again!
Bite them!
He's going to bite her shoes!
Sorry! Byebye! .. Byebye!
He keeps trying to bite her shoes
Escaped?
She escaped from the dog!
She covered her face!
That concludes this scene
She covered her face at the end right?
You were totally running away from the dog right?
I thought I shouldn't cry
You were thinking something like "If it wasn't for this dog" right?
This dog is a little bit weird and different from other dogs right?
This dog is on a godly level!
But .. Itou you wasted your chance
Itou-chan
If the dog keeps biting your shoes
It means that she should have acted as if she didn't want to leave the dog's side!
As an acting skill right?
I came with my favorite boots
And then it suddenly bit my boots .. I really wanted it to stop that!
Acting < Boots
So her boots are more important
That's right, boots are more important right?
Let's move on to the next situation, here it is!
「 A battle between female gang leaders 」
A fated confrontation
This seems feasible!
It's a school thing right?
Such things happens at school too
That's true
Let the battle between the female gang leaders start!
Ehh~
Scary!
I've got something to say to you
Ah, this is good
Sometime ago, I saw you and Yuki walking together
It does not have anything to do with you!
I saw you and him walking out of the park
Stop your griping!
What?!
You're so tiny I can't see you at all!!
Yuki is mine!!
What are you saying? He's mine!
Yuki has no feelings for you!
I love Yuki more than you do!
Are they deciding on who gets Yuki?
What the hell are you saying? I'm the one who loves Yuki the most
She's right!
Next, Takayama VS Ikoma
Keep watching for an epic moment between Takayama and Ikoma!
Sakurai Reka
Ohh! Things are getting heated up!
What the hell do ya want?
Don't go running your mouth about me!
Her being cool is good
What's with you?
Which prefecture are ya from?
Ya might not know where this is but I'll say it anyway
I'm from Chiba
What the hell was that?
By the way, I'm from Akita
Next up, 13 year old Higuchi corners Hashimoto!
I'm Hashimoto from Nogizaka High School B Class
Let's settle this after school
Oh! This is good
Fine, you're on!
Why did you come to our school for?
This is good
I can only see you as a mushroom due to your hairstyle
I can only see you as a japanese doll
You're praising her
I came here before you did
You've been @#$%^&
Say it!
What are you saying?
I see, I get the idea behind this
At the last part because she pushed your buttons resulting in you jumbling up your words
Unexpectedly you all had destructive power in your words
That's scary!
Isn't that good?
Matsumura your delinquent acting was a surprise to me
Because your outer appearance looks like you're in a daze
You can actually act like a delinquent
I tried my best
It was like we were fighting for Yuki
Oh so the Yuki you all were fighting over was me?
Thank you, that made me happy
But at the end, I actually kind of moved towards Osamu (Shitara)
Eh? Did you say that?
Ahh I didn't say that
Then I wouldn't know about it!
I'm sorry!
Eto you were good too
Is that true?
Her glare was scary right?
Perhaps there's a real delinquent among you?
The thought of that slightly worries me
What was the exchange of hometown between Takayama and Ikoma about?
Because we came from rural prefectures
It was better to use our local dialect
So we decided to say where were our hometowns
Yes .. Thats ri .. Yes ..
So that's it?
Yes that's what went on
What's with your stammering
She said everything that you wanted to say?
That's true
Here is the next situation
「 Conveying your farewell over the phone while crying 」
TEARS!!
Are there going to be tears?
Cry acting is impossible
You never know, there might be a star among them!
If you cry you're a star!
First up, Nakada Kana challenges the crying scene
It would be impossible for Kana
He hung up ..
Uwaa .. this seems good
This is good!
Right?
5mins passed
Eh?
Ah, she's waiting
Are the tears coming?
20mins passed
20mins have passed!
Ahh, but the tears seem to be coming soon
Her eyes seem to be teary
There is there is
The result after 20mins
Some tears fill her eyes
Next, Itou Nene challenges the crying scene!
Hello?
Ahh, he hung up on her
Uohh? Ehh?!
Woahh Ehhh!
Woah awesome .. AWESOMEE!!
This was immediate right?
She cried immediately!
That's awesome!
Next up, Sakurai challenges this scene
Sakurai
Sakurai quickly shifts into the mood
This is good
She's crouched up
This is awesome
Cut!
I'm sorry
Oh she didn't cry
(Staff) You didn't cry?
EHHHH?! She didn't cry?!
I didnt cry!
But isn't this awesome instead? She had us fooled
Unexpectedly an awesome fake acting
Sakurai at the ending you weren't crying?
I thought you cried
I couldn't seem to cry
Umm .. while I was waiting for my turn, I was practicing with all I've got
You couldn't seem to cry right?
I felt the feeling that the tears were coming out
And the tears seemed to accumulate in my eyes
But the mucus from my nose kept flowing out
But if you ignored that wouldn't the tears flow?
The moment I entered that room
My tears just seemed to disappear into thin air
Oh they were "reset-ed"
Himura, you previously sticked a finger into your throat
Yes I did
You did that and said "Let's starts!"
Because I kept doing that to get the vomiting feeling to force tears out, now I can just feel that feeling even without doing that
I'm the worst actor
Itou Nene
You're good! The tears came fast
Thank you
That's awesome
Yeah, you cried instantly
Yes I did
What did you thought about to cry?
When I thought about the situation where I return to my home in Gifu
Where my family welcome me back at the doorstep just made my tears start flowing
Oh so it's tears of joy!
If you make yourself feel certain feelings and thoughts you would be able to cry quickly right?
That's right
That's awesome right?
She's a genius
She's an actress!
She's an actress
Nakada you took 20mins ..
I'm sorry
No no, it's okay, you managed to cry at the end right?
I did cry but it didn't seem that obvious right?
No, I could tell that your left eye was teary
Whoever could shed tears within 30secs is an actress
That's true
Isn't the amount of pressure immense?
If the camera constantly films you for 20mins straight, your tears would instead not flow
That's true
「 From a northern country 」 First Love Jun-kun couldn't cry while hearing Ozaki's song, couldn't shed tears at that time too
The staff kept waiting patiently for him, Jun-kun was so touched by the staff's patience
That he cried and his tears wouldn't stop flowing, those tears are the same as hers
Oh .. because they waited so patiently for him
Let's move on, the next situation is this
「 A confession to your senpai whom for 3 years you had a one-sided emotions towards 」
This is good~
This will be good!
First up, Ikuta confesses her one-sided emotions towards her senpai
Cute~
What she did just now was good
Senpai!
Sorry for making you wait!
What did you want to talk to me about?
Umm ..
I wanted to talk to you about something ..
I've always ..
Liked you!
Cute~!
If you would like, please go out with me!
Ohh, cute~
I'm sorry
Why did he reject her?
I already have a girlfriend
Ahhhh!
Ahh, so that's it ..
Please don't bother yourself over this ..
Oh, she's good
Next up is 13 year old Kawago's acting
Senpai!
What was it that you want to tell me?
Sorry for taking up your time
Umm .. since some time ago
Ever since you transferred here, I've had a crush on you
If you would like, please go out with me
Cute~
Sorry
Ahh
Right now, I already have a girlfriend
I see .. mmm
Ahh .. sorry about that
She moved back
Ahh, poor thing!
I see
She's moving back!
THAT'S SUPER SCARY!!
SOMEHOW THAT'S SUPER SCARY!!
Next up is Takayama, will her confession be successful?
Oh! Takayama
Kazumin
She seems natural
Mmm ..
Senpai!
We've always walked home as friends but
From today onwards, please let me walk beside you as your girlfriend
This is good
Yeah it's okay with me
Eh? He said okay?
She got accepted? Oh so there's an 'okay' pattern too
Oh this is good
Good
That's cute!
Cute~!
Somehow it made me go kyun
They were real good
I want such a drama to be made
For this scene there's the rejected version and the okay version
The okay version seems so good right?
Takayama you got the okay version right?
Yes! Thank you
Takayama you were good
Your acting was cute
Thank you very much
It was good and natural
Thank you, thank you
She was quite natural
Her happiness when she got accepted showed at the end
Hehe, I was happy
You were happy (LOL!)
Ah! You were genuinely happy?
Ah, it's like umm ..
He told me okay in a nonchalant way
Ah yes he did
The way he said that in a nonchalant way was very cool!
Ahh, you went kyun from that too?
I want someone to say that to me too
Like in a cold manner
That's it!
That's good?
Yes, I want to be told that!
You all would want to act in a drama like this right?
With the contents of the drama all being confessions
Ah I get what you're saying
Everyone take their turns to confess their love
And make sure the guy's face isn't filmed at all right?
So that the one watching would think that the members are confessing to him or her right?
Yes that's it! I want to do that!
I want to be acting as the male role since the guy wouldn't be filmed
Yes that's it, as long as the person playing the male lead isn't filmed
I want to play the guy's role
Well then, Himura
Since we're at it, Himura you will play the guy's role
Oh! That's good!
I super want to play that role!
Then shall we get someone who hasn't acted in that scene?
Well then, Ichiki
Ichiki you play the female lead
Gambatte! Go for it!
With that said, Ichiki would confess her love for Himura senpai when he is on the way home
Okay and ready!
ACTION!
Right after this, the confession time which makes the members super excited!
Ichiki confessing her love to Himura when he is on his way home, what sort of acting would we see?
Okay and ready!
ACTION!
Oi Fujiwara! Shut up!
Stupid! Shut up I tell you
Shut up stupid!
Ahh I'm tired, think I shall get some katsudon before heading home
Himura senpai!
Oh! What is it Ichiki?
Umm .. today I have something to say to you
Oh, I'm hungry so could you make it quick?
I've liked you since a long time ago!
If you would like, please go out with me!
Sure, no problem at all!
I'm very happy! Thank you very much!
FINISH!
Okay that's a wrap!
Ichiki you were good
Yes you were good
She was cute right?
Yes
Her acting was good
That acting scene felt like it was from a novel
What about my acting?
You didn't do a proper "catchball rally" to properly receive the feelings she tried to convey to you!
Catchball?
Because you just nonchalantly said "Okay okay whatever"
Please accept her feelings properly this time
Okay I understand
I'll leave the reason to you
Okay I've got it
Next up, Hatanaka confesses her love to Himura senpai
Okay and ready!
ACTION!
Bye then!
Thank you!
Thank you~!
What was that thank you for?
Ahh ..
Umm .. I've something to tell you
What is it about?
Senpai, I've always liked you
Please allow me to be your girlfriend!
Sorry!
I'm happy that you said that but I .. 「@#$%^&*」
What is the shocking thing that Himura said to Hatanaka!?
Senpai, I've always liked you
Please allow me to be your girlfriend!
Sorry!
I'm happy but, once I've graduated I'm going somewhere far away
I'm going somewhere far away!
Despite that, it's still fine with me
If you say that ..
I would have to bring you along with me far away
Even with that, is it still fine with you?
Bring me along with you~
BRING YOU ALONG?!
Okay then!
From today, you're my girl!
FINISH!
You were good!
Your acting was good
Someone told me this before
I was told that "For people who have dissatisfactions about this world .."
I was told that it's good to have dissatisfactions about this world
People who are less straightforward tend to act better
Just them sitting back in that posture, is already good, that's what I've heard
Somehow .. I'm not badmouthing you but, you seem to have dissatisfactions about this world
You just joined (Nogizaka) right?
For this episode's unseen footage, please go to the official website