--------------------------------------------------
Today on Nogizakatte Doko, the senbatsu members show their talents.
The high level performance has the studio excited.
The debut of Nogizaka46 latest music video: Guruguru Curtain.
Don! Nogizakatte Doko! We are the hosts, Bananaman.
And these are the Nogizaka members.
Our guest this time is Ijiri Okada.
It's here! Artist's performance
It's very fast, I could hear the tongue go "pata pata pata pata".
Why do we have Ijiri's fast tongue here?
Himura, with a fast tongue impression, announce today's theme.
Examination of the members' talents.
It's like a talent assessment is it not?
Where you write down your various skills.
We have evaluated your individual talents.
This time we will judge to see if you really have them or not.
This means yes, and this means no.
Whomever gets 3 'YES' from the jury will be have their skill officially recognized.
The first on display is Nishino's ability to draw.
The first is this.
Nogizaka46 formed in this year; the year of the dragon.
Very artistic.
There are someone riding above the head of this dragon
-Yes.
Who is that?
-We'll find out afterwards.
So we will know after seeing the following picture?
Is it there?
-Yes.
What appears is...
What is this?
It's disgusting.
Isn't this Himura-san?
Even I'm not that bad.
What is this?
What is it's name?
The name is Doiya-san.
Huh?
Doiya.
What's Doiya?
He's a god.
God?
What is he the god of?
I want this to remain a secret.
Secret?
Is it because you're embarrassed that you don't say it?
Is it testicles?
-Hey!
I hardly ever stop a dirty joke...
Why don't you draw hair on Doiya like these two people?
Doiya brothers?
Through these 2 pictures, is Nishino's talent recognized or not?
Here we go!
Ah! Shitara does not recognize her.
Correct.
I don't understand what Doiya-san is?
I think you should explain it in more detail.
You should also ask for the input of others
and finish his character profile.
Can he talk?
What does he eat?
I assume Doiya-san is a man.
He must be male.
If there is a chance to show Doiya-san,
it would be more interesting if he was male.
Then he is a man.
You have to think about it.
Next is Nakada who had 3 years of baton twirling.
Let's see Nakada's skill, if you please.
Here we go!
The next to show their skill is Shiraishi.
You're using a VTR?
Yes.
You're not an okama, right?
100% women.
Try a "Dondake".
Dondake.
Very good.
She imitated it quickly.
Let's take a look at his VTR.
VTR start.
Dondake.
What skill will Shiraishi show?
I am at a baseball cage.
How do I look in this uniform?
Kawaii!
-I've been playing since 4 years ago.
Left-handed?
I will show my batting skills.
We will now see her batting skills.
Well... I'll air for center field.
Aims for center field.
Isn't that ball fairly fast?
It did go to center field!
Very good.
The ball really go to center field, as she said.
And again...
Hit!
And now for the real challenge.
Unfortunately, she just misses the home run.
Vexing!
With that we saw the batting ability of Shiraishi.
You looked really cool with the helmet on taking it seriously.
Cool
We rarely see an idol batting well.
Very rare.
Here we go!
Thank you!
Next we have Ichiki whose skill is Latin dancing.
She's already here.
This is Latin dance. If you please!
When did you start?
Since the 6th grade.
So you've been doing it a while.
It's been about 4 years, right?
Impressive.
While dancing I feel happy and excited.
Your appearance is captivating.
With this, I'd agree!
Next is Hashimoto.
Hashimoto's skill is...
Can recognize the smell of the members.
Ha?
What do you mean by this?
When in high school, I was a club manager.
At that time there were many members clothes,
and there was no writing of their names on the shirts.
Through the smell I could tell whose was whose.
So you smelled them and could recognize whose clothes they were?
Yes.
-No way!
Not just the smell of sweat?
Everyone has a different smell of their sweat.
So you remember their smell?
Yes, I remember.
Well, let's have you smell a member's clothes.
If you can guess the member by the smell of their shirt,
We will admit that it's your skill.
The AD is in the waiting room.
AD = Assistant Director.
AD-san, where are you?
Where's the AD-san?
Hello.
I'm the AD!
AD Ijiri-san.
Hello AD.
-Hello.
You're at the Nogizaka46 dressing room?
Yes, I just happened to pass by.
Accidentally?
Yes.
I also happen to have the dressing room key...
Can you bring some members' clothes?
I understand.
Gathering members' clothes without knowing which clothes belong to whom.
Will Ijiri do anything other than that?
Good morning!
Huh! Wait a minute!
Take a look at these beverages.
Partially drunk tea discovered
I'll line them up.
All lined up.
I will not do anything.
Don't do it
After this, Nogizaka's in danger!
Also, Hashimoto demonstrated her remarkable ability.
I won't do it.
I won't do it to my beloved Nogizaka.
While in the dressing room, Ijiri finds...
Shitara!
I found something interesting.
What is that?
Take a look at this.
A bento?
Onigiri?
Whose meal is this?
Ami!
It's Ami's.
It's okay, right?
No, Ijiri-san, don't do it!
Ijiri-san, don't do it!
A new one...
Ijiri-san really forgot his initial goal.
I asked you to get clothes from the members.
That's right.
I got this in front of my right eye, so it's not easy to see.
Grab clothes from 3 random members.
Okay!
Will Hashimoto be able to recognize the owner by smelling it?
Hashimoto's skill is to recognize the members' clothing from their scent.
Hashimoto can't see the members' clothing.
You can't see right?
-I can't.
Really can't see.
Everyone keep quiet.
Whose is this?
Please start.
I know!
You already know?
So, whose is it?
It's the usual aroma of Maiyan... Shiraishi Mai.
Well done!
Great.
This is next.
Whose is this?
Don't talk.
Interesting...
I know!
It's Reika.
Continuously
Correct.
This is the last one.
It's between two people.
Already narrowed it down. That's amazing, just like a dog's nose.
Did you figure it out?
I'm still 100%.  There's a little doubt, but I don't think it's Yuttan's.
Is this Sayurin's?
Divine work!
That's very cool.
There's one more.
Whose is this?
This isn't a girls'.
There's perfume... The owner sprayed perfume on the neck.
You can remove the blindfold.
Incredible.
Hashimoto's olfactory skills are recognized!
Next is Ikuta with the ability to play piano.
"Études" (Chopin)
That was magnificent.
That was too good. It's great to hear that from such a graceful lady; it captivated everyone.
Can any of us request a song?
Do you take requests?
I can do the intro from "Akai sweet pea" by Matsuda Seiko.
Talent like this, we have to admit it!
Can you play "Get Wild" by TM Network?
I don't know that one.
You don't know that one?
Can you show her, Himura-san?
Great.
Seeing him adept at something startled me...
Original (Indonesian) script:
zaka46sembung (zaka46sembung.blogspot.co.id)
English Translation: BSFEMA