www.IkuchanCheeks.blogspot.fr
Translation: Sayuringo Gundan
Timming: Wakasama Gundan
Translation Eng: DOZO
Today on Nogizakatte, doko?
"Christmas Tournament Game Exposure Battle Outbreak!"
This sub is far from perfect. There might be translation and syntax mistakes.
Please bear with us! :D
In this episode we'll reveal embarrassing things about the members
And finaly, the Christmas gifts !
Here we go ! Let us start Nogizakatte, DOKON~ !
DON~ !
And here are Nogizaka46 members
Lots of members, right!
Well let's just get started...
- Let's get started ... - Hey, hey ! Wait a minute !
Why are you ignoring me ?
Excuse me AD-san, there's a weird guy here...
I am a guest today! A guest !
This is Kano-san
Ramen tsukemen boku ikemen
So what are we doing today ?
Himura-san please announce it
In a happy manner
Understood
Nogizakatte Doko, Christmas Party~ !!
Tonight, the members will be divided into 2 teams.
Team White will be led by Himura-san.
and Team Grey will be led by Kano-san.
If we compare it to White Team...
my team feels like it has no aura.
EEEHHHHHHH ?!!!
I'm just trying to stir you up.
If that's the case, this Team will definitely win !
laugh
if that's the case, this Team will definitely win !
These member will win for sure
But we're also confident we will win this, right ?!
y- yeah......
You just don't know what the hell your captain is talking about right ?
You're doing it wrong, let me show you
YEAH
Perfect Breath
Impressive, right ?
[vigorously]
YEAH
Impressive
Impressive, right ?
we will definitely-
Win !!
How to make it?
Inspiration Game~
Five members of each team will have to give an answer
And we will see if they manage to all answer the same
They will receive points each time they answer the same
After 3 questions, the team with the most points will be victorious.
First up is Team Grey led by Kano-san
Captain Kano from Team Grey
I think this team will not use their brain and just say whatever comes through their mind
Alright, do your best
Anyways, the first question for Team Grey is this:
What do you eat for lunch at school ?
About this question, we're talking school food only or can it be popular foods ?
No, only school food please.
It must be different when we talk about a public shcool, right
Nowadays ?
I heard that in the city there are menus which you can choose from
At my place (Sendai) lunch was already prepared and you couldn't choose but it was good.
Well to each time period its own foods
For example Himura-san only ate kinomi
Are we talking about serving temperature too ?
What do you mean?
Whether eating a cold serve, half cold, or hot...
It shouldn't matter ! - This is incredible
The number one served lukewarm meal in the popular meal menu, what could it even be ?
Your Captain always says things that no one understands.
Anyways I think I've decided
Your boards are messed up now because of Kano-san
Now, please show us your answers !
Open please
Curry, Agepan, Curry, Curry, Curry
Do schools still give Agepan nowadays ?
They do, many members here like it right?
Yes...
They really likes that
We don't know about it
Is there no agepan in kansai?
There's not
Others that have a different menu in school?
In Aichi we've got Bibimbap
I did not have any rice in school
Mushrooms were just too good, right ?
They didn't provide rice ?
Yes, they didn't
Your kidding.
So what did you eat ?
I loved Koppepan
You just took your koppepan like that and....
No no, they served other foods with it of course, small ones, large ones...
What kind of school did you go to ?!
Anyways they did pretty good, 4 points all in all.
Next question is this
Speaking of songs
What song is the most popular in karaoke ?
Easy one
But there might be different answers
About this
you have no choice but the options already provided,right?
Please stop your dirty joke
This was a really popular song
Everyone could sing it
Kano did you sing too ?
Yes I did
What's wrong ?
They think you're disgusting
While singing, do you dance as well ?
Everyone will dance to it, definitely
You also include dancing, Kano
Yes it's dancing
Let's look at the answers, starting with Kano
Kano-san answer is....
"Heavy Rotation"
It's a disaster if you sing it
Matsumura what's your answer
Oogoe Diamond
Almost
this is also a song from AKB instead
Ikoma-chan, show us your answer
What is that? Memeshikute ?
Golden Bomber's...
Ahhh, It's awesome.
People who don't play instruments
With their attention-grabbing performance, the visual-kei air band, Golden Bomber
Didn't you say you must also dance while singing this song ?
Hence, enjoy Kano-san dance for Heavy Rotation !
Wrong !
Completely different.
I told you I can sing better than him
Let's move onto the next question
Name an ugly comedian
Everyone please answer right
They definitely do not like ugly comedians, right ?
That's right ?
So many ugly comedians out there...
The Really ugly comedian and ugly comedian ?
it's two different categories.
Oh, I see
Please stop confusing us
Don't think about what he said !
Everyone please show your answers !
Himura, Himura, Himura, Himura !
Everyone said the same
And so, Team Grey is now at a total of 12 points.
It's now Captain Himura's team's turn.
The first question for Team White is this one
Food that you find in parties
Please you write down the answers
I know, it's easy
What is Himura thinking of ?
Because the question's subject, he's not allowed to answer your questions.
It's not just a party meal
I understand
But due to the age difference, their answers might not be the same
Himura has about 50 years difference with the Nogizaka members am I right ?
It's not 50 years
Everyone has written down their answers
Please show us your answers !
Himura-san
Yakiniku (Meat BBQ)
Takayama
Cake
Don't you think it's delicious ?
You just thought about yourself
This is a game where you must think about other people answers
Moving on.... What is that
- Meat ?? - Meat with bone
Ahhh this one
The meat you turn while roasting it ?
- On a stick like that - Yes
Well..... We'll accept this.
Next is: Yakiniku of course
3 points so far
Turkey
Maybe at a Christmas dinner party ?
Yes, there will be that
You roast it the same way as the other...
This one is.... No !
3 points !
The next question is...
Most famous historical figure
This one's kinda difficult
It's a miracle if you all manage to get it right
Choose someone from the first grade lessons
Choose someone whom you've learned about in first grade
First Grade ?
- What did we do in first grade? - Between the 3...!
- From the 3 - ok just select the third
What are you even talking about ?
Why choose n°3, you don't even tell me completely
Everyone's finished ?
Alright, let's see
Why not start with Himura-san.
And answer himura-san answer is ....
Tokugawa Ieyasu
Takayama
Sakurai
Oda Nobunaga
He's number one !
Ah so he is the actual number one
Tokugawa Ieyasu
3 points so far
Yamato
Tokugawa-sama
If the other one was wrong, this can't be right !
Which Tokugaya are you talking about ?
Tokugawa Ieyasu-san
4 points
What a weird game
Team Grey has a 5 points advantage
If they don't get a perfect score on the next question, Team White will lose
Here's the last question ...
A very cute animal.  This should be easy.
Write down your answers please.
Guys, listen for a second !
Think about an animal that looks like me
No one will understand if you say that though
I'm sure they can do it
If you think hard you might find one that's cute, but not too cute
Please show us your answers !
Do pandas really look like Himura-san ?!
I think dogs should be the most common answer
This one though, I get it
- Because Himura-san said to pick something that looks like him
Lion sea, right?
I understand
Understand what, your answer's different !
With that, Team Grey wins the first game !
The next game will be
Nogizaka Basketball~ !
This time the challengers are these 8 members from the two teams.
All of them must take a seat
They will have to move over to another seat when signaled.
The one without a seat will be disqualified.
If 3 people from the same team are out, their team loses.
Topics will be drawn from this box.
They will be related to your private life, you can choose not to answer them if it's too personal.
and the one that doesn't get a seat will have to wear this deer nose.
Let's head on to the first round.
As soon as I say "Nogizaka Basketball" the game begins.
Here I go
"Nogizaka basketball"... means the game starts
Ready
Nogizaka Basketball !!!
The first topic is ...
If you have habit or a secret that you can't tell the other members about.
Ready...
Nogizaka Basketball !
Team White Saito Asuka: OUT
So do you have a secret habit ?
I have flat face fetish.
Flat face.
What do you mean by that ?
- Like, this line right here.... - Ah, on me ?
The face and the eyes are in balance with each other.
And who do you think has the best one ?
Like, Rotti...
Beautiful, you're right
Embarrassed (⁄ ⁄•⁄ω⁄•⁄ ⁄)
Who else moved...? Itou ?
I don't to want say it
Well I was about to ask but  you already said no...
Let's take things slowly
Or is your secret so embarrassing you can't say it on TV ?
Like she doesn't want us to know about her past
One time I was exhausted, so I slept on the couch
And when I woke up I rubbed my face on the cushion like so...
Don't you think it feels good ?
Like I'm supposed to know !
Miyazawa how about you ?
At school, the smell of the books...
I really like the smell of the notebook pages.
ahh ... it has a distinct smell, right ?
Have you brought a book today ?
Yes, I have it...
This...
Open it to the page you like the most
History books usually have a good smell
My favorite part is the middle...
Ah what a nice smell
That's the good stuff
Can I have it for a second ? It's been so long...
Ahhh how nostalgic.
Ah I understand I understand ...
Brings back old memories !
Alright, what's our next topic ?
Those who have a complaint against another member
Well...
Let's just get started
Nogizaka Basketball !!
Iwase OUT
The oldest member, Iwase, has a complaint about another member.... What could it be ?
Yamatomato
What is it?
As always she's wearing a skirt....
But the real problem is that she's wearing it too short !
aaahhhh!
So she wears it shorter than all of you ?
Way shorter.
She wears it over her hips like this ?
It's not short at all !
No no no, very short !
We can see her butt !
Is it that bad ?!
Do you not realize people can see your butt ?
When she walks she does not realize her butt is visible
What is it this time ?
A member who did wrong, but didn't apologize.
Is there one ?
Get ready....
Nogizaka Basketball !!
Yet again a Team White conflict
But, after being down 3 members, Team White has something to say against Team Grey !
All of you !
Eh, what's that ?
Everyone's pointing, who is it ?
It's Minami !
But I've always apologized
- Yes you did
Do the members really hate Hoshino that much ?
- Itou, you also moved.   - Yes.
What happened?
With Marika....
Yes, what is it?
We will determine what has happened between the two!
What is it she did ?
In addition, there will be a big announcement at the end of this show!
Itou Nene wants to apologize to Itou Marika. What happens next......
At the time of the audition for Nogizaka46
We were both sitting side by side
And obviously we both have the same name (Itou)
At that time I thought her full name was Itou Ochiro.
And so you want to apologize to her about that
Try your most honest apology.
Sorry to have thought your name was Ochiro.
You two are like rivals
Hence you shouldn't be mistaken about your rival's name
Are you relieved now that you've properly apologized ?
At the time you did hold fiercely onto that chair though
And so... with a 2-0 score...... Team Grey wins !!
Just as I predicted
I'm sure as a Captain you are proud of your team right now aren't you ?
Yes !
Looks like they still don't like you
Next show will be Christmas Carols !
www.IkuchanCheeks.blogspot.fr
Translation: Sayuringo Gundan
Translation Eng: DOZO