VOZ48 with love
Today Nogizakatte Doko!
First cooking contest
It's feminism's advantage, but we have so much failure
Even UNJASH is wordless
More than that, we have special cooking methods that make the whole studio in turmoil
Nogizakatte Doko! MC Bananaman
and Nogizaka46 members
Let's introduce our guests, they are Watanabe from UNJASH
- The studio is amazing
- Thanks
So enthusiast
and me
Let me
You are forbidden to say a word!
No idea
You all know Watanabe
Who is the guy wearing green outfit?
Do you know?
What's your impression, Takayama?
Kojima usually have a role that is mocked by the others
So funny
So can you mock Kojima ?
Make fun of him
You wearing that to prepare for the Xmas ?
Yes, Xmas is coming....
Hey, don't mock me
Now we go to the main content. What do we do today ?
Himura, please introduce us with your lovely voice
Nogizaka46
First cooking contest
It's all about cooking
At this time, we've tried dancing, drawing
Only cooking is the thing we've not tried
- Cooking method
- That is it
- This game has been on TV so many times
- Exactly
Now it's time for the member to challenge with cooking
Please watch the VTR
Himura please introduce VTR
I know. VTR Start! Cause I am right-handed
First dish is Kakiage
Grating vegetables
Mixing eggs, cold water, flour and we have wrapping powder
Mix the vegetables and powder and fry it
When the colour turned light yellow, we're finished
First person to make kakiage is Shiraishi Mai
I still cook sometimes
The last time I went to the kitchen is to make hamburger
Onion
Carrot
Sakura shrimp
Cooking everyday, Shiraishi does it smoothly
Does it look good?
Shiraishi processes like the guideline. What the taste will be ?
Crunchy! I want to taste that
Absolutely perfect
A stunning performance by Shiraishi Mai
The next candidate is Eto Misa
Currently I am living alone
So I think, in the group, I am the one who go to the kitchen most frequently.
Onion
Carrot
Eto sliced vegetables with her skillful knife
Tapioca starch
It makes ingredients sticky
Why do you use tapioca starch in kakiage
It's going to be finish
Args! But no problem
Sticky
Uh uh, it is sticky
Can be removed
Left food?
Kakiage doesn't look like food. Is it edible?
Greasy...
Full of oil
It's like eating cooking oil
First, try to cook something edible
Shiraishi is so good
You can get married now
Putting tapioca starch is a bad idea
It's like fried and then put it into micro oven for more than once
Rubbish?
Next dish is spring roll
Slicing vegetables and pork
Stir-fry pork and vegetables together until we see it a little bit sticky
Wrap it and fry it in 170 Celcius degree
So the spring roll is completed
First person to do this is Ikoma Rina
I've seen it in cookbook
Args, it's oakwood mushroom
Bamboo shoots
Oakwood mushrooms
Next step is choosing the wrapper but..
So many types
I choose this wrapper
Fun guo wrapper
Start wrapping spring roll using fun guo wrapper
Maybe it's suitable?
Why wrap 2 layers?
Oh, why there aren't any fizzle sound ?
Cooking oil is not heated
Looks good
Ikoma has completed the dish "spring roll using fun guo wrapper", does it have the taste of a spring roll ?
It's terrible
Use with soy sauce and it should be better
Please make spring roll properly
Next person is the oldest member Iwase
I was having time living alone
If I remember those days it should be fine
Iwase is so clever, she slices ingredients skillfully.
Bamboo shoot
Oakwood mushroom
First is minced beef
Smells good
No use pork
Is it too much for the filling ingredients?
So much
Time for packaging
Big spring roll
Should not be a problem
And then fry it
So fast
It's beef, there shouldn't have any problem
Spring roll fried in 10 seconds
How are the filling ingredients will be?
Raw
IT'S RAW
Non-edible
Please make edible dish
Next is Matsumura
After thinking, I choose paprika, carrot and coleslaw
Slice carrot without peeling
Slicing bell peppers and vegetables
And then...
All in boiled water
Have no idea why does Matsumura boil the vegetables
Filling ingredients contain minced beef, noodle and boiled vegetables
Adding cheese and tenmen
I am wrapping it
Torned
Can't be wrapped
Waste-paper?
Now frying!
Just throw it in
The vegetables...
It's floating up
Hell on earth
I will leave it as until the colour turned yellow-brown
The colour is not important anymore
It looks good
Unidentified object
Finished
A spring roll dish with abstract art style, is it safe to eat?
Doesn't have any taste at all
The dish is full of style, but make edible dish first
3 people make terrible dish
Iwase, what have you done ?
It looks like summer roll than spring roll
The last candidate
It's out of my imagination
What have you cooked ?
Like the emperor of a landfill
But the appearance is good?
It looks dirty
Your responses aren't good enough
What are you saying?
Need to use more strong words
Really? Then you shouldn't be a comedian anymore
What? Don't mock my job
We are talking about their cooking
I still like to mock you
Mock shit
So slow
Next dish is rolled cabbage
Mixing minced beef, eggs and sliced onion
Wrap it in cabbage and cook it in the soup
First candidate is Hashimoto
I am living alone
I cook my favourite dish everyday
Today I will try my best
First is hashing onion
Mix it with minced pork and eggs
I want to tell you that I am the one who can cook
Cause before that, I looks like a girl who cannot do anything
Don't wanna step back
Using cabbage to wrap
Tie it
Put it in to the soup and cook, we're finished
A perfectly cooked rolled cabbage, what will the taste be?
No weird smell
It's the smell of rolled cabbage
You can eat with rice
Hashimoto shows us a different view on her and does it perfectly.
Next candidate is Hatanaka
What thing is cabbage?
Cabbage
Napa cabbage
Which one?
Moreover, she uses non-minced beef
Put it there
Roll and wrap it and cook it in the soup
You use napa cabbage to wrap pork
Use toothpick to fix it
The solution consists of nutmeg, alcohol, vinegar, and chicken soup
At this stage, out of the blue Hatakana cares about the colour
What can I do to make the colour lighter?
Put the cream in?
Cow milk?
Adding some milk and the colour is faded
Adding milk, the solution becomes a mysterious thing
Cook it and we're finished
Rolled napa cabbage with milk, how does it taste?
So delicious!
The miracle of napa cabbage
Like my mother cooking
It's different
Is it really delicious? Matsumura will taste that
It's really good but... this thing is napa cabbage
What have you added?
Milk, chicken soup, vinegar and men's egg
Nutmeg
Don't mistook the ingredients with the other. You've to try more
Hatanaka, you use the magazine
How can you make this mistake?
So funny
Adding men's egg
- But is it really delicious?
- Yes, it's yummy!
It seems that we can use Chinese cabbage, Napa cabbage or Watercress to cook this,
Only use in hot pot
Hashimoto
So incredible
Perfectly cooked
You want to emphasize that you can cook
Just that and you proven that you're an incredible girl
So happy!
People will look at you with a different eye.
Until this, we can only see this via VTR
This time we will allow you to cook right in the studio
Ikuta-chan
How will she fair? Can she do it?
First candidate is Ikuta
The meal that she will prepare is dashimaki tamago
Dashi: soup from seaweed and fish
Maki: Roll
Tamago: Egg
To make dashimaki tamago, you just need a few eggs, sugar and a pinch of soy sauce
This is dashimaki tamago
Time limitation is 5 minutes
Start
Dashimaki tamago?
Where are the eggs?
Egg Egg
You need a lot of eggs and stock too
Shocked
Dashimaki tamago?
No no no no, just wait !! What are you doing ?
Directly
Dashimaki tamago? What is it ? I still don't get it.
Seaweed is dashi?
This thing should be dashi ?
It can't be helped
Adding "dashi"
Hurry up and finish. This is destroyed already.
5 minutes feels so long
I shouldn't have pour on top of this
Let's listen to what she's going to do now.
- Ikuta
- Yes
What are you trying to do?
I don't know this device, I think it's a frying pan
So tell me your progress?
It's not hardening at all
What do you think is the main point of Dashimaki Tamago?
It should have Tamago (Eggs) and Dashi (Stock)
What kind of stock did you use? Can you show us ?
I use kelp and anchovies but...
We are running out of time, only 2 minutes left. Do your best !!
In to the frying pan
Everything is in now
Ikuta
What are you doing?
I thought pouring it directly was a mistake
So you use a frying pan?
Yes
Anchovies
Bay leaf
Wait! Who is going to eat this later?
Aren't we?
Me? Me? Oh, man
Slimy
We're finished
With kelp and anchovies as its main flavor, I present to you the weirdest omelet in the world.
Who is going to eat this first?
Obviously, the guest should eat first..
Are your sure it is safe to eat?
How can we eat it?
Just close your eyes
Everything tastes like anchovies
At first, when you pour everything in the hotplate
What the hell was that?
I thought this is a frying pan
It was just a mistake
Normal people would use the frying pan and wait until heated
But you just pour everything on it
Negligence
First of all, try to recognise all cooking equipments.
Our next candidate is Matsumura
Then, Cooking Monster Matsumura use her wonderful weapon
This time is a simple meal, house rice platter
Please do it in 5 minutes
Start
I pour the cooking oil in
Too much
Danger
Quickly
So hot
Just put all ingredients in
Adding tenmen sauce, nutmeg and oyster sauce
It's worse than kids playing with mud
1000 times worse
Pour some water in
Why adding water?
Preparing the eggs, but...
It's black pepper
All in
What is this?
I will add everything into it now
Chemistry experiment?
No one can recognise this dish, what the taste will be?
What have you done for us?
House rice platter
A disaster
Watanabe-san
Wait a second
You've to try this first
Must eat it?
Spicy!!!!
Hell of black pepper
All I can see is spiciness
2 warriors have surrendered
SO SPICY!!!
First time I see it....
args... so hot!