This is kinda harsh for them.
Tonight on Nogizakatte Doko? Announcing the selected 16 members for the debut single senbatsu!
And chaos's everywhere, the unpredictable shifting between the members.
-I'm frustrated. -Frustrated.
Unpredictable result even until the very end.
Members in Shichifukujin has been changed.
Will the other surpass the current Shichifukujin*?
Shichifukujin ( Seven Deities of Luck, 七福神 ). Basically Nogizaka46's version of AKB's Kami 7.
Subs: NeruestSub
Nogizaka46 Debut Single Senbatsu Announcement!!
Selected from 38000 participants on 22nd August 2011.
Nogizaka46's 33 members.
The senbatsu system makes every members to work hard in order to become a real idol.
The first senbatsu result announced 15 members.
The front members were chosen to become Shichifukujin, aka the center of the group.
After four or five months of activities, they're back to their starting point.
On 22th February, Nogizaka46 will be having their CD debut.
Finally, the greatly awaited CD debut will be on 22th February!
Next shooting, we'll be announcing the 16 members that made it into the debut single senbatsu.
Here it is, the announcement of the 16 members!
The members has been waiting at the backstage nervously.
-Lets check out the situation. -Ok.
What is their feeling right now?
Everyone look lifeless.
This is kinda...but well this is the debut single senbatsu right?
That's right.
-This is really important for them, whatever if they'll get selected. -That's right.
So, let us talk with the members over there for a while.
EVERYONE.
It startled me.
Did I startled you?
-Can everyone hear me? -Yes, we can.
Alright, today there'll be an announcement for the CD debut senbatsu.
And we'll start announcing them right now.
For the announcement,
will be announced using cellphones.
So for those who are going to be picked, the management team will call on your cell phone.
So if your cellphone did not ring at all, that means you were not selected.
That's right.
Unexpectedly, cellphones will be used to announce the result.
Only sixteen members will be selected,
and will received a confirmation call from the management team.
But if one did not receive a call, it means they're out.
First of all, let's begin with the new Shichifukujin.
These members were currently the Shichifukujin.
Shichifukujin aka the faces of Nogizaka46, will there be any changes?
Is that Shiraishi? She's already praying.
Yeah, that's Shiraishi.
Ichiki-chan didn't show her face at all...
Who will be the first member to be selected as the new Shichifukujin?
-Eh? A phone rang. -Yeah. A phone rang.
Oh! Its Shiraishi's cellphone!
Thank you very much.
-She says thank you right? -Ah, Shiraishi.
-Shiraishi will be the first to be the new Shichifukujin. -Thank you.
In this case, the other members that are like good friends to her until now...
Congratulations.
Man...I can't take it anymore. It's so harsh.
The first one to be picked was Shiraishi Mai.
She's very popular even from the beginning,
and the only one to have a solo photo shoot currently. She was like the ace of the group.
Entered without a doubt.
-Ah Here's she is. -Ah! Shiraishi.
Congratulations.
The first one who's phone rang.
-Congratulations to you. -Congratulations.
What is your thought right now?
About the senbatsu...
Whether can I make it or not.
I thought I was not going to make it.
But now I'm one of Shichifukujin once again.
I'm really happy.
Who will be the second member to be selected as the new Shichifukujin?
Oh! Someone's phone rang. Who is it?
Who? Who's that?
Is that Matsumura?
Yes, it is Matsumura.
It changed.(Shichifukujin)
She became one of Shichifukujin.
If she's in, that means someone in Shichifukujin dropped out.
Wow. That's Incredible.
The members in Shichifukujin changed.
Always leaving a strong impression from the beginning, Matsumura.
outstanding and highly regarded, she became a Shichifukujin as expected.
Hey, Matsumura.
Congratulations!
What on your mind right now?
Umm... actually this is really... ummm...
-Well, your current situation... -You joined the Shichifukujin, you'll work hard right?
Yes, I will work hard. I will work hard.
Alright. Let us witness your hardworking together. Congratulations.
The first seven to be called will be the Shichifukujin.
The second new Shichifukujin is going to be Matsumura Sayuri.
From that, one of the previous Nogizaka Shichifukujin is going to drop out from it.
Nogizaka Shichifukujin, the third member will be...
It's here!
Hashimoto. Hashimoto is in the new Shichifukujin.
Thank you very much. -Wow! Sugoi!
That means there's two...
Congratulations.
Beautiful and often very active, Hashimoto.
Although she did not make it into the previous senbatsu. But because her unique and brave personalities,
she is finally one of the new Shichifukujin.
Here she come!
Congratulations.
What was on your mind when you're waiting for the result?
I already lost one senbatsu.
-Lost one? -The first senbatsu.
I know the feeling of not getting selected very well.
So I thought I was still not ready yet.
I worked very hard after that and keep thinking about
if I did not make into it this time, I might suffered from a emotional blow.
Ah, is that right?
So when I was selected I'm really glad that I worked hard for it.
Yeah, because you didn't make it once right? So you hoped to prove yourself with your hard work.
The third new Shichifukujin member is Hashimoto Nanami.
So two of the previous Nogizaka Shichifukujin is going to drop out from it.
The fourth members to join the new Shijifukujin is...
-Oh. It rang. -Who is it?
Is it Ikoma?
It is Ikoma!
Leaving her parents and came to Tokyo from Akita all by herself.
Because of her uniqueness she created a lot of memorable scenes, Ikoma Rina.
She joined the new Shichifukujin splendidly.
Congratulations!
What is your current thought?
Right from the start I always wondered what's my strengths.
But until now, I haven't really know what I'm really good at.
But obviously, I'll work hard regardlessly, like there's no tomorrow.
Only three slots left for the new Nogizaka Shichifukujin, who will be the fifth members?
Oh? Who is that?
It's Takayama.
Moshi Moshi...
Thank you very much.
Always put up a good smile and a high standard for herself, Takayama.
With the help of her unique and charismatic personalities, she joined the Shichifukujin once again.
Here she comes.
What is your feeling right now?
Whether I'm going to make it or not,
I'll have more self-awareness
and force myself to work harder.
Only two slots left for the new Nogizaka Shichifukujin.
The sixth member will be...
Who is it?
It rang.
Oh. Is Ikuta!
Moshi Moshi...
Although she had no confidence in her personalities
she was still managed to create a lot of memorable scenes, that's Ikuta.
Please work hard towards the goal of becoming an essential member of the Shichifukujin!
Ikuta. Congratulations!
Which part of you do you think that was recognized by everyone?
I never thought I had any kind of special personality or abilities at all.
But since I'm selected, I'll still do my best.
And I thought "This is a good matter for me."
-Ah, is that right? Alright, do your best. -Congratulations!
Alright, for now, there are already six members over here.
-Only one slot for the Shichifukujin left. -Wow. Only one left.
There is only one slot left for the new Nogizaka Shichifukujin,
Who will be the last one to join?
Hmm? Did it rang?
-Eh!? -Oh!
Hoshino?
Hoshino Minami.
Thank you very much.
WOW!!
It's Hoshino Minami.
-She's in the Shichifukujin! -Thank you very much.
-Congratulations! -Congratulations Minami.
So three members did not make it in.
Only 13 years old but already a Shichifukujin, Hoshino Minami.
With her freshness personality and hidden abilities, she will become an impressive member.
Congratulations!
What is your feeling right now?
I never thought that I would've make it.
I even thought that I wouldn't make it into the senbatsu.
But I'm really happy that I'm one of the Shichifukujin.
Right. That's good.
All of the new Nogizaka Shichifukujin members has been confirmed.
Next up, there will be 9 slots left for the senbatsu.
The previous Shichifukujin which is Ichiki, Nakada and Sakurai did not make it.
That's right.
Who is it?
Oh! It's Kawamura!
Congratulations.
With her highly regarded dance skill, Kawamura.
With her great dance moves and impressive performances, she is finally an official member.
What is your feeling right now?
-I'm really happy. -Really happy. -That's good.
Give your best from now on ok?
Yes.
Alright, congratulations.
That's good.
The three previous Shichifukujin are still at the backstage.
Ichiki, Nakada, and Sakurai.
That's right.
Will they ever make it into the senbatsu? A little worried.
That will be really bad. Can they make it?
Only 8 slots left and the ninth members will be...
It rang. Who is that?
-Who's that? -Who is that?
Ah! It's Inoue.
Oh! Inoue made it.
Congratulations.
Her energetic personality that keeps on shining no matter what, Inoue!
Although she did not make it into the Shichifukujin, she made it into the senbatsu.
Congratulations.
Very frustrating.
Very frustrating? Please tell us about your feeling right now.
I'm frustrated.
Why? What makes you frustrated?
I had a higher goal than this.
You hoped that your cellphone had rang earlier than this, is that right?
-Yes. -Is that so?
But I'd still made it into the senbatsu
so I'll do my best too.
You can climb to the top from here.
There is only seven slots left, who is going to be the tenth member?
Ichiki, Nakada and Sakurai's cellphone did not ring at all.
Will they ring?
But....Oh? It rang. Who is it?
Nishino!
-Thank you very much. -It's from Nishino's cellphone.
Gifted with the ability to draw
and even became the first to have the "fashion leader" title.
EP09 regarding the "fashion leader" title.
The highly regarded Nishino Nanase. Congratulations on her making into the senbatsu!
Your cellphone rang, right? What's your feeling at this moment?
I'm really happy.
That's good.
Only 6 slots left!
The original Shichifukujin still has three members...
This is kinda unbelievable right now.
Oh, it's Nakada!
Nakada's rang!
Moshi Moshi...
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Unfortunately she dropped out from the Shichifukujin
But just like during the acting test, Nakada worked really hard until her tears fell.
Congratulations on making into the senbatsu.
I'm frustrated because I did not make it into the Shichifukujin.
I kept thinking what if I didn't even make it into the senbatsu...
What should I do after that?
So I'm really happy that I made it into the senbatsu.
Thank you, everyone.
Only five slots left.
Man...Ichiki and Sakurai.
I wonder how they feel at this moment.
It rang. Who is it?
Who is it?
-Oh?Sato? -Saito..?
Saito Yuri!
-Saito Yuri! -Thank you very much.
Felt like she's lagging behind,
but she actually gave her best silently, Saito Yuri.
Working very hard even she's behind everyone, she finally made it into the senbatsu.
I'm one of the "lagging-behind-dancing-trio" during the class.
So I bought a bunch of dance lesson CDs
and kept practicing at home.
Lately, I received a few compliments saying that "I did great".
Only 4 slots left!
Oh? Who's that?
-Saito Asuka! -Saito Asuka?
Moshi mos..
-I'll work hard, thank you very much. -After Saito Yuri is Saito Asuka.
A little bit of childish aura, but her dancing skill is still highly regarded.
Saito Asuka, congratulations on making into the senbatsu.
I don't have any confidence at all.
I don't really understand that which part of me is recognized by everyone.
But I'm really happy that I'm in, so I don't want to think about them right now.
Only 3 slots left.
Ichiki and Sakurai have yet to be called, the two of the original Shichifukujin.
It rang, who is it?
-Ichiki? -It's Ichiki!
Ichiki's cellphone rang!
Moshi Moshi...
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, thank you very much.
The fourteenth members.
Dropped out from the Shichifukujin,
but because she's a jack of all trades she entered the senbatsu!
I thought I won't made it.
I'm really happy.
I won't give up. I'll believe in myself and do my best.
There's only two slots remaining.
The only Shichifukujin member that did not receive a call yet is Sakurai.
Will she receive a call?
It rang. Who is it?
-Oh! Noujo? -Noujo!
It's Noujo!
-It's Noujo Ami. -Thank you very much.
Noujo, who is almost giving up on the senbatsu.
But during the show her actions showed us her unique charisma and she made it into the senbatsu!
Honestly, I almost gave up.
But I'm shocked to hear my phone rang.
I'll do my best thank you, everyone.
We finally reached the final members...
The only Shichifukujin member
Sakurai, her phone has yet to receive a call.
There's only one slot left and the last member is...
Konichiwa, we're Nogizaka46.
Have you checked out our official website yet?
Other than members profile, the website has everything you need to know about us.
Please do check out Nogizaka46!
And please come and see us!
We'll be waiting for you at our official website!
Only one slot left...
Who will be the last member?
It's here!
-Yes, thank you very much. -It's Sakurai! -Sakurai.
The last original Shichifukujin member Sakurai
Although she was the last member, her experienced variety show appearance helps her made it into the senbatsu.
I thought that this is totally impossible for me.
Really...my tears...the tears...
there are no more tears left to cry anymore.
When Nakada was picked, you cried just like you entered the senbatsu.
-Nakada. -Yeah, she's still crying.
-Congratulations. -Congratulations Sakurai.
That's all. The 16 members that will be participating the debut single performance has been confirmed.
This time the members which did not make it received a message from someone.
Akimoto Yasushi ( 秋元 康 ) also Known as Aki-P. Producers for multiple idol groups such as Nogizaka46.
Eh... it's sad, to those who did not made it into the senbatsu.
But please do not give up yet.
This is just the beginning
did not make it for once does not mean you're bad.
Let's just give it a try, the debut single.
We're still testing the music
And we have to consider the business collaboration with others. So that's why these members got picked.
But really, it's still just the beginning of it.
So we still have to consider who's better at this and who's not good at that kind of stuff.
Please work hard and find out your own true color and let that color
become a part of Nogizaka46, a part which will become essential to the group.
I'll look forward to it.
Well Akimoto-san said that, right? Please do your best from now on.
-Yes. -Alright.
Well, that's it for now.
-Congratulations! -Thank you very much.
Finally, Nogizaka's senbatsu members are recording their debut single.
They're recording with all their might.
Nogizaka46 Debut Single will be available on 22nd February! Please look forward to it!
After this Nogizaka46 are going to celebrate the end of a year.
Yoroshiku Oneigaishimasu. Merry Christmas!
Inside Sony's building in Ginza,
Nogizaka46 had their Christmas Special Week Event!
-Everyone has been queuing up from the early morning. -There's a crowd! -That's right.
We're really happy.
Really happy and it warms my heart.
Because it's Christmas there are even people who dressed up as reindeer
Yeah, and even Santa Claus.
Honestly, this is my first time to have this kind of memory during Christmas.
First time since I was born.
It'll be the same for next year.
-Yes, even that it's end of the year. -We'll be happy hold an event. -Yes.
Nogizaka46 who always working so hard towards their goal every day.
Please do not divert your attention from them for this year too!
Next week the new senbatsu members will show us their shocking side.
Next week we are having "new senbatsu members" series!
Their shocking side is going to be revealed!
Concerned questions and unexpected answers!
Because members' invitations were really annoying, so I declined every time.
The incomprehensible wishes of the members are...?
Why did you laugh?
Well because it's weird.