www.ikuchancheeks.blogspot.com
Translator: Tamami46chan
English translator: DOZO
On today's Nogizatte, Doko
Members will make short trips to 8 locations across the country
This sub far away from perfection
translation and syntax errors might still be there ! Please bear with us :D
Striving to promote thir Debut Single
Going to a ski resort for their promotion, that's hell !
Members will cry
Can they accomplish their task ?
Hello ! Let's get this show started
We're Bananaman Crazy TV !
No, no, no. That's wrong
This is Nogizakatte Doko, right?
Don~, this is Nogizakatte Doko.
Good afternoon.
As you can see, today the members aren't in the studio
and there's not the usual members introduction like "Here's Nogizaka-chan~"
Only 2 people
because they're not there
If you do that, there's just a refrigerator over there
Himura-san, let get it on with the theme
A short PR Tour to promote in 8 locations !
Today we'll talk about their upcoming Debut
On February 22nd
The first single:
"Guruguru Curtain"
They will debut
We had the senbatsu members do a short PR countrywide for the single promotion
and we "stole" it from them
for us to show you !
Don't say it so seriously
Like we actually did it
January 29th at 4:00 AM
Without knowing anything about this, an emergency announcement is made to the members
- Good morning everyone.
- Good morning !
Today you will be promoting the single Guruguru Curtain to the public
you will do the promotion in different areas
- Don't they all look tired ?
16 people will be divided into four groups of four people each.
And each group will have to go to two cities.
And there, you will be handing out 4600 tissues in one day.
All in a day ?!
Saito Asuka, Hashimoto, Sakurai and Ikoma will go to Sendai and Sapporo
Ichiki, Kawamura, Matsumura and Nakada will travel to Niigata and Osaka
Nishino, Saito Yuri, Takayama, Wakatsuki will go towards Kyoto and Nagoya
Some senbatsu members couldn't be here because they had an exam to take.
Ikuta and Wakatsuki look forward to promoting the single
Furthermore
Shiraishi, Inoue, Noujo and Hoshino will travel to Hiroshima and Fukuoka
Their job is now to promote the first single by giving out the tissues
The number of tissues (4,600) represents the 46 from Nogizaka46
Each group is assigned to distribute 1150 tissues
Each group must give all the tissues within the given time limit.
Each group will move from one city to another to share the tissues with the public
The fans suggested locations for the distribution through Twitter
Then, based on that information, the members will choose their destination
Members are divided into groups and they leave for the city
first, four members went to sendai
We have arrived. In Sendai.
Look, it's written over there too.
It's pretty cold right now
even the air feels cold
According to twitter their first goal is Aoba
See the big screen over there...
I imagine the "Guruguru Curtain" PV on it
Huge Vision
Would be nice, best way to promote it
Must be very nice yeah
According to Twitter information, the 4 members will visit famous places in sendai
First up is Aoba
We've arrived at Aoba
Seeing the statue of Masamune made these 4 members eager to begin, but...
There's... no one here.
Nobody
Since we're far from Tokyo...
Although this is a touristic attraction in Sendai
Because it's 9 AM and in winter, no one's around
The 4 of them change plan and decide to head for the souvenir shop
Sorry to interrupt
Good morning.
we are from the idol gorup named nogizaka46
On February 22nd, we will be launching our debut single
"Guruguru Curtain"
Please accept this tissue
and also, if you don't mind, can you please put up this poster for us
can you put it up ?
Yes
Thank you very much !
In pursuit of promotion for the single, they visit interesting specialty shops
and they also sign their posters in the shop
That's when...
This is a typical Sendai dish, our specialty
Sharing with others
I'll give you one as a special gift
This is the freshest
It's all green
Sendai is a city famous for its miso and bakeries
Is it good ?
Very soft, it's delicious
Since we're in Sendai, please say "zunda mochi", okay ?
1, 2... zunda mochi~
typical mochi of Sendai
Thank you very much
Then the members receive good news from the staff
You remember the big screen in front of the Sendai Station ?
Well, I tried to contact the owner and
They said we can play the PV at 10:54:15
To meet the members's expectations, the staff contacted the owner of the big screen near the station
The big screen in front of Sendai Station will display Guruguru Curtain's PV
8:30 AM
Inoue, Hoshino Noujo, and Shiraishi have reached the Hiroshima airport
Then, they immediately look up Twitter  what places the fans have recommended
Lot's of suggestions coming in, that's nice
What's this ?
"Marina Hop"
from a small 4-wheeler society
(the name of his tamiya group)
What's "4 small wheels"?
What is it like?
Makes you wonder
Meanwhile the staff has negotiated for the place
and they have chosen Maria Hop as in the fan's suggestion via twitter
but they did not see any fans from Hiroshima present
neither were they at the plaza, but...
Ah there?
Is it a toy car?
Ah i'm so nervous!
It'll be fine
and then the group introduced themselves
We will release our debut single "Guruguru Curtain"
on February 22 and we came here to promote it
We'll be handing out these tissues,
please accept them.
Though, most visitors did not understand what this meant
They feel like they can't muster the courage to do it
I tell you, it's too much of a distance, so...
You must be brave...
- I'll try
In the end, they manage to break the ice and go on about distributing the tissues to the public
Please support us
Thank you.
Please
What's your name ?
I am Shiraishi Mai
Most people did not really know about Nogizaka46
At last, these 4 members managed to promote their debut single
Center?
I'm not a center
Let's go
Following the crowd, the four of them went to see the tamiya races
The members receive a warm welcome inside
and then...
Would you like participating in the game ?
Can I, really ?
Emergency Offer
Can we?
I want to try !
They then borrow tamiya from the contestant
if they win in this race, it will be a good public relations
But Nojou's car only has one little problem...
Her car had a small problem but it worked out for her, she's first !
Really ?
And so the promotion for the single continues
February 22nd, we will release our first single titled "Guruguru Curtain"
A happy and cheerful song
Everyone, please listen to it
It was nice meeting you !
Joining in on the competition was a good push forward for the campaign
We're from nogizaka46, plese remember about us, okay ?
ah, you just gave me some !
Since participating effectively in the race competition, members have distributed as many as 200 tissues
Meanwhile, another team is in Osaka, Niigata
After waiting for a long time, they finaly decide to first go to Tokyo Station
It's now the fans that must decide where the promotion will take place
And the suggestions they receive from Twitter are...
The Ski resort
Ski resort
There are many people present at the Ski resort
A promotion from the radio DJ booth would be great too
With that, all the members go to SKI GALA in Yuzawa
7:30 AM
They have reached the station Yuzawa GALA
Good morning
First, they meet with someone who recommended the place via Twitter
DJ starts at 9:00 AM
at this time they are being treated and checked
at 09:00 o'clock, the DJ is already at work
So they'll go somewhere else
We're from Nogizaka46 and...
Sorry for bothering you, but please accept this
But no one paid attention
The temperature is -4.4°C
The heavy snowfall makes the distribution tissue all the more difficult
Good morning !
Suddenly that snowboarder stopped
Will he accept the tissues ?
We are from Nogizaka46
Yeah, I know you guys
...at the Tokyo Dome
Eh ?!
Tokyo Dome City hall, the live show with AKB
Ah thank you !
Please accept this
Thank you very much !
Finaly, after 30 minutes, they succesfully handed out tissues
But since they're having a hard time giving out tissues, the 4 members will move to another location
Please accept these
Thank you.
I know about you guys
you were with Bananaman at an event right ?
Thank you.
With heavy wind and snow, the members keep on giving out tissues.
9 AM, time for the DJ radio show to begin
Good morning!
Today, our guests are some very cute women
We are Nogizaka46 !
Energetic because it is indoors!
Thank you.
Can you announce the name of your single ?
it's Nogizaka46's-
"Guruguru Curtain"
Thus the campaign of the first single "Guruguru Curtain" in the ski area was successful !
and then they continue distributing tissue to the visitors
I will buy a CD !
For real ?
I've become your fan
After doing their best on the last location
they have successfully distributed 400 tissues
Nishino, Saito, Takayama and Wakatsuki will now leave
First PR in Kyoto
We've arrived in Kyoto !
First they'll look at the suggestions place from the fans on Twitter.
If we're talking promotion, of course Arashiyama will be popular
It appeared several times
We have to go there
Go to Arashiyama radio
Everyone says Arashiyama
Wah, you're right!
Well it's settled then
Let's go to Arashiyama!
The four of them walked in a natural forest in Arashiyama, but...
But there's no one around!
No people
Yup, no one in sight
no one
I thought it could have been the right choice for Kyoto but...
We thought there would be many people here !
Yeah
Its beautiful, so why is there no one around!
They finaly find people
Good morning~ Good morning~
We're Idols from Nogizaka46
Please accept these tissues
Thank you
We are from nogizaka46...
Thank you.
Nice to meet you guys, thank you
Since it's early in the morning, there are few people around
They do not waste their time, they still share with the people around
Don't think about it, we only have to reach our goal
I was a bit worried to be honest
in Sendai, as they have time before their PV is displayed on the screen
they headed to the Shinseido CD shop
We Nogizaka46 will be releasing our debut single on February 22nd, thank you very much
And, also... the poster
ah, I see
2 pieces.
A kind manager allows them to install four posters
and right in the middle !
It's about time the PV will be playing on the big screen
and members and fans meet at the sendai station
Finaly, the PV will soon be promoted to the public !
Soon after the PV, the four members sang along and danced to the music
After that, they continue handing out tissues to the fans
after meeting with fans at the sendai station, they quickly distributed 200 tissues
and they have distributed 400 tissues total
This time in Hiroshima
Fans have suggested to Nogizaka46 the tower of Hiroshima
Unexpectedly, around 200 fans had been waiting for Nogizaka46
They then start promoting
and one member found someone who knew her
Since Wada Maya is from Hiroshima, she also invited here friend
Hang in there
I will try my best
With the help of Wada Maya all went well
On February 22nd, we will officially release our debut single
Adding up the previous location, this group has also distributed 400 tissue
On the other hand, the Ski group in Nigata is now headed for the city
Even in the car, they keep on promoting
Thank you.
We are the official rival of AKB48... Nogizaka46
We are making our debut single, so, please accept this.
Thank you.
Thank you very much
Do you know the group in the picture?
I really don't
but I know AKB48 !
Then, members go the to Bandai Plaza in Niigata
Suddenly...
- Sayuriiiin !
Haaiiiii
It turns out, the fans had been waiting for them here
with more than 100 people present
Finally, the Niigata team has successfully distributed 500 tissues
Meanwhile, on the other side of the group, in Kyoto
Many tissues remain to be shared
and they start handing them out in the streets, but most don't know about Nogizaka46
But then, one member is crying
It's okay, all is well
What is going on?
We are Nogizaka46, please accept this, thank you
despite being ignored by some passersby
Takayama, Saito and Wakatsuki keep smiling and continue the promotion
but one member couldn't do it. Nishino.
staff was wondering what happened to her
Ganbare
and that's the reason why she cried while handing out tissues
Nanase
It's okay
as long as there are others who accept it, it's fine !
Nishino seems sensitive to seeing the people ignore her
because for her, it hurts to be rejected
Calm down
after I finish my share of tissues, I will help you out
Don't make a big deal out of it
Go in with positive
Thank you.
Worried that they might not make it, they fought hard to hand out Nishino's part
3 members that won't give up try to complete the task without Nishino
It's okay, do not worry.
People gradually start taking more tissues ... and later when
nanase has recovered, after the breakdown...
With the support of the members, Nishino has gradually stabilized and can carry on
doing their task
Nice to meet you
I will support you!
With Nishino back, it makes the other members become more enthusiastic
Within half an hour, the members had distributed 500 tissues
Thank you very much, ah I'm happy
One box is empty !
Thank you.
and all teams move onto the second city
Will they manage to complete the promotion goal ?
www.ikuchancheeks.blogspot.com
Next.
PV "Aitakatta kamo shirenai"