ongxom × show46
Today Nogizakatte Doko!
Test reaction by roller coaster and the haunted house.
The high tension leads to strong reaction.
Moreover, the bursting balloon makes the whole studio panic.
Doooon!This is Nogizakatte Doko !
We are the MC ...Bananaman
and the Nogizaka46 members.
Our guests today are the members of Dachou Club.
Only two members?
Jimon is busy today, he has to eat meat.
It is Hongyou no Show ?
What should we do today?
We have to invite Dachou Club here,
Himura, introduce the show please.
This week, first-time : reaction check!
It is the special ability of Dachou club
In reaction category, including Himura, we have the trio.
Of course today is for Nogizaka to learn but the people really need to learn is us.
To test the reaction of Nogizaka, we go to Fuji Q Highland
First, the maximum height - 70m and the speed is 130km/h.
The reaction with Mount Fuji.
So what kind of reaction Nogizaka will bring ?
The first to go is Nakada and Sakurai.
The roller has come to the height at 79m.
Scary!!
It is time to go down!!
This is the generic type of reaction.
Don't do that! Wait a sec!
Wait a sec! I am going to die!
I can't ! I can't !
Droll
Sakurai's droll comes out, a really good reaction.
The next person is Shiraishi
What should I do? Can I survive after this?
Still not going down yet?
Eyes opened
I can't take this
What should I do?
No way.
bye bye bye AAAAAAAAaaa!
Shiraishi closed her eyes and...
Arg! No way.
You can see
the Mount Fuji
I cannot see it.
I don't open my eyes.
Despite of closing eyes, but she shows a good reaction.
The next person is Hashimoto Nanami
WOW! So beautiful !!
Closed eyes
budhha?
and then there is no another reaction.
looks like an old lady sleeping in the metropolitan.
after it goes down, she becomes another person, a really weird reaction.
The next person is Hatanaka, has no confidence in sport.
What kind of reaction?
Laughing or crying??
She ends it with a confusing face.
Like Hashimoto, Hatanaka has a weird reaction.
The last one is Ikoma
Cries before starting
Crying out loud.
the train is going down
and then accelerated suddenly.
Feeling high?
Ikoma shows us a nice reaction with an extraordinary facial expression.
The test for the roller coaster ended here.
Ikoma is not a baby anymore.
She cried since entering the cab.
But she stopped crying when the cab was going down.
Very new.
It feels like you are going to die.
the wind bangs me.
The wind attacks you ? Fascinating .
At this time, I cannot breathe
I open my mouth and it becomes vroom-vroom.
This scene is so cool.
Because cute girls don't do this.
I am curious about the droll girl!
She is Sakurai
What about the droll?
Droll is not required, it can be any type of water.
- She is an idol !
-Thanks for your comment.
The next destination is fuji Q highland
You will face an abandoned hospital with ghosts.
What kind of reaction will Nogizaka show?
The first to go is Matsumura Sayuri
Crying out loud
Despite of crying, she goes ahead, this is the general type of reactions.
The next person is Noujou Ami
Keep your head held high... go ahead!
Mommy!
Don't do that.! What is this? Don't come here!!
Collided with the camera
Please be careful with the camera.
The next to go is Sakurai.
Run fast
Collide with the camera again
Sakurai has collided with the cameraman like Noujou
and cries because it hurts.
The next to go is the one who has weird reaction before , Hashimoto.
Exiled?
Drop the cameraman
run too fast and left the cameraman behind.
The next one is lousy Nagashima
overcomes the K point
RUN
Although she tries to escape....
Blocked by a devil!
A shouting reaction.
The next one is Shiraishi, who closed her eyes in previous scene.
Crying?
No way! What should I do! No way ! I am sorry.
No way ! What should I do ?
I can't do this!
Afraid of camera.
I am sorry!!
I am really sorry.
GIVE UP
Suddenly, she has given up.
The next one is Hatanaka with a confusing face in previous scene.
This time she also shows us a very confusing reaction.
Hashimoto , what is it ?
Look like a criminal is being wanted by Manbiki G-man.
"Stolen !" "Stolen !"
I was escaping.
- You are scared ?
- Yes
You don't scream when you are scared, even in the roller coaster.
This category is exciting.
You do nothing but you show a no hope face.
You like screaming a lot, Nagashima
You screamed too loud, the people stand 200 meters away from you can hear that.
Your volume is amazing!
You should lower your volume.
Screaming like you can make the audio technician scares.
If the staff hates you, then you are done.
In the studio, we have prepared some situations to test the reaction of those members.
We should start now.
The first game is "bursting balloon".
When I say "start", the balloon will be filled with air.
Himura will describe the answer doing something.
If a member can provide a correct answer, the balloon will be passed to the next person.
If the balloon explodes on a member, then she losses the game.
The first to go is those 6 members.
What kind of reaction will be shown in this game?
Prepare! The bursting balloon! Start
Chimpanzee
- Monkey
- It's like a monkey but it is not.!
- Orangutan
Gorrila
- Chimpanzee
- ah betul! selanjut nya
Police
What is this?
- Police
- OK
Tanoshingo
- Tanoshingo
- Correct!
Doraemon
- It is easy
- I don't know.
What is this?
- A manga character
- Doraemon
Correct.
Ramen
- Ramen
- Correct, the next one.
- What is this?
- KARA
Correct, go to the first person.
Giraffe
Correct.
Kendo
What is this? Sport!!
- Kendo
- Correct.
Takano Hana
The sumo wrestler
Ikoma, are you alright?
- How is the reaction?
- Very good.
This is a good face expression, keep it like this.
Ikoma's expression is very good.
- We have to keep this face
- Correct.
Keep this face expression to the next game
This is the next groupt and we have a sample.
We have Ueshima too.
Can I participate ?
Please.
- Wait a minute
- What is it?
Ah, you are negotiating.
Those basic things are very important.
The most important thing here is the gas pumping guy.
Ready to go! The Bursting Balloon ! Start....!!
Drunken
Correct.
ice skating
What is this?
Ice skating
Baby
Dandy Sakano
Gets
What is the name?
Dandy Sakano
Correct, Ueshima san
Pitcher (Baseball)
What are you doing Himura?
Hey, Himura
Scary!
What are you scare of?
I am really scary
You stay outside, you just have to tell me the answer, is it simple ?
It is because of you, hold the balloon and run over.
You are going to say I am an idiot???
@#$%3@@$%%亲
It's all scripted!
The next game is "What is inside the box". A classic game to test the reaction.
What is inside the box?
The first to go is ...Noujou Ami
I will open it. In this game all people in the studio must work together.
- Expressions like "ah, uhm" are prohibited
- The reaction is very important.
You must show you are scared extremely.
Inside the box is.....
So good!
Konyaku
That must be it
Noujou, what is inside the box ?
Deep breath, so good.
You are doing great..... Noujou
First, go with a fast touch.
Just a little bit
Have you touched it?
Nice gesture.
Have you touched it? What is the feeling?
How is the feeling?
It has many sides, what is this?
and it's slippery too
You grab it.
This is.......... konnyaku, isn't it?
Correct
The next to play is Hashimoto Nanami
Up to now, all of your reactions are weird.
Inside the box is
Here is it.
Octopus
This is the worst.
Ready
What is inside the box? Please !
I am scared.
- Mine is very disgusting, isn't it?
- Maybe that.
- You are doing great.
- You touch it.
It's good!
My hands get wet.
What is this? Disgusting...
Touch it completely.
Turtle?
This part is wet.
What happens?
It sucks my hand.
It sucks your hand?
The unexpected reaction from Hashimoto makes both the octopus and the studio in panic state.
- What is this?
- What is this? It should not be too disgusting
You don't scare? It is easy.
What is inside the box?
- Cobra
- Cobra???
Please see the answer.
- In the front ?
- You can see from any side.
It is good.
How do you rate this reaction?
She should raise her hand like this.
Makes me feel touching.
- You are doing great.
- Congratulation
The next challenger is.....Ueshima san
I have played The Bursting Balloon.
What is the problem, just play it.
I won't do this for the second time.
Then leave it to me.
- Then I will do this
- I want to join.
Me too.
- I will do this too.
- Please.
You do like this a lot, don't you ?
Inside the box is...
Lobster
This must be scary.
Go please!
- You see it
- I don't see anything.
It's clear that you see it.
I don't see it.
OK, you don't see anything.
So we start now.
- What is inside the box?
- Lobster
You see it.
No way? I guess it from the atmosphere.
OK, inside the box is a lobster? What is the problem?
What?
try to catch it.
and then....
And then
- Plug it to your nose
- Wait
Let me do it by myself
I did it.