In tonight's Nogidoko, Members from the Chiho region take the Tokyo Quiz to see who are the country bumpkins!
The member's answers far exceed expectations
THIS WILL NEVER END!
Furthermore, members from Chiho take on a challenge to run errands in Tokyo for the first time!
What is the reason for these tears!?
Timed by Cloud Strife
Translated by Jiaemi & Fuyufahri
For more subs visit Facebook.com/IkomaSubs
Brought to you by IkomaSubs
Let's stop this!
DON~!!!
Let's begin "Nogizakatte Doko?" tonight, we are Bananaman!
And these are the members of Nogizaka46!
Also we welcome this week's guest! Erm .. T - K - O ..
Glad to have you here!
You read it together!
This week, her first time appearing, from Nagasaki, 13 years old Kawago Hina!
Let's we announce this time project, Himura! Please do title call in an interesting manner!
For today's show
To get Chiho region members used to Tokyo quickly!!
So as said, we definitely want the members to get used to Tokyo, right?
Ikoma you're from Akita, right?
Yes
And Yamato from Miyagi
Also Hatanaka from Oita
There is a challenge for you 3
With that said, Himura, please do it subtly
Heres the VTR .. son son son ~
Someday in November, at the SME Nogizaka building in Minato-ku Nogizaka, the 3 members have gathered without knowing being informed of anything
For today, you 3 would film-on-location
Yes
What kind of film-on-location would this be?
In your own clothes?
Today, in order to for Chiho members get used to Tokyo quickly
For that to happen, each 1 of you would go to a designated location in Tokyo alone
And complete your given task and assemble at the designated spot
They said that we would do this alone!
Yeah
This is the worst!
I can't go alone
For Ikoma from Akita, the task is to
"Kibundou (紀文堂)": a waffle chain store
Buy the waffles from Kibundou in Azabu-juuban and gather in Shibuya Town Hall
The estimated total time taken would be 45 mins
For the instruction for Hatanaka
"Ebi-Ebizushi"?
"Ebizushi"?
It's "Ebisu"!
Is she for real?
Woah this is something new!
The most glutton member, currently on a diet, the instruction for Hatanaka is
"Kimu Katsu (キムカツ)": a tonkotsu chain store
Buy the Kimu Katsu sandwich from Kimu Katsu and gather at Shibuya Town Hall
The total estimated duration is 35 mins
The instruction for Yamato Rina from Miyagi is to go to the AKB48 Shop in Harajuku and take a photo there
And gather at Shibuya Town Hall. The total estimated time is 25 mins
It's the closest, right?
Which part of Shibuya is this?
Can we use our mobile phones to navigate to the goal?
"Ebizushi"?
No, we will take your mobile phones away
No way! Why you are like this!
They take your mobile phone? It would be impossible!
Yes
"Wellcom" is also no?
Would the 3 of them meet again safe and sound?
Without much planning, Hatanaka starts walking aimlessly
Where is the train station?
Where am I?
Oh shes aiming to head for Roppongi station?
I don't know
What should I do now ..
She doesn't know where is Roppongi
First things first, Hatanaka heads to the nearest convenience store to ask for directions
Excuse me, could you direct me to the nearest train station from here?
Just go straight ahead, you will find the Hibiya Line
Thank you
With that, Hatanaka heads for the nearest station, Roppongi station
What is this place?
Before anything, I'll try to find my way there myself
This is the spirit of trying!
Yamato heads to Harajuku via Nogizaka station
She got the nearest goal right?
Lastly for Ikoma
What should I do .. its scary ~
You dropped something
Hatanaka has reached Ebisu station from Roppongi station via the Hibiya Line
This looks like its her first time in Ebisu
The crepes look delicious!
I want to eat them
Doremi fa ~ so many varieties of crepes
Yamato who has reached the Meiji Shrine Station from Nogizaka station via the Chiyoda Line
I don't know where is the AKB48 shop! But ..
She's doing well, right?
I'll just walk
Optimistic wherever she goes
At the same time, Ikoma walked for around 30 mins from Nogizaka to Azabu-juuban shopping district
You walked there?
Eh?! Its quite a distance you know!
Can you even walk from Nogizaka to Azabu-juuban?!
As expected I don't know the way there ~
So many buildings, so many people, so many trains, and the air here is thick ..
Why is the air here so thick!
She expresses her dissatisfaction about Tokyo
I think I should ask someone for directions
But even if they give me directions, I don't know this streets well ~
And at that time!
A bookstore!
She discovers a bookstore! And then!
I think I shall buy a Mapple Map
Mapple: A popular guide map brand
It should be okay to buy a map
They didn't say that I couldn't buy a map to aid me
Let's buy Tokyo's "Mapple"
But unfortunately the map is sold out! Please aim for the goal on your own
Where is the convenience store?
Convenience store, convenience store
She keeps searching for convenience stores
Instead of searching for her goal, Hatanaka is looking for a convenience store
Without further delay, she heads to her favorite convenience store and asks for directions
Excuse me, is there a shop called Kimu Katsu around here?
Go out from this street and cross the road, the shop is on the right side
Right side, right?
Hatanaka quickly obtains useful information from the convenience store! But however..
It isn't here! There's no Kimu Katsu Sandwich shop here
Because there's no convenience store nearby, I can't ask anyone!
KIMU KATSU
Its just there!
She is almost reaching
Unexpectedly, she totally didn't see the shop and just passed by the shop
You're kidding me right?
At the same time, aiming to get to the AKB48 shop Yamato has reached Takeshita street but ..
Where is AKB48 shop?
Where is AKB? Where is AKB?
And then ..
Ah! There it is!
AKB48 Harajuku is written on the signboard
Unexpectedly, she has quickly located her destination
There is Suu-chan's file here!
You've already in Nogizaka you know!
Cool!
There are fans of AKB in Nogizaka too right?
I think I'll buy it ~
With high tension she takes the photo and finishes the mission! The final destination is Shibuya Town Hall
At the same time, Ikoma
It's scary .. scaryy
I don't want to ask anybody ..
There are so many people here ..
Without asking anyone for directions, Ikoma does not know which direction to go
This is an issue, you seem afraid to approach strangers
Also, for the lost Hatanaka ..
Yes I was afraid of strangers
Convenience store, convenience store, where is it?
Other than asking directions from the staff at convenience stores, you have no other measures?
As a last resort, she searches for a convenience store
Excuse me
Why you always go there?
There is a shop called Kimu Katsu around here, right?
You just walk straight and turn left
Oh, really? Thank you very much
You just walking in loops right?
Hatanaka obtains vital information from the convenience store staff!
Aiming to reach the the Kimu Katsu shop!
Here it is! Here it is!
Can I buy anything I want?
After asking directions from convenience stores 6 times, she has finally reached her destination!
Excuse me, one Kimu Katsu sandwich, please
As per the mission, she orders a plain Kimu Katsu sandwich
Excuse me, one more, cheese Kimu Katsu sandwich please
The other two have already finished their missions! What would you do Ikoma-chan?
Excuse me, could you give me some directions?
Umm .. I am searching for this shop named Kibundou
You can see a heart signboard, right? In front of the signboard, turn left
the shop is located at the edge of the building
Thank you very much
After building up the courage to ask, success in obtaining directions to the goal!
I'm done!
I've bought it!
Having completed her mission safely, she heads to Shibuya Town Hall
There are so many people!
Yeah, there are many people here
Noo .. there are so many people here!
The atmosphere too
What? What? What?
It's looks like she is going to cry
What? What? What? What?
What's wrong?
It's an ambulance!
Its scary~
It scares me
The sound of the siren is scary~
Why can't they just turn off the siren!
What you've said about the siren is amazing!
Thats Ikoma-chan, right?
Ikoma~!!!
Ikomacchi!
Oh, not bad!
Oi, you're slow!
You've worked hard didn't you
It was scary?
Are you okay?
It was scary!
You cried eh?
Yamato why did you cry too?
Whats with you all?
All of you are crying
Yamato why are you crying too?
Yamato Rina took 1 hour 30 mins to reach the goal, which usually should take around 25 mins
Hatanaka Seira took 1 hour 45 mins to reach the goal, which usually should take around 35 mins
Ikoma Rina took 2 hour 15 mins to reach the goal, which usually should take 45 mins
I never want to walk here alone ever again
I will not walk here alone a second time
Yeah, me too
Its been hard on you 3, good work!
This was just a mission to go somewhere nearby in Tokyo, who would have expected tears
Yeah! Everyone cried in the end
Yamato you seemed like you were progressing smoothly, but still you took an hour and a half to go there
To be honest, even though I was humming songs, I felt lonely as there was no one to talk to me
So you cheered up yourself by humming songs right?
Ah .. I see. Because it's scary right?
But your self-confidence also plays a part right? Whether you can move forward or not
By believing in myself and moving forward, a path would surely open!
Very good!
Shes like Antonio Inoki!
Antonio Inoki: a Japanese politician and former pro wrestler
Yes, Inoki-san!
If you move forward, what would the result be?
Hatanaka!
Yes!
From what we saw in the VTR, you approached a total of 6 convenience stores for directions right?
Even though you asked so many times, why were you not able to find your way?
Erm .. The people that gave me directions were bad at it ..
OI!
Even though they took the expense to give you directions?
Thats not good you know
Ikoma!
Yes!
You seemed like you weren't able to call out to passer-bys to ask for directions
I was scared to do so
What were you scared of?
Because the people were walking so fast
Ah, so to you they walk fast?
Yes, they walk fast
Eh? In Akita people walk slower?
Yes, they walk slower
I see
For T.K.O, how many times have you all failed to enter into Tokyo's showbiz?
This time is the fifth time
So the fifth time you finally succeeded
Currently T.K.O isn't that popular
We are quite popular, you know!
Stop itttttt! It was weird just now!
Stop saying such things!
Lets help the members from the Chiho region to get used to Tokyo, the next project is ..
Who is the country bumpkin!? Tokyo Question & Answer!!
The 9 Chiho members are divided into 3 teams and given Tokyo-related quiz questions
There will be a loser from each group and the losers would advance to the next stage
The "winner" which remains at the end would be crowned "Miss Rural"
For the member who is the most unfamiliar to Tokyo
You would go tour bus sightseeing with me around Tokyo, just the two of us
EHHHH ~
We wanna go ~!
But Himura would be constantly ..
You're with me only you know
He would be constantly toughing your thighs, is that okay?
EHH EHH EHH?!
Because it's a punishment
The 1st preliminary round consists of Yamato, Shiraishi and Nagashima
Question!
The Yamanote Line in Sugamo station is called 「Obaachan's OOOO」 ?
Ans: Harajuku
Ikoi no Ba - A spot for relaxation
It's not a place for relaxation!
Shokudou no Ba - A place for dining!
Wait a minute! You all answer too fast!
After you've pressed the button, and the sign comes up, I will prompt you to give your answer first!
You all overlapped each other!
Heres a hint, it's a twist on the name of a place in Tokyo
Yes, that the place!
Shibuya!
Ahh! So close!
NOT THAT .. BUT!
It's here! Okay, please answer!
Harajuku?
Correct!
Shiraishi and Nagashima is left, who would advance into the finals!?
The name of the movie consisting of 48 works, set in Tokyo - Shibamata Taishakuten is called 「Guys are OOOO」 ?
Ans: Tsurai yo
Now, whats the answer?
Okay! Answer it!
Tsurai yo
Tsurai yo: Its emotionally painful
Wait~!
Ah, you both overlapped each other again!
Correct answer!
Even though you overlapped each other, you're good!
Yes, she is
I didn't even have to provide a hint
The next preliminary round consists of Ikoma, Hashimoto and Kawago
Question! These are the Tokyo Tower's mascot
Ans: Noppo-kun
What are their names?
Hashimoto!
Tower-kun
Top-kun
Top-kun? Close answer!
Ikoma!
Noppo! Noppo! Noppo-kun
You were real close to the answer!
Ah sorry! Teppo-kun?
My mistake, Tappo-kun? Ahh wait!
Wait a minute, it's not fair to the others if you give multiple answers!
Only press the buzzer after you have your answer, and only give one answer!
Noppon!
Correct!
Ikoma has passed this quiz!
This is great!
Hashimoto and Kawago are left, who would advance to the finals!?
A famous food of Tokyo, the Fukagawa Don, what are its main ingredients?
Ans: Saltwater Clams
Shrimp?
Shrimp?!
Duck?
Ah, its not duck
Beef?
Incorrect
Fish?
Shall we go for a smoking break?
Lets just accompany them
If they keep guessing, sooner or later they would get the correct answer
Okay, continue, go go!
The ingredient is part of the seafood family
Tuna?
It's not tuna!
The answer is coming!
Kisu!
A fish commonly found in Japan - Sillago
It's really not that one!
Blowfish?
It isn't that expensive!
Shiromizakana
White-fleshed skin fish used for sashimi, sushi, etc
Shiromizakana??
Sanma?
Commonly known as Pike
Not sanma!
Mackerel?
THIS WOULD NEVER END!!
This would never end!
It does not belong to the fish category, like something in rice bowl, that is shaped like this
Scallops?
Surf Clam?
OHHHHH!!
Its a shellfish that can be frequently found in Hokkaido
Basket clams?
SO CLOSE!!
Saltwater clams?
Correct!!
The third preliminary round consists of Itou, Hatanaka and Etou
Question, how do you read this kanji?
Ans: Nippori
Nishi nippori!
Hatanaka, it's your great chance!
Great chance!
Nichi nippori!
NICHI NIPPORI?!
Nichi noppori is incorrect!
Hi nippori?
HI NIPPORI?!
Hatanaka again?!
Hinishiri!
Sadly, incorrect!
All your answers are really close!
Nippori!
Correct!!
They all had that word in their answers!
Wonderful!
Why did you answer Nishi nippori?
Because I've heard about it before
But there's no "nishi" in the word!
Hatanaka and Etou are left, who would be the last one to advance to the finals!?
The place where madams usually gather, Futako Tamagawa street, what is it also known by?
Ans: Nikotama
You might have heard its nickname before
Futago?
The answer ends with "tama", the first part "futago" isn't included
Futatama?
Please answer it correctly!
Your answer is kind of erotic~
Futagotama? Futagotama?
THE BUZZER SOUND OVERLAPPED WITH YOUR VOICE!!
How many times must I tell you to only answer the question when your voice is able to be heard clearly!
If you answer straight away after you press the buzzer, the buzzer's sound would overlap with your voice!
You flipped his switch!
I beg of you to follow that procedure!!
Lets continue this quiz
Ninotama?
Your answer is close! The correct answer is coming!
Nanitama?
Nanitama is the question!
It ain't nanitama!
If you lose here you advance to the finals!
Nikotama?
Correct!
YAY!
Correct, the answer is Nikotama
Its so vexing I lost!
Yeah, I know right!
With that, the members that advance to the finals are Nagashima, Hatanaka and Kawago
Who would be crowned Miss Rural?
I won't lose here!
I definitely won't lose!
I won't lose!
Sounds good, they said it with their own local dialect
Yeah, it's really good to hear
Without further ado, lets begin the final round of this Tokyo Quiz!
The nickname of Akihabara is "Akiba", what is the nickname of Ikebukuro?
Ans: Bukuro
Ikebu! Ikebu!
Ikebu?!
Ikebuku?
Buuike!
Your answer's close!
It's close!
Buuke?
Bukuro!
Bukuro?
Correct!
Okay!
You've slipped through
Right after this a battle that would leave its mark in history! Who would be crowned Miss Rural?
The final match of the Tokyo Quiz! Who one will be crowned Miss Rural?
Here is the question!
What is the nickname of Tokyo Dome? 「Big OOOO」 ?
Ans: Big Egg
Kyoutou? Kyoutou?
Shall we give them a hint?
It's a food
Its a food thats of similar shape as the Tokyo Dome
Big Mochi?
If you answer the same way, you're bound to get the answer
Big rice?
It's not rice!
Big bread!
It's neither rice nor bread!
It's a side dish!
It is stored in the refrigerator
What is normally placed beside the rice?
Big dried plum!
It is among your usual meals
Big miso soup!
Beside it!
You have it for breakfast!
Breakfast!
Big Takana?
Takana: leaf mustard
You're really close!
You usually have it for breakfast when you stay in an inn
You will definitely eat it!
The thing that a hen gives birth to!
Big seaweed?
Big seaweed?!
It's not seaweed!
THE THING THAT A HEN GIVES BIRTH TO!
Egg?
Correct!
You did a good job in getting the correct answer!
Hatanaka you did a good job getting the correct answer
With that, Kawago Hina from Nagasaki has been crowned Miss Rural
After this, Nogizaka heats up Osaka!
Nogizaka46 has venturered into the Kansai region!
Currently in progress, the members are there to meet-and-greet the fans in the Chiho region for the first time
The members also have another goal, and the person who appeared in front of the nervous members is .. ?
Welcome!
Nice to meet you!
TV Osaka's president, Mr Tateiwa
The girls convey their gratitude for allowing Nogidoko to be broadcasted
Have you watched Nogidoko before?
Erm, I watch it sometimes
Thank you very much
You all are having fun recording the show right?
Matsumura represents Nogizaka in giving the President a present
Sayurin, Sayurin, Sayurin-rin
Sayurin, Sayurin, Sayuringo!
I'm filled with sweetness, am I to your tastes?
I see ..
The members has conveyed their gratitude with all they've got
The members head for the next fan meeting site at Nagoya
Even at Nagoya, the fans welcomed them warmly
This events that the members were nervous about has safely concluded
I'll be going ~
The girls are on a tight schedule
The next location where the members head for is TV Aichi
This day, the girls appeared live in a famous informative TV show 「San Jikan No Tsubou」and did some self PR
The meaning of '46' is that even we have lesser members than AKB48, we would not lose
Oh, there is even a sense of rivalry in the naming of your group?
Yes~!
I will support you all
Thank you very much!
Furthermore!
Nice to meet you all
Nice to meet you!
They greeted the president of TV Aichi, Mr Kotani
Mr President, have you watched our program before?
Yes, I watched every episode of it
Thank you very much!
These activities were even publicized on newspapers!
With that said ..
We will go to your city and visit you!
For further details, please check our official website!
Furthermore
Nogizaka46 will appear in Tokyo Motor Show! For more details, please check the official website!
For more subbed Nogizaka shows, visit Facebook.com/IkomaSubs