There's someone with a super-incredible luck for wealth.
After Shuhei Shimada's* evaluations,
A Japanese comedian and a fortune teller.
He'll determine who's the most _____ among Nogizaka46's members!
The unexpected results caused a big panic among the members!
Everyone was like "Ehhh!!?"
What's the shocking truth behind Takayama's palm reading!?
Nogizakatte, Doko?
Credit: NeruestSub Team
Subber1: PleaseEnjoy-san
Don!
Welcome back to this week's "Nogizakatte, Doko?"
We're the MC Bananaman! Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu!
And here are the Nogizaka46's members!
Our guest for this week is the palm reading expert - Shuhei Shimada!
Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu!
So with Shimada here that means our plan for today is...? Himura-san.
Please read it while doing a funny face.
Sh- I can't see the text on the board.
Shuhei Shimada's curse! Who's Nogizaka46's most _____ member!?
The 16 senbatsu members will have their luck evaluated by Shuhei Shimada-san.
With different themes, we'll determine who's Nogizaka46's most _____ member!
The first theme will be
The most likely member to become very rich.
-I wanna become rich. -Who doesn't?
The other might not be that important,
but this luck is all that matters. -Yes, money is important.
There's someone with a super-incredible luck for wealth.
Better than anyone else.
Please reveal the member who most likely to become rich!
Who's the most likely to become rich among Nogizaka's members?
It's Shiraishi-san.
(Subber: You're really rich now 2k18.)
Shiraishi! How do you feel now?
-I'm really happy. -Wait Shiraishi what happened to you?
I've caught a cold. -So you were sick since the past week?
Her palm has a really good sign called the "millionaire sign."
-What's this "millionaire sign?" -Really?
From the "fate line," that's on the middle of the palm and straight down,
and beside it there's this "money line," the longer the better.
And going out from the pinky finger another "money line" to form a triangle shape.
These together has the "millionaire sign," the "conqueror line."
Conqueror line. Best wealth luck.
t was said that Konosuke Matsushita might have this line too.
Shiraishi's palm was the closest to the sign.
Another good news, the "heart line" formed an arrow shape at the end.
Both of the Bananaman has this line on them too.
This is the "lucky charm sign." You'll bring good luck to anyone who stays around you,
Like a Lucky Goddess.
Lucky charm sign. Able to discover and
improve others' hidden talents or charisma.
If Shiraishi stayed with the group,
the group will do well.
She's probably like an essential member of this group.
No..no..no...
-It's cool. -We'll let you know when we wanna buy something.
Buy a pair of sneaker for me ok?
Buy me a sports jacket alright?
Oh? The most suitable member to become the leader.
Haven't decided who's gonna be the leader? -Yeah.
There was a questionnaire for the member,
you guys wrote the name down why don't just let her be the leader?
-It's what everyone wished after all. -So who is it?
Ummm... Sakurai.
Oh, Sakurai.
8 votes received out of 16 votes.
But the palm reading said otherwise.
Please look forward to who's going to be the leader according to the palm reading.
The most suitable member to become the leader is...
It's Inoue-san!
Everyone was like "Ehhh!!?"
What do you mean "Eh!" Inoue's not suitable?
But it's still Inoue.
The reason is that the horizontal line here called "heart line,"
there are these small circles in front of it.
Usually there's two to four circles, it's called the "insight line."
Insight line. Has a very good mind.
Able to act or see into a situation very fast.
The power or act of seeing into a situation in a split second.
It also means that your intuitions are always right.
If you ever ask her something,
she'll probably give you a good suggestion.
The side of her thumb has two small lines, like these...
that's the "charisma line."
That name kinda makes you jealous, what a great name.
Charisma line. Good responsibility and righteous.
Loved by everyone. Good leadership.
With the "charisma line" you can lead the others,
and they will follow you.
You also have good responsibility...
and your palms are like the artist Eikichi Yazawa's*.
Japanese famous singer-songwriter/rockstar.
Even President Barack Obama has it.
Don't worry in the future, just teach anyone a lesson as you liked.
If they do not listen to you, show them your palm like this.
I'm "The Charisma."
The next theme will be...
The one who'll do well even if she's not an idol.
Maybe like an actress or a model etc.
The member who'll do well even if she's not an idol is...
-Saito Asuka-san! -Really!?
The middle of "wisdom line" has an obvious branch.
-It's called the "writer line," which means you have high literary skill.
Writer line. The best sign for the writers.
Has a creative mind.
She'll probably publish a book and become a writer.
It means she's very creative.
She probably has a lot of good ideas inside her head.
Does that mean you're good at writing?
I participated in an Advocate Contest* once.
(Nationwide Essays Contest.)
Is it the one you have to recite? -Yes, an essay writing contest,
I was the representative of somewhere I think.
Forgot the most crucial info.
Now I really wanna know where were you representing for!
There's another interesting line,
the "money line" shifted to the right side over here.
This is the "beauty line." She has awareness for beauty.
Like Uno Kanda-san, IKKO-san, Tsubasa Masuwaka-san.
Beauty line. Wit and artistic.
Suitable to have beauty-related works.
-You might have a secondary job! -Yeah there's a chance!
-ASUKA Brand Fake Eyelashes or something else. -Oh not bad!
How old are you currently?
I'm 13 years old.
If you have a business at this age, it'll be really scary.
I said not suitable but that's not all,
it means there's another talents to be found out. But...
let's talk about who's the most suitable to become an idol. Vocation as an idol.
-There's something like that? -Yes.
-It's Ikoma-san. -Ikoma-san!
The reason? What line affected that?
From "life line," to "wisdom line," until "heart line," they formed an M-shape.
There's a lot who has this M-shape, which means that the current job is suitable for her.
Vocation line. The current job is suitable for that person.
So they actually has this line in Palmistry?
So at the end of the "fate line," there's a branch over here.
This is what Idol needed the most. "Fame line" and "demand line."
-That's so powerful! -What a great line!
Fame line. A must have for a famous idol or artists.
Able to attract opposite sex. Seductive.
AKB48's Tomomi Itano-san has a long line of this.
But Ikoma's pretty long too.
The bottom of her index finger has a curve.
This is "ring of Soloman," aka "ring of luck."
But unexpectedly, she has two of it!
Ring of Soloman. Indicates that the person is very lucky.
-Eh? Ikoma has them? -Yes.
It's a good news. You'll earn a lot of money.
So good things will happen? What will happen?
Like, win a lottery?
Let's go to our next theme.
The member that everyone should be careful of.
-What does this mean? -A dangerous person?
It's more like, she's too concerned about what's happening around her.
So everyone had to take care and protect her.
Ah! So it's an annoying person?
Nobody wanted to be called. Who's the member that the others need to beware of?
It's Ichiki-san!
Ichiki looks very gentle.
-She looks like an obedient child. -Yeah, a good child.
First of all, there's a lot of lines.
There's a lot of gully too.
-The lines are everywhere. -There's gully here and there.
These lines represented how much stuffs you're thinking of at once.
She's always concerned of what's happening around her.
Gully line. Emotional. Often cares too much.
She's emotional.
Not just the good things, she also cares about the bad things.
So that's the reason why she's so emotional.
The "wisdom line" represented how she thinks.
There's a sharp turn over here.
The bigger the curve, the more emotional she can get.
Wisdom line with a big curve. Cared too much. Easily overwhelmed.
It also means that she's easily overwhelmed.
If you're already depressed and you get overwhelmed again
there's no chance the others can comfort her.
My mom always tells me... Ah sorry for the voice...
How were you all overworked this badly?
My mom told me that "When you are that sad, nothing will comfort you."
So you were told before.
Ok let's say that there's a job today
instead of thinking "Hmmm, I did well." and "Not bad."
you'll think about "What if I did that, will it be better?" and "That's really bad."
-Yes, I do.
Me too.
This part of the "heart line" went up like this.
The bigger the curve, the easier to become agitated.
Emotional and easily agitated really sound like an annoying person.
But this curve also indicates that she has good potential.
Heart line that goes up. Easily agitated but it
will become a good ability if controlled well.
So everyone must be really nice to her.
Make her thinks that she's doing ok.
Must protect at all cost.
Koji Tamaki* has these too.
Japanese singer-songwriter.
-Yabai. That's yabai. -You should be careful.
Similar?
Will you go home suddenly during a live performance?
Or got engaged all of a sudden?
It's here.
The most pervert member.
Kinda embarrassing if called out, but who's the most pervert member?
It's Ikuta-san!
Ikuta? You have a pure face. This is unexpected.
-No, it's not true. -Your palms betrayed you.
-There's no such thing. -No more excuse. It's the truth.
What's the meaning of this?
Overall there's no clear lines. But...
the "ero line" was the only clear line.
Ero line. Able to attract opposite sex easily using her charisma.
This curve over here is the "ero line."
Somehow there's more. Two lines...three lines.
There's a lot!
-Ikuta you little pervert~ -It's not true.
Were you looking at me with perverted eyes all the time?
You're the one with the perverted eyes!
Who has this line too?
-Noujo-san has it. -Noujo.
-Noujo has this "ero line." -Eh...what to do.
They are the perverted duo.
There's a lot of artists with this "ero line."
For example Masaharu Fukuyama* has it.
Japanese musician, singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist and actor.
AKB48's Atsuko Maeda-san has a few of this line.
Suddenly this line became a good thing.
So let's continue to the next theme.
The weirdest member?
Weirdest? What's this?
A weird person...and she might even become an abnormal person.
Pervert? If it's about pervert could it be Saito Yuri?
變態. "Abnormal" and "pervert" shares the same Kanji. So it could be either meaning.
Who's the weirdest member among Nogizaka46!?
It's Hashimoto-san!
(Subber: Yes, this is correct. You're weird Miss.Hashimoto.)
The "ero line" we discussed was like this.
But Hashimoto-san's was small compared to it.
It's very clear and it's very rare.
The "abnormal line."
"Abnormal line?" Are you abnormal?
How's that, Hashimoto?
How are you abnormal?
Not at all, I'm a normal person.
The way she thinks might be different than the others, she also has different focus point.
Abnormal line. Has different ways of thinking than the others.
As an artist, you'll have advantages if you can think out of the box.
The member with the best overall luck in 2012.
It's here.
-Everyone wants this title, right? -I really want it.
-Best luck for this year. -Who's it gonna be?
Who's going to be the member that has the best of luck in 2012?
It's Saito Yuri!
-Saito Yuri appeared over here!?
Eh really!?
Around the "fate line," there's a split over here that formed this shape.
-Like a "fish?" -Yes, like a "fish."
The "fate line" describes your life and a "fish" over there means good things will come into your life.
So it means good things will come to you.
Fish line. Good things will happens.
And you might experience it during 2012.
-I'm really happy! -So jealous of you~
So does this mean this "fish" will appeared on other lines too?
Yes. If it's on "wisdom line" it will boost your working luck.
If it's on "marriage line" it means your marriage will be good.
If it's on "good line" it means many good things will happen to you.
But to have it appeared on "fate line" is the best.
The luckiest member during 2012 is Saito Yuri.
Who doesn't know their reading yet?
Actually, I intentionally put Matsumura's at last.
There's this long horizontal line.
Both of her palms has it. -Both of hers?
What line is this?
-Masukake line? -Yes. Masukake line.
-Nani? Nani? -This is a great line.
Actually, Nakada-san has this line too.
There's rumors of Tokugawa Ieyasu* having this line too. The "sign of world domination."
(He was the head of the Tokugawa Clan. One of the three unifiers of Japan, along with his former lord Oda Nobunaga and Toyotomi Hideyoshi.)
Masukake line. World domination sign.
Rumors of Tokugawa Ieyasu has this line too.
Amazing! She has the "sign of world domination!"
But why she doesn't have a good luck for this year.
Usually, the person with "Masukake line" tend to do things at their own pace,
And will not bother to listen others' suggestions.
So if that person go astray the situation will become dangerous.
Masukake line. Tend to do things at her own pace.
It's like a double-edged sword.
So she'll go astray easily if she's not careful?
But if everything's good you'll become like them...
Masaharu Fukuyama, Masatoshi Hamada, and Mana Ashida.
Who else has not seen their reading yet?
Takayama-san. After I finished her reading I thought it was really good from another aspect.
What's the shocking truth behind Takayama's palm reading!!?
Takayama-san...after I finished the reading I thought it was really good from another aspect.
After looking at her palm I had a conclusion.
"THE·NORMAL."
Totally normal.
You're really something else. "The·Normal."
She has very standard palms.
I thought so too.
Her palms are so standard that they can be used as a golden guideline for Palmistry.
Not about palm reading. But an earlier today a temporary leader was announced.
We'll announce who's going to be the captain.
Sakurai Reika.
Loved by everyone, now she's the temporary leader for Nogiazka46.
I'll do my best to unite Nogizaka46!
Everyone, yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
There's only less than a month before their debut single - Guruguru Curtain.
CD will be divided into three edition. The CD cover and the songs inside will be different.
It'll be A, B, and C edition.
Inside them are all 33 members' self-directed performance special videos.
Which means...
we're going to reveal some of the special videos!
No more waiting, please enjoy!
Forward! Hashimoto!
Just like everyone else they greet the morning,
I, Hashimoto Nanami greet the morning as well!
First, open the curtains and prepare for the day.
I thought I was prepared but that's not the case.
"When I'm going to become an adult."
I love swimming. I'm good at frog style swimming.
I become happy whenever I swim.
Lately, I started to learn English,
so I can have a conversation with you in the future.
My name is Erika.
Oh!
Goddamn!!
With the help of world's top director,
they created these scenes.
Ikoma Rina.
What's your height?
153cm.
Tsutsumi Yukihiko, a director that participated in a lot of famous works,
and there are lot more special videos to look forward to!
Debut single - Guruguru Curtain, available on February 22nd!
Also...
Nogizakatte, Doko? will have a public recording session on February 12th.
Do you want to meet Nogizaka46? Register before the deadline!
After this, we'll reveal the latest finished song!
This is the recording of "Nogizaka no Uta", one of the songs in their debut single.
The director is the dance teacher, Minami Sasuga-sensei.
What does the teacher have in mind for this?
This time...I wrote a story.
Everyone's working hard on their own
and slowly they developed teamwork, and it will not be easily shaken.
"It's better instead of working hard all alone by yourself."
I wanted that message to be noticed by the fans.
To capture those precious moments,
we'll use real footage of them working hard and becoming more teamwork.
What do the members think of the director's idea?
The staff also told us that, even if we faced hardship before,
all of us have to continue to work hard together towards our debut.
Everyone showed all kinds of thoughts and emotions,
and some of them even cried.
That's the point.(The MV)
There's when we danced,
and ran around the scenes.
Sometimes it felt bad when you tired of running.
when we're doing seiza*, we tried really hard to do it perfectly.
正座 or 正坐, literally "proper sitting". The Japanese term for one of the traditional formal ways of sitting in Japan.
This video will show the true side of Nogizaka46.
It's not a simple video.
After this, the first reveal of "Nogizaka no Uta."
Where is Nogizaka?
We came here without knowing anything,
We were just looking for an undefined dream.
"If we go there, will we find it?"
We asked someone that's ahead of us,
By the time we realized it, we had climbed the hill.
Our flowing sweat and worn out bodies,
Our overflowing tears and an unclear picture of the future,
These are called life.
Planting our feet on the ground,
We'll steadily walk on.
The pure blue sky,
The wind blowing by,
The song of Nogizaka.
Even if you choose a path that looks easy,
In life, there are no shortcuts.
To become stronger, we climb the hill.
Next week, Nogizaka46's members will go all across the country.
I like SKE48 more.
Promoting their own songs in the middle of a snow.
Lots of situations appeared while they were doing promotions!
Also a touching reunion.
What hardship did they face?