An unexpected development for Nogizaka46 during the new year.
Last week we announced the 16 senbatsu members for their CD debut single, available on 22nd February.
For tonight the senbatsu members will be performing their songs in the studio for the first time.
And the song they're going to perform is?
Also, Bananaman and the new senbatsu members will have a face-to-face interview too!
Members' unexpected true form and charismatic side are going to be revealed!
Nogizakatte, Doko?
Subs: NeruestSub
DON!
Nogizakatte, Doko?
We're the MC Bananaman, yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
And here's the Nogizaka46 members for today.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
So starting from today the new senbatsu members seat positions will be different right?
So let's introduce our guest for tonight...
-BAKARHYTHM. -Hello, yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Masuno Hidetomo(升野英知). Actor and comedian. Stage name Bakarhythm(バカリズム).
Masuno-san you're currently doing a show called Idoling!!! right?
Idoling!!! (アイドリング!!!) is a Japanese TV show with attached female idol group created by Fuji TV.
-That's right, for a long time. -How many years?
More or less 6 years?
Obviously the girls over here are more kawai.
They won without a doubt!
So what's our plan for this week?
-Himura-san, onegaishimasu. -Got it.
To know more about the new members
Bananaman face-to-face interview!!!
We gave the new 16 senbatsu members some questionnaire.
From there we will select 5 members' answers so we get to know more about them.
First up, Saito Asuka who just entered the senbatsu for the first time.
-The youngest, right? -Yes.
-13 years old? -13 years old.
Your mom is from Myanmar(Burma)?
So you're Taylor Swift mixed race? -Yes.
So do you know any other language than Japanese?
My mom can speak it but basically, I don't know how to speak it.
How about some easy words? Do you know any Burmese words?
Thank you in Burmese is "cè-zù tin-ba-deh."
ေက်းဇူးတန္ပါတယ္။.  "Thank you" in Burmese.
cè-zù tin-ba-deh. It's easy to memorize.
The reason you joined Nogizaka46
was because you wanted to change your silent and the wicked personality.
-Do you not like to talk? -It's not like I hate to talk, it's more like I'm wicked.
Kurokatta* huh?
Kurokatta(黒かった) usually means either the person is despicable, wicked or evil-minded, but not always.
Eh..Why? What's wrong?
How wicked are you?
Like pouring water into an ant-hole and stomp them, that kind of wicked?
I don't interact with my friends in school either.
I just kinda daydreaming alone in the corner.
-Do you draw circles when you're daydreaming? -No.
Well, then you're just like a ghost, no?
You knew that yourself, right?
I always hated that side of me.
So if there's someone just like me, I wanted to spread the happiness to them too.
-You're only 13 years old and you thought of that already? -That's incredible.
So you're happy now, right? You have many good friends here.
-That's good. -Yeah.
So from your questionnaire's anwer let's see what you wanted the most right now.
Although any answers is fine, it doesn't mean we have to give you.
The stuff she wanted the most might relate to her age.
But the answer she wrote is totally unexpected.
Cellphone strap.
Aint that kinda cute? -Yeah, it's cute.
But didn't we usually wanted shoes or dress that kind of stuff?
-I don't really... -You don't want them?
So, you're not materialistic?
At the age of 13, didn't we usually asked for a lot of stuff?
I really wanted a robot that looks like a female.
You need help ASAP Are you really ok?
Next up, Noujo Ami who entered the senbatsu for the first time too.
Noujo Ami. Your dream, when you're in primary school, is to become an idol.
She learned how to sing and dance every day.
So basically, she does not have memories of playing with her friends.
-Really? -Yes.
Every week my timetable was filled with lessons and classes only.
But I actually enjoyed during that time.
So basically I do not have memories of playing with my friends.
And after the lessons ended or if there's any holiday, you just want to sleep.
If someone asked you to hang out together, you'll just decline them without a doubt.
Must be really tired because of all those lessons.
But for me, instead of tired
you just don't want to hang out with another person because it's too much trouble.
If I had to choose between going out or sleeping
I would've chosen to sleep every time.
Eh? You don't want to hang out with friends and go shopping or eat crepe together?
Crepes are really sweet you know?
You probably don't know. -You probably won't know.
There's a salty flavor too.
That's why you should've opened your heart more.
After all, you just have to open your heart to everyone.
You know, this lesson(Social interactions) is going to be harder to master than every other lesson.
"Human interaction is harder than other lessons." - Master Shitara 2k12
Whats up, Master Shitara!
So...that's all from me.
-I think I should be allowed to leave after I said that. -Is there any rule like that?
There's a info coming from Takayama.
-Takayama -"Annie"?
Annie. From a broadway stage performance called Little Orphan Annie(1982).
Annie...ummm...
The song "Tomorrow." Yes, that one.
She said that she always wanted to perform as "Annie". That's her dream.
-So "Ami" wanted to become "Annie". -Yes, that's right.
-Ami and Annie sound alike. -Ikuchan and Ami always say that Annie is their goal.
That's kinda challenging, right?
-So two of you think of Annie as your goal? -Yes.
-We even made it into the final review. -Really!? That's incredible!
But Takayama also mentioned "Annie" has already become an ongoing gag for her.
Ami has a deep voice but Annie has a higher pitch.
So I thought she can't reach the note. I asked her to sing it.
And it turned out to be really funny, so it became an ongoing gag for her.
Let show it to everyone.
I'll just sing the child part which I used for the audition.
( I had no idea what she's singing, so I'm just gonna quickly go through of what I heard.)
"You'd make me like her hair, through my nose..."
...together octopus...
...Eye to eye.
-That's kinda nice! -Incredible!
This is incredible. It will definately become a strong comedy joke.
You should just link Annie and yourself together after this.
Understand Annie?
"You'd make me..."
That's nice! That's nice! Good reaction time! Not bad!
-How was it? -That's great!
Please teach me after this!
Next up, the one and only adorable Hoshino Minami♥
It mentioned that you auditioned for AKB before.
Because a friend told you to do it.
You made it into the second phase.
Whatever the other asked you, you would just say "Isn't that normal?"
Like "Why do you want to be a lovely idol?" she would say "Isn't that normal?"
So this is like your catchphrase.
Do I say that often? -Yes, you do. x6
-It seems like it. -You're not that confident, right? "Isn't that normal?"
Himura-san has this at the beginning of every sentence.
-"What I said might be wrong, ok?" -Yes, yes. That's right.
That's because he did not have much confidence.
"Might be wrong..." "Isn't that normal?" sound more like a self-comfort.
But you don't have to worry about it.
No talents or strengths?
It wrote, "My talent is that I do not have any."
I don't have any skills that can be a talent. -Sound just like Shitara-san.
I think so too. I really don't have any sort of talent.
That's why sometimes I said "Collecting mugs is my talent/hobby."
Won't they asked, "How many did you collect so far?" -Yes, they will.
But I really did collect a lot of mugs.
But...there's nothing special about it, right?
It felt unreliable(her talents).
Yeah, you guys are totally the same.
Maybe she treated herself very strictly, so she thought she was not special at all.
Let's hear it from the everyone else.
Hashimoto, what do you think of Hoshino?
I found out about this today. She can eat breads that have the same taste over and over again.
Always eat the same flavor's bread...
Hoshino, do you really eat the same flavor's bread over and over again?
What flavor?
Strawberry Specials*.
A popular product from Yamazaki Baking. "Strawberry Specials" is a strawberry cream sandwich cake.
Ah! Strawberry Specials is really tasted! I ate that a lot too!
That's tasty. Can she eat that forever?
-Always saw her eating that. -Kawai.
-Well your "talents" could be the Strawberry Specials. -That's cute!
Everyone...I've heard the news!
It seems like you guys were featured in some kind of commercial.
That's really incredible!
Sugoi! That's really incredible!
Nogizaka46 first ever CM!
They did not expect to be able to participate in a brand that was highly regarded. Meiji's*.
(A popular Japanese snack food company. They manufacture a wide range of products.)
Because this was their first ever commercial deal they felt nervous.
The first member to shoot, Shiraishi Mai.
I like Nanamin because she can be interesting and cute at the same time.
I'm first again plus this is our first commercial shooting.
I was very nervous.
My heart's pounds really hard.
I did not think of any lines to say
but I kinda improvised on the spot during the shooting. I was very nervous.
Actually, this CM required the members to speak up their own mind while improvising the lines on the spot.
From now onwards whether you're my teammate, friends or my sister
I want to rely on you Kazumin! Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu!
Hearing what Ikoma had just said Takayama started to tear up.
Thank you~
One after another the words that they don't normally say to each other
was passed on to them as lines for the commercial.
They finished their shooting nicely.
We experienced a lot about shooting techniques.
It's beyond my imagination that they can create a commercial with this result.
Also, they appeared on a big CM press conference on 12th.
I'm very happy that we get to spread happiness to everyone.
They never had a big crowd presented in front of them so they're a little nervous.
Please enjoy the CM topic in the studio after this!
The CM was already out on yesterday. Nobody has seen it yet, right?
-Not yet. -We haven't seen it yet too.
Well, let's watch it together.
-Meiji! -it's Meiji!
Handmade Valentine.
Wow, Sugei!!
Guruguru Curtain / Nogizaka46
-May I? -Sure!
What did you make?
-That's a secret. -A secret?
-Continue to do your best ok? -Me too!
-That's really cute. -You're cute too.
I handmade this with my thought for you.
If its chocolate that you want, pick Meiji!
-Wow! Sugei! -That's Incredible!
-Sugoi! It's Meiji's.
There was like a faint background music during the commercial.
Could it be...
The debut single song that's going to be released on 22nd February? -Yes!
It seems like Nogizaka is beginning to show some good results, gradually.
-The debut song... -I wanna hear it.
There will be an opportunity for them to perform the song on here, right?
But the time has not yet arrived. Sorry everyone, but not now.
But as a consolation, they will reveal their debut single's CW song.
CW Songs/Coupling song/B-side tracks. Basically refers to the songs that are not the title song(A-side track) of a CD single.
-It's finally here. -Sugoi!
Let us watch this together, shall we? You won't find it anywhere else.
Let's watch the VTR. Dozo!
After the commercial break the reveal of the coupling song. The song will be...
-Eh!? -What!? This is!
Wanted to see you, wanted to see you, Wanted to see you, yes!
To you...
I climbed the hill as I pedaled
my bike with all my strength,
Even the shirt inflated by the wind
is now frustrating.
I'll go on honestly,
with the true feelings I realized at last
Run on the only road there is!
If I love you, I'll say so
I'll be honest without deception
I'll disclose the depths of my heart
Wanted to see you, wanted to see you, Wanted to see you, yes!
To you...
Wanted to see you~
Incredible! I did not expect to hear this song!
So this is that song AKB48's "Aitakatta(Wanted to see you)"
But the melody is kinda different than AKB48.
What's the song title? Three two...
"Aitakatta kamoshirenai (Wanted to see you...maybe.)"
Well played Aki-p.
What do you mean!? Do it have different lyrics?
It's the same lyrics.
This is probably going to change how everyone views the original song.
The song should be popular since it's impressive.
We saw how the members had danced during the christmas broadcast.
But for the first time, the dance and the songs fit so well together.
-Not bad at all. -Sugei.
Especially the last part of the performance was really nice.
I too listened to a bunch of Idoling's song.
They had no chance to beat the girls over here.
If there's two CD in front of me...
I'll definitely choose Nogizaka46's. I'll buy their CD!
The next member for the talk is Kawamura Mahiro.
Kawamura, you started to dance during 3rd year in primary school? -Yes.
During that time, around second semester my friend asked me to learn Hip Hop together with them.
Your mother always accompanied you when you had dance lessons.
After that, you always buy and eat breads together with your mother. -That's right.
Lately, you discovered a food chain store in the city that sells the same food
And you cried after you ate it?
What happened? Homesick?
You know, this kid worked very hard on her dancing skill since she was small.
After knowing that she did not make it into the Shichifukujin
she went to the Karaoke by herself for 3 hours.
To escape from the sad feeling huh?
Even she's kinda like a happy go lucky, deep down inside she still has ambitions.
Lastly who once again entered the senbatsu, Saito Yuri.
You modeled for Tamago Club* when you're still a baby?
Tamago Kurabu たまごクラブ. A Japanese magazine that usually talks about pregnancy & motherhood. Usually featured mothers and babies photoshoot in it.
But actually I do not have a clear memory of it since its around my first and a half year.
My mother probably went to apply for it on a whim.
Are you kawai since from the start? -Not kawai at all.
There's a lot of cases of babies that are really cute but not so good when they grew up(their looks).
-You're these cute from the start, right? -There's really nothing cute about me.
Ummm...Saito Yuri has some kind of bad habit, you know?
You like to touch other people's butt.
She really wanted to touch members' butt to the point that nothing could not hold her back.
What's so funny about it?
That's because you're just a total pervert weird. Touching people's butt etc.
I had the urge to do it everytime we were practicing.
Urge? I beg your pardon?
What do you mean urge?
The urge to touch them?
Everytime they danced they also shaked their body, right?
I wanted to touch them but we were still practicing so I had to hold back.
The only chance I get was when the teacher's explaining stuff in front...
Wait... how's that not a pervert!?
Those who got their butt touched by Saito Yuri please raise your hand.
Wait, what? Everyone has been touched before!? Really?
Was it like a big grab?
Well played Shiraishi.
She just used her fingertips to tease you?
That's kinda NG, right?
Sometimes she just grabbed the whole butt.
She even surprised us during events.
During events!?
Even in front of the fans?
She'll stand behind when there's a crowd and do this...
I never thought something I did would be discovered. I'm sorry.
You even put your hand inside Sakurai's skirt.
She abruptly put her hand inside my skirt.
That's funny.
Inside your skirt?
She did it like this and I was like "No no no no...stop it!"
But like what she did.
maybe in the future when,
all of you have concerts or other stuff and she grabs your butt
and you say "Yameteh," that kind of stuff might ease the nervousness.
Only if you guys are comfortable with it.
The same goes for me too. Everytime before a broadcast...
Himura-san was really nervous, every time.
I usually kicked his butt or stab his anus.
Gave him a big clap on the back.
He'll say "Stop it!" So something like that will relieve him.
Interesting. Very Interesting. -Where can you find a idol like this?
After this, Nogizaka46 will be visiting Nogi Shrine for their debut single.
Their ambition for this year was really big, what could it be?
January 5th, 2012. Nogizaka's members visited the Nogi Shrine located at Minato, Tokyo.
This is a big day for Nogizaka46 who's going to debut on February.
Praying for their debut single, wishing it to become a big hit.
Let's listen to their "first dream of the year"* from the members.
初夢(Hatsuyume はつゆめ). Usually refers to the one you dream on the night of January 1st going into the 2nd and is supposed to fortell how good your year will be.
I dreamt of a scene where I caught a fish.
Because it's my first dream, so I think it will be a good year for me.
Next up, Nogizaka46's first fan meeting event of the year.
Nogizaka46's New Year Blessing Event has started!
First off, knocking the rice cakes and
every member revealed their own wish for this year.
2012 has become the year when Nogizka46 first debuted!
I'm sure that there will be changes in the future
so please continue to support Nogizaka46, we'll be really happy if you do!
My personal goal is to hold a concert on Budoken one day.
One two... Our goal Budoken!
A good result was shown even right before they debuted on 22nd Febraury.
Please keep on supporting them!
After this, the girls met a bigwig in an elevator!?
How will Nogizaka46 react to these!?
Next week on Nogizakatte, Doko?
The girls are learning about "What should you do if you met a bigwig."