Tonight on Nogizakatte, Doko?
The comedian will teach the girls how to react if they ever met a bigwig!
The imitation class accidentally revealed members new talent!
Finally, their debut title song will be revealed tonight!
Nogizakatte, Doko?
Subs: NeruestSub
Don! This week's Nogizakatte, Doko? is starting right now!
We're the MC Bananaman!
And here's our Nogizaka46 members for today.
We also have guests for today.
"Tamori-san" and "Sanma-san"!
Oh! It's synced! It's well synced!
That will do....what are you doing?
I'm talking right now...
Ehyaaa~~What are you doing!?
Famous punchline
You're sensitive huh?
Ok let's introduce our guests again
Koji Tomita-san and Haraguchi akimasa-san*!!
Popular Japanese impressionists.
Himura-san please read the plan for tonight using "Go Hiromi*" style.
Hiromi Go 鄉裕美 a Japanese singer, part of Sony Music Entertainment Japan.
Fomous artists corresponding test!
You guys are going to be in all sorts of shows in the future, right?
Which means you guys will encounter all sorts of artists too.
Definitely!
So we asked for these two guest, to learn the right reaction when we saw an artist from them.
Let's have fun together. -Onegaishimasu.
That's how Sanma-san's* variety show felt like.
明石家さんま Sanma Akashiya. A Japanese TV comedian and actor simply known as Sanma.
That's how Sanma-san usually act.
Here's when I went to the backstage to greet him. Knock knock.
Oiii~ -Yoroshiku.
Oh! Which show are you on later?
Sanma-san, it's your show.
You sure? How can it be my show...Oh It's true!!
I'm in your care!
Right up, in a mysterious elevator
Koji and Haraguchi will be playing as different artists
and the members will encounter them inside the elevator.
Firstly, Takayama. Who will she meet inside the elevator?
Her movements are kinda weird.
Tsurube Shofukutei. A Japanese actor and rakugo comedian.
Konnichiwa.
Konnichiwa, domo. I'm Takayama Kazumi from Nogizaka46.
W-w-w-what?
I'm Takayama Kazumi from Nogizaka46. -Nogizaka...46?
Where are you from? -I'm from Chiba!
Oh! Speaking of Chiba it's famous for their rakkasei(peanuts), right?
Thank you very much. Yes, its delicious.
Do you eat them often? -Yes. I ate a lot of it.
Why do you kept eating them?
Famous body movement.
Ganbatte ok? -Thank you!
What's your name.. Takayama...Kazumi?
Speaking of Kazumi, my wife has a female friend called Kazumi.
Oh.. I'm honored! -She's cute too.
You'll be famous soon. -I'm really happy, thank you very much.
Not bad, right?
Thank you very much.
Takayama showed a good correspond for someone she just met.
Next up, Matsumura. What kind of artist will be waiting for her?
Hehehehe...It opened.
Junji Takada. A Japanese actor and comedian.
Really sorry I'm Jang Keun-Suk* hahaha..!
A South Korean actor and singer.
Talking nonsense
Oh I'm sorry that's a mistake. Oh you're a pretty lady.
Oh wait a minute, let me just pressed all the buttons.
What a move, right hahaha..!
You're really kawaii, how old are you?
19. -19? That's really young.
You look liked 17, 18 or maybe 19 years old.
Mr.Random
I'm Nogi.. -Did anyone ever told you that you look like Yukie Nakama*?
A Japanese actress, singer and former idol.
Uh...nobody told me that. -Not even once?
-I'm sorry. -Yes or no?
Well..either yes or no is fine. Hahahaha..!
I'm sorry did I stand too close Hahaha..!
I'm sorry. Should I introduce myself once more?
Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu! -Hi, I'm Ken Takakura* hahaha..!
He was a Japanese actor and singer who appeared in over 200 films.
More nonsenses
You have to know my name, ok? Do you know or heard it before?
Yes, I know.
I'm sorry but I'm kinda tiredahahaha..!
Sorry..sorry.
May I? I was gonna stayed for a while more thouhahaha..!
I'm sorry. Oh it's the wrong floor hahaha..!
Seems really nervous. Please do your best next time!
Next challenger, Noujo Ami.
Thanks for the hard work.
I'm Katsura Utamaru who wanted to see my wife's treasury even once.
Katsura Utamaru. He was a showa era Rakugo commedian.
Umm...I'm Noujo Ami from Nogizaka46.
So please tell me a quiz using "Noujo Ami."
"Noujo Ami" quiz...Here I go.
Quiz out of the blue
Just like butadon(pork rice)... -Butadon? So what's the answer?
They're both... -Alright.
Yamada-kun, you can take the zabuton(floor cushion) away.
Confiscated
Where are you from, Noujo-san?
I'm from Kanagawa.
Kanagawa? Alright please tell me a quiz using "Kanagawa."
More quiz
Eh...Just like "hatosabure*"...
A very popular cookie from Kanagawa.
Hatosabure. So what's the answer?
They're both... -They're both...
I'm so sorry I'm still an amateur. I'm sorry I'm sorry.
Not prepared
Shōten 笑点 is a Japanese TV comedy program. It's the second-longest running variety TV show in Japan.
This is the end of Shoten*! Please look foward to it next week, thank you!
She did her best trying to come up with a quiz when asked so suddenly, good try!
Next up is Inoue. Which bigwig will she met?
Good morning, thanks for the hard work.
Kunie Tanaka acting as Goro Kuroita from "Kita no Kuni Kara".
This thing...can move?
It can, yes.
In Furano, there's nothing like this.
Furano. Where the main story happened in "Kita no Kuni Kara". A city in Hokkaido.
Furano, gomenasai.
I'm Inoue Sayuri from Nogizaka46, yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Did you know where's Hotaru*?
Hotaru Kuroita. Goro's daughter in "Kita no Kuni Kara".
Still finding his daughter?
Hotaru left home and went to Tokyo, have you seen her?
He came here to look for her daughter?
Kunie Tanaka never did this, right?
That's Goro Kuroita.
Are you crying?
No, I'm not.
Are you ok?
I'll give you pumpkin ok?
Tell me, "sincerity"...
...What's that?
Tell me what's "sincerity".
Do you mean "life"?
"Life"? You said, "life"?
It's impossible to communicate like this.
I'll tell that to Jun for you.
Jun Kuroita. Goro's son in "Kita no Kuni Kara".
He's slow.
There's a snow fox.
(??????)
There's none. There's none.
Very sorry but there's nothing worth to discuss.
Next up is Shiraishi. Who will appeared this time?
Good morning.
I'm Shiraishi Mai from Nogizaka46.
Did we met before?
Eji Bando. A Japanese television entertainer and a former baseball player.
Ah..this is the first time.
Oh ok, so this is our first meeting. I'm in a hurry. After this I have to reach Hataka-ku*.
ward of the city of Fukuoka.
I always make a round trip within a day.
His catchphrase.
Thanks for the hardwork.
So...Shiraishi Bai-san?
I'm "Mai". -"Bai-chan"?
I'm sorry my nose are bad, Shiraishi Bai-chan. -Yes, I'm "Bai".
Nogizaka48?
It's 46.
Do you guys earn any money?
Love to talk about salaries.
I mean like...salary deductions? Like appearance fees etc...
I have no idea.
You had no idea? oh...I still think salary deductions are good.
Likes salary deductions.
You don't know me, right.
I do actually. -You do? What's my name?
Bando Eji-san. -Oh, you do know!
Alright, I'm kinda in a hurry. I have to make a round trip between Hataka-Ku later.
What kind of egg cuisines do you like?
I like boiled egg. -Ah...I like that too.
Egg yolks or whites?
I like the egg yolks. -Ah. We're the same!
Very happy.
So..because I have to make a round trip to Hataka-Ku...
Alright. Please do your best!
Thanks for the hard work.
Thank you very much.
Shiraishi smiled from the beginning till the very end, very good reaction!
Next up is Ikuta. Who's going to be in the elevator?
Egashira 2:50 (Hideharu Egashira, better known by his stage name Egashira 2:50, is a Japanese comedian.)
Too slow!!!
Freaking out.
How long do you have to make me wait!!?
Going up!? -Yes.
Thank you. I'm Ikuta Erika from Nogizaka46. Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu.
....Yoroshiku!
Unexpectedly well-mannered.
Are you tired...?
Ovbiously!! Can't you tell!?
Can't you tell by my face!?
I understand.
You're kind. -Thank you very much.
Are you nervous?
How can I not be nervous!?
Only two of us in an elevator!
Ummm...Egarashi-san's a good guy right?
Who the hell is Egarashi!!?
Should be Egashira.
E-GA-SHI-RA!
I'm just messing with you, sorry.
Messing with me? You little brat!!
I wanted to know you better that's why I was joking.
That's great!
I'm Egashira. -Yes, Egashira-san's a good guy, right?
Don't say that!!
He's a annoying character.
Never say that again!!
It will cause a rebellion!
Don't say that!
I understand.
Sorry for waiting.
I'm sorry...
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu. Thank you very much.
You should've been more scared if this is the situation!
Please matched up with the character's image.
Next up, we have this plan.
Title call, please.
Please read it while imitating someone else's voices.
Definitely useful impersonation lesson.
Everyone should've one impersonation skill, right?
Maybe when there's a punishment game they will ask you to imitate someone.
Let the guests give you a lesson. -Is that right? That's good.
Haraguchi-san, yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Let's learn how to do a Ken Shimura impression from Haraguchi-sensei.
Basically, act like an old lady.
Your pose should be like an old lady.
And you need to do a sour-face.
When you have a sour-face, this voice will come out naturally.
You're good if you can do this voice.
Everyone let's stand up.
Let's become an old lady.
I'm sorry but I can't see anyone right now.
Looking at the floor.
Lets say "Ah~~" together. Ready...
Ah~~~
Alright. There's one line that I hoped you guys could say it out loud.
"Well I'm always alone anyway!!""
When you act it out think of it as Shimura-san was asked to take someone's order.
Like...What do you want to eat? Ok one ramen. Ok one dumpling.
"Well I'm always alone anyway!!"
Just remember to add that line inside your acts.
We're we going to add that line ok?
"Well I'm always alone anyway!"
What a weird group.
Ikoma look hyped when she did that.
Ikoma and Takayama both look really hyped.
We're starting with the "Ah~~" ok? Ready...
"Well I'm always alo...."
We haven't reached that part yet!!
Sneaky Beaky.
From "Ah~~" ok? Not the line first.
"Well I'm always alone anyway!"
Ikoma's good!
Ah sorry, I added a bit of Akita dialect... -It's ok.
Ah~~~ One two...
"Well I'm always alone anyway!"
Next up Koji-sensei is going to teach us about Tamori's* impression.
A famous host for Music Station.
So, face expression first. Firstly, raise your eyebrows really high.
Like this, raise it up like this and you're good.
After that, you need to stretch your nose down.
Keep that expression and grin.
This is the basic form.
After that just say something randomly during an interview.
"What a small face."
Or maybe "He's really good at talking."
While everyone's doing it, let the excited Hashimoto become our representative.
Hashimoto's going to accept the challenge as the representative.
Not bad, not bad.
Raise your eyebrows and pull your nose.
Oh not bad at all.
Pick someone to have an interview with.
There's something funny about that.
Doing that kind of expression while wearing a sunglasses.
Wait a sec. They actually looked alike!
New talent found!
The way she holds the mic is really good too!
Let's have a talk with the members behind you.
"What were you saying!?" Something like that.
You were you saying?
I umm... I think it's really interesting...
"Yeah it's interesting. It's interesting after all."
Music Station?
I guess only Hashimoto can imitate Tamori-san this well.
Her face looks similar too.
After this, imitation battle between a mountain goat and Tamori-san!
Say...Himura know how to imitate an animal, right?
Yeah sure, I can do it.
Let's start, shall we?
Alright...a goat.
What a realistic screaming.
There's someone else who can do this kind of voice.
Koji Kato can do that.
If you can do the goat's you probably can do Kato-san's too.
"You can do that too."
"Laugh like that."
Why did you turn to a goat when you laughed.
Oh looks like someone's good at it. Takayama.
Here I go.
Lets do a talk between a male and a female goat.
What the hell is this?
Ended.
If there's a request for a goat imitation you'll do it. -I got it.
And when everyone's done. "Well I'm always alone anyway!"
Hashimoto, after that line...
say "What are you talking about?" -"What are you talking about?"
First of all, do the goat again.
"Ba~~"
"Well I'm always alone anyway!"
"What are you talking about?"
A dream team!
on January 1st, Nogizaka46 appeared at an AKB48's Live Show.
Unexpectedly, they're going to perform their debut song "Guruguru Curtain" over here.
Everyone, Konnichiwa! We're Nogizaka46.
Nogizaka46 performed "Guruguru Curtain" flawlessly in front of AKB's fans!
We, the Nogizaka46 has a goal that we would really like to surpass.
The goal is...
AKB48!
We'll do our best to achieve that goal.
So we could become a worthy opponent for them one day.
Please look forward! Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
From 29th January onward, Nogizaka46 will have missions on 8 cities.
We'll revealed the details soon! Please check the official website for more info!
Revealing Nogizaka46's debut title song next!
Last time we released the debut single's CW song.
We're surprised by it.
"Aikataka Kamo Sshirenai"
This time we're going to reveal...
Finally, its here!
So everyone, what's the title?
"Guruguru Curtain"
VTR! Lets go!
Inside the curtain, the sun, she and me
rolling and are wrapped up. Privacy.
What are we talking about? I won't tell.
Somehow, I calmed down in that special seat in the class.
It's a world for just my friend and I.
"Um," "Well I," we're so close that we became as one.
We'll understand anything if we're together. (She and me)
Inside the curtain, the breeze and the smell of flowers and
warmth are wrapped. It's a secret.
Who have I fallen in love with?
Yes, If it's a girl
They always love to hide in the corner.
For the sake of that I guaranteed,
no boys are allowed.
The wind that blew through the opened window.
The curtains of my heart
expanded because of my delusions for love.
Inside the curtain, the breeze and the smell of flowers and
warmth are wrapped. It's a secret.
Who have I fallen in love with?
Yes, If it's a girl
They always love to hide in the corner.
For the sake of that I guaranteed,
no boys are allowed.
Next week the senbatsu members will show us their true skills!
That's cool!
Next week the senbatsu members will show us their true skills
High quality performances and incredible body skills
Reika's!