Tonight, a public recording of the show with 300 fans.
What weird personalities did the Shichifukujin discover from the psychological test?
Nogizakatte, Doko?
Credits: NeruestSub Team
Subber: WheresAmonSensei-san
Timing: KatakanaKeyaki?-san
Proofreading: TsuchidaIsBae-chan
Don!
Nogizakatte, Doko? has started!
We're the MC Bananaman! Yoroshiku!
The first guest for today is,
Famous comedian and MC. Member of Katakana Keyakizaka46
Tsuchi*(Tsuchida-san).
Here are Nogizaka46's members for today.
Yayaya...It's really spectacular.
Is this everyone? -Yes, everyone.
Tsuchi, what do you think? Know any of them?
I know they existed. Lately, I kept seeing them on TV.
The song with the AKB48's lyrics, and the same location etc.
But the melody sounded different.
Aki-P really knows what he was doing eh!
So, Himura-san...
What's the plan for today's show?
Please read it with an energetic sound.
Revealing the true Shichifukujin! Nogizaka46's psychological test!
Today, we invited psychology expert Takashi Tomita-sensei.
He'll take a look at Shichifukujin's psychological conditions!
So let us do this.
The question is...
Use these four different shapes to draw anything you want, you can reuse the same shapes again.
The square means group(Nogizaka46). The circle means oneself.
The triangle shape means the male.
The downward triangle shape means the female.
They'll have different meanings when appeared on different drawings.
Because Ikuta, one of the Shichifukujin has to take an exam she'll be absent.
Firstly, let's check out Hashimoto's psychological condition.
The circle rolled away from the structures, right?
(Subber: Hashimoto, are you taking a physic test?)
-The circle means herself. -She rolled away.
Probably because she's still not fully adapted to Nogizaka46 yet.
But I'm working really hard to adapt it.
What do you mean "working really hard..."
It kinda sounds like "It's impossible..."
So, Hashimoto, you think it's impossible right?
...No
Did she just admit tacitly?
I'm ok with the group, right?
Just tell us the truth alright?
Earlier today we actually gave the others a secret questionnaire to investigate about the Shichifukujin.
-Iwase? -Hai!
For Nanamin, she didn't reply back to members' messages very often.
So did something happened privately?
When Nanamin was sick, I was worried so I sent a message to her.
"Are you ok? Don't force yourself too much." Messages like this.
But I never received a reply back.
Eh? Didn't reply?
Yeah...I want to be alone at that moment.
Ikr, I totally understood.
Sensei, the problem kinda appeared.
Yes, because the circle rolled very far away.
-I see. -She's kinda far from everyone.
I often saw Nanami alone during our break time, she kept practicing her funny faces in front of a mirror.
So everyone was like "Is she ok?"
What happened here?
She probably wanted to control herself.
She wants to control herself by doing funny faces in front of a mirror!?
What kind of practice did you do?
I'll just look at my own face in front of a mirror,
and I'll be disgusted by it because I had no confidence.
You had no confidence in how you look? -No.
Look over here. A bunch of weirdos.
Himura-san's gonna commit suicide if that's the case.
I don't even think my face's THAT weird.
He even wore a sunglasses at overseas.
Next up, Ikoma's psychological analysis!
Wow...it's completely different.
What is that?
Only criminals would draw something like this, right?
The obvious one was the huge self-consciousness covering almost everything.
-Ah, the circle represented herself.
-Yes, whether male, female or the group.
there's a feeling of "I can do everything all alone."
She's wanted everything to be under her control.
She doesn't have that kind of aura yet. So are you slowly cultivating your confidence?
Nope.
This is the result, it's accurate.
It came out, alright? Your deep psychological condition came out.
She's good at dancing but she wanted to teach us even thou that she did not pay attention(to the class.)
That's one heavy burn.
You taught them because you're really confident, right?
I never taught them anything!
Memory loss?
But I'm sorry.
Yabai...you good?
Well, that's ok too.
It's a good thing that you have confidence.
-A good thing? -Yes.
Well, that's fine.
Next up, Matsumura's psychological analysis!
-She drew a lot of stuff. -Indeed there's a lot going on.
There's a dog. What are those at the above?
Dog?
Is that oden*? Looks like oden?
A Japanese one-pot winter dish consisting of several ingredients in a light, soy-flavored dashi broth.
Oden*?
Did you draw the dog first?
I drew these first.
Ah, you drew those first?
So what's next?
The next one was the dog.
But why did you draw an oden?
Because there were spaces left,
and I haven't use the square shape.
Ain't that a square on the dog's body?
If you really cared about the empty spaces, why there's nothing at the bottom.
-So what's your opinion sensei?
-The dog's circle head represented herself,
and she drew the circle above "the group"(square.)
So you think the group is like a dog?
Probably her existence was like a leader in the group.
But take a look at the above, she drew three triangles.
She's attracted to the opposite sex.
Because there are two circles between the triangles, right?
She even drew those first.
Actually, she's not that attracted to the male,
she just love to eat.
Yes, it's really weird.
This morning she ate ten pancakes.
Eh, no...I only ate the small pancakes.
It's true! I'm telling the truth!
-What da hell are u talking about? -The hell you talking about?
You should be careful...eating that much.
Yes, I really agree.
Yeah like what if you become fat.
But if there's a fat member in the group wouldn't it be more interesting?
Yeah, it's kinda cute.
There's a KPOP group called Super Junior, right?
There's one fat person in the group,
(Subber: Shots fired. RIP Shindong.)
and he's kinda dazzling too.
Well, it kinda works, no?
But there's none in Japanese groups.
That's because they were all fired.
What kind of deep psychological condition does the 14 years old Hoshino have?
She drew a house.
The group and herself are far apart from each other.
It's like she is cynical and has no interest in other stuff.
There are a few sentences Minami like to say
"I'mma sleep," and "I'm hungry." She always said those two sentences.
-Well, even you guys said that right?
-Nope. Not even once. Minami's the one that said those sentences.
-You guys too. -No, we did not.
Minami's not interested in other stuff except foods and her hair bangs.
She called me very often, "If you're free..."
"let's go to the Mcdonald's and eat some fries, Maya."
Isn't that another meaning for "Ya better buy me some fries!"
"Ya better go and get me some bread and snacks!"
But the fact that she's interested in her hair bangs, it's kinda mature.
Yes, she's afraid that people will discuss her hairs if her hairs' not cute enough.
Just like NON STYLE's Inoue-san?
His hair bangs are really smooth and tidy.
Next up, Shiraishi's unexpected psychological condition!?
What the hell are those?
What the...
A stack of triangles covered by a lot of circles.
There's a cube on the right too.
That's a box.
Are we not usually draw stuff in the middle first when we get the paper?
This drawing was split into two parts. -Ah, you guys noticed that.
The drawing was perfectly split two parts.
The left represented both genders and herself.
The right represented her job and the group.
-She separated them completely from each other. -Oh! Sugoi!
So her working(public) and her private life were completely separated.
So she's that kind of person.
For Maiyan, she was very loud on the bus.
So she was very bothersome when we're on the bus.
She was excited.
But she's very calm in front of the staffs.
She totally separates her public and private life.
So works are works and vice versa. Her mood switched between these two.
So do you get excited when you were working?
Yes, something like that.
Next up, Takayama's deep psychological analysis.
Eh? An elevator?
Ummm...does the triangle buttons or what have some different meanings?
I thought that it'll be better if I drew them.
Playing Takayama-mopping-windows.mp3
The elevator, do you want to go up or down?
Ummm...Up? Going up.
Well, the circle obviously represented herself.
This might represent her future career's path?
You went right into your own career(elevator.)
So there's that big rectangle, right?
That's probably the fate of Nogizaka46.
When you open the door you can discover more interesting things.
Which means she can travel to different places,
and she will have more possibilities in her life.
So you thought Nogizaka46's your everything.
Yes, for now, I really thought Nogiz...
You just said "For now" right?
-No no no no... -Does this mean after a few years...
you'll probably hop to other company? -No. It's not like this.
I stayed at Kazumi's house before...
Kawai. Staying at friends' house etc. -Not bad, there's that right.
Tsuchida over here invited me to do that yesterday.
Because I worked until 2 AM yesterday,
and I complained because this studio was far away from my house.
"Well, stay at my house." This guy said.
If you're 20 years old or what that's totally fine.
But you know...
Two old men that's over 40 years old, the hell were you thinking!?
We won't say "Ayyy, come and stay at my house after tomorrow's works!"
Ah! So after that, Kazumi told me that she always wanted to be a nurse.
-Do you want to be a nurse? -Yes.
But she said that since she's already in Nogizaka46, she'll do her best in Nogizaka46.
So I thought she's cool since she's fully focused on Nogizaka46.
Say, what do you wear when you were sleeping?
What a "good" topic.
She wore thin green pajamas, right?
-No idea. -It's impossible for us to know.
Not the colors, this guy asked about what did you wore.
I'm asking about the materials of the pajamas.
Those warm type.
-Fluffy? with green color? -Yes.
Takayama, you too?
Ah! I wore a thin green and blue co-
ENOUGH WITH THE COLORS!
-Enough! -These kids had no idea what the old man asked.
I know you all wore a thin green pajama.
Next up, the reveal of the type of men that these girls' desired unconsciously.
Our next test is going to be...
"You got your driving license recently and can't wait to go out,
but you had an accident at the junction,
what kind of car did you crash into? Please draw it out."
First up, the car that Ikoma crashed into.
Eh? 夜露死苦*(Yoroshiku)?
The act of assigning kanjis to words that ignore kanji's meaning is called 当て字(ateji). 夜露死苦(Yoroshiku) is an "ateji" more unique to the biker gangs culture of Japan.
Is that like a yanki's* car?
A yanki was basically the subgroup for delinquent students. "Bosozoku" a.k.a. biker gangs had a similar style to yanki, but were known for their outrageous and illegally modified motorcycles.
It's really bad if you really hit it.
If you hit this car on a junction you're dead.
(Subber: *cough* Majisuka *cough* Gakuen *cough*)
They probably all have weapons with them.
You will get beaten up really bad like you're in hell.
What's the deal with this, sensei?
So the drawing represents the kind of men the girls will attract without knowing.
So Ikoma might attract delinquents?
Probably someone like Masahiro Chono*? Those kinds of dangerous looking people.
(A semi-retired American-born Japanese professional wrestler.)
Wait, wait...that's Keiji Mutoh*.
(a Japanese professional wrestler.)
Sorry I got the wrong person.
Which of them do you prefer?
Wait...she's going to pick one from these hellish people?
There's no idols or superstars over here.
But I kinda like men with fluffy hair.
That's why these two...
It's just simply because she really hate you. -No, it's not like that!
But I really like you, Ikoma.
Next up, Hashimoto's car.
Ummm which one is your car?
Ah, they're the same car.
Ah, so it's from a front and a side view.
Just like an automobile catalog.
-Yeah! -They have a front and a side view of a car.
If it's a compact car, it means those who are younger than her.
the other person is not that strong,
But the car on the left is more bigger.
Yeah, a big compact car.
Just like a giant baby.
Is it for those who are really short, but wanted a higher car seat?
What a weird balance.
That kid's really sick.
Next up, a weird car that was drawn by Shiraishi.
What kind of car is that?
Why's the rear side curved like that?
Because I hit a really fast car, like those convertible cars.
The hell is a convertible look like this!?
Well I mean, it's from your imagination.
By the first look, I thought you might attract someone who's really weird.
But after listening to your reason why, I think it's fine.
There's no such car like this, right?
Probably because the rear side of it's really weird.
Because cars don't look like that.
I relieved after hearing your explanations.
You better draw it better next time,
it looks like Suneo Honekawa*'s hair.
Dat fox-faced rich kid from Doraemon.
Maybe she likes Suneo?
By the way, Takayama drew an expensive car so she will probably meet a rich person.
Hoshino who drew a four-door family car will attract fatherly-figures.
Matsumura who drew a taxi might meet someone that's hardworking.
Next up, the member that nobody wanted to be friend with?
The next question is going to be...
"You're going to send one member to the space to have a location shooting in a rocket."
"-Who's going to be in the rocket?" So which member will be most likely to be sent? -Ah, I got it.
Who's the popular member here?
Hashimoto!
-Ah I know right. -Yes. I know right!
"Ikr...Ikr..." They even clapped their hands.
What's the meaning of this, sensei?
Going into space, a far place.
So going somewhere that far means you won't be seeing that person for a long time.
It means they don't want to see her.
Well, you guys even clapped for a while.
Its too late to apologize, alright.
Saying "No, it's wrong." It's obviously a lie.
It's not that they hate her, it's like "if that person did not do it, I'll be forced to do it."
Like a rival?
Those who picked Hashimoto, please raise your hand. There are 7 members.
Alright, Hashimoto, remember them so you can have your revenge later.
The space suit really fits Hashimoto.
Do you think we're stupid?
Who would be happy if someone says "the space suit fit you."
She often said that she liked to be alone, so I thought why not give her a chance.
The studio will probably become like "Suzuran High School*."
From the manga series "Crows Zero,"Suzuran All-Boys High School", an institution infamous for its population of violent delinquents.
-No, it's not like that. -You all kept saying no, but this is your true psychology.
Next up, they're going to perform "Nogizaka no Uta" in front of the crowd.
Next up, they're going to learn how to do Oogiri!