Timing, Typeset & Translation by DOZO
Woof !
Nogizakatte Doko is starting
We're your hosts Bananaman, yoroshiku onegaishimasu
- Yoroshiku onegaishimasu !
And here are the members
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu !
Starting this week the previous senbatsu members have been replaced by the ones for the second single
And about our guest this week
She'll be the first female guest we receive on the show
That's right
It's Okubo !
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu
Well, I already appear on Onedari Mascot
[Note: A show that features gravure models]
but I can tell the vibe here is totally different
Of course !
- That softness
Let's just say the girls on Mascot are a little bit edgier
The members are more 'fresh'
Who was it...
Ikoma
Shiraishi
and what's her name
- I'm Ikuta
Ikuta
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Seen each other on London Hearts
I see, so you've already worked with some of them
Ikoma-chan, don't you think of me as sort of your big sister in the entertainment world ?
See, you already get a forced laugh
Alright, Himura, please announce today's agenda while showing your teeth as best as you can
I want to know more about the new members !
Investigation of Iwase, Miyazawa and Hatanaka !
In this episode we will get to know more about the newly elected senbatsu members: Iwase, Miyazawa and Hatanaka
It seems you guys already went on a location shoot ?
Yes we did, just the three of us
Sort of like a 'girls get together' then ?
That means we'll get to see them as they really are, it'll bring out their personalities
So first let's have a look at this VTR
Have you ever had a conversation just between the three of you ?
No, it'll be the first time
So I'm pretty excited to see how it will turn out
I've seen this place before
Where should I sit...
Alright I'll be in the middle
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Center position secured
The first time I saw Seira
She seemed like the cool type that doesn't speak much at all
But once we got a little closer
I realized that this wasn't the case at all
We'd laugh together when we saw something funny
Ah, Seira
There's no one else here
Hm ?
Yeah...
I was lonely
I wonder if Yumiko will be here soon, she's late
We can't start eating until she's here with us
Text her, tell her to hurry up
But what if she gets here too late and we can't order anymore ?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Iwase
What will you have then ?
What do you recommend ?
To say it very bluntly...
Hatanaka is a complete baka
Sometimes I really do wonder how you can be that much of a baka
She's badass !!
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Hatanaka's curse ?
If we speak just between the three of us today, I'm worried this will be rather difficult
Hatanaka is like a bomb
It will depend on what we end up talking about
Uwa that looks good
Ah Yumine !
She's arrived
The eldest has arrived
So pretty !
- Yeah
- Damn !
A restaurant fit for Yumiko
Let's order together since you're here now
You were waiting for me to order ?
Yeah
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Let the talk begin
We were just trying to decide what to order
Isn't it crazy that we get to eat in this place ?
And with these members
I've never been to this kind of place in my entire life
I bet it's going to be delicious
From afar you'd think this is some sort of trendy coffee shop
Something like Renoir.
Yeah...
I'd want an aquarium like that in my house
Isn't is way too big ? There's no way it would fit
You don't need that kinda stuff
I don't need that, she says
- It's unnecessary
Then I want one like this one
- It's okay if you only see this kind of thing every once in a while
But, seeing it everyday
you'll end up wanting to go in the water yourself
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
What ?
No way...
Coming up, the story behind the announcement of the new senbatsu members
We're senbatsu members now
Yeah
I'm thankful for that
I thought I wouldn't make it
Same
But I mean, I could tell, judging by how the staff behaved that something was coming
Yeah you can tell
There was this cameraman that only comes
during the senbatsu annoucements
Really ?
Yeah, he's got brown hair
That's how you recognize him ?
This guy only comes during the senbatsu elections
What's this thing ?
Isn't that green onion ?
Bamboo ?
This has to be green onion
- It's pineapple.
He said it's a pineapple leaf
Alright let's talk for real
During the auditions
I didn't like Hatanaka very much
Why ?
- Because of her appearance ?
- Yeah
She's pretty much a gyaru !
I mean look at her !
You decided that based on my appearance...
But I like you now
I know
I can tell by your everyday behavior
How ? What do you mean
I can tell because-
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Onion dropped
Do you ever wonder why you're such an airhead ?
Nope
Isn't she also kinda bad at japanese ?
Yeah
Is it alright if I get an oolong tea ?
Sure, go ahead
That's what I'm talking about
She does often interrupt a conversation in the middle like that
Yesterday too, someone-
I don't think she even understands the meaning of bending the waist
[note: hanashi no koshi wo oru, lit. "to bend the waist of a story", means to interfere mid-conversation]
She's really funny
You think so ?
You don't really notice it yourself, but you are
Have some salad
I've had my fill
What does that mean ?
You don't know what No Thank You means ?
No thanks (sounds weirder in japanese)
"No thanks" sounds funny
The difference between a genius and an idiot is paper-thin
What you just said is the sign of a genius, I think
"No thanks"
I don't know what "paper-thin difference" means
That's what I thought
It's like, they resemble each other
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Uninterested
Pay attention to the prodigious girl's way of eating pasta
Honestly I really wanted to...
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Double sword style
What are you laughing at ?
I mean
The way she eats is just too funny...
Do it again
You were laughing because of the pasta ?
Yeah
Anyway, there are a lot more things we could talk about
Like what ?
Let's talk about the things we only get to talk about now
And it's the first time we're only us three
You mind if I go to the bathroom, first?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Freedom
Sure, see you later
She's a real baka
But she's a good girl
Yeah
Her heart's in the right place
She seems like she'd be a good confidant
I see what you mean
Help the members get things off their chests
She'll seriously listen to what you have to say
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
The prodigy returns
Do I have any presence at all ?
I don't feel very energetic today
I'm always like that, personally
Me ?
No, me
That's not true
We all get caught up in you
You're the moodmaker
- Exactly
Your mood is contagious
Alright then I won't say nothing for the next 20 seconds
You don't have to do that if it's only for 20 seconds
'kay I'll drop it then
If you shut your existence up, it's the end
Sounds like a famous saying
Please take me as your disciple
Sure thing, apprentice
Ahh I'm full
I want to go in there
- Help yourself
- Then get in !
We'll wave at you from the top
So what did you think about this little talk between these three ?
Do you guys have any awareness about the cameras that are filming you ?
I mean, you kinda kept going on tangents
I bet Hatanaka doesn't think so
Really, I forgot about the shooting halfway through
I mean if you pay close attention,
I was properly making conversation wasn't I
Yeah we can see that !
You were freestyling it
She's getting annoyed now
It seems you don't like to talk about things you don't know
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Getting
lectured
You shouldn't act like that
Since Hatanaka is getting scolded
First you should feel sorry for not knowing something
and humbly ask about it
Should I take her in for a month or something ?
Yes please, I'd like to
I'd like to
I refuse.
Other than that, you two seem fairly mature
I agree, Iwase is pretty much an adult
Yeah, she's got that aura
There's just that part where she sprained her ankle
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Fell for real
I was actually trying to play it cool
You know, pulling my hair aside like a classy lady
- It worked though, that looked cool
- It worked
And then I managed to trip where there was nothing to trip on
Not many people manage to fall when just walking like that
And what's with your way of eating
I unwillingly ate it
What did you just say you bastard !
You freaking ate it anyway didn't you !
Why the reluctancy !
Well, up until the shooting I was dieting pretty hard, I had lost 2 kilos
And since the staff told me that it was okay to eat plenty during this shooting
- I thought "now's the time"
So you thought you had to eat a lot
So I ate
But it was difficult
We went back to the company's building
so I took my temperature and I had a fever of 38 degrees
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
What kind of
story is this ?
Wait, what ?
What's with the sudden nonsense
I've got a complaint !
So yeah, that VTR was a little... you know
We didn't learn much about you from this
So that's why we'll do this, individually:
The others will reveal information about the three senbatsu members !
And now, the other members will reveal information about the 3 members to expose their true faces !
First target is the oldest of the three
Iwase
The first information
is from investigator Ikoma
Yes !
So Yumine is actually a gamer
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Quite the gamer
- Gamer ?
- A gamer
She's got the fever
She wrote about games in her blog
I didn't understand a single word she was saying
We've got an example here
From the blog ?
What, no way
You're talking about the parts in brackets ?
Yes, I don't understand at all what's in the brackets
I can't even read it
How's that read...
"Tou-..."
Or is it "Sea Dragon" ?
"Imperial Wrath of the Sea Dragon" and-
That's from Monster Hunter
Yes it's Monster Hunter
- Oh so it was Monster Hunter !
Yeah that item doesn't drop often
I know right !!
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Getting excited
It doesn't !
I had to beat him so many times
before it finally dropped !
You really got to beat him perfectly and-
Alright can we change subject ?
We get it
It's really amazing !
What do you make with this item ?
With this you can craft a weapon, a bow actually
You play with a bow ?
Yeah I'm playing Archer class
Why are you two getting so excited over this ?!
Stop talking about that !
It's fucking boring
Yeah exactly
We got it, you can stop talking about it now
Don't you want to put some pictures in your blog or something ?
Yeah but I'm pretty bad at it
You know about that recent trend of taking a picture without makeup on ?
Ain't that a good photo idea
Okubo's face just now looked like she was about to throw up
There's no way I'd throw up just like that
That's not what she was trying to portray !
Can you show us one more time ?
Well since I'm holding my phone it'll look like that...
What the hell !
Let's move on to the next person
Investigator Ikuta !
Yes !
Well, please say what you've got to say
Right
So, Yumine
Everyday she'll tell us "Since I'm an old lady, you know..."
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Says "Because I'm an old lady" a lot
I hope she doesn't become too negative
and tries to have a more positive outlook on things
So kind...
You're saying she says that very often ?
It feels like she's given up
At 21 years old ?
What exactly has she given up on
Is it because you're one of the oldest amongst the group ?
I mean, I do view myself as an adult
but definitely not as an old lady
Okay, but you do say it, right ?
In fact, the members have been saying that same thing to me a lot
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Break up ?
Look, they're already laughing
Have they been saying that for a long time ?
- Yeah !
They say it to me
I-
Who's saying it ?
Hashimoto
- Hashimoto ?
Hashimoto you say that to her ?
Well, I mean
Since she went for this kind of character
I thought it was okay to tease her about that...
I see
To be clear, she apparently says that kind of thing often
but she doesn't actually behave like an old lady or anything, right ?
Like saying "yoisho" for example
Or wiping the microphone with a cloth after she's done singing
Who even does that
I'm not sure but...
But I've got proof !
Oh you've brought evidence ?
This was written in her blog
The blog... What could it be
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
The members seem happy to have gotten snow.
They said they wanted to have a snowball fight.
Being young sure is nice.
I wonder when it began
Not getting excited anymore when snow falls
Shobon (‘•ω•`)
This would make you worry
about the trains not running because of the snow, right ?
Meanwhile these high school girls think about having a snowball fight
They'd be ecstatic
Ahh that's what you meant
It's true that there eventually comes a time when it's not as exciting
The snow reminds you of the fracture, right Okubo ?
I shouldn't have gone outside
But for real, when you've got a person like Okubo with you
You can rely on them
When you're all playing a game for example
You're bound to get some laughs
if you yell "Keep it up grandma !" or something
I would respond with "Thank you, grandma is very pleased"
Why don't you try it right now ?
"Grandma"
Grandma !
Calling her Yumine is now prohibited
Let's stop calling her Yumine
But "grandma" is a bit too much for an idol, so how about "old lady" ?
[Note: Actually its the same word but the difference is hard to translate. It's gentler.]
Old lady Yumi !
Yubaaba also works
[note: The big old lady in Spirited Away]
Next, Investigator Nishino
Yes sir !
So...
Don't "Yes sir!" me !
Cute !
When we were each shooting our individual Pvs
Baaba went to Okinawa by herself
There she visited a kindergaten
The plan was to go there and have some good time, play with the kids
At some point the kids asked her
something along the lines of "How old are you ?"
And she answered "I'm 17!"
[Note: Actually was 21 years old]
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Lied about her age to kindergarten children
Is she telling the truth ?
It's the truth.
I see
Well ain't that something you're acquainted with, Okubo
This is common in the show business, you like to know each others age to break the ice
I mean, the kids just thought it was cool and that was the end of it, right ?
Yes
Of course, they wouldn't know
How about doing the opposite ?
"I'm 40 years old"
Increasing so your age
Since young looking middle aged women are pretty popular right now
That's a good idea
Even though I have no idea what I'm saying
Miyazawa Seira is next on the grill
First up, Investigator Sakurai
Yes !
What will it be ?
Secchan
She often does an impression of Lola
I think she does it really well
- I'm interested !
- Let's see it !
You do ?
Ah, she already started
Eh ?
And that's a wrap
Nah, do some more !
How are you today Lola ?
Hmm let's see
What did you eat ?
Today ? I had onigiri
So cute !
It's hot in here !
You've got to keep going !
Don't stop it yourself
Yeah you have to keep it going, right Lola ?
Okay !
Here comes the old man again
Keep going even when you think you're ridiculing yourself
Yep, it's very important
Yeah
Can you do someone else maybe ?
She can do weird faces too
If it's alright, would you show us ?
...Yes
Here we go
3, 2, 1...
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Ayiiin!
That was the Ayin, right ?
That was cute
Himura would you do one as well ?
Let's go. 3, 2, 1...
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
A ghost ?
Cute !
That was cute !
Weird faces are cute, as you all know
They didn't think it was cute though
She was on point
When the time is right you can pull out a slightly lighter version of this and it'll be great
Right
"Right"
Are you still doing the Lola impression ?
If not, one might think you're getting slightly irritated
Please do the hand movement when you're doing it so we can tell
- Yes
Let's continue, Investigator Shiraishi
Yes !
She did that yesterday too
When me and Nagashima Seira went to buy some things in Harajuku
In this certain clothes store, we found a mannequin
that looks just like Secchan
And we took a picture of it, here it is
In a moment
The look-alike mannequin makes its appearance !
It does look like her !
That's just an insult to her !
In this certain clothes store, we found a mannequin
that looks just like Secchan
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
The perfect copy mannequin from harajuku
And we took a picture of it, here it is
It looks like her !
Looks like her, right ?
- Yeah
That's just Noppera-bou !
[Note: A faceless ghost from Japanese folklore]
Where is the resemblance !
- It's the overall feeling !
Saying she looks like this is just insulting !
I can understand that the hairstyle sort of looks like hers
but it doesn't have eyes or anything
Saying she resembles this Noppera-bou is like saying she's unremarkable
- I think it does look like her
- Yeah it does
- Yes
Why though...
Well Okubo what did you think about that ?
I don't really care
if it resembles or not...
What we could do next is have the members
take pictures of various mannequins
and see who resembles who !
Next is Hatanaka Seira from Oita prefecture
First we have investigator Hashimoto
- Yes !
Seira says that
Oita has a richer legacy than Tokyo
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
She says that Oita has a richer legacy than Tokyo
Oita is more prosperous than Tokyo ?
There's this idea that Oita = rice fields, however
It's not like that at all
What I'm saying is that
The cities in Oita are very developed
It has already gone out of business, but there was this PARCO-like building
[Note: A huge shopping center located in Shibuya]
It was like a 10-15 minutes drive away from my house
That's pretty far though
10 minutes, 10 minutes !
But is it really more prosperous than Tokyo... ?
Yes it's growing faster
And comparing Oita to Shibuya ?
I'd say Shibuya is better off here
That's exactly what we're saying !!
But in defense of Oita
Since I there are many placesI know
It's easy to navigate
That's got nothing to do with it !
Would it be easier to navigate if you'd been in Tokyo your whole life ?
I'm not sure I would be able to remember the places...
Of course you'd be able to, no problem
No, I can't
You're just retorting to everything I say !
Of course you'll remember...
Next up
Investigator Ikuta
Yes !
So, I was doing my homework for school
And then Seitan said
"I'll can help you"
You're one grade further in school, right ?
One grade further
I thought she wouldn't know how to help me, but...
You thought that ?
But since she was insistant, I allowed her to help me
But after I showed her, she said:
"Yeah nah I don't get it"
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
She offered to help with the school homework,
but couldn't actually do it
Since she was the one to come to me, I thought she'd be at least able to help a little bit !
Yeah, things like that tend to happen in everyday life
Why made you want to help her ?
You thought she was waiting for you to ?
Well, since she was here...
"I must resolve the problem at hand !"
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Famous
saying
The moment I handed her the paper she was like "The hell is that ?"
Hatanaka how are your results in school ?
Pretty much perfect !
But I've seen some of her tests before, their full of red marks...
Not true...
She turned around
Next, the reveal of the morning sleeping case !
Let's continue, investigator Hashimoto
- Yes !
You see, I have the reputation of not being a morning person
So I asked her to wake me up if I didn't wake up by myself
I see where this is going
No no, she was like "let's do it"
- That's nice of her
I was really thankful
"Please wake me up at 5AM tomorrow"
So I wake up, open my, get up
I checked my phone to see if she had tried to call me
But she didn't
The wake up call never came ?
In the end, when I met with her at the meeting place
she was like "I was sleeping, sorry"
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Made a promise to wake her up,
but didn't keep it
Why do you do that ?
This is the same pattern as the homework one
First you go "Let's do it !"
and then you don't
This one time was because my alarm clock had broken
Your alarm clock was broken... ?
Really ?
I'm not the only one affected by this
Who never received the agreed upon wake up call
Raise your hands
Damn, I'm sorry
Amazing
That was real right there
On March 17
Nogizaka held a charity event to help fund the reconstruction after the earthquake
The best you guys can do for us is to keep smiling and be happy
Asking for clothes donations
The performed at full power for all the fans
One day we'll all go on site
To try and bring a smile to everyone's face
And we'll give it our best