Tonight, a close-up documentary about Nogizaka46's pre-debut era.
The hardships they endured during their difficult days.
Louder! Louder!
That's strict.
What's the biggest problem they faced before their debut?
Nogizakatte, Doko?
Credits: NeruestSub
Subber: Coffee-san
Timing: MintTea-san
Proofreading: Coffee-san
Don! Nogizakatte, Doko? has started! We're the MC - Bananaman!
Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu!
So, every member showed up, except those who took a sick leave!
Nogizaka46's members!
-Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu! -There's a lot of them.
You guys were incredible lately!
Thank you very much.
You guys appeared on every channel.
Congratulations on your 2nd place on the Oricon's Weekly Chart!
That's incredible!
Why did everyone show up for today?
Nogizaka46 was formed around August last year, right?
So what's the song title again? Bichabicha Curtain(wet curtain)?
Guruguru Curtain was the one that got the 2nd place on the Oricon.
From the formation of the group until now, how did you guys deal with it?
We're going to use a video to conclude it, so everyone can see your growth.
Tokyo Minato-ku. Nogizaka.
Countless artists once started their careers at this place.
Among them, it's the official rival of AKB48 - Nogizaka46!
These were the 154 days of training for their debut single.
August 2011, the final evaluation for Nogizaka46.
56 finalist were selected from 38,934 candidates for the final evaluation.
I come from Yurihonjo, Akita.
Both Natsuki Kato and Shu Watanabe came from Yurihonjo too.
I would like to become the third artist that came from Yurihonjo.
Hello everyone, my name is Shiraishi Mai.
I like to eat sweet potato,
and my favorite sauce is mayonnaise.
U gonna regret saying that, Maiyan
After serious evaluation, they announced the starting members.
Ikoma Rina, please come in front.
Entry No.3, Ichiki Rena.
Nogizaka46 was formed with 33 members.
They're going to give their best along the way for their CD debut.
Two weeks after the announcement, members have started their first dance lesson.
Members started their first dance lesson with unease and nervous feelings.
With the help from their teacher, they put their maximum effort to it.
After their lesson, they heard some unexpected feedback from their teacher.
After looking at everyone, the most obvious aura I felt was,
you guys thought you're still in school.
Even with that kind of basic learning consciousness, it was far from enough.
Since everyone set their goal to debut,
you guys should have shown us your professionalism during the lessons.
Not only you have to learn the moves,
you have to learn how to engage with the audience, express yourself.
The place they're standing is not a playground, it's a serious entertainment stage.
They  learned the ways to engage with the audience during their first lesson.
Next up, a mandatory skill for a CD debut, the singing lessons started.
Firstly, the members had to perform songs, one by one in front of their teachers.
Is that the best from you?
-Hmm? -Is that the best you got?
I accidentally looked down.
Can I sing one more time?
Sorry, we don't have much time, next.
I'm Saito Chiharu, I'm going to sing now.
-Can you tell me your name again? -I'm Saito Chiharu.
-Again. -I'm Saito Chiharu.
Again, louder this time, be energetic.
-I'm Saito Chiharu. -Louder.
I'm Saito Chiharu. -Louder!!
-I'm Saito Chiharu!! -Yes, that felt more energetic.
If you want to leave an impression, you have to be energetic like you did just now.
If you're nervous, you can move your body a bit.
How do you express yourself when everyone can see your face?
Undoubtedly everyone gets nervous on the stage.
But if you show your nervousness out, you'll look like an amateur.
Everyone here wanted to become a pro artist right?
So that's why even when you're nervous you have to express yourself more.
I know you were nervous earlier.
But please do your training.
So, let's continue.
Imagine yourself on a stage.
Imagine yourself on a stage!
As a professional artist and as a performer,
fooling around is not allowed.
The members had to go through a harsh lessons step by step.
After their lesson,
today we have something important to announce.
Nogizaka46's first variety show has been decided.
But not everyone can participate in the show.
After the combinations of training and official poll,
they selected these members to participate.
Here it is, the first ever recording of the show has started.
No please, it's embarrassing.
Their first variety show debut, and their first own show.
Before the appearance, the members were nervous behind the scene.
I'm really nervous now, yabai.
I'm super nervous, no idea what should I do now.
Gambarimasu! I'm going to do my best.
Alright, welcome!
Everyone waved at us, thank you very much.
The talks between Bananaman relieved the members' nervousness.
Members started to talk more, and the recording finished without a hinge.
Actually, we have a big announcement to make.
Nogizaka's Shichifukujin.
Unexpectedly, they were going to announce the Shichifukujin members during their second recording.
Shiraishi Mai-san!
Sakurai Reika!
Ikoma Rina!
I had no confidence in myself.
I thought I'm not worthy to be the one standing here.
After the announcement of Nogizaka's Shichifukujin,
they started to work towards their debut, the interaction between fans also started.
Their first ever event, the members designed their own posters for the meeting event.
Doiya-san
This was the first time the members interacted with their fans.
The members formed a circle to boost their energy.
Is everyone energized? OOOOYYEEEAAHHHH!!
one two, "Doryoku, kansha, egao, uchira wa Nogizaka noborizaka FORTY-SIX!"
Translation: Effort, gratitude, and smiles! We’re the 46 who are going to ascend Nogizaka!
To shorten the distance between them, the members introduced themselves one by one.
From: The Phantom of the Opera - Think of Me.
"Think of me, think of me fondly When we've said goodbye."
Although I read tons of books when I was a child,
I still love the Galileo·Galilei Biography I read when I was in fourth grade.
The book had shaped me into the person I am today.
Next up, some unique interactions between members and fans.
Speed drawing of the fans in a limited time.
Nishino who's really good at drawing finished her artwork very quickly.
The oldest member, Iwase also drew some good drawing.
Other members also finished their own unique artwork.
Next up was the message recording session from the members.
I like you, always!
Good morning, the sun came out, time to get up!
Thanks for the hard work, do your best for tomorrow too!
As the Nogizaka's Shichifukujin, the members went through 4 months of activities.
There's another announcement...
February 22nd is going to be Nogizaka46's CD debut date.
Next up, the senbatsu of 16 members for the CD debut.
Unexpectedly, they're going to reveal the 16 senbatsu members for the debut on the show.
Cellphones will be used.
Those who got selected, will receive a call from the management team.
Those who did not receive a call will not make it into the senbatsu.
First up, the Shichifukujin's!
Shiraishi's phone is ringing!
Thank you very much.
The next Shichifukujin.
Oh! Who's it? Matsumura?
Ehh...how do I say...
More new Shichifukujin appeared...
Ikoma Rina, Takayama Kazumi, Ikuta Erika also made it into Shichifukujin.
Unexpectedly, there are 3 new Shichifukujin members that joined the ranks.
Next up, Nogizaka46's hardest trial yet!
After the senbatsu, the members started to work towards their final goal!
Announcement! Nogizaka's going to do Meiji's commercial deal.
Nobody expected themselves to have a Meiji's commercial.
Nogizaka46 has officially debuted into commercial deal!
They did all kind of promotions around the country.
At the same time, the lessons for the debut single and CW song did not stop at all.
Following their working schedules, they shot a PV.
They also finished the recording work.
For the first time ever, the members experienced overloaded works/schedules.
The members were battling against pressure and uneasiness.
Although they were determined to carry on,
but they started to become exhausted at the same time, one by one.
Finally, on the day of their recording, Hashimoto was sick.
Because of her extreme nervousness, she was suffering from hyperventilation.
She couldn't do anything but rest.
But it was the recording day for their song "Guruguru Curtain."
One member's absent might caused a big trouble to the rest.
"I'm not the only one that's going through a hard time."
Hashimoto seems to hear her teammates' inner voice.
She went back to finish the recording.
Going through a hard time altogether,
they thought of their responsibilities and each other,
Nogizaka46's was one step closer to become professional artists.
Around January, Nogizaka46's members arrived at AKB48's live show.
They performed "Guruguru Curtain" during AKB48's concert.
It was Nogizaka46's first time to be performing in front of the audiences.
The members felt extremely nervous for their first live performance.
Meanwhile, the other members that are not in the senbatsu stayed at the backstage to cheer on them.
We're on the same boat. So even though we're not performing our heart beats together.
10, 9..."Doryoku, kansha, egao, uchira wa Nogizaka noborizaka FORTY-SIX!"
Finally, Nogizaka46 went up to the stage full of nervousness.
Everyone, good evening! 1, 2, We're Nogizaka46!
The senbatsu members sang their song in front of audiences without being nervous.
The members on stage were performing for everyone that supported and cheered for them.
Those who could not make it to the stage also cheered for the members on stage.
Finally, Nogizaka46 finished "Guruguru Curtain" in front of AKB48's fans.
We, as Nogizaka46, has a goal we would like to surpass.
The goal is...
The goal is... AKB48.
We'll work hard and do our best so we could become AKB48's real rival.
Everyone, please support us!
After that, "Guruguru Curtain" achieved the 2nd place on Oricon Weekly Chart!
But Nogizaka46 just debuted recently.
They only started their first step of a long journey towards the top of the hill.
To surpass their target, to the top of the hill, to reach beyond the horizon.
With thankful and hardworking thoughts and the smile on their face,
Nogizaka46's going full speed towards the higher goals!
So from the look of it, everyone did their best to carry on.
So what's the harshest experience for each different members?
Let's talk about that. Firstly, Takayama.
For me, before we have our own songs, I could not sing during events.
Because you guys have no songs yet?
Yes, so we have to learn how to do talks, it's very hard.
Indeed, right? You must be able to talk all of a sudden, with no prior experience.
But at least you kinda know how to talk now, right?
Yeah, kinda now...
Hashimoto, what do you think about her talking skill?
She can now talk very smoothly even without any scripts.
So you already surpassed me.
You're competent. x2
Next up, Matsumura.
During Meiji's commercial filming, I'm not a senbatsu member,
Everyone was filming, but I'm not the senbatsu member so I finished my filming part very quickly.
Because they filmed for the whole day, and I went in the lounge to wait for them.
So when I heard them laughing and having fun, I became sad and cried.
When I heard their happy voices, I realized that I finished my part very quickly.
It was kinda sad.
Well, everything has two sides, the happy part, and the sad part...
Nanamin~~
Eh, what happened?
Hashimoto looks like she's gonna cry too.
Sorry, I feel like crying too.
We faced the same problem.
I understand the pain.
But I still love the members,
so I thought was there another way?
I love them so much, but there's no place to release my anger.
Why not just hire a staff as a sandbag for you to punch.
After this, another big announcement!
Because I Don't Want to Lose You / Ushinaitaku Nai Kara
I was surrounded by the sound of cicada's cries,
The summer fever spread throughout the schoolyard
Your white shirt and grey skirt
Heartrendingly wavering at me like a mirage
Within my heart
A wind silently begins to blow
My true thoughts are suddenly stirring
People fall in love because they don't want to be alone
Pretending to tie the laces on my Converses
But I was really looking at you the whole time
My thirst had been quenched
But somehow I'm always sinking Into the desert of my heart
Guruguru Curtain's worldwide handshake event has started!
Their first event attracted around 5 thousands people!
I had a dream since I was a kid that I'll be able to perform in front of a lot of people
I achieved that dream today, I'm really happy.
Next up, the dream stage.
Please listen next, "Guruguru Curtain."
The live performance was a big hit! The members continued to work towards their dreams!
Congratulations, Guruguru Curtain achieved 2nd place.
Thank you very much.
So since you have the first single, of course, there'll be the second single.
So next week, senbatsu announcement for the second single!
It's really fast, right? Ikoma's already in tears.
It's coming.
But that's Nogizaka46 for you right?
Finally, senbatsu for their second single!
Next week, senbatsu for their second single!
More shocking and unexpected results than the previous single's senbatsu!
I'm getting goosebumps.