Tonight on Nogizakatte, Doko?
We're going to scoop Nogizaka46 members' comedy skills!
Unexpected and weird answers one after another!
The correct answer appeared!
Is it ok to be an Idol if they're vulgar?
What actually happened!?
Nogizakatte, Doko?
Credits: NeruestSub Team
Subber: NeruNeru-san
Timing: Coffee-san
Proofreading: Miru-chan
DON!
Nogizakatte, Doko? has started! We're the MC Bananaman!
These are the members for today!
Our guest for today, Hamaguchi-san*! Yoroshiku!
Japanese comedian, and actor.
Same as the last time, we invited the fans to our studio.
-There's a lot of fans here! -Thanks for coming!
So for today's plan, Himura-san.
What's the plan?
Please read the plan while acting cute.
Yes~ alright~  I'm realli cute and funny too~ Nogizaka Comedy~~
Speaking of comedy, the girls should know a few of it right?
Because comedy appeared on different shows very often.
Like AIUEO Sakubon* and "Nazokake*, MC like to use them during a show.
Both are a form of wordplay jokes in Japanese.
So you wanna do an AIUEO Sakubon?
Well...this is not the time to betray me.
Today's questions were already answered beforehand by the members before the recording.
Although we'll be looking at some of the weird answers,
but if all of them were really lame,
Hamaguchi-san will answer instead.
He even bought his own equipment for this.
well-prepared?
I bought a lot of cards today, I'm totally prepared.
Before the recording, I was told to prepare some witty answers.
It'll be better if Himura-san could...
Nani!?
Friendly-fire.
I might ask you later, so you should kinda prepare too.
Aha...Ummm...I'm kinda pissed when you said that.
Everyone, please help us too.
I might even ask the fans too.
They'll be like "Eh!? Really!?"
If you were picked, just laugh.
Let's get started!
The first question is...
There's a "dating ban" rule in AKB48,
other than that, what are the other rules people do not know?
So there might be those unspoken rules...
-The answer range is kinda wide. -Yes.
We'll see how did you guys answer this question.
Alright, first up is Ichiki's answer.
Oh, it's here!
Ichiki's answer is the following, let's see.
"Only buy the electric appliance in Akihabara!!"
Yes. I had an inspiration earlier.
Akihabara. Interesting.
Not bad as the first answer.
The answer was smooth and stable. Not bad.
The flattering words from two comedians with each up to 20 years of comedy experiences.
Just in case.
So next up, Inoue's answer.
What's the other rule people do not know?
"Don't catch a cold."
Oh!! This is important!
I mean it's not for Nogizaka only, everyone should not catch a cold!
It's like a worldwide rule.
During the recording, a few members caught a cold,
and we kinda caused some troubles.
I know right!
Even if you wrote a small matter like this, it's still funny!
That's nice! Not bad, not bad!
Not bad too as the second answer.
How strange.
No matter what was written, these two will always be giving tons of feedback.
A new type of jokes.
How interesting. This might become a new oogiri's segment.
All credit goes to the girls.
Next up, Ikoma's answer.
What's the other rule people do not know?
"Marriage is ok."
*cough* AKB's 49th Sousenkyo *cough*
Oh, I see.
No dating, but if it's marriage, it's ok?
I thought that they can just skip the dating part.
Like the other countries, where they met their fiancé only during their wedding ceremony.
Well if that's the case, I think it's ok.
Kinda like finding a loophole.
Yes. I finally got to see the smart side of Ikoma.
Please beware of these two's endless feedbacks!
Alright, the last one which was Shiraishi's answer.
What's the other rule in AKB48 that others do not know?
"No farting."
@Oshima Yuko
Not just for AKB but for other idols too, right?
You guys do not fart, right?
But...
But!?
Spilling the bean!?
Nani?
Are you trying to betray your fellow members?
That's bad.
What happened?
-Can I say it? -Sure, sure.
We had a lesson before, and Saito Yuri was beside me.
Wait you can't say that!
She's like "I kinda wanna fart, may I?"
After that, she kinda turned to where Sayuri (Inoue) was standing and released her chemical weapon.
-No, it's nothing like that! -You can't do that!
After I said that, Kazumi who was beside me said
"Sure, but please fart at where Inoue's."
The Mastermind?
What's the meaning of this!?
-But Yuri said "Ah...it won't come out," and she went back.
-Yes, I did not fart.
-Since you're an idol. -Yes, I'll never fart as an idol!
You didn't! You couldn't! No discussion!
Not bad!
Well, it's the time to listen to their answers.
Ah...ummm...
The standard answers...
What kind of show pulled out an answer from a plastic bag.
Well, this will do.
Alright, let's go.
What's the other rule in AKB48 that others do not know?
"Don't use "rock paper scissors" to decide everything."
*cough* Janken Tournament *cough*
Ah, not bad!
Well, I mean...there's more...
Not one answer for one question?
What do you mean? Only one answer for each question.
Not just one time?
You're really scary.
If there are good answers it would be easier for the editors.
"Do not meet face to face with SDN48."
-This is a good one too. -Sugoi!
What's the other rule in AKB48 that others do not know?
"Don't think that everyone who wears suit and glasses is Producer Akimoto."
Please use the one with "SDN" as my answer.
Alright, let's continue. The next question is...
The title for a new song which makes us think
"Aki-p were you being lazy?" So what's the title?
If they did not answer well enough, they'll get scolded.
-First up, Hashimoto's answer. -Yes.
Aki-p's lazy new song title is...
"Someday, Kachuusha."
Original song from AKB48 21st Single - "Everyday, Kachuusha"
Not bad. It's not "everyday."
-Incredible! -Not bad! Not bad at all!
That's a typical standard answer for oogiri shows' opening.
Yes. Just change a few words and you got a standard oogiri answer.
That's right. A few changes and it's already funny.
Next up, Mastumura's.
Aki-p's lazy new song title is...
"Heavy Rotation, probably?"
"probably" has become a series.
Not bad!
-Did you come up with that? -Yes.
You got talent girl~
Not bad right, for these bunch of kids.
Next up, Nishino's.
Aki-p's lazy new song title is...
"Guruguru Curtain 2."
He's definitely being lazy.
Maybe the next song will be "#3."
After this, there'll be no other songs except "Guruguru Curtain."
"Why the same old outfit..."
They might even reach "#14."
The road for them, just like that until the end.
Next up, Takayama.
Not bad, Takayama.
Wait, we haven't show her answer yet.
Can't resist.
Can't help but to give feedbacks, it happened often.
Like when the feet of a runner leaves the starting blocks before the starter’s gun.
Let's continue with Takayama's answer. Aki-p's lazy new song title is...
"Please look forward to it next time."
-So for this time, we just give up the song? -Yes.
That's bad if someone was told with it, "so...there's a next song?"
Hatanaka's answer,
Aki-p's lazy new song title is...
"Hill!!(Saka)"
How did you come up with this?
Like the feeling of climbing a hill.
Oh, I get it. Going up the hill(saka) and rolling down(guruguru)...
Will "Nogizaka" be referred as "Saka?"
"Nogizaka."
If we slowly changed it to "Saka," that'll be nice right?
Our guest for today is "Saka."
"Today I climbed a hill(saka)."
After this, "going to a live concert" will be referred as "climbing a hill."
Not bad, not bad!
So it's decided, no more "Nogizaka."
Kawamura's Aki-p's lazy new song title is...
"Dung Beetles."
-Oh! -It became really bad!
That's incredible. So kids these days like these kinds of stuff.
Yabai! These two will give positive comments no matter what.
Well, at least she wrote it.
How do we sing it?
"Dung beetles~ Dung dung dung~"
So the lyrics are going to be "Dung beetles~ Dung dung dung~"
Next up, Ito Nene's.
Aki-p's lazy new song title is...
"Mori Mori Supplied Food(Kyushoku)"
Original song - Maru Maru Mori Mori
How does it sound? "Mori~ mori~ supplied~ food~"
It totally sounded like a plagiarized song.
"Everyone~ let's eat~"
This is actually lazy. When you heard the song "Eh!?"
Let's check out sensei's.
Example!
Don't know whose answer is better yet. Even dung beetles appeared.
Aki-p's lazy new song title is...
"I took off my sailor uniform, probably?"
-It's the "probably" series.
-It'll be better if I showed this during the opening.
Ah, right...the "probably" series.
But the girls already showed it.
So do you have more?
There's more! There's more!
Aki-p's lazy new song title is...
"High and Mighty Yasushi."
(Original song from AKB48 24th Single - Ue kara Mariko.
"Yasushi" as Akimoto Yasushi 秋元康, the producer.)
Ah! Not bad!
Like "Ue kara Mariko."
-One more... -There's more?
If you have it, let's do it.
Aki-p's lazy new song title...
Don't make that face ok? Like you have to confirm the answer with me first.
There's no need for it.
Aki-p's lazy new song title is...
"Well, it's still Yasushi."
*Edit this part out*
Alright, next question...
This kind of Idol that will never become popular! So what it is?
"Ya won't become famous ya know?" x500
Kawago's the kind of Idol that will never become popular is?
"Do not sing, do not dance, do not talk."
Do not sing, do not dance and do not talk.
-Ya won't become famous! -Ya won't become famous!
What kind of Idol is that?
Eh, like she only has a pretty face?
Next, Takayama's.
Not bad, Takayama's.
-Wait, we haven't shown it yet. -Not bad right, Takayama's.
The kind of Idol that will never become popular is?
"Only become the center once every three years."
Oh!! That's good! That's really good!
Like only become the center when it's a leap year.
Umm, a leap year does not appear every three years. -Eh!?
-It's once every four years. -Four? Ah! I messed up!
Ahhhhhhh~~~~~~ That's good! That's good!
-Not bad! -Next up, Ikuta's.
-Ikuta's really tired today? -Eh!?
You good with your studies?
-Ah, I'm good. -Did you have a class today?
Yes, I'm taking exam this year.
There are others that work as Idol while studying too right?
You have to prepare for exams and these oogiri answers...Sugoi.
You should have declined it.
The kind of Idol that will never become popular is?
"Those who forgot their group name."
That's kawai.
Those who forgot?
Like, "ready, set...Eh??"
Just like Nogizaka's introduction, "one, two...Eh??"
Kawai.
After this, a funny masterpiece appeared?
Kashiwa's answer.
The kind of Idol that will never become popular is
Nobody in the group is cute enough.
Nobody in...hahahaha!
-What a straight forward answer. -A correct answer appeared!
-So their turn is over. -Is that so?
So, the kind of Idol that will never become popular is? Himura-san let's go.
Ya won't become famous ya know!? x500
Ya can't say adult jokes ya know!
Oh, did you finish? So Himura-san's answer.
So, the kind of Idol that will never become popular is?
"Vomit the second she's on stage."
Not that good.
Ya can't do that ya know, and *vomit*
Nogizaka46 reached a new milestone again?
Nogizaka46 had a JFA press conference.
The members appeared to be wearing a sports uniform, what's that about?
Introducing SKYP TV! J-league 2012 Official Cheerleaders - Nogizaka46!
Nogizaka46 has become the official cheerleaders for SKYP TV J-league 2012.
"Hidari Mune no Yuuki" was chosen to be the official theme song.
How does Ikoma feel about this?
Nogizaka46 was chosen as the official cheerleader for SKY TV J-league 2012, I'm really honored.
From today onward, Nogizaka46 will continue to cheer for the teams and the league,
we hope to make J-league more interesting, and raise the bar for the sports.
1, 2, let us witness our dream come true!
To commemorate the selling of "Guruguru Curtain," they had a worldwide mini handshake event.
There's a lot more fans that showed up than expected.
The members cried tears of joy.
Thanks to the fans, the event was a big success!
Don! Yes! Everyone thanks for the hard work!
The Daruma doll was really cute.
-We drew stars and hearts on it. -Why stars and hearts?
Well, I thought it was better than just drawing circles.
Ah yes, this one.
Yeeee~ The handshake event is a success!
Thank you very much!
Please continue to support Nogizaka46!
Thanks for the fans' support, "Guruguru Curtain" achieved the 2nd place on Weekly Chart!
They also achieved the 3rd place for female artists debut single!
Please continue to support Nogizaka46!
Next week, the reveal of Nogizaka46's formation and their road to debut.
The members grew up as they worked together.
Some of the changes are massive!