This week, Nogizaka46 members will perform tasks of critical importance
In order to promote "Guruguru Curtain"
nation wide
as many as 4600 tissues will be distributed to the public to signify the group's debut
Traveling to 8 locations across the country sometimes in extreme weather !
Doing PR at a ski resort with this weather, this is hell
Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu
But Nogizaka members will face an unexpected situation
Woah~ !
So many people came
The second part of their promotion tour is underway !
And there's a big big surprise from the members !
www.ikuchancheeks.blogspot.com
Hello.
We are Bananaman.
Continued from last week, this is the promotion for their debut single, launching on February 22nd.
"Guruguru Curtain"
The members went around the country to hand out tissues, to promote their first single.
This time it's the second part... they went abroad
Are they already famous overseas ?
Seriously though, still in Japan for now.
Each team has a limited time to go to two places
and give out tissues as PR (public relationship)
The fans will suggest places for them to visit in their respective areas via Twitter
Then, the members will choose where to go
First team is Saito Asuka, Hashimoto, Sakurai and Ikoma
They had successfully distributed 400 tissues in the Sendai area
After that they were headed to Sapporo, however !
They were blocked by a heavy snowstorm
The tissue-sharing takes a blow
But the snowstorm didn't stop the fans from coming
It's snowing so badly yet the fans came in numbers, we're really happy
Even in extreme weather, more than 200 people gathered in Sapporo
They are fighting a snowstorm to support the members
Hashimoto was touched, since it's her hometown
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
The members handed out 200 tissues successfuly in poor weather.
Next in Sapporo,
an area with a fresh seafood market in Hokkaido
Konichiwa!
Hello everyone! We are from Nogizaka46
on February 22nd, we will release our first single.
If you don't mind, could you please put this poster up for us ?
Sure no problem
Two posters, yoroshiku onegaishimasu
Konichiwa~
We're the members of Nogizaka46 and...
I knw you guys
You do ?
Thank you very much
My daughter knows you!
really?
The store manager then plays the CD on the spot
The members listening and the fans clapping made for a live concert of sorts
4-wheel mini racing PR activities in Hiroshima area
Team Shiraishi, Hoshino, Nojou and Inoue
successfully distributed 400 tissues
Thank you very much
Next, the 4 members went to Fukuoka
Arrived at Hakata Station
Time to check the suggestions from the fans on Twitter.
This? What is this?
RADIO LOVE FM INFINITY
Radio Infinity Zone 2
-Hopefuly a lot of people will be listening -Right?
Wait
So about on radio ?
Alright, let's go to the radio station later
First, they go the first point mentioned on Twitter, Hawks town
Many fans have gathered there
We are Nogizaka46
More than 100 people gathered beforehand waiting for Nogizaka members
They then distributed their tissues, hoping for the fanbase to grow
Next, they go to the aforementioned LOVE FM radio station.
Konichiwa!
-Konichiwa!
Since there a was a request on Twitter, we actualy came but...
Thank you
No problem at all, yoroshiku onegaishimasu
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu
Unexpected interruption
They then immediately entered Infinity Zone 2's studio
Many fans have gathered to welcome the members
Good afternoon everyone !
We are Nogizaka46, yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Can they manage a good broadcast and promotion ?
The name of the song is "Guruguru Curtain"
We wear a long skirt, well, it's a one-piece
then, swinging, dancing
All members in a circle
Having fun together and playing with each others skirts
A very cute dance
In fact, after this, we will move to our next location
to share tissue for our promotion tour
Thanks for coming everyone! Please buy it
Please listen to the song !
Greedy
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu
with the help of the radio staff, the promotion is successful
Meanwhile, in another city, Kawamura, Matsumura, Rina and Nakada
did their promotion at a ski resort
and distributed the most with more than 500 tissues
Next they're going to Osaka!
Osaka being the hometown of Kawamura and Matsumura, they contact family and friends
How does it look?
Maybe there will be some people coming
Yay ! What about you Sayurin ?
Maybe my mom and sister are coming
Really ? eeeh ?
First up, the mall in Tenjinbashi Suji where they begin carrying out the PR activities
We're Nogizaka46, AKB48 official rivals
On February 22nd we will be making our debut
Please accept this
Do your best !
Where are you in this photo ?
Mahiro... this one!
Thank you very much
We're Nogizaka46, AKB48 official rivals
Hello, nice to meet you
Please accept this
Yes
AKB48 members usually eat our takoyaki
I want to have some too !
Do you want to try it ?
Get Takoyaki
Thanks to the owner's kindness, they get free takoyaki !
Here they prepare to make their gourmet report, however...
... it's hot !
It's actualy really good
The taste is very noticeable, more than usual
Delicious
tasty tasty
As they kept walking from store to store in the streets of Osaka, the team ended up distributing 300 tissues
Next, the group that visited a temple in Kyoto and met with tourists
Nishino, Saito, Takayama and Wakatsuki team
Although Nishino nearly gave up because sha was ignored by one person
However, with the help of the members, they have distributed a total of 500 tissues
Carrying on, they travel to Nagoya
We have arrived in Nagoya !
We're have arrived !
Yay~
Thank you very much!!
They received suggestions on Twitter
to go to Nagoya Metro where there will be many people
Nishino also took part to continue promoting
and with that, 300 tissues were shared
Then they went to Nagoya CBC radio station
Where they will be playing their debut song
When...
Ahh ! It surprised me !
Ah, Nagashima
Nagashima Seira
I knew you'd be coming to Nagoya
I saw it on twitter, I had to come to support you !
And so, Nagashima Seira joined the team, and will participate in the promotion in CBC Nagoya
Ohisashiburi desu ! (Long time no see)
Are you all doing well ?
We are !
As a matter of fact, Takayama and 11 other members, in November of last year
have done PR on the same radio program in Nagoya
Right now, I am really grateful
If you would, here is our song, please listen to it
Please accept it.
Right, actualy now his program has started
Eh ? - Houso-san program has already started
Ah I see
Please accept these tissues
Thank you very much
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
At this moment, the staff brings good news
His show has already started
it's on air so...
Would you like to join in ?
And so, 4 members are invited to join in live
Konbanwa, we are Nogizaka46 !
Onegashimasu
-Onegaishimasu !
I was surprised, you came so suddenly
How do they promote over the radio
Can members do a good PR ?
Nishino-san, what's something you like recently ?
Something I like ?
Yes, anything
Something I like are birds
Fly? or eat?
I see
How about you Saito-sama ?
For me, well it's not recently,
but I like to touch the butt of others members...
Touching their butt ?
So you like touching someone else's butt
Yeah that's it
It's been 5 minutes, and they've only talked about birds and butt-touching
To make everyone remember Nogizaka46,
I know you guys are excited
So, finally, please announce the title of your single debut.
-Thank you very much
Did completely....
1, 2 ! Guruguru Curtain !
Thank you very much
Thanks to all of you
Very good voice Seirarin
I'm so sorry
It's alright.
Despite the very casual debut announcement, they succeeded
On the other side of the team, in Sapporo
They came to a tourist destination in Sapporo: Ramen Yokocho
To be done here:
Put up a signed poster in every store
for a good PR
Here seems fine
There's a lot of signatures here
GLAY-san
Let's try to put it here
I am from the idol group Nogizaka46
May I put up this poster in your store ?
Sure
and another one if I can put our signature here!
Yes no problem
Hall of fame!?
Thank you very much
I'll put it upper on Bobby's.
Bobby Orogun's signature (comedian)
Bobby's signature covered by Nogizaka46
They also put up signed posters in other stores
Ah, I'm so hungry~
There's a lot of delicious looking food here....
I wanna eat ramen...
'Cause i really rove ramen
Please eat here
Is it okay ?
Kind shopkeeper, quickly makes some ramen when seeing the memebers efforts
to keep them excited and on the edge
itadakimasu!
mmmmh! its delicious!
its delicious,
I just choked!
150 tissue packs remain to be given
Next location is the nearest subway station
Unexpectedly, many fans had already oustisde waiting for the members
There were more than 300 people !
The 150 tissues were guickly gone, so give the fans a high touch to not leave them with nothing
1, 2! The team has finished distributing 1150 tissu packs in Sendai and Sapporo successfully !
the remaining 120 tissues
Here is the last pack, thank you everyone !
The team that went to Nagoya and Kyoto successfully distributed 1150 tissues
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu
Suddenly, Kawamura's friend arrived at the shop
Matsumura's big sister
That's my mother
Matsumura's mother
And her friends also came to the store to support her
I saw you on TV
they also distributed tissues to friends and family
On February 22nd, we'll be releasing our debut single. Please support us !
Team traveling to Niigata and Osaka distributed 1150 tissues
On the other hand, Hoshino, Shiraishi, Inoue and Noujo
moved to Shinseido
Informed by radio, more than 200 people gathered there
Although there are 250 packs remaining...
We should stay a little longer
There are still 220 packs left
I think there a lot of shops here that we can give these to
Let's try to finish it
In hope that there will be many people here, they feel motivated to complete their mission
I thought there would be a lot a people, not quite what I expected
Let's keep at it
They went to the night market to hand out tissues
Thank you very much
Fukuoka's team is the only one that has not finished yet, can they actualy do it ?
Still not finished...
It's 8:20 PM right now
We only have 20 minutes before the last flight
Next to the night market, there's a restaurant with many customers inside
As the members kept trying to power through their last tissues,
they encounter a big fan
Of course I'll support you !
Aitakatta kamoshirenai !
Thank you very much
They continue to hand out tissues on the street
Start sharing to passersby
50 tissues remaining
To get people in Fukuoka to remember Nogizaka46
they carry on with the PR
Thank you very much
We're from Nogizaka46
But the clock is ticking: 10 minutes left.
Thank you very much!
I'll definitely support all of you'
This is your last one ?
It is
Congratulations !
5 minutes remaining
She's adorable
I'm finaly finished~
Sayuri Inoue has finished distributing tissue
yatta! yatta!
Shiraishi also managed to do so
Our time in Fukuoka finaly ended
Actualy doing this made it feel even more rewarding
With this, I hope the debut will sell well
Hiroshima & Fukuoka Group has successfully distributed 1,150 tissue packs
Finaly finished within the time limit
Under members Team also participates in PR
www.ikuchancheeks.blogspot.com
Translator: Tamami46chan
Indo-Eng translation: DOZO