Translation, Timing & Typeset by DOZO
Nogizakatte Doko is starting
We're your hosts Bananaman, yoroshiku onegaishimasu
- Yoroshiku onegaishimasu !
And here are the members !
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
Alright, let's introduce our guest for today
It's Tsuka-chan !
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu
Shitara-san
Shitara-san !!
Don't start without me !
I'm here too, you know ?
It seems like Kaonashi has lost its way again !
[ Note: The black faceless ghost from Spirited Away ]
Drunk Dragon
Suzuki Taku
Stop going "Ah~"
Don't agree to it
Forcing it like that is just rude
Why are you guys doing it too !?
What's up with you...
It's the first time I heard you be so loud
Yey !!
Yeeey !!!
Woah !
That was good !
You did it for real
Very nice
Impressive
Himura, please announce today's agenda
[ Note: An 80's drama in which the main character stutters ]
in the style of Hadaka no Taishou
Who's got a thing for Konto ?
Nogizaka's Konto ability check !
Seeing idols trying their hand at Konto on a tv show
is something that has existed for a long time
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Search for idols who can do Konto
Let's check who's got some Konto ability !
AKB is pretty good at it too
AKB does it too
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Let's have Drunk Dragon show them the ropes.
The members will challenge taking the role of Tsukaji or Suzuki!
Drunk Dragon will show the members an example of a skit
and they will try to play the part of either Tsukaji or Suzuki
Let's see who's got a natural talent for Konto !
So first could you please show them the example skit
Yes
Onegaishimasu
Konto example n°1 "Shinkansen Announcer"
What is it ?
Dear customers, thank you for choosing to travel on our Shinkansen line
Thank you, very, very much !
Isn't he being way too thankful ?
This is the Nozomi 365 line, gonna go from Tokyo to Shin-Osaka station
Informal speech ?!
That's rude
We'll be stopping at Shinagawa, Shin-Yokohama....
Umm...
Shinagawa, Shin-Yokohama....
And other wonderful stations
Don't say it like you're doing great !
Please be respectful to the other passengers on board
Smoking is prohibited outside of the restaurant wagon
Finally he says something useful
Also, please never give up on your dreams !
I'd rather not hear that sort of things from you
Ah, the doors will be closing now
They were open all this time !?
Thank you very much
I think it would be better if you could, um...
Bring out the feel of a Shinkansen personnel a bit more
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Giving advice to the younger ones ?
Are you a judge ?!
Captain Sakurai will be the first to take on the challenge !
Dear customers, thank you for choosing to travel on our Shinkansen line
Thank you, very, very much !
Isn't he being way too thankful ?
Who was that ?
We'll be stopping at Shinagawa, Shin-Yokohama....
Umm...
Shinagawa, Shin-Yokohama....
And other wonderful stations
He's avoiding the subject...
Well then, please enjoy a comfortable travel across the skies
This isn't a plane though...
Ah, the doors will be closing now
They were open !?
That was good !
So how was it ?
It was pretty hard
I couldn't think of anything to say
You couldn't think of anything...
Was it embarassing ?
No I don't think it was that embarassing, but...
I couldn't think of anything really clever to say
What did you think of her ?
Since she showed some good emotion
It felt even better than when Suzuki does it
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Game over for Suzuki ?
Replacing Suzuki !
I just replaced Suzuki
Don't replace me just like that
Sakurai showed us some good emotions
She fared alright !
Next challenger will be Matsumura from the Kansai region
I don't remember Tsuka-chan looking so much like a goby
[ Note: A kind of fish ]
His face is really something else
His face is really weirding me out
Did you guys say something ?
We were saying your face is weird
Oh okay...
What ?!!
Dear customers, thank you for choosing to travel on our Shinkansen line
Thank you, very, very much
Isn't he being way too thankful ?
This is the Nozomi 365 line, gonna go from Tokyo to Shin-Osaka station
Ah, Osaka...
And informal speech !?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Nori Tsukkomi !
[ Note: Nori Tsukkomi - inserting quick & funny remarks in the midst of a conversation ]
We'll be stopping at Shinagawa, Shin-Yokohama....
And other wonderful stations
He actually forgot !!
Not bad !
To the car in the front, please stop !
What !? There's a car in front ?
Don't stay there !
So how was it ?
I think I wasn't able to fully overcome my shyness
During the slight ad-lib part
She was going along and nodding to what I was saying
This is something that Suzuki can't do
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Throwing punches at Suzuki yet again
Yeah I can't do the 'hmm' in between sentences
I can feel the Kansai roots...
She was pretty good
You did nori tsukkomi, right ?
Yeah she did
I think you were amazing
Oh my, thank you very much
I'm happy to hear it
Matsumura showed us her tsukkomi abilities
As expected of someone from Kansai !
Following up, we'll see more of everyone's own sensitivity
It's Takayama's turn !
Dear customers, thank you for choosing to travel on our Shinkansen line
Thank you, very, very much !
Isn't he being way too thankful ?
This is the Nozomi 365 line, gonna go from Tokyo to Shin-Osaka station
Eh !? Informal speech ? Eh?
We'll be stopping at Shinagawa, Shin-Yokohama....
Umm...
Shinagawa, Shin-Yokohama....
- You can do it, you can do it !
And other wonderful stations !
Don't dodge the issue !
Please give me back my wife !
Hang in there !
How was it ?
Well...
It's really hard to act natural
But, um...
I was nervous !
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
It was nervousness,
after all.
So you were nervous after all, huh
I was
Talk about being "so bad it's good"...
But when I said "give me back my wife" near the end
"Hang in there !"
I think she might be more the boke type...
That might be it
The members retort a lot to things I say
It seems she's leaning towards being a boke
They've prepared some more konto skits for today, so...
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Thank you very much.
It's here
Tsukaji-style Jumbled up Kenpo
*enters*
Excuse me !
Who the fuck just said the forbidden words "Excuse me" !!!
So someone was here...
What is it ?
I already paid for the last 7 months of electricity
I'm not from the electricity company
And isn't electricity something you pay for each month ?
But this is not what I'm here for
I want to learn kenpo
Oh, kenpo...
Alright you're admitted
Really ?
Have I lied even once in my entire life ?
Well..
It's the first time we meet so I wouldn't know...
Anyway, this is the Tsukaji-style Jumbled up Kenpo
Starting with the first stance
First stance !
Second stance !
Third stance !
Fourth stance !
Fifth stance !
Alright now from the start !
First !
Second !
Third !
Fourth !
Fifth !
Next person !
[ Note: play on words with kata, can mean 'stance', 'person', 'something hard'...]
What ?
Next person !
- Next person !
That's hard !!
What ?
That's hard !
Stop that !!
We're not doing stupid-style Kenpo !
That was so random !!
Since this skit is pretty fast-paced, I think they'll have a hard time inserting themselves
I think the best here is to not get caught up in the flow too much, refrain yourself from saying out of place things
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Doing something weird like this is scary
Can they do it while not going overboard ?
So act like an apprentice, don't retort too strongly
I see !
I think they'll feel pretty embarassed when doing it
But seeing them get embarassed can also make things more interesting
That's right
First up is one of the Seven Lucky Godesses
It's Shiraishi's turn !
What is it ?
I already paid for the last 7 months of electricity
No I'm not from the electricity company
And isn't electricity something you pay for each month ?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Friendly Tsukkomi
Anyway, this is the Tsukaji-style Jumbled up Kenpo
Starting with the first stance
First stance !
Second stance !
Third stance !
Fourth stance !
Fifth stance !
Alright now from the start !
First one !
Second !
It's "Sei Sei" !!
Third one !
Fourth !
Fourth one !
Fifth one, fifth one !
Fourth !
T- That's hard !!
H- Hard ?
Stop that right now !!
We're not doing stupid-style Kenpo !
How was it ?
It was fun !
Ah you had fun
What suprised me was,
I felt like a weird adult being persuaded by someone
Being like "You can't do this"
When she didn't know what to say
and went "uoooh!" that was funny too
Did you feel a bit overwhelmed by Tsukaji's loudness ?
Yeah I didn't really know how to react to it, so I went "oooh!!"
Suzuki could you say something a bit harsh to her ?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Does he dare to ?
Something harsh ?
Since you play the part too...
What did you think of her ?
You can tell she knows what he will say next
Even though she did her best
But it's true
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Real advice
Yeah it's true
Acting natural and innocent is very important
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Even though you know what's coming
you need to act as if hearing it for the first time.
Since it is something you've written yourself
Act as if it's the first time, even though you know it all
That's how it should be done
Why'd do get so serious about it ?
He asked me to !!
Try to act it out less obviously !
Next is the mysterious Saito Yuri
There it was ! Tsukaji-style Jumbled Up Kenpo
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Laid back style
What is it ?
I already paid for the last 7 months of electricity
I'm not from the electricity company !
Do I look like it !?
Anyways !
I want to learn the Jumbled up Kenpo !
Oh, Kenpo...
Yes !
Alright, you're admitted !
Really !? I'm so happy !
Have I lied even once in my entire life ?
Nope !
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Negative answer even though
it's their first meeting
First stance !
Second !
Third !
Fourth !
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Sexy moves
First one !
Second one !
Third one !
Fourth one !
Stop it !!
This isn't Stupid-style Kenpo !!
Aren't you the one at fault !?
How was it ?
The "chotto" part was weird !
The chotto was...
Kind of erotic, wasn't it
No way, I didn't do it like that !
Fourth stance.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Sexy trainee
Isn't it exactly how you did it before !
Right after, Ikuta Erika's talent for Konto is discovered !?
This time
you'll try to play Tsukaji's part
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
The members will challenge Tsukaji's Boke role !
Do the skit with Suzuki
Hey
Hey you
Yes ?
We'll begin the interview in just a moment
Even though it will be live,
there's no reason to be nervous
No problem, I'm fine
I'll just do a short intro and then I'm onto you
- Understood
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu
Oh, we're going on-air already ?
Good afternoon everyone !
I'm here in Saitama prefecture, at Yamada middle school
to visit the Japanese Game Research Club
without further ado, let's have a word with the president of the club, Tsukaji-kun
So, Tsukaji-kun, can you tell us what this club is about ?
Yes.
We, at the Japanese Games Research Club,
Noticed the modern days trend of indoor entertainment such as video games, films, karaoke...
So we looked back at how our ancestors used to entertain themselves
In other words, enjoying outside activites is what we do
As the saying goes:
"In old things-"
...
And that's basically it
Umm...
It seems we couldn't hear everything because of a little problem with the microphone
But I'm sure that he meant to say, "In old things, we find new knowledge"
Can you tell us how they used to play, back in the days ?
Yes
We, at the Japanese Games Research Club,
Noticed the modern days trend of indoor entertainment such as video games, films, karaoke...
- You already said that...
So we looked back at how our ancestors used to entertain themselves
In other words, enjoying outside activites is what we do
As the saying goes:
In old things-
we find new knowledge !
I'm glad you managed to say it
See you next week !
Thank you very much
So you'll be playing the role of Tsuka-chan
Gotta pay attention to your face, the pauses...
The way you talk...
- And there's a lot of lines !
Is there anything specific they should know beforehand ?
You have to capture that emotionlessness, that feel of someone just reading text
We've all seen these tv shows where they interview some random kid
and he's obviously uncomfortable and acts weird
I hope the members can portray that
15 years old Ikuta Erika will tackle this new challenge !
Good afternoon everyone !
I'm here in Saitama prefecture, at Yamada middle school
to visit the Japanese Game Research Club
We have the club president here with us today, Ikuta-san.
Let's have a word with her.
So, Japanese Games Research Club, can you tell us what it is ?
Yes ! Um..
We, at the Japanese Games Research Club,
In a world where video games...
Am I speaking too fast ?
Basically we try to go against the grain and revive outdoor activities
Umm...
As the saying goes:
"In old things-"
Well...
It seems we couldn't hear everything because of a little problem with the microphone
But I'm sure that she meant to say, "In old things, we find new knowledge"
And, um..
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Emotionless
Is there anything more you can tell us about the club ?
Ikuta-san...
Ikuta-san !
We, at the Japanese Games Research Club,
Noticed the modern days trend of indoor entertainment, television, and...
We've heard that already...
In other words, we aim to practice outdoor activities
As the saying goes:
"In old things we find new knowledge"
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
"I did it" Face.
See you next week !
That emotionless face, she really pulled it off
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Emotionless
Yeah she had that perfect blank stare, that was good
Well then, Tsuka-chan...
Please say something a little harsh to her
Right
Basically she completely
ignored the point of the skit (the nervous character)
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Completely different characters !!
That's super harsh !
Apologize !
So harsh !!
Right after, Nogizaka46 new unit announcement !?
The 2nd Single will be released on May 2nd
And it contains a track where 4 of you sing
Who are the 4 people ?
The 4 of you sing it ?
Yes
And what's the title ?
Guuzen wo iiwake ni shite
(Using an accident as an excuse)
And what's kind of song would that be ?
As far as songwriting goes
It sounds like it could be used as an anime opening
It gets you hype ?
Hype ?
Kinda like when your focused on a game ?
Ah, well, I'm not so sure about that...
Forget it, I'll just listen to it !
I'm excited for it
Guuzen wo iiwake ni shite
Atarashii sekai knock wo shiyou ka ?
Kinou to wa chigau itoshisa no katachi
hisashiburi no shibuya wo burabura to
PARCO atari aruiteru toki ni
sure chigatta bimyou na Johnny Depp
masaka konna toko de battari nante ne
campus de attemo
kitto hanashi kakerarenai
hisoka ni akogareteru
anata ga konna ni chikaku ni iru no nara
hitsuzen wa nakanaka konai
kitto junban machi da
jibun de tsukamu shikanai yo
hitsuzen wa nakanaka konai
odoroita you ni koe wo ageyou ka ?
ima kara hajimaru kono koi no domino
kouen touri koko de atta
kakuritsu wa arienai yo ne
jijitsu wa kami-sama no okuri mono nanda
ganbare jibun yo
hitsuzen nakanaka konai
odoroita you ni koe wo ageyou ka ?
ima kara hajimaru kono koi no domino
I see
It was cute
Next week, we'll show the 2nd Single in the studio !
Wonderful !
Can everyone please announce the title of the 2nd Single ?
Let's hear it
One, two...
Oide Shampoo !!
Oide Shampoo ?
So it's not Guru Guru something ?
I thought you were doing a Guru Guru series
- They don't have to Guru Guru everything
And so, the 2nd Single will be released in full version next week !
To celebrate the good reception of Guru Guru Curtain
Nogizaka will be holding handshake events all over Japan !
Supported by many fans in various places
The girls are looking forward to the release of their 2nd Single
However, there's a problem...
That is...
Turmoil in the entertainment world !
Nogizaka46's 2nd Single
Sashihara Rino's Solo Single
"I swear its not a marketing stunt!" - Aki-P
Violating the unspoken rule: Releasing the same day !!
Basically, she suddenly announced the release date of her Single
It started talk about her wanting to rival with Nogizaka46
Interim Captain Sakurai said:
"She wants to be seen as our rival, so I'll give it to her"
"I want results"
is her narrative
In reponse, Sashiraha said...
Speaking about Nogizaka46...
Sashihara-san
It seems that my Solo Single is to be released on the same day as Nogizaka's Single...
Oh my !
Of course, Mii-chan, I can count on your support, right ?
Yeah for sure ! You can count on me for supporting Nogizaka-
- Eh ?
Then Yukirin, you'll support me, right ?
- Yep ! I'll support Nogizaka !
Eh ? Wait a minute...
But what about the public ? Who will you guys support ?
"Nogizaka !!"
- Hey !!
Nogizaka
Wait a second...
Don't worry I've thought about it, I think that with the help of Maeda-san and Yuuko-san, there's no doubt that it will sell well !
Sashihara... !
You coward !
But that's why... !
We love you !!!
Much obliged
Thank you very much
She thinks it'll be an easy win
Both parties are showing excitement
30 days until the fateful release date !