アイDOL
www.myAidol.net
On tonight's Nogizakatte Doko, the members will be doing their first pranks.
With everything secretly filmed, will we see members slip in some inside stories?
There will also be a prank for a secret guest!
Nogizaka tte Doko?
[Following orders, there will be harsh pranks from member to member.]
[Let's trap the secret guest with a prank!]
Here we go! This is Nogizakatte Doko? We're the MC, Banana Man. Great to have you here!
Banana Man
Himura Yuki
Shitara Osamu
And here we have Nogizaka46!
We'd usually introduce a guest here...
...but right now, there's no one.
- Yeah, no one's here.
And well, you'll all come to understand soon enough.
Guest Absence?
Himura-san, can you announce what we're doing today in an astonished fashion?
- Okay.
Nogizaka46's...
...first time pranking!
Himura-san, you've been pranked on countless of times, right?
In the whole year of 2006 alone, I was pranked 24 times!
- What!?
I was pranked so many times.
He was pranked 2 times per month.
- Yes, that much.
And I was on the pranking side on all of those pranks.
- That's right.
It's quite difficult, being the one who does the prank.
For the one being pranked, they can just continue on without a clue.
But if the person pranking stuffs up, it's all over.
- Yeah.
You have to make the situation more normal than usual.
So today you'll be doing a dry run.
- Oh! That's a good idea!
To test things out a bit.
- I see, that does seem interesting.
This next prank will involve a cream puff filled with mustard.
A regular cream puff will be switched with a mustard-filled one.
They will then make the target eat it.
They will need to distract the target while they nimbly switch the cream puffs.
It will depend on how naturally they can get the target to eat it.
The first pranking target is Ikuta Erika!
These 4 have been called to record a small show.
But everyone other than Ikuta will be the ones pranking.
Hey look here, we've got our snacks!
Ikuta: I already had a bunch of small cream puffs earlier.
- What!?
I ate a bunch of them...
Then Ikuta, you don't need any, right?
- Well...
Don't need any?
- I guess I do.
Tasty Cream Puff
But this is a regular, tasty cream puff.
Mustard-filled Cream Puff
Their mission is to switch with the cream puff behind Saito Yuri's chair then make Ikuta eat it. However...!
Itadakima~su!
Ikuta straight away wants to eat the normal cream puff!
It is in this dire situation that Iwase acts!
Itadakima~su!
Forcefully stopping her.
Saito: You can't do that Ikuchan! You've already had 2!
Don't do it, Ikuchan!
Everyone blocks.
You all have some left, right?
No, none at all!
Ikuchan, don't!
- This looks bad.
They won't be able to switch it.
- Will the ones downstairs not have enough?
Let's eat.
- Someone should hold out.
I want to leave some for the others downstairs.
So just tell them only two are left.
And two members will share one.
Misinformation?
No!
Ikuta: So I'll have some first.
Then Iwase will be next.
At this point Saito Yuri grabs the mustard-filled cream puff near her feet...
And amazingly, Miyazawa and Iwase move at the same time, completely blocking Ikuta's view.
With an incredible display of teamwork, they follow Saito Yuri's lead.
Mustard-filled Cream Puff
Iwase, will you have this one?
- For the time being we'll do...
Anyway...
- Iwase.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Why did you take mine away?
We want to eat a lot of them!
Here, I'll give you mine.
See?
How immature.
Mustard-filled Cream Puff
Nicely done!
- Bravo!
Mustard-filled Cream Puff
Somehow you girls managed well.
With force, they've managed to get the mustard-filled cream puff in front of Ikuta.
All they need to do now is make her eat it. However...
-What? She won't eat it?
Go on, eat it.
I'll have the one Iku-san ate then...
Then what was with the switching before?
- Right?
Suspicious of the Unnaturalness.
I guess we took it.
-  Ehehe~
EHEHE~~
Desperate Comeback.
Yeah. Before they were like, "You can't!" and now they want her to eat it.
Gazing Suspiciously.
It's okay, go ahead and eat it.
Let's eat together.
Let's just have 1 each.
This is getting bothersome.
It's becoming awkward, right?
- Can I have half of yours, Yumiko?
Sure, you can eat first.
Oh, she's going for it.
- You can have half.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
What's up?
It's spicy!
- What's wrong?
What's wrong?
Ikuta, what's wrong?
Ikuta-chan!
Saito: She's even wiping her mouth!
Cleaning even her tongue.
That was mean, Yuttan!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- I wanted to eat a tasty one.
But, Ikuchan.
Ready, and...
Successful Prank!
- WHAT!?
What's going on!?
Argh!!!
We did it!!
Geez!
And there we have it.
A prank which involved making someone eat a mustard-filled cream puff.
- I see.
Yeah.
Ikuta, did you think that something was off?
I thought that something was strange in the middle because they switched.
That was the hardest part, right?
- Yeah.
Like she tried to eat it, then Iwase grabbed her.
I just had to stop it.
Okay, there are still more.
In fact, this one is still going on.
Oh, really?
- Yeah.
There are people here who have been pranked, but they have no idea.
m 0 0 l 400 0 l 400 60 l 0 60
m 40 0 l 80 0 l 40 70 l 0 70 m 120 0 l 160 0 l 120 70 l 80 70 m 200 0 l 240 0 l 200 70 l 160 70 m 280 0 l 320 0 l 280 70 l 240 70 m 360 0 l 400 0 l 360 70 l 320 70
A prank not revealed is still
going on with some members
What do you mean?
The prank is still going on.
- What?
So they've done something, but still don't know what it was for?
They still haven't done the "Successful Prank!" thing.
- Oh!
All alone, the instigator asks for advice on how to deal with the fake situation of "I was asked to have a meal with Banana Man's Himura."
By suddenly being asked,
how will the target respond?
No! This is bad!
Takayama is the first target. While Nakada is the prankster.
Leaving the two alone, the prank starts!
Actually, the other day...
I don't want people talking about it though...
But... I had gone alone to the departmental store get packed lunch...
- Yeah.
And I thought of returning quickly...
Yeah.
- And when I came out of there,
At that time...
I bumped into Bananaman's Himura-san there...
And he invited me to go out for dinner some time,
And we have the recording for the show on Tuesday, right?
- Yeah.
So what should I do?
There's nothing to worry about.
If I was asked to go, should I go?
I'd want to go. I want to chat in private.
Not talking to him from far away, but to have a normal chat close up.
What do you think of Himura-san?
I don't care about him, but I want to chat with Shitara-san.
Shitara Supporter Confirmed.
Nice.
Next up is Shiraishi. The instigator this time is Sakurai.
There's a chance she'll say something awful, don't you think?
No, please don't!
Hey, you know.
This is something that I can only say to you. Please don't tell anyone.
After filming NogiDoko the other day...
I bumped into Himura-san while heading out.
-Oh.
And there...
...he asked if I wanted to go and have a meal with him.
What!? He asked you?
- Yeah.
Isn't that dangerous?
Himura is dangerous.
"Himura is dangerous."
Ah! That's scary!
- Scary, right!
Himura is scary.
As the older sister of the group, what would you do?
If it were me who was asked by Himura-san, I don't think I would go.
Declined.
But if it was Shitara-san instead...
Pwned by Shitara within the Prank.
If it was Shitara-san, I'd go.
- Seriously!?
The last target is Matsumura. This time, the instigator is Hashimoto.
I was alone.
- This might be a good laugh.
Then I bumped into Himura-san while leaving.
And then...
...he asked if I wanted to have a meal.
- Okay.
I'm not sure what to think.
That shouldn't be allowed, right? How did it go?
But he wouldn't give dirty looks to the others?
Did he give you dirty looks?
Eyes judging secret intentions.
Dirty look?
Dirty looks?
But if you had to say...
Do you see Himura-san...
...as a guy?
I don't.
I do see Shitara-san as one though.
Himura: 3 losses.
But that's if I had to choose between the two.
Well.
With this last prank...
Other than the 3, there is another who became severely torn apart.
I'm sorry!
- Yeah.
So, you've all found out just now, right?
This is the second block of shooting.
In the first block we had the targets...
...think that "This guy asked her out!" right?
Why? Is it that bad having a meal with Himura?
It's not!
All I said was, "Want to get something to eat?" right?
When asked "Want to get something to eat?" in such a situation,  you might think, "What kind of meal is it?"
"Some disgusting meal?"
Yeah, it'll be scary, so scary like AAAAHH!!!
But the fact that it's only the two...
- Oh, is that why?
Yeah, because it'd be only the two of us.
But I really like you a lot!
Declaration of Favoritism.
Wait, wait.
Don't respond with such serious remarks.
Already Too Late.
But I really do like you.
- That's enough.
Actually, we have one more prank for today.
And today we'll be having you girls become the instigators.
We didn't have a guest this time, right?
- Nope.
We'll actually be having you prank our guest for today.
That's how it will go down.
Who will be the guest that will get pranked today?
m 0 0 l 325 0 l 325 40 l 0 40
Kojima Kazuya (Anjasshu)
Today's target is an ordinary person, right?
That's wrong.
- Oh, it is?
Is that Kojima-san?
Kojima was brought in to film for a fake show.
He is currently in a cafe, discussing the details for the fake show.
It is in this place where the members will have hidden earpieces and will chat with him.
While receiving orders from Banana Man, they will have to do the pranks without raising any suspicion.
The first one up is Takayama Kazumi.
While in the meeting, the director leaves.
It is there where Takayama pretends to bump into him and introduces herself.
Take a seat for now.
Please excuse me.
Say, "There's something I want to ask."
Um, there's something I'd like to ask.
"3 stripes today, right?"
Ah! You're wearing 3 stripes today, right?
Yeah.
That's not an insult.
Finding fault with her insult.
Yeah, it is 3 stripes.
"It's 2 stripes!"
2 stripes. Oh! It's 2 stripes!
It's 3! Yeah, like that.
Was the one now good?
- Yeah, it was.
"Can I please ask you for a big favor?"
Can I please ask you for a big favor?
"Please give me some gag."
- Um...
Please give me a gag.
A gag?
- Do you have any?
I don't have any.
What's your full name?
- Ah! It's Takayama Kazumi.
Takayama Kazumi. Then I'll make a gag based on your name.
- Okay.
Oh! A gag based on my name? Thank you so much!
Can you act like you're dozing off?
Takayama...
- Please act like you're dozing off.
Dozing in Action!
Just don't use it all over the place.
- Ah!
Did you sleep just now? Were you listening?
- "I've been really busy!"
I've been really busy.
- Are you alright?
I'm fine.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'm Kazumin! Ze ze ze ze zei!
- Oh, nice one!
- That one was good.
- Oh, really?
Now do it once really loud.
I'M KAZUMIN! ZE ZE ZE ZE ZEI!
- Shh!
Don't Be Noisy.
Say, "Thank you so much. I look forward to working with you today."
Thank you so much. Please excuse me.
Sorry for disturbing you. But I look forward to working with you later.
Say, "2 Stripes, right?"
2 Stripes, right?
- It's 3!
Embarrassment.
Kojima is acting naturally. So far he doesn't suspect anything yet.
The Dance Version PV for Nogizaka's 2nd Single "Oide Shampoo" (release date: 2nd May) has been completed!
Please take your time enjoying it.
After Takayama left, the meeting for the fake show with Kojima continued.
The next instigator heading towards Kojima is Ikuta.
Nice to meet you, Kojima-san.
- Same here.
Do your self-introduction.
I'm Ikuta Erika from Nogizaka46.
Pleased to meet you.
Right after she introduced herself, the director leaves once again.
Say that you're a fan.
I'm a really big fan of yours.
"I like the way you aimlessly act as the boke (funny man)."
Um... I like the way you do the boke (funny man).
My boke?
- Yes, boke.
Tell him, "You've been saying "Oi, you!" a lot recently."
You've been saying "Oi, you!" a lot recently, right?
And "Oi!"
- And stuff like "Oi!"
Well, yeah.
- I really like that.
- But that's not being a boke though.
"Snapping at someone's performance" is not being a boke.
"When would you use that technique?"
What should I say to get you to say those things?
"I..." Facing me like this...
- Okay.
If you said something like, "I'm a really big fan of yours, Watabe-san!"
- Ohh.
"Watabe-san!" "Watabe-san!"
Watabe-san!
I'm Kojima! Oh! I forgot to do that.
A normal response.
"Can I say something harsh?"
Can I say something harsh?
- Yeah, yeah.
"Your face is weird!"
Your face is weird!
Oi!
Successfully Made Happen.
"I'm so happy!"
- Ah! I'm so happy to hear that!
"Your face is weird!"
- Your face is weird!
Oi!
- "Ah! I'm so happy!"
Coming up, the instructions escalate! When will Kojima realize it's a prank?
"I passed the entrance exam and made it into senior high."
Starting from spring, I'll be in senior high. I passed the entrance exam.
- Congratulations.
"I passed."
I passed.
"I'm a big fan of yours."
- Um...
And because I'm a big fan...
"Please give me a congratulatory gift for making it."
Please give me a congratulatory gift for making it in.
- Congratulatory gift for making it!?
Yeah.
- What's a congratulatory gift for making it?
Please give me a congratulatory gift for making it through.
- What's that?
Anything is fine!
- Even if I were to give you something...
"Money is fine."
- Money is fine.
You don't usually give money for that.
- No.
But I did get money from my grandma.
- But that...
But that's because you're relatives.
But I'd definitely want to get money from you.
- "Your face is weird!"
Your face is weird!
- Oi!
Ah! I'm so glad!
"Then give me those clothes."
Then give me those clothes.
- But the thing is...
I just bought this.
- "That 2 striped one."
That 2 striped one.
It's 3 stripes.
- Oh?
Oh, it really is!
- "Are you angry?"
"Are you angry?"
Are you angry at me?
- What?
I'm not angry.
- No, I'm sorry.
"Your face is..."
- No problems.
I mean, but... your face... is...
...weird!
- Oi!
But you are angry.
I'm not angry.
- I'm sorry.
"Did you have a meeting just now?"
Did you have a meeting?
- Yeah, I did.
"And it seems like we're hard pressed for time."
And we're hard pressed for time.
"We had individual song recordings..."
We had like, song recordings individually...
Because we'll be having a lot of different units and all...
"And in order to do the recordings for that song..."
You've been doing that since the morning, right?
- That is right.
"We've been doing it since 3 AM today."
We've been doing it since 3 AM today...
WHAT?!
- Yeah.
Believed.
"Shall we go and see?"
- We've been at it for many hours.
You have that in your Music Videos, right?
"Why don't we have a look at the studio?"
- Why don't we have a look at the studio?
"Actually, all the members are big fans of you."
Everyone is a big fan of yours...
And so, Ikuta drags Kojima into the studio.
Attaching a mic through force.
Ready, and...
Your face is weird!
OI!
The hell's going on?
And so they revealed that all those things were just part of a prank.
You've got to be kidding me...
Our guest for today was Anjasshu's Kojima-san! Thank you so much!
End of Appearance.
Thank you very much!
Okay then, take it away, Takayama!
I'm Kazumi! Ze ze ze ze zei!
- What the...
See you next week!
Kojima's Gag Fails.
Okay, that's it.
- Good work today everyone!
It's over?
- Yep, it is.
Is it seriously over?
- Thanks for today.
Is it really over?
I'm not the sound technician!
Thank you for your hard work.
Why is everyone leaving so hurriedly?
What's going on?!
This is terrible!!
Coming up, Nogizaka46 and Sashihara will have a full-blown showdown!
May 2nd, 2012. Judgement Day.
Nogizaka46's 2nd single, "Oide Shampoo" on sale!
AKB48, Sashihara Rino's solo debut single, "Sore de mo suki da yo" on sale!
Which will you choose?
On April 11, Sashihara made an appearance at the press conference for "Muse no Kagami the Movie".
Her first starring role.
She made a strong showing, fueling reporters' questions, promoting the film to the world.
Meanwhile, Nogizaka46 held a fan event with enthusiastic supporters in Nagoya.
They performed to a cheering audience of 2000 people.
Receiving a passionate welcome, they secured their constituency in the Nagoya and Tokai districts.
Both sides continue their fierce competition.
16 days until Judgement Day!
Which will you choose?
Next time, we'll be checking on the members' modeling abilities.
An eruption of laughter at Takayama's posing!?
Next week, we'll be having a check on the members' modeling abilities.
Joy
They will test themselves to see how well they portray joy, anger, pathos and charm.
Anger
How well will the results of learning turn out?
Pathos
Wow!
- Nice!
What were you thinking of at that time?
If my mom died.
- Wow.
I can say "Butadon" in a sexy fashion.
[Next week: Check out Nogizaka's members' modeling ability!]
[Who will be the top member?]
Tamori
Will Hashimoto's imitation of Tamori appear once again?