Nogizaka46's going strong currently with a 2nd place on Oricon Chart.
But the unexpected results shocked the members once again.
Last week right before the show ended,
With that, the second single is coming soon.
So for the next week,
second single's members senbatsu announcement!
That's fast.
Tonight, the announcement for the second single's senbatsu.
What changes will happen to the members?
Everyone kept crying after each announcement.
Nogizakatte, Doko?
Credits: NeruestSub
Sub: Coffee-san
Sub: SDD-san
Timing: MarryMe_Ikuchan
Proofreading: SashiharaSaiko
Nogizaka46's second single's
member senbatsu announcement!!!!
Their second single will be similar to "Guruguru Curtain."
It's going to be Shichifukujin plus another 9 members.
So the Shichifukujin are sitting in front together.
Yes, the previous Shichifukujin and the 9 senbatsu members behind them.
A few of them are already crying.
What kind of tears are they shedding?
Probably a mixture of nervousness and emotional complexity.
So we're going to connect with the backstage right now.
Everyone! Can you all hear me!!?
We can.
Must be really nervous right? Your heart must be racing right now.
Let's start the announcement of the second single's senbatsu.
The method of announcing the result.
The member that was selected first is going to call the next selected member...
Because there's no first member yet, so I'm going to announce the first one.
The Nogizaka46's Management Team will explain the whole senbatsu.
So let's begin,
there's a lot of envelopes over here.
So, the first envelope.
Oh! I have goosebump already.
The first member,
during the previous senbatsu, she cried when she was shocked by the result.
After that, she began to work hard as the temporary leader.
She received a lot of good comments, Sakurai Reika.
Congratulations, Sakurai!
So she came back into the Shichifukujin once again, right?
Yes, she was in the first Shichifukujin.
The first member is Sakurai Reika, who dropped out from the Shichifukujin during their debut single.
Now, she's back.
Good for you.
Honestly, it was very painful for me to drop out from it.
You dropped out from the Shichifukujin for the first single.
Please continue to do your best.
-Thank you. -Congratulations.
So, there's another important stuff.
Inside this is a member's name.
Please announce the next senbatsu member.
Although you were restless at the beginning,
it must be hard for you to be the center all of a sudden!
You did it very well, let's continue to work hard!
Ikoma Rina.
She has shown everyone the responsibility and confidence of a real center!
Ikoma Rina entered the Shichifukujin.
Standing here as a center,
it was the first time for me to work with confidence.
Rather than saying I'm one of Shichifukujin for sure,
instead, I think it's the motif of wanting to be in it.
I'll continue to do my best.
Yes, very strong indeed. You found your confidence while leading the group.
You've changed, Ikoma.
Next up the third member, please announce it.
She can create a happy atmosphere whenever she goes,
she also has very unique ways to prove her own existence.
Takayama Kazumi-san!
It's Takayama! -Congratulations!
With her very unique's character,
she entered the Shichifukujin!
Everyone worked really hard to become the Shichifukujin.
So every time I heard that,
I can really felt everyone's improvements.
Because of that I felt pressured every day.
To become a unique idol, I'll not waste this chance.
I'll do my best.
4 members left for the Shichifukujin.
She worked really hard. I'm not joking, I think she's a great member!
She has great dance skill.
Let's do our best together,
Nakada Kana!
Ohh! Nakada's also in the Shichifukujin!
With her amazing dancing skill, she came back into Shichifukujin!
-Congratulations! -Must be happy, right?
I dropped out from the Shichifukujin last time,
this time I'll be sure to take this chance and continue to work hard!
The next member's name is here.
So there'll be two Shichifukujin that's going to drop out.
Although she was a dance beginner, she worked really hard.
So she can dance well now, she's very happy too!
Matsumura Sayuri-san.
Ah! Matsumura!
Active as a Shichifukujin, Matsumura continued to be in the Shichifukujin once more!
When I was picked to become the Shichifukujin last time,
I thought that my dancing was very bad when I danced in the front row.
But I'm still in the front row, is that suitable?
So to prove that it's ok for me to take this position,
I'll continue to do my best!
Next member, please announce it.
There are still two Shichifukujin members.
Although she did not do very well at the beginning,
but she's very hardworking, let's do our best together.
Hashimoto Nanami.
Oh! It's Hashimoto!
A unique existence member, Hashimoto continued to be in the Shichifukujin!
Honestly, I did not know what will happen to me this time.
I thought about it a lot, and I evaluated myself during the backstage.
I'll do my best with everyone for the second single.
With that, the last Shichifukujin member in this envelope.
It's the last slot for Shichifukujin!
A position that everyone had always looked forward to.
She tried to improve herself at all time,
and she never gives up.
She had been working hard with a mature heart.
Only one of the three previous Shichifukujin will be chosen!
Only one slot left, who's it going to be?
She tried to improve herself at all time,
and she never gives up.
She had been working hard with a mature heart.
Speaking as a female too, I really respect her.
Shiraishi Mai.
-So, it's decided. -Yes, it's confirmed.
Last Shichifukujin is Shiraishi Mai who has great strength.
I'll continue to work hard, and I'll not stop so I can be better.
I'll continue to do my best!
Congratulations!
So Shiraishi's in the Shichifukujin once more.
The last 9 senbatsu members will be announced right now.
She worked harder than the others,
let's continue to work hard together too.
Inoue Sayuri.
Even if she was not in the Shichifukujin, she made it into the senbatsu.
During the debut single, I did not make it into Shichifukujin.
This time I failed to go in once more,
it's probably because I did not work hard enough,
that's why this happened.
Well, it's not easy to say you worked hard, but we can only continue to work hard now.
-Do your best! -I will.
Thank you.
Congratulations! Do your best.
Now, the next senbatsu member.
She's very kind and always trying to cheer the other members up.
Thank you for everything you did.
Saito Yuri.
A cheerful member that always make the other happy, Saito Yuri.
She entered the senbatsu once more!
I actually have no self-confident at all,
so I'll work harder than everyone's expectation on me.
Only 7 senbatsu members left.
Ummm, I learned a lot from her as I did not know how to dance at all,
finally, she's in the senbatsu with me so I'm really happy.
Let's continue to work hard together!
Miyazawa Seira.
Miyazawa! Sugoi!
-It's Miyazawa! -Miyazawa Seira!
She did not make it during last time,
Miyazawa Seira finally makes it into the senbatsu.
I did not make it into "Guruguru Curtain's" senbatsu,
as an under member, I felt really discouraged.
So I'll do my best since I'm in.
Well sorry if it's all of a sudden,
but the staff is currently calling Miyazawa's mother.
Of course, your mother still has no idea about the senbatsu yet.
-Is it her mother? -Yes!
About the second single, your daughter made it into the senbatsu.
Ah, is that so?
That's great Sei-chan, congratulations!
That's good, right?
Very good, do keep up the good work!
Keep encourage yourself.
Thank you, sorry to disturb you.
Thank you very much.
Last 6 slot left, will there be any first timer just like Miyazawa?
It was very hard to take care of both her study and idol career.
She always studied hard before the lessons.
I really respect her.
Ichiki Reina.
Oh! Ichiki! Congratulations!
Ichiki Reina who has to take care of her study too, she made it in again.
I'll cherish the opportunity to stand here from today onward.
Hardworking and believing myself really do payback! I'll work hard!
She continued to smile even if she's not happy.
She loves to eat tasty food!
She was really cute when she said that she was on a diet.
From the under and now in the senbatsu. Congratulations!
Let's work hard together!
Hatanaka Seira.
-Hatakana! -Hatakana's here! Incredible!
She did not make it into the senbatsu last time,
but she's always cheerful, and now she's in the senbatsu.
You entered.
How do you feel now?
I'm not happy during the last senbatsu because I didn't make it.
Even if my family and fans were cheering for me.
I'm really sorry. But I made it now and I'll do my best.
Actually, Hatakana's mom's on the line now.
Can you hear us?
Moshi moshi~~
What a hearty voice! Hi, we're Bananaman.
The result of the second single senbatsu is here.
Your daughter entered the senbatsu.
Ah! Thank you very much! I'm really happy!
Congratulations, Seira!
-Thank you! -That's great!
Don't forget to appreciate the fans and the staffs ok?
Do continue to work hard from today onward too!
-I understand. -We're cheering for you!
Also please tell Bananaman I'm their hardcore fan!
Thank you!
I'll continue to teach her from today onward!
Thank you for the hard work! I'm a fan too!
Only 4 slots left with the new senbatsu members,
will there be more new entries? Who's gonna be the 13th member?
She arrived in Tokyo just not long ago, and she felt worried.
But she worked really hard, Nishino Nanase.
With her fashion sense and her drawing skill, Nishino Nanase entered the senbatsu!
I worked really hard when I entered the previous senbatsu because I wanted to do my best. That's great.
Currently, there's still two first single's Shichifukujin left,
Ikuta and Hoshino who haven't been called yet.
Only 3 slots left!
We smiled together even if we faced hardship,
I'm really happy that we entered the senbatsu together.
Congratulations, Hoshino Minami.
Hoshino! She entered too! Congratulations Hoshino!
Hoshino Minami, the center for "Guruguru Curtain."
Although she dropped out from the Shichifukujin, she still entered the senbatsu.
I was happy when I was in the Shichifukujin, but I also had a lot of pressure.
But I'm still happy that I entered the senbatsu.
I'll continue to do my best!
The 16th senbatsu slot for the second single.
There are still 4 members that were in the first senbatsu.
But there are only 2 slots left, who is it going to be?
She worked really hard and taught me a lot.
She worked hard as a Shichifukujin too, and I want to say thank you.
Let's work hard together!
Ikuta Erika.
Ikuta. She was only mentioned until now.
One of the center previously, 16 years old Ikuta Erika.
As a former Shichifukujin, she entered the senbatsu.
So you dropped out from the Shichifukujin this time.
I'm very sad. Very sad.
Do work hard to go back into the Shichifukujin.
Congratulations!
-Now, the last slot. -The Last slot!
Only one slot left for the senbatsu, will it be a new entry or not?
She took care of me like a big sister.
She's kind and nice to talk to.
She supported everyone from the start.
Thank you very much our eldest member,
Iwase Yumiko.
Iwase's here!
The last to enter is the eldest member, Iwase Yumiko.
She's like a big sister for the members, and she had always support the members.
Congratulations!
I worked really hard for the next senbatsu with the other members,
everyone worked really hard.
I was really happy when my name was mentioned.
That's great.
And someone's on the phone now.
Nani? Nani? Nani?
-Ummm, ma'am. -You're joking right!?
We're recording a show right now,
and the result of the 16th senbatsu member for second single is here.
Your daughter entered!
Thank you very much! Yumi, congratulations!
You worked really hard, congratulations!
Your mother knew you worked really hard.
-Yes. -That's good.
-Thank you very much -You're welcome, thank you too.
So over here, are the senbatsu members for second single.
And here, we're going to reveal the 3 Centers.
The formation for the second single is the same as the "Guruguru Curtain."
3 as center, 4 members on second row and 9 members on third row.
After this, the 3 centers will be revealed!
Who's it going to be?
There's another envelope over here,
and the names for the 3 centers is inside.
Ikoma Rina.
Second center, Sakurai Reika.
Third center, Nakada Kana.
So they're the center for the second single.
So here's the formation for it!
So please do your best!
And there's another big announcement!
The second single will be on sale on the 2nd of May!
If it's on 2nd of May, Nogizaka's official rival
AKB48's Sashihara-san is going to release her solo single on that day too.
So, please win! I believe in you guys.