--------------------------------------------------
On this day, Himura invites Ikoma to go shopping.
But a trio of Himura haters invades the recording.
What are you doing here?
What makes Shiraishi cry?
And what prediction did Sakana-chan make that made the senbatsu members panic?
Nogizakatte Doko! We are the hosts, Bananaman.
And for today,
We have the selected senbatsu members for the 3rd single present.
There are some new faces present and the seating arrangement is different.
Himura-san, please say the title of our event today,
Okay!
with a happy feeling
-I understand!
Buy clothes for Ikoma! Himura and Ikoma go shopping!
Before, when we had a clothes check, we found that Ikoma wears a lot of pants.
That's not good for an idol, she needs to wear a cute skirt,
So Himura-san offered to help buy you clothes.
How was the result?
I didn't expect it to be true.
You really went?
I did.
We went immediately.
Just the two of you?
Let's wait and see the VTR.
Huh? Why?
Buy clothes for Ikoma!
Ah, it fell down.
Microphone disappears
You did it too strongly.
Their destination is the fashion center Laforet in Harajuku.
Today, Himura will but Ikoma cute idol-like clothes.
I'm buying.
-I understand.
I use my personal money. See, I brought my own wallet.
Your real one?
Personal luxury wallet
This is 100% my real one.
Really?
Really!
Yuki Himura
-Ah, it's true!
This was a gift from Shitara-san.
Just when Himura thought it would be just him and Ikoma, 3 more members appear.
Why are you here?
It was supposed to be just me and Ikoma.
There's no need for you.
But looking back, thinking about Himura-san, Shitara-san said that...
You intend to persuade me?
So the three of them accompanied them with the shopping.
What about here?
Cute.
Well, Ikoma?
I think I'll try it.
The first shop, Crisp, is for girly and natural items.
How about the three of you help Ikoma to choose clothes.
Okay.
Something suitable.
Like what?
A dress?
I do not understand the clothes here.
I do not know what suits me, what should I do?
40 year old in real trouble
They then consult the sales associate to find clothes suitable for Ikoma.
This is good!
Can I try this outfit?
Try it.
Ikoma immediately tries it on.
And what are the other two doing?
Can I ask?
What are you doing?
Doesn't this suit me?
Don't ask me. What are you doing?
I thought they looked cute, so I wondered how I would look...
I want this.
Don't "I want this"...
Today is for Ikoma
-Right, of course.
Put it back.
But this is really cheap.
How much is it?
Only 7000 yen.
How is that cheap?!
After the interruption by Matsumura, Let's see the clothing Ikoma tried on.
Please.
Cute!
An angel!
-It suits you!
What about this, Ikoma?
It's cute, but...
Why?
I'm not too confident in a dress like this.
But it looks good, right?
-It's cute.
You look good in it.
Try to be a little more confident Ikoma.
I'll buy it for you.
These three members didn't help at all!
I want you to make your own choice.
I understand, so I will make the choice myself.
Next is a small shop, but with trendy clothes,
Lowrys Farm.
This is cute.
Try it with a brighter color.
My shoulders will show.
Show them!
Please let me see them.
Desperate bowing request
Just once, show your shoulders.
I'll give it a go.
Thank you.
Fulfilling Himura's request, Ikoma tries on the outfit.
and those two also tried something on...
They went inside, right?
Why did they go inside?
They both will ask for opinions about the clothes they tried on.
Cute.
Cute. This is really cute.
You're done, right?
Then let's see Ikoma...
Isn't this cute.
It is cute.
You get a discount when you buy 4 clothes.
We should first see the clothes that Ikoma tried on.
We'll talk later.
Ikoma, are you ready?
-Yes.
Please.
Cute.
How does it feel to show your shoulders, Ikoma?
It does look good, right?
Ah, the same?
-Yes, but different colors.
How is it?
Ikoma, how do you like it?
Cute.
Want me to buy it?
Can we look for another?
-Yes, that's fine.
Let's look at one more store and then I'll decide on it.
You're the patiently waiting type?
This has turned out to be fun.
They end up going to a third store.
Suddenly...
Eeh? It's Nanamin?!
Why is Hashimoto...?
Hello.
No way...
This looks prepared, but...
What is this? Was this part of the plan?
What are you doing here?
Shopping by myself.
You are off work today?
Yes.
And you are shopping alone?
Yes. I like shopping alone.
If you are free, can you help us out?
Definitely.
Let's go.
Do things like this really happen?
This is for real, everyone.
Hashimoto starts lending a hand in choosing clothes for Ikoma.
At the time...
Do you see that, the three of them are all wearing hats.
Feeling full of themselves?
Takayama, Shiraishi, Matsumura come here.
What's with the hat?
It raises my spirits.
Just because it raises your spirits?
-Yes, that's right
Just remember that we are here to find clothes for Ikoma.
-Of course!
Help select.
However, Himura-san I unaware of Takayama who gent to try a dress on.
What about this one?
-I'll try this one on.
It's just that Kazumin is already in there trying something on.
Takayama is inside?
Wait...
I really don't understand this.
Why did you try it on?
I just decided to do it.
That's Kazumin-like.
What are you actually here to do?
It should be Ikoma to try on the dress.
Since the three members are constantly disturbing them, Himura has decided!
Do you really want me to buy clothes for you
-Yes.
Don't say "yes".
I see.
Let's play Acchi Muite Hoi.
If you win, I will buy it.
If you lose, I'll definitely not buy it.
Eh, am I included with that?
Taking advantage
Because Hashimoto is with us, you can also play.
Alright! I'm so happy!
The first match is  Takayama vs Himura in Acchi Muite Hoi.
Let's go.
I couldn't lift my head.
Take off the hat.
Don't do this.
Diagonal faces are prohibited
We can't tell what you're doing like that.
Take it seriously?
-Okay, I'm sorry.
Prohibited diagonal face
It's clear her eyes went that direction...
Takayama actually managed to escape from Himura's attack.
Next, Matsumura also defeated Himura.
Next is Shiraishi, will she get her prize?
Instant loss
Black tears
I want a do-over!
Please give me once more chance?!
Can Shiraishi get revenge?
Don't cry!
Last is Hashimoto.
With that, Himura will buy all members clothes.
Thank you very much!
Ah! Ikoma has finished trying it on.
Why did you just come out?
Cute!
This is really good.
But what does Ikoma think?
I can't decide between this and the previous one.
Int eh end, which clothes Ikoma choose?
Kazumi are you buying that?
Himura-san is the one buying it.
-That's nice!
I'm very delighted.
Which one suits me more?
Don't ask me!
How much money will Himura have to spend on the five members?
We will announce it back in the studio!
To begin with, those members beat you in Acchi Muite Hoi,
the "Himura Kirai 3" and Hashimoto.
Let's call out those four.
-Alright.
Please.
You all look really cute.
Why did you choose this outfit?
I rarely wear a white dress.
That's why you chose it?
Yes, because it was Himura-san who bought it,
so I decided yo get it.
-I didn't intend to buy it for her.
None of them helped Ikoma find clothes.
From start to finish, they were just looking for clothes for themselves
-That's right.
It's not like that.
I also helped choose a dress for Ikoma.
But I tried it on because it looked like it would suit me.
That's definitely not right.
"Wouldn't this look good on me?"
"What should I do?" is what you kept saying.
And there was one who truly bought personal clothes.
This is obviously very casual clothes.
I only bought just the t-shirt.
Different from everyone else.
Yes.
You said "Toos" just now.
It sounded like you were saying "Toos!".
Which one was the ultimate choice of Ikoma?
Please come in!
This is nice.
Ah, you choose this one?
You chose the second one.
-Yes.
You look cute.
Showing your shoulders is nice, right?
I have the courage to wear this.
This looks really nice.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Thank you very much!
No problem, if it's Ikoma.
Because you were the one who offered it.
Yeah, so its' no problem.
With that, let's have a quiz.
How much money did Himura spend on the clothes for the 5 members?
Whoever is the closest to the correct amount,
Himura-san will give a special present.
There's no such gift.
And these are the answers from the members.
They range from 40,000 to 60,000 yen.
But there was one person who answered with a very different answer than the rest.
80 million yen?
Put the marker down!
Show us your answer!
8 billion yen!
Well then, Himura-san,
what was the answer?
60,000.
If you were lower than 60,000, put your board down.
8 billion is out!
These four answered in the 60,000 range.
But the correct answer was?
6... 4,379 yen.
Therefore...
Almost perfect.
So next time, you'll go shopping with Sakurai.
Sakurai, you don't really want to go shopping, right?
You want to buy clothes, right?
I really want it.
What is this?
We want to go too
-You're already done!
Is it okay if it isn't clothes?
What do you want to buy instead?
A humidifier would be nice.
This is just what you need to do is ask you again?
Isn't that fine?
Wasn't this segment fun?
It was a little fun.
Next, for the new senbatsu members Fukagawa, Itou, and Wakatsuki, we'll hear their fortunes.
The fortune teller this time is Sakana-chan.
The first fortune theme is?
Which members are likely to become rich.
Fukagawa-san.
Fukagawa Mai, you will become rich.
It's because she is a woman who loves herself.
Abnormally.
Although she doesn't show it.
So you feel like you love yourself that much?
Loving yourself is advantageous in getting more money.
Do you love yourself?
I have a bunch of complexes,
about my whole body.
You have complexes about your whole body...
What about Himura-san? He should just kill himself
-That's right.
What are your shortcomings?
I have short legs.
-Short legs???
Your legs are not short!
They are short.
Stand up and let's see.
They're long...
It's not very clear,
try lifting your skirt...
It's because we can't tell.
You want to hear people say "They're not! They're not!!".
So you mean that she feels good about herself inside?
Yes, she says that to have people say "no", and that makes he feel good.
It's not like that.
So, in other words, she wants to hear other people's praise for her?
So she pretends to cry?
Nothing like that.
But among these three members you are the one who will have a lot of money.
Having lots of money is pretty good, right?
For the other two members, what is the reason they ranked lower?
For Itou-san,
You're a natural genius in shopping.
You will spend a lot of your money shopping.
You mean she's bad at shopping.
What do you mean "natural genius"?
That's what we're talking about!
Some people are born under the "Nature" star.
Those people know how to spend money, but are not good at making money.
She will easily waste money, right?
-Exactly.
So don't worry about it too much and just continue...
Don't give her bad advice!
For example, when I put money in my wallet, the next time I open it, it's already gone.
That's pretty bad!
When I open my wallet, my money is gone!
But you're an artist,
so you don't have to think about money.
What about Wakatsuki?
Despite her hard work, it doesn't produce any results.
Originally, you don't have much money.
So even if she fights so hard, she won't get any results.
Why try hard if it doesn't produce anything?
She does have the greatest spirit among the members,
-Oh, I see.
but it doesn't make money.
-What should I do?
Int he future people will say "she tried hard, but it didn't produce anything".
In addition to these three,
who among the Nogizaka members will be the richest one?
Hashimoto-san.
Hashimoto, you will get a lot of money.
Is that so?
She's the same type as Fukagawa-san.
The same? Ah, you guys are the same!
It's true she often complains about her negative points on this program, right?
She always says "I'm not good at this",
but in your heart, you say "I love myself".
The following theme is...
Who is going to get married the soonest?
They will all get married sooner or later, right?
Who will get married the soonest, Sakana-chan?
Wakatsuki-san.
Wakatsuki you have no money, but you married the fastest.
Why is that?
-Because she's a very nice person.
She's really sensitive to her surroundings.
Because you're a hard worker, men will want to marry you.
The ideal woman!
When you find a man with stable income,
you will decide to get married.
So when she gets married, she will then have a lot of money?
I don't think it will be like that.
They will be an ordinary couple!
That sounds kind of sad!
You don't have any money...
-But you're the best woman!
Besides these 3 members, who will get married immediately?
Next, the unexpectedly surprising predictions!
Takayama-san.
Takayama?
How come?
More than anything else, it is her useless smiles
-Huh?
Her useless smiles.
Her useless smiles?
It is true she likes to laugh.
Even if no one notices, she will still laugh.
Even if the camera isn't on her, she will still force a smile.
The meaningless smiles from laughter will make him happy.
So those smiles will make the men come closer?
It's true that many will approach her, but it's a useless technique.
People who you don't like will come.
-Ah, I understand.
You'll get tired, so you should stop.
I understand.
This will be hard!
When you're an idol on TV, how do you limit it?
Try showing your normal face.
No imagine your face before a Kendo match.
Don't laugh!
Show your serious face once more.
Original (Indonesian) script:
zaka46sembung (zaka46sembung.blogspot.co.id)
English Translation: BSFEMA