www.IkuchanCheeks.blogspot.com
Translation: DOZO, Tamami-Chan
Timing: HKazuto
Special Thanks to HKazuto
Today on Nogizakatte, Doko:
Learn the basics of variety game
The fight heats up
forgotten all purpose
This sub far perfect,
translation and syntax errors might still be there ! Please bear with us :D
A precedent of variety,
First  "Round and Round Bat Game!", people will fall!
Furthermore, First painful foot massage !!
Member's shout loudly
Nogizakatte, Doko ?
First painful foot massage & round and round bats
Quick summary of the to-be-shown variety games
DAN~
Welcome to Nogizakatte Doko, we're your hosts Bananaman !
There seems to be a different atmosphere today,
here are the Nogizaka members !
And we also have a guest with us today
It's Amano-san !
Hiroyuki Amano
Himura-san...
Please read it like Udo-san
(Udo Suzuki is Amano's partner)
Hurry up and read
Learn the basics of games that are common in variety programs !!
You had a better pronunciation than him
To be able to respond properly when appearing on game broadcasts
Let's learn the basics of the representative variety games that often appear on programs
In another place Himura-san and Amano-san did it, right?
-Yes
I wonder if this is good?
To do this or not because it might be a bit tough to look cool
Generally, I like that game.
This time, members will be divided into Amano team and Himura team.
Let's learn by playing a team battle.
Basically, the ones who have a red armband,
are people that somewhat dislike Himura.
It's the truth
So that's how it is ?
It is not!
Especially the front row.
Yeah the front especially.
Slap or protect yourself: Rock Paper Scissors !!
They have this game on VS Arashi for example
- No we don't !
This is the basic idea,
we're going to try that for the first time here
First up, it's Amano Team's Hashimoto vs Himura Team's Inoue !
Alright everybody let's get started!
Here we go: 1, 2...
Hit, Protect, Rock Paper Scissors !
It was tied !
You had your hand on it didn't you ?
Point 1:
Touching the props before the end of the Janken is forbidden
You can't do that
- Yes
Next time, I'll have to punch with my bare fist
Even though they're children.
When playing Hit, Protect, Rock Paper Scissors,
you should be moving your body, right
Let's go!  1, 2...
Hit, Protect, Rock Paper Scissors !
It's good
Even if it's too late it's better to hit anyway.
Let's go! 1, 2.... Hit,
Protect, Rock paper Scissors !
It was tied! It was tied!
It was tied!
Second Round will be Amano Team: Matsumura vs Himura Team: Sakurai
Let's go! 1, 2....
Hit, Protect, Rock Paper Scissors !
What ? What ?
She lost, yet she's holding a hammer !
You took the hammer even though you lost,
took a hammer and dodged the hit.
You can't do that !
I'm throwing this game away.
The game of this hand is comparatively
Twenty hours a day like live TV
Because they often do.
It's going to be an awkward
atmosphere when you do this
It's dangerous.
The moderator is a big deal,
1, 2...
Hit, Protect, Rock Paper Scissors !
This is good !
That's the best.
Now that was good
This poor guy is left out
Whith this she went like that
And the captain will just...
That was a good reaction !
Good reaction.
It's a good reaction.
Third round: Amano Team Takayama VS Himura Team Saito
Your throat was in bad condition last week ?
-I'm better right now
Try saying "Dondake"
[Note: "Dondake~" is a famous word popularized by the Japanese trans woman make-up artist and TV personality IKKO]
Dondake ~
Takayama today you hair little....
I've pulled my bang up this time
Did you bring in the joy?
-That's right, Snap to Kendo here
You've practiced Kendo ? Woah !
Stage 2 Kendo
Right ! This is awesome.
You must win for sure
( said "gaji" instead of "maji")
I will work "branch" hard [???]
I will work "branch" hard !
Maji (sincerely) I will do my best.
Let's go!
1, 2...
Hit, Protect, Rock Paper Scissors !
It was tied! It was tied!
All right, all right!
1, 2...! Hit, Protect, Rock Paper Scissors !
Nice, nice
Hit, Protect, Rock Paper Scissors !
That was fast !
Ah~ close one !
Safe
Hit, Protect, Rock Paper Scissors ! -It was tied !
It was tied!
Safe, Safe
Hit, Protect, Rock Paper Scissors ! It was tied!
It was tied!
And the winner of this game is Takayama !!
Now it's time to have the captains go face to face !
There it is! Is that Aja Kong ?
[Note: Aja Kong is a female pro wrestler]
Is it Aja Kong ?
Who is it?
This is a showdown for you all
I will fight fiercely
For real, this is serious
First time I did this with Katsumata-san, it's how I learned
I will try hard
Get ready !
1, 2....
Hit, Protect, Rock Paper Scissors !
You lost.
Sample?
That wasn't right.
Amano san
You win
Hit, Protect, Rock Paper Scissors !
Too slow,
though you've learned before to hit anyways
1,2... Hit, Protect, Rock Paper Scissors !
It was tied!
Please give me a sample
Somehow it's a bad fight.
Why would it?
Hit, Protect, Rock Paper Scissors !
Safe!
Winner Himura
This shape
Here's your leader
Round and round bat!
You guys might have seen this game before, right ?
they'sVS Arashi for example...
Or maybe on Tore! and Dore!
The essence of this game is
We want to see
when you are in dizzy situation
The most difficult thing is to calm down
Trying to walk normaly
It's not what you want.
Standing in a stuttering state
That kind of thing.
To make things better,
before you do it,
lot of commenting before do that. "I'm an expert at this"
How much does that double line
It's what's going on.
The mat is there for safety.
It's okay to fall.
Please just don't overdo it.
The most important thing in variety is safety !
Laughing comes after.
That's important.
Please become great entertainers
Wrong !
Performer lecture?
thats wrong
Don't say "Yes".
First challenger is Shiraishi from Amano Team
So, personally, I-
You do not look back on me.
Striking loss
I was just checking to see if the bat was functioning properly
-Of course
-Let me check it.
I was just checking to see if the bat was functioning properly
Yosh, it's a good bat.
Do you think you'll get dizzy easily ?
I think I will but...
I can afford to be
- Oh, good.
So it's important to comment.
On your mark... Start !
One... - Too slow, too slow
Two
Slow !
-Three !
Four
Five...  -Faster! Faster!
Six
You're going too slow !
She can still do it
Slow, slow
Last one !
Time's almost up ! No time ! Go !
That was wonderful
How was it ?
-It was very messy wasn't it ?
You're proficient at it Shiraishi.
Well done!
It was fun.
That was the first challenger, Shiraishi,
what was her run time ?
9,65 seconds !
- Great!
Next challenger is Himura Team's commander: Hatanaka
How do you feel about being dizzy ?
I don't get dizzy at all.
I'm not dizzy at all.
Are not you dizzy at all?
How much time do you think it will take you ?
- About 5 seconds
Woah, impressive !
It like runs normally.
with confidence Hatanaka's turn.
Will Shiraishi's record be broken?
It's danger
You can do it, go go !
Move all your body  !
That was fast !
What's Hatanaka's time is?
8,90 seconds !
Nishino from Amino Team is third to take on the challenge
How about you Nishino ?
I think it's probably okay.
(Nishino has a Kansai accent because she's from Osaka)
Do not you get dizzy?
(In Kansai dialect)
I'll get dizzy for sure,
but I think I can still run fine.
Really?
(MCs blabbering in Kansai dialect)
Why?
Why are you doing that ?!
It does not hurt, does it?
It does !!
Are you fine over there ?
I'm not okay !
Will Nishino break Hatanaka's 8,90 seconds record ?
Amazing !
Like running away from the battlefield
What is Nishino's time ?
7,81 seconds !!
Whaaat ?
It's getting faster and faster.
The fourth is Nakada from Himura Team
I did ballet,
...Balance?
Such as equilibrium
might be of little..
Oh, like, with the "turn" for example
Yeah, so ...
That is why..
So, rotation...
Is it possible that it'll make you stronger ?
Possibly.
It's good
How will Nakada fare, as an experienced ballet player?
Time! Time!
Hurry up !
That was fast !
Nakada could you a little ballet pose for us now ?
I'm not sure I can
That's cute
With ballet experience,
what's nakada's time...?
9,38 seconds !
Nishino is victorious !
Fifth, this is the ballet experienced Miyazawa.
Miyazawa, you did ballet as well ?
Yes
So you did ?
Do you feel confident about this then ?
Will the one with ballet experience prove herself to be superior ?
Start !
What's this ? So slow !
It's slow!
What was that just now ? That's new.
Did you feel very dizzy ?
No I didn't
Be defeated
You didn't feel dizzy?
It's always like that
What was the record of Miyazawa who was experienced ballet?
8,38 seconds !
Fast
Because she was tumbling down
Captain Himura will now take on the challenge !
Uh? What?
Ichiro? What is it?
Ochi, not Ichiro
who? Ochiai's?
It's Ochiai's push.
Style of Ochiai
Baseball Form Simulation ?
In these period
Now, place your forehead...
Oh! Himurock!
"BOOWY" start!
[Note: BOOWY is a Japanese rock band that was active in the 80's]
It's not a yo start, but a "boowy" start
Here we are. Himura-san.
He's done the BOOWY start.
Start !
Forehead! Forehead!
Keep it onto
the white patch
Stick it firmly.
Now, start.
You must be kidding !
His time is...
3,78 seconds !
You're lying !!
Why did you not stumble like everyone ?
Truth is... Himura...
Is someone who doesn't get dizzy-
Should've told me!
Tell me first
I was wondering if anyone was fine with this
Rena wanna try
-I want to do it
Can you do it?
Miss Dance
I'll do my best
Can you do it?
Up next:
Ichikawa, another experienced dancer, will challange Himura's record
You'll be able to endure it
Try to endure it
Right.
It's always dizzy going to right
But you got to correct it
Don't think about the fall
just have to run with it.
Will her skill as a ballroom dancer help her ?
She was just rolling at the end
What is the last challenger's Ichiki time ?
5,24 seconds !
In the end, it was impossible
I lost !
Of course is impossible
Something like
I do not know where to run
What is this?
Like Tenjinya
(The buzzword of the magician Yamagami brother)
After this
What made Shiraishi break into tears ?
Who is the real one !?
Two out of three chosen team members received a painful foot massage
A game in which the opponent team matches a person without getting the foot massage
Is there a point here?
The point is you must try to handle it
If you can't hold it in, you can hit them
Doing it like this, while saying "Wait !" and things like that
It might be a good way to act and fool us.
Amano team is made of Hoshino, Matsumura and Shiraishi
"Act Performance without a foot massage" Challenge !
Let's get started with Shiraishi over here. Get Ready... Start !
She's getting it right now
She's acting as we speak
She looks a little angry...
She's like, upset for some reason.
Oh, good. Good.
It's over !
Let's move on to Matsumura.
Please !
Matsumura doesn't look like nothing out of the ordinary.
She looks like she's getting her nails taken care of?
Like she's at a cafe in Harajuku
Finished !
Let's continue, Hoshino's turn.
Please !
As usual
Hoshino always gets a massage after school
Even if it hurts you must not show it
It's because Vice President foot pressure
A study of foot pressure...
Stop! Stop!
Good !  I really can't tell at all !
Let's have them all massaged at the same time.
Please!
Good! It's getting pretty clear.
What? What are you doing?
I have no idea what you're trying to do
But this one person does something weird....
What?
You don't have a very casual face right now, Shiraishi.
Acting?
Shiraishi-san
It's not a casual face.
She's acting !
You alright? Acting ?
I can't tell. We might have gotten a little bit of acting.
Lastly: Please press painfuly hard on their foot !
Ready, start!
Shiraishi !
Here we go! It's the end !
Shiraishi
what's wrong with your face just now
Shiraishi cried! Shiraishi cried!
Shiraishi Tears came out!
Shiraishi, this was all just acting right ?
It is acting.
actress
It sounds real.
Who's the one person that did not received the painful massage ?
1, 2....
Minami!
Well, I will announce the correct answer.
Please start massaging their foot
Please, everyone start acting again
Acting, acting
Let's see !
Here I go ! The answer is... !
They've done it !
Hooray!
Okay, it's over ! Finished.
Well, that's team play
However Hoshino didn't seem to react to the painful massage
Acting
- Great!
Hoshino, it must have hurt really bad right ?
My foot was going numb
It's really painfull
even you don't know it is
Well, because you can hold it,
if you could just show us one more time...
Please no ! I really hate it !
Is it that painful ?
And you endured that ?
That's impressive !
What "point" did you press on Shiraishi's foot ?
The head.
Head point
Could you show us one more time too ?
It's fine if you can't endure it
Just wait a while to see how painful it really is.
It hurts~
Crying aloud
It did hurt after all
Shiraishi endured the pain for TV
It's perfect for variety.
Next the team of Himura
Iwase, Ikuta, and Ikoma will take on the challenge
It's fine if everybody in this team feels pain.
Let's trick them ! Fool them !
First, Ikoma. Start !
Wait, wait, ! Stoooop !
Acting? Not acting ? Which one is it ?
Please stop !
Stoooop please !
Acting? Not acting ? Which one is it ?
Now for Ikuta's turn.
Erika-sama !
She just bashed her with her hand !
I don't even know if anyone ever did this
Was it an act or not ?
There was a real slap !
Now it's Iwase.
It hurts !!
I can't do it !
You can't believe it ?
Suspicious
Then like last time, let's get everyone done at the same time ! Start !
Someone among them is only pretending !
Someone is acting.
Who was the one to not receive the massage ?
1, 2...
Yumi !
I see...
I will announce the correct answer.
It was Ikuta-chan !
Then who did she slap ?
Her own leg.
A Planner
That's great.
Amazing
You made the sound by hitting your own leg, right ?
- She did
Iwase is a little bit as bad as she did her act on purpose
Unexpectedly good results?
It really did hurt !
Once again, just...
I've had enough !
You don't have to act this time, just your normal reaction
That's where it hurts !!
Are you holding it in ?
Does not it hurt?
Doesn't look like it does !
It looked like it hurt really badly for Ikoma too.
One more time
No! Stop it ! It really hurts!
It huuurts~ ;_;
This looked like real pain.
Did it hurt ?
What about we give Ikuta a massage too, what do you think ?
Ikuta always seems so calm and composed.
It huuuurts !
It hurts.
I'm sure it's a fake, she's acting for sure !
It must have hurt before
after this
important announcements nogizaka
www.IkuchanCheeks.blogspot.com
Translation: Dozo, Tamami-Chan
Special Thanks to HKazuto
The result is,
1 point vs 2 points
Himura team victory with one point