TamamiCheeks
www.IkuchanCheeks.blogspot.com
Translator: Tama-chan
This sub is far from perfect, mistranslations and typos are to be expected.
Please bear with us.
Timing: Sayuringo-Hime
Translator Indo-Eng: DOZO
Today's episode is the continuation from last week.
Useful Conversation Examination Episode: Part Two !
This area is swollen.
We'll reveal Hashimoto's strange eating habits
TamamiCheeks
What is this embarassing mistake Erika-sama made ?
And the birth of these famous words by the problematic child Hatanaka !
[Who is the Talk Queen !?]
[Nogizaka's secret stories big reveal !!]
Alright, our first theme is this one:
"Am I the only one doing it ?"
There are a lot of these
Hashimoto.
I like spicy food.
I have Shichimi and Itchimi,
[Note: Shichimi & Ichimi are a kind of spicy powder sauce.]
I have about 4 different types,
And I have about 3 types of Tabasco,
I also have 3 types of raayu.
[Note: ラー油 (raayu) is a Japanese chili oil. It is used in Japanese-style Chinese food or commonly used as a condiment for gyoza or ramen.]
When at home, whatever I might be eating,
I add all kinds of hot sauces.
What, did you bring some with you today ?
Ah, if you ask for it, I will bring some !
I can bring it myself !
I mean, do you aways carry some with you ?
Ah ! I do bring Karashi with me.
So you always carry Karashi ?
Do you think it tastes bad if it's not spicy ?
Like, when having a second serving of something,
that's when I like to add some spice.
I also put raayu in stew.
Raayu in your stew ?
In a cream stew?
Yes.
Then it's almost not a stew anymore.
You don't think it's spicy ?
Right ?
You surprised her.
You don't think it's spicy ?
So you like spicy food ?
You don't usually add spice to a stew.
Do you like Korean Nabe (Kimchi Nabe) ?
No ?
- It's really good.
Korean Nabe is good, however
[Note: taka no tsume (鷹の爪) is a type of chili.]
I like it much less if I don't add Taka no Tsume.
You want it even spicier ?
Isn't that a taste disorder of some sort ?
Right now she looks very pleased.
This area is all swollen.
This kid is amazing,
It's not normal.
she can guess whose clothes belong,
she can guess precisely, just by smelling it.
Her olfactory level is incredible, isn't it ?
When I gave her my shirt
She knew  "This belongs to a man"
Incredible.
That's a pretty interesting story to talk about.
Right.
There will be many incidents going on like being caught at the airport.
Like being stuck.
Like you are bringing a "spicy bag" along with your make-up bag,
and instead of getting lotion you use raayu by mistake.
I made a mistake
Mecha Holiday~ !
Let's continue with Iwase.
Iwase
[Note: ~117°F for you Americajins out there]
I always bathe at home with a temperature of 47°C.
That sure is hot !
47°C is pretty hot.
I often hear that it's very hot,
What is a normal temperature ?
[Note: ~106°F]
Like, 41-42°C.
40°C is barely hot.
Its perfect between 42°C, 43°C or so.
In my opinion 42°C is just a bit too hot.
Having your water at 47°C, isn't that too hot ?
I also think it's too hot.
It's really hot, but-
You can't just do that, how do you do it ?
Are you okay? Are you used to it?
You're going to go numb, right ?
I've also tried 50°C
But for me, 47°C is the sweet spot.
Is it not hot?
It is !!
Of course it is hot, however,
- Even though it's hot
First, I'm the first person in line to take a bath
And after that when the family comes in,
they say it's at the right temperature.
Ah it's hot at first.
One time, I was in the tub at home
My leg was itching
So I scratched it
When I got out, my feet were numb and I couldn't feel the pain
So I got out, and the skin peeled off
Terrible, terrible.
What a story
When she started talking about her legs itching,
I was already thinking this is going to be a disgusting kind of story
This is horrible as expected !
When finished, ah there is no skin.
But for an episode, this is pretty good right ?
It finishes when the skin is gone.
I'm itchy and have no skin.
Is it okay to end it like this?
Next, Hatanaka
Here she is ! Will this be okay...
Hatanaka
Lately, I often do it
For breakfast,
usually you have bread for breakfast, right ?
Depends on the person.
So when I eat bread
First I add "Pasero"
[Note: Maybe she meant "parsley"]
Pasero?
Wait a minute,
Please pause,
Time Out
What did you just say?
I add green sauce.
It changed.
Please tell us what you said first!
Pasero
Paseo? What, Patcho?
pasero?
Basil?
Wait a minute, let's review this
It's very strange
It creeps me out
So you say Pasero ?
Patcho?
Many words like Patcho and Pasero are popping up
Patcho, but not a regular patcho, like a dressing that you put on salad
First off, we don't know what Patcho is.
I don't even know what "normal Patcho" is so...
I've never seen Patcho
What exactly is Patcho?
Patcho is... is put on top of pizza
It's like basil sauce ?
That's Patcho
Do they call actually call it Patcho ?
Do you all know what Patcho is ?
No one knows !
Does that really exist?
Isn't it just a nickname you gave it ?
It's really written a lot
A lot ?
Patcho, Patcho, Patcho, Patcho, Patcho, Patcho
She said it's written on it a lot
A lot of it
You mean Basil dressing, right?
Yes, I add it, then I also add butter two times
It's super good, please try it !
"Please try it"
Incredible
I've dealt with Hatanaka several times,
this child needs special attention.
She screwed up everything we did since the beginning
At the end of the episode talk "Am I the only one doing it ?" she goes:
"This is really delicious please try it"
saying this isn't really necessary, isn't it ?
- So it's good ?
Even though it's dressing, just sprinkle it on and it's delicious !
How many times do you plan on saying it !
"Sprinkle it on", I know I heard you !
So does it taste good? Was it originally used on pizza ?
But that's dressing, right?
Well, usually-
Its basil...
Why are you laughing at me ?!
Oi !
You can't scold her !
She laughed at my nose
She's still a kid, relax
When he spoke, Eh is he our senpai ?
Why did I even laugh ?
What am I supposed to do?
With this we learn about Hatanaka
We got things we didn't know previously from other episodes
Right, but...
This would probably appeal to the average person
People would say "Wait what ?" and be curious.
But this...
As there is no basis of it
Ah I understand!
Probably, in a show, when Hatanaka's time for some "episode talk" comes,
the mood will becomes like this.
A gloomy mood ?
Yes, a gloomy mood
"Why is today so gloomy" there might be such a thing
A gloomy atmosphere, that's interesting
How about this? At the end of the story.
It's so gloomy
Its gloomy
Do it, that's good !
When the mood is like this: "Today's very gloomy !"
Gloomy atmosphere.
Let's move on to the following theme
The following theme is...
Ah... The embarassing story ! Something like this.
We want something more than a faulty story or a little stupid thing you did.
It does not matter if you have both of them.
You got anything ?
No, let's get started
Oh, I see!
Talking about embarassing stories, Himura-san has a lot of them.
It often happens
Well one time I was walking and bird poop fell right on my foot...
It's a shame, isn't it
Does that sort of thing happen everyday to you ?
Sometimes, it often happens
Hm, it's a bit gloomy today isn't it ?
You can use it!
Do use it !
In this kind of situation you use it.
Briefly look the other way and say "It's gloomy today isn't it ?"
Very interesting, gloomy.
Our first embarrassing story is from Miyazawa.
One day, when I was daydreaming...
- When you were daydreaming...
Very good, nice start.
Well, because I was not paying attention,
At the station, I entered the men's restroom
At that moment I hadn't realized it yet.
In such circumstances, I then sat on the toilet
Eh?
After sitting down, I just realized it
I had a feeling something was off
So you felt the presence of men
So when you went in, you were daydreaming and didn't notice if anyone was using the toilets ?
Yes
Eh~
[Note: Could be interpreted as "I came out (of the toilet)" or "It (ahem) came out" which is probably why they're laughing]
Came out.
Uh, you mean...
Like a nasty story
Out of nowhere?
Right now ?
From here
It's an incredible story you just told us.
You can't tell that because it's not idol-like though
Which one is it ?
I went outside.
So Miyazawa came out?
- Yes I came out.
You speak spontaneously
Was that good ?
Should I fix it ?
I think it's a good story, but, well !
What is it...
Maybe not so much of an embarrassing one.
It would be better if the story was more embarassing.
Also I'd like to hear you're voice a little louder
Can you do it?
That's because she sort of mumbles along
Needs to be more cheerful
I want to say "What is this person really trying to say"
Like,
there's this technique
"Listen- !"
And with that feeling in mind...
This person has something to say
For example.
I will give you this awesome technique.
When you tell a story, before you reach the most important part: "blablabla and that's when- !"
And right there you pause for a second.
With that kind of voice.
Or also
For example I was in a panel like that with Nakao Akira and I went like "Nakao-san, that is... !"
This is Technique
If you don't advance in your story and talk at lengths
It will be cut
Even if it's somewhat interesting
Woah, I taught them a lot
But if you try it won't come easy though
Next one is Matsumura
After the practice, I started going home with Nanamin
So we're walking together, though I'm also on my phone
I say "Thank you for your work" to everyone we cross
Nanami does the same
And with the way Nanamin said it this time, I say "Who was that ?"
I had absolutely no idea who that old man was.
Didn't recognize him.
But when I say "Thank you for your work"
He gives me a big smile as he says "Thank you for your work"
Hmm I see
Hmm, it's pretty gloomy in here
Scary!
It's not gloomy!
Sad, sad
This is a sad story!
You're wrong
What a sad story
In fact this is a pretty good story
You can speak lively easily, without straining yourself
But the people around you...
Only Matsumura laughed
She was enjoying herself
Talking to one person only often happens, right ?
Well, I also have a story
There were young men and women in front of the station.
I thought I had seen them before
In this industry, greeting is very important
So I greeted them with a strong "Good morning"
I did that, and after a while
Apparently they were both assistants at the place where I get my hair cut
Since I was sure to have seen them before
I greeted them with a vigorous "Good morning"
Turned out I greated an employee.
Now I've done it too
Hm ? It's gloomy in here
Same
it's not gloomy at all though !
A gloomy atmosphere doesn't look like this !
Wouldn't be like this if it was really gloomy.
If it's really gloomy, it wouldn't be like this.
You'd be surprised if you felt a real gloomy atmosphere
That's right, someday you all will experience it.
By pointing out beautiful teeth and dry lips
And you have to do it, for 30 minutes in front of everyone
This often happens in comedy shows you have no choice but to do it
There it's reeeeally bleak.
It's scary, you don't want to do it, you want to go back home as soon as possible.
"What did I get myself into"
And next Shiraishi
Shiraishi
One day I went shopping alone
I was thinking of taking the elevator
And the elevator was open
All right, I'll take the elevator
When I ran to get into it in time,
The elevator door was closing and I was stuck like this
When entering the elevator
But it opened back up, since I was blocking it
So I entered and there was this middle aged man, alone
He was like this...
Totally awkward, unable to say anything.
I was so embarassed
I entered the elevator like that
That's a cute story
Pretty typical pattern, isn't it ?
Simple stories like that are good, really.
I often hear stories about girls having their skirts or bags stuck in the train doors
Stories about being pinched / stuck
Does anybody else have a story like that ?
I have an incredibly ridiculous story, can I say it ?
Go ahead.
In a story segment, it's okay, go ahead
Well, I-
What did Matsumura say that made her laugh by herself so much ?
I have an incredibly ridiculous story, can I say it ?
Go ahead.
In a story segment, it's okay, go ahead
So, I,
I was rushing to get to the train in time
I got in just before the door closed
And apparently my hair was stuck in the door
Only my hair got stuck
About how much of your hair ?
Quite a lot, about this much
That's a lot ! Woah !
With that much hair stuck you couldn't move
Of course I didn't want to say anything, too embarassing
In this state of shock
Then the train started moving, and my hair waved outside all along
How ridiculous
Matsumura looks very happy though
It's okay, that's kind of cool
Smiling while telling your own story is good too
It makes the listener want to join and and smile too
That's important, you know.
Smiling
She can't stop herself from laughing
Even though we don't really know what she's talking about
Good, good
There must have been an unexpected event at the next station, like did the doors open only on one side or something ?
Did they open ?
Ah yes they did open
They opened in the end
It would be more interesting if the door didn't open
With such conditions, what if the train had to go into trains garage
Well then, next, Inoue.
An embarrassing story
I'm often hurt by my own foolishness
One day I was walking home
When entering, I rammed my foot pinkie into the corner of the door
And I had a broken bone.
It was the day before the school trip
The day before the outing?
- Yes
Of course I still had to go to school
During morning class
Personally, I was sitting at the most further spot in the class, I couldn't sit there anymore
There are rules like that ? - Yes
Then, because I had to do some sort of greeting
"From now on let's enjoy this outing together" I had to say something like that
And so I came from the very back, slowly moving forward
I said, "Let's all go and have fun"
It's like discriminating, "Did you come along, too?"
Right
It was so embarassing, I never would have thought it'd be like this
And the next year
This time, after finished club activities,
I ran to the entrance and fell
This time I peeled my bones
And I had to be in a wheelchair
And again, it was right before the school trip.
This time, I was chairman of the committee
I had to go to say hello to everyone again
Moreover, since it was a planned school trip,
They were all waiting in line in front of the station ticket gates
So I had to come, using my wheelchair in a public place like that...
Poor thing...
"Let's all have fun together..."
So embarrassed
That was a good story !
Yeah, good story.
While giving the greeting speech,
you don't have to say "'Do not hurt yourself".
That's nice.
"In fact I'm hurt right now too"
Aaah that's great
The guy is there! staff whose hands were broken
How did you get hurt?
I fell off my bike
On May 2nd, AKB48 Sashihara Rino and Nogizaka46 Battle results
The 2nd Single "Oidee Shampoo" released
And the Oricon Daily Chart results
will be revealed to the members.
"Oide Shampoo" rating is......
Number 1!
Nogizaka46
Sold 111,222 thousand on first day sales
Nogizaka46 won the game against Sashihara
It topped the numbers of the Debut Single "Guru Guru Curtain" by 85,000 pieces
And also in the weekly single ranking,
It also beat Sashihara with over 150,000 units.
As a newcomer who debuted this year
they quickly snatched the first position !
Thanks to everyone's support we managed to reach first place !
With this momentum, we will work harder and harder, in the future
We want to spread Oide Shampoo even more
From now on, we're counting on you, everyone
Thank you very much
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu !
In addition, to commemorate the release of the second single
The members held mini handshakes events in about 12 locations in Japan
Surrounded by many fans who come every day
We can see to the crowd
From now on we will do our best and keep fighting
Please send us your support !
Thank you very much
Tonight we'll show the PV from the 2nd single on "Oide Shampoo" CD
Please enjoy the video for "Ookami ni Kuchibue" !
Somewhere on a full moon night
I can hear a roar
Whistling to the wolves
A melody of love
Keep your fangs for someone, Instead of biting them
Whistling to the wolves
Sing the song gently
Just by smiling
The world will change
After this, Erika-sama will reveal her most embarassing mistake !
What is it that Hatanaka said at the end ?
Alright, moving on, Ikuta.
So, um, at that moment...
Ah, right
Hm ? What was it again ?
Ah I got it, I'll start over.
It's alright, go ahead.
Do you have an embarassing story ?
We were taking the train
At that moment, my mother is next to me, reading a magazine
You went with your mother ? - Yes
However she doesn't usually read magazines on the train, that's quite unusual right ?
We wouldn't really know...
I think it's quite rare-
So it's unusual for your mom ? - Yes.
So I went like "What are you reading~ ?" while gently hitting the magazine.
And it turns out, that it wasn't my mom.
Eh~ !!
Seriously ?
Totally not the right person.
What happened?
I thought she was next to me
And it wasn't her.
Without me knowing it, she actually changed seats.
Ah~ and so you thought that it was your mom ? - That's it
Where did you hit ?
On her magazine
Her magazine ? While she was reading and you hit it so it fell ?
No I didn't hit it hard
More like a playful "bashi~"
After that, what happened?
Since I didn't know what to do at the time,
I just turned my back and left.
If I were her, if I was reading a magazine and an unknown woman did that while asking "what are you reading"
I'd go "Haaaah !?"
It's dangerous
That was super embarassing.
Alright, everyone got to tell their embarassing and interesting stories
But so far, everyone has been quite interesting, don't you think ?
And we'll end with that,
Watanabe. - Yes yes
The story that you find the most interesting today
Ah~ the best story.
All of them were good but,
Of course today was the comeback of the word "gloomy"
This is it
It's been a looong time since I heard that word
Saying "suberu" (another version of the word) doesn't have the same effect right ?
"Isn't the atmosphere a bit gloomy ?"
I think it's amazing
That's why I chose Hatanaka-chan to be MVP
Hatanaka is like this
She can create things out of not understanding
That's impressive.
I'm often told that
What do they say ?
for example the fans say "Maybe something will come out someday."
I said to him "Please look forward to it."
That's what fans say.
How gloomy.
Good, that was good
She said it just right.
Good work.
www.IkuchanCheeks.blogspot.com
Timing: Sayuringo-Hime
Translator: Tama-chan
Translator: Indo-Eng: DOZO