Today programme : Nogizakatte, Doko
All Nogizaka46 members are gathered
Junior Team vs. Senior Team
Nogizaka46 Sport Festival
We cannot lose
What is this type of situation!
All members have had a fabulous relay running event.
A tough dodgeball battle will be played
And a series of penalty shoot-out
For pride, all members will give their best.
Tears have fallen.
It's really hard...
And our programme starts
- Nogizakatte Doko? is here!
- Nice to meet you.
We go back to this situation again
This is the meeting room.
We cannot meet the girl anymore?
We should be back to the studio but..
It seems that they have done a great event.
- They've done something?
- Yes, of course.
Himura-san,  it's written here
Please announce our plan for today
Today programme is
Nogizaka Autumn Sport Festival
That is it
It is a sport festival
It is going to have some big battles
So good.
It has been recorded in VTR
Nogizaka46 Autumn Sport Festival
We will replace Banana-man as the host and referees.
Hope you help me
And this is Nogizaka46 members
There will be 2 teams, one team consists of 17 members under 18-year-old
and one team consists of members over 18-year-old
The victory will be decided by 7 factors
The winning team
In the next TV appearance
Will have the chance to perform 3rd single "Hashire! Bicycle"
Only winning team can do this
- Yes
- It's not senbatsu
So the first game is
You should bow to each other
First team, the captain is Ikoma
Face each other and say something.
We are the younger team
We have freshness
So we will take the most out of this
We won't lose to some grannies.
They call you "Grannies"
We are shocked
At this time, the oldest member is Iwase
You always call us grannies
In our eyes, you are just some kids.
Inoue in younger team has appeared
They are grannies
It's sunny, remember to use skincare products, otherwise you get skin aging.
See my face, there is no acne at all.
Despite of mocking, but our seniors are not giving up yet.
Takayama is concerning with her skin.
What do you say?
Our skin is rough, is there any problem with that?
Oh, no need to give a look like a granny.
After 2 years, your skin will be like this
So please respect your seniors.
This is the real words from adults
Betting on the third single
The battle between Team Junior vs. Team Senior starts right now.
Opening battle is
Answer with 7 people and 8 legs
What is this?
You've heard that?
This is the game we were waiting for
From this white line, 7 people will walk with 8 legs
Bypass the mat and go to the table behind
Go back to the starting point with a number you've choose.
Which team gives the correct answer will win
Although there are many questions here,
but those questions have many correct answers.
You've to answer from left to right.
In 30 seconds, if all members give the correct answers, you win.
That's it.
But if the whole team cannot answer, you have to start again.
- The order is an important factor to be considered
- Yes!
The farther to the left, the smarter you are.
The first in the right side is the most idiotic person
So consider the position in your group
- Yes.
- This is the correct strategy to win.
Harsh punishments are waiting for you.
Am I affected if my team lose?
After all, I am just a MC.
Of course, you will face the punishment if your team loses.
So I've said to myself I cannot lose this match
2 MC will choose the members for 2 teams randomly.
Members who play this game are
This is 7 members of younger team.
This is 7 members of senior team.
Who is the smartest here?
What? Why do you raise your hand?
Ami is the oldest
So stay in the left side
- The strategy is dummy people go first.
- So it is.
Saito Yuuri goes first
Maimai is also an idiot.
So that?
Honestly Captain (Sakurai) is also belongs to our (dummy) group.
Sometimes I feel dummy
- I think I should stay this side
- Stay this side?
Third place is Sakurai
Takayama stays here.
I will patrol here
This is the line-up for two teams after discussion
It's based on the winning potential.
7 people 8 legs
Line-up please
Both team started well
First obstacle is a big mat.
The older members has overtaken the juniors
Be careful
Seniors have grabbed their question, get back to the position and answer.
So fast, they do it so fast.
When the younger team was moving at a turtle speed
The older team comeback to the start line quickly.
- Number 5
- Question No. 5
Seniors come first and this is the question
- Please give us the full name of our Prime Ministers.
- Don't understand, don't know.
Start
Koizumi Junichiro
Hatoyama Satoshi
Wrong
- Just say it~
- I only know Koizumi-san
Hatoyama Takashi
Hatoyama Yuuichirou
What can I do?
30 seconds, 30 seconds left
Just say it, one name
Hatoyama Hatoyama
This hopeless answer puts the senior team into 2nd position.
They have to do it one more.
Question for younger team is?
- Question NO. 3
- No. 3
Tell us 7 states in America
States of America, so easy
South America
It's not, wrong answer
North America
Oceania State
What the hell is Oceania?
Europe State
Wada Maya answers wrong all the time.
I am done
Asia
Maya is suck, so we bid a farewell
And the seniors comeback with the next question.
Saying 12 months in English
Ready, start
JULY
MARCH
NOVEMBER
AUGUST
SEPTEMBER
JUNE
What ?
FEBRUARY
Correct answers, senior team wins!
In the other way, junior team has lost.
Maya who could not give the right answer, has cried.
Unacceptable tears
It's all Maya's fault.
Do not say those meaningless words
English question has brought red team to triumph.
You should know the Prime Minister of Japan
- I know
- We knew the answer
Say it.
Yoshida Shigeru
Hatoyama Yukio
Tanaka Kakuei
The answer of Captain Sakurai is?
Abe Abe
Only Abe
Abe the Prime Minister and ....
You must say the full name
This is not an answer
This is the separating line
Who are you?
Why do you mention a series of Hatoyama ?
Cause younger team lose, this is their punishment
Bursting Balloon
A Big Balloon ?
The balloon will be inflated, at some level it causes a big explosion.
Of course, all members and the supporter will face the punishment.
Slowdown, so scary.
I am going to die
So powerful
I am still alive!
- I have ringing in the ears.
- I am scared to death!
- The explosion was tremendous
- My teeth were going to drop.
What a shame.
We're finished, come here.
So scary
Maya has cried immediately.
Just name the states of America, but she couldn't do it.
Crying is good.
The priority for this programme is crying scene
You don't need a reason to cry.
So many members I haven't seen for a long time.
We can see some new haircuts here.
Ah, Noujou Ami has a new haircut.
She looks like Tamori-san.
Has Noujou cut her hair?
There are so many interesting stories to come
Next game
The next game is relay eating wankosoba
Noodles will be served continuously.
Two teams will choose 3 representatives respectively.
Noodles will be served in those trays.
Three people will have to eat 50 bowls in sequence.
But each member has to eat at least 10 bowls.
20 bowls can be eaten in any order.
I will choose the players randomly.
Two MC will choose players for this round.
Younger team consists of Ami, Inoue and Ikuta
Older team consists of Shiraishi, Takayama and Matsumura
First, I think you should say something to improve the mood.
I think I can eat anything
It's nonsense !
I am worrying for a member...
Who?
Sayu-nyan, her speed is so slow.
It's an disadvantage to have her in this round.
- It takes her one hour to finish a pie
- What, just a pie?
It's going to be difficult
And I hate soba noodles.
The older team might have won.
First elimination, one person must eat 10 bowls, otherwise you are disqualified.
Thinking about this makes me Ooops !!!!!!
Funky feeling
- What is your strategy?
- I should swallow instead of chewing.
This side is going to lose
You are the Ace, aren't you?
- No chewing
- No chewing?
I usually say those words
I don't play this today
Don't force yourself like this.
Ready for this round! Start!
With a loud sound, two teams have started.
One person seems to be slower
Kazumin is eating with a slower speed than Ikuta.
The senior team is losing with one bowl.
In younger team, Ikuta is fighting with a good speed.
Looks good
What a feeling
Takayama has eaten 5 bowls, Ikuta has eaten 10 bowls.
Ikuta has finished her first 10 bowls
Younger team continues with super slow Inoue
Clean your hand first
Sanitation
Stop this, do it quicky , oh my god.
Can you eat 10 bowls?
This is just 1/3 of the progress
It's the huge chance for senior team
Inoue has struggled with her slow speed.
Will she give up?
Inoue has hold back her team...
At this time, Takayama has caught up and finished 10 bowls.
Inoue does not have a chance.
Stand up, switch to other member
Takayama has been substituted by Shiraishi Mai
More noodles
Lightning speed
Speedup, continue this trend
Shirashi has caught her opponent.
Inoue has just finished 2 bowls.
It looks like she wants to stop
What is your feeling right now?
Oh, you eat Tempura.
Who told you to eat Tempura?
Changing flavor
Inoue is tired with noodles.
The strategy is eating Tempura to change the flavor
Will she relaxed by this?
She is praying for a faster pace.
In the other side, Shiraishi cannot stop eating.
Inoue just finished 3 bowls, Shiraishi has finished her 10th bowl.
You are doing a great job
You do it so fast.
Next candidate, Matsumura has joined us.
Keep it up Sayurin~
It's a little bit slow
Swallowing, it's good.
Wait a second ,Suzuki, I have an idea
Your team is going to win
We cannot catch up with you
So can we substitute member?
Please
With this amount of bowls, you are going to win anyway.
You can win with this advantage.
Accept the request from junior team, the rule has changed.
Hatanaka is substituted in and the battle continues.
Why do you eat Tempura?
This girl Inoue is...
2nd time of changing flavor
In senior team, Matsumura has finished her 10th bowl.
After complete the first round, all candidates are allowed to eat freely.
Who can eat more?
Senior team has come for its 31th bowl, Hatanaka has finished her 20th bowl.
After that, can Noujo Ami catch up with her opponent?
So superior.
You see that!
You see that! This is the real eating contest!
Ami continues with 26th bowl, it's Takayama turn for the opponent.
- How many bowls are left?
- This side is going fast.
I am going to turn the table.
In senior team, Matsumura has come in
But her speed cannot be compared to Ami
Have some flavor.
With a blazing speed, can Noujo Ami change the situation?
Can Matsumura The Ace eliminate her opponent?
What is the result?
With Ami, younger team has refreshed.
But at the last bowls, there is a strange thing.
Breathless?
Time is running out
Honestly, she is substituted for 2 candidates.
- Quickly
- Switch people
All hopes have go to Ikuta.
The Legend will show her hidden ability.
You are doing a great job.
So good.
Very fast.
She is eating with lightning speed.
Ikuta use her strength to reduce the gap to 4 bowls.
Matsumura is just eating some fried dishes.
The senior team has 4 bowls to go and it depends on Shiraishi Mai.
Gluttonous Ikuta is going with an unpredictable speed.
But the senior has come for its last bowl.
Senior team wins !
Ikuta cannot change the situation, and the senior team wins.
The punishment for younger team.
The punishment is foot massaging.
Hatanaka, you have some questions? What?
I am just the guest, not an official member.
But you've said that you want to participate.
- I just want to eat.
- No way!
You will face the punishment of Dr. Katouno Miho
Please
So stress
It hurts~
It's so painful
It hurts
Ah, no way, I am going to sweat.
Wait, you can't
Can't you do it in a gentler way?
Why do you press so hard?
Next time I will bring your smile to hell.
The next game is penalty shoot out.
Nogizaka46 will fight until the end
Next week will be the continuation of Nogizaka Sport Festival
The penalty shoot out ended with a surprise.
And in shouting contest.
The unsatisfied mood of Sakurai with member is!?
Why do Hoshino cry?