--------------------------------------------------
On tonight's Nogizakatte Doko, Himura goes shopping with the members, part 2.
And a surprise new unit, Himura Daisuki 4, appears!
and shocking answers for a Himura-san quiz.
We are hosts, Bananaman.
And these are the Nogizaka46 members.
Today's program is...
Spending money like crazy.
Himura and Nogizaka goes shopping part 2.
I'll buy Sakurai Reika whatever she wants.
This is the second time we've done this, with the first being with Ikoma.
You went clothes shopping.
What happened this time, let's take a look.
Shopping for captain Sakurai Reika.
On the previous shopping episode with Himura,
Sakurai Reika correctly answered the questions and gets a Himura reward.
We are at Lumine Est in Shinjuku.
What do you want to buy?
-I want to buy a dress!
During the recording, there were several members sneaking around.
Good morning~
Taking it easy.
Wait, you are coming too?
Why are Wakatsuki and Nakada here?
Reika wants nice clothes,
but her personal clothes are not very idol-like.
Therefore I will help her choose clothes that suit her.
Therefore I am here beside Reika.
There's no need.
This is an example.
Rocker style.
You dress like this, Sakurai?
-That's right...
After hearing Nakada's explanation that Sakurai's clothes are not very idol-like...
Wakatsuki too...
Mysterious companion.
Like Sakurai, Wakatsuki also wears rocker clothes, which is not very idol-like.
She also wants to buy clothes fit for an idol.
Humidifier?
I will help choose clothes.
If that's the matter of Himura-san will give her...
-Stop joking!
Continue the right?
Why should I buy her a humidifier?
After the talking was done, the shopping started.
Ah, Yuttan!
Hello Himura-san!
-What are you doing here?
The last time you went shopping, you met Nanamin.
I just happened to be waiting here and ran into you.
This is definitely not a coincidence!
Convincing crime.
Why are more members showing up? This isn't right.
outsiders increase.
Pretending to have accidentally met Saito Yuri.
The first goal is a place just looks feminine and adult, the store Amavel.
What about this?
It's Reika-like.
This would be perfect for Reika
-Cute!
I think this suits you.
Wait!
This is 14,000 yen!?
Too expensive.
Oh no, this is expensive!
This one thing is 14,000 yen!?
-How about the set?
After Sakurai, Himura now helps Wakatsuki look for clothes.
Cute!
I have never seen you like this before!
You look cute, but you don't like it?
It definitely doesn't match with me.
Don't worry, you look great in it.
And then Wakatsuki too.
Cute!
I really like it, but...
-But you look cute!
The next store, Par Avion, has a vintage feel but very cute fashion.
Huh?
What is it that Nakada found?
There is someone there!
Ah, what a coincidence!
By chance?
Himura-san!
What's up with this?
I heard Himura-san wants to shop and that you'll buy us...
I'm not here to buy clothes for you!
Begging girls.
This looks good
-It's cute, right?
I won't buy it!
Today's plan was to give clothes to just these 2 members.
Why did more members appear?
I really love Himura-san.
"I like you" strategy.
Ito and Fukugawa join in.
At the beginning, it was only 2, but is has increased to 7 members.
Chaos shopping is starting now!
Everyone facing backwards.
Let the camera take your picture!
In the middle.
Even though you're shopping, this is still a location shoot.
and then!
Did someone just go in there?
Trying on clothes?
Who's in there?
-Nobody!
Nakada!
Don't do as you please.
I was curious if this fit...
-Cute!
It's cute, but this isn't right...
I want to try on too.
Another went in.
Wait!
Please don't bother us, we're changing.
Suddenly a woman.
Where is everyone?
There's nobody here...
Everyone in fitting rooms?
There's nobody here... How many members were there...
What are you doing?
What do you think?
-It's definitely cute.
Pleading eyes.
Ah, cute!
Everyone looks really cute.
The 4 members here form a new unit.
Because we all love Himura-san...
We're Himura Daisuki 4 (HD4).
Because there is Himura Kirai 3 (HK3), we love Himura, so we're Daisuki 4.
Daisuki 4!
We love Himura-san!
HD4 really make Himura blush?
Today I only promised to buy clothes for Sakurai and Wakatsuki only.
So we will go to one more shop. Okay?
When get get to that other shop,
you can pick just one item.
1 set?
Okay, one set.
Sugar daddy.
But only if one of you play a game for it.
The winner will get the prize.
Next is a store with beautiful clothes for women of all ages, Auntie Rosa.
Let's go shopping!
They all look serious.
Suddenly unite.
Why did it become this way?
The HD4 members became enthusiastic.
Even Sakurai and Wakatsuki, who had finished shopping, helped.
I will buy 1 set of clothes,
so we will have a quiz.
You like me, right?
-We like you!
You really like me, right?
I will give you one question about me.
A quiz on Himura. One question.
I'll buy for the winner.
Question: What side dish does Himura like to eat?
I'll write the answer.
Side dish?
I said it once on this show.
-Yes, side dish.
Sudden in-house broadcasting.
Let's listen to this.
We inform you that the store will close soon.
Store closing.
Better do it fast.
Alright, write it fast!
Let's start with Nakada.
Potato salad.
Mapo tofu.
Are you sure about your answer? Yo don't want to change it?
This are your answers?
-Yes.
Potato salad, potato salad, potato salad, mapo tofu.
The correct answer is...
Mapo tofu.
Collapse.
I asked if you wanted to change your answer...
This is the outfit that Sakurai chose.
These clothes make her look more idol-like.
And Wakatsuki choose this dress.
She looks more feminine than before with her jeans.
And Saito Yuri, who won the Himura quiz, chose this dress.
How much money did Himura spend on this?
This was terrible.
Nakada is the culprit this time.
What's with you, Nakada?
Evil boss.
But I didn't buy anything.
She's keeps saying that.
Because I really really like Himura-san...
There was the Himura Daisuki 4; who were the HD4 members?
HD4 was horrible, wasn't it?
You didn't answer Himura's quiz.
-That's right!
Only Saito Yuri.
I guess I'll be the leader.
The HD4 leader?
-Yes.
Disband the group!
Instant extinction.
There's no such group.
The Himura Kirai 3...
Who's with HK3?
HK3 is definitely a group though...
After seeing this, Akimoto sensei, please establish the Himura like and hate units.
Featuring Himura?
How much was the total cost for the 3 members?
Last time was 64,379 yen for 5 members.
This time was 57,120 yen for 3 members.
It was very expensive. Even though the total was only slightly less there was less members.
But this made you happy, so don't think about the amount.
Who hasn't gone shopping with Himura?
Let's have and Shiraishi say,
"Who likes Himura-san" for the title call of this quiz.
Who likes Himura-san? A Himura-san quiz!
That was good. You didn't sound like you were lying.
How much do you know about Himura? Participate in the competition and the winners will be rewarded.
Divided into 4 groups of 4 people, the winners in each group will advance to the final.
The final winner will get a prize from Himura.
The first group consists of Shiraishi, Hoshino, Nakada, Wakatsuki.
Please listen to the first question.
Himura's weakness is?
After Himura wrote the answer on the board, the quiz started.
Start!
Wakatsuki!
Weak against pressure.
Nakada.
-Weak when someone touches his ear.
Next.
Doesn't like people to mention his moles.
-Why did you mention that?
Why do you go with moles?
Let's give a hint.
Wait, we have not heard an answer from Shiraishi.
Indifference?
A hint...
In my mouth
-Seen on variety shows.
Does like eating soft things.
Normally the opposite.
Why can I not eat a soft meal?
This has nothing to do with food, but in the mouth.
Rubber snap?
Gomu patchin - Bite the elastic band and have it snapped back at your face.
Correct!
I'm not strong with rubber snap.
The second group is Matsumura Sakurai, Saito, Inoue.
You you all Himura?
We do!
Matsumura didn't say it!
As expected?
Say it!
Even if you really hate me, at least pretend!
This time a survey about Himura.
A survey of 100 people in Shibuya: "When you think of Himura?"
From the results of the survey, what is the third answer?
Start!
Hair.
-What about hair?
-His hairstyle is distinctive.
The answer to number three is "mushroom cut".
So we'll accept his hairstyle is distinctive.
The third group is Takayama, Ikuta, Fukagawa, Ichiki.
What does Himura always buy in a convenience store?
You must strongly press the button.
No reaction.
-Yes, I did.
Batteries.
Himura battery?
Why would I always buy batteries when shopping?
I only buy them occasionally.
Takayama, you're going to break it. Someone else already pressed first.
Potato salad.
Incorrect.
Wait, I buzzed in, but it didn't left up because of my elbow...
Own elbow stop.
It didn't lift up because your elbow was on it?
That's too stupid.
You really are a member of HK3...
Idiot panic.
Ikuta.
Vegetable sticks.
I only buy them occasionally...
Sliced burdock.
Close.
Burdock?
-Yes.
Ichiki.
Seaweed salad?
Convenience store?
Almost.
Correct answer: Burdock salad
Takayama.
What was last time?N-Sliced burdock.
That's close.
Sliced cabbage.
A shredded choice.
Ah, sticking with "Sliced".
Yes... fried burdock?
Roughly.
No, no.
Burdock salad.
Correct!
The last group is Ikoma, Hashimoto, Itou, Nishino.
This question is about a questionnaire about Himura.
Survey of 100 people in Shibuya "What kanji do you think of when you hear Himura?".
We are looking for answer number 4.
Give us answer number 4. Start!
Looks like.
-Ah, you mean his face.
Fun.
-This must be true.
That's not is.
Strange.
-It's obviously not that...
Number 4 is "Strange"!
The last game will have a lot of laughter.
The finalists are Takayama, Sakurai, Itou, Wakatsuki.
The final question is: Himura's unusual behavior that he thinks is normal?
Don't peek.
Don't peek at the answer.
Chaplin appears.
Please answer.
Wipes his hands abnormally in the dressing room.
Do you think we need to give then a hint?
He does it suddenly...
Suddenly runs.
A picture?
It's not that he suddenly runs.
Suddenly sits.
Wrong.
Suddenly yells.
Great!
When I suddenly shout "AAAAAAH".
Like when taking a taxi, although nothing happened, he'll suddenly shout "AAAH".
With that, the winner is Wakatsuki!
Original (Indonesian) script:
zaka46sembung (zaka46sembung.blogspot.co.id)
English Translation: BSFEMA