m 0 0 l 0 1 1 1 1 0
TamamiCheeks.blogspot.com
Translator: Tamami-chan, Dozo
Typeset&Timing: Sayuringo-Hime, Dozo
Translator Indo-Eng: Dozo
Tonight, pictures of members taken by other members will be shown !
That shocking picture causes an uproar in the studio !
Did you eat that poodle?
Inoue cries because of Shitara's question ?
Take care of yourself okay ?
[Private Pictures Exhibition, rapid fire style !]
[A new side of the members !]
Right now I'm being Udon
This sub is far from perfect.
Mistranslations and typos are likely to be there.
Please bear with us.
This kid's got talent doesn't she ?
Don~ !
Nogizakatte Doko has started and we're your hosts, Bananaman,
And here's Nogizaka-chan~
All right, today will be... Inoue !
Please announce today's title with a loud and energetic voice.
Yes
One two-
Photos by theme: Let's take pictures ! Nogizaka Photo Exhibition !
This time, members are asked to take pictures based on 4 themes "Happy" "Angry" "Sad" "Fun"
With each members "sense", what memories are brought by the members?
Starting with Ikuta's picture.
The theme is "Angry"
Reika-chan...
Is that sakurai?
Why, what in this photo is "Angry" ?
I took that when she was daydreaming and I thought she was pretty frowny looking.
You didn't notice Ikuta snuck a picture of you ?
Heh~ What's this? When was that ? I have no idea.
You didn't realize it.
What are the circumstances of this ?
Ikuta thought you looked pretty angry
Well not really angry, just daydreaming.
So this is you when daydreaming ?
It's Daydreaming ? Eh!
So when you're on TV and you start daydreaming
it will look like this, so be careful.
Matsumura Sayuri "Happy" theme
Ah, it's rice !
What is this?
It's rice.
You told us before that you love rice, didn't you ?
-Yes, I like to eat.
What has been your favorite thing to eat lately ?
Recently,
[Note: Shitara thought she said [ - uma] horse, when she meant [ - umaishio] delicious salt.]
Most delicious, delicious salt
Horse?
Ah ~
Recently!
Sometimes I add umaishio as a dressing
You add umaishio as a dressing
Put it as dressing and eat it just like that? -Yes
Eh~ !!!
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Shocking Reveal
Are you joking?
But why ?
Without side dishes?
Is not it better to add with side dishes?
Yeah I do like it too but I don't have any in my house
So with that as dressing you just eat it like that ?
-Yes, without side dishes.
- That's a lie
Nogizaka are that strict with their diet ?!
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Concerned about
their health
Matsumura Sayuri. "Angry" Theme
What is that ?
- Its beautiful
The sea?
We still haven't heard her explanation,
let's hear what she has to say.
Well this a picture of the sea, however,
On the left you can see it's very cloudy,
and on the right the weather is very bright.
You know, sometimes people are angry, deep down, but they don't show it on their faces ?
Incredible ~!
That is what I wanted to express.
With that kind of picture. - Yes !
Such a sight reveals the psychological state of this kind of person.
After showing us a bowl of rice, you bring this ?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Extreme
difference.
It's the same as it was before, adding salt to the rice...
I think this person has great talent.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
New talent ?
Matsumura Sayuri, "Sad" theme.
Hm ?
- What is this?
What's this, a "sexy device" ? ;)
Nooo~ !
No ?
That's not it !
But really what is it ?
Unfortunately, this is only from the bathroom in my house.
Ah, in your house ?
- Yes.
Easy to wash while I flush it in the toilet
Like cleaning
And because it's been there for a long time, I wanted to replace it,
But it's such a pain.
I just put down a new one and forgot about the old one.
But after thinking about it,
If I try to imagine the feelings of the one that got replaced,
isn't it really sad ?
If I throw it away
I was thinking very much about this picture.
Yeah you're right that's sad, if that was me...
The one on the left, because it is not needed anymore...
I imagine myself, not in need anymore and getting replaced by other people that work harder.
So the sadness comes from the fact that while he once was effective and doing his best
Finally the new guy came in and replaced him.
Like it is for Idols...
Like it is for Idols.
Look at the others, they all think the same.
This is very...
It's not sad.
Right,
the entertainment industry is like that,
So let the cleanser in the bathroom just like that !
Matsumura Sayuri's "Fun" theme.
Ah, it's the members.
During a lesson ?
- Yes, during practice.
We were resting in the practice room,
Looking good.
-Yes, very pleasant
Doing your best, looks fun.
So I noticed something about the two in the middle.
Nishino-san
Nishino and... ?
and Takayama-san.
With Takayama.
- Yes !
It looks like Na-chan is touching her mouth ?
Like feeding her a snack?
- No, this is...
I remember that
Her philtrum,
I pressed it down.
Ah, this part here.
My philtrum, it's a little deeper than other people.
Therefore, the other members like to tease me about it
But Nachan deliberately narrowed it down like this
Unevenly
We'd play like this
I remember that moment
Saito Asuka's "Angry" theme.
Who ? Who is this?
Reika
Who is this?
Sakurai
So this sakurai
Sakurai has appeared twice already on the theme "Angry".
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Queen of [Anger]
You don't want that, huh ? Sakurai.
Why the mask ?
Since I have dry skin,
I usually apply it before getting my make up done...
Asuka took a picture because she thought it was interesting.
Many like to take photos of you
But where is the "Anger" ?
Isn't she looking kind of angry ?
I'm not angry !
Like her, Sakurai has an angry face
So be careful in the future, you never know when a member might take a picture.
Saito Asuka's "Fun" theme.
That's Chiharu.
Like american people that love sweets.
Like "Fun TV games !!"
Fun television game !!
Why is this "Fun" ?
Chiharu seems like a shy and quiet person at first.
In fact it's the opposite.
She's always like this.
She's a "TV game is super fun !!" type of person ?
"Why can't I finish it ?!"
This is her true self, right ? When you took that picture.
Sakurai Reika's "Angry" theme.
What is this?
What...
This is all keys.
- Oh in Korea right ?
Yes, that's it !
-There's a tower.
So this is in korea,
It's a famous place among couples.
- Close to Seoul tower, right ?
Like, with your family-
Did you go with your boyfriend ?
- No !
Can you please stop that...
Well it's that kind of place...
Not like that... With my family,
when we all went to Korea,
everyone looked very happy, locking their padlocks...
What's wrong ?
Ah, because these couples looked happy, you wished you had one too...
Isn't that great ?
No, it's better not to go to a place like that.
Sakurai Reika's "Fun" theme.
What is this?
When we were filming a PV some time ago,
I found a Moai statue that looked a lot like a member.
With a face that looked like a member ?
Don't you think it resembles someone ?
With that haircut, maybe yes.
- Ah I see.
That's Ikuta.
Ikuta.
- That's right, Ikuchan.
When everyone found this they shouted "Aaah there's Ikuchan !"
Ah~ It does look like her.
It could also be a sad photo of Iku-chan turning into stone.
Iku-chan what's with you, Ikuchan?
Ikuta, what do you think about this ?
Eh ? Only the hair looks similar in my opinion...
Everyone shouted at me "Iku-chan, Iku-chan !" when they saw it
Can you give us a facial expression like that ? Without expression.
Somewhat similar, right!
Similar,
Similar, similar
Wakatasuki Yumi's "Angry" theme.
What is this ?!
- Scary~ !
This is kind of scary.
Like a work of art. A painting ?
I couldn't find the right picture for the "Angry" theme...
So I was thinking of making it myself
For this ? - Yes.
So this was made in my kitchen.
The thing underneath, is it aluminium foil ?
- Ah, yes it is.
And I kept crumpling the foil
And next you cut your wrist open.
No, not like that~ !
Why the cutting part
Then, I sprayed some ketchup.
Ah ! It's ketchup. Not paint, then ?
So it was ketchup
And the dark brown bits are coffee.
Ah ! This is from items collected from the kitchen.
- That's right.
And then I put two knives crossed, in order to look like a fight, or a war.
You really played deep into the theme.
Because the theme is "Angry"
We can really see the approach everyone has.
Nishino Nanase's "Angry" theme.
Please do not give anything to the pigeons
This is "Angry" ?
- Wouldn't that make you angry ?
Ah, "Please do not give anything"
That made you irritated ?
- Yes.
But for me personally,
- You love pigeons, right ?!
That's right, you like fat pigeons, right ?
For me personally, I really want to feed them...
That's because you might be able to see a fat pigeon...
I see...
- So that's why.
If you keep doing it, it will be a problem later.
Fukagawa Mai's "Angry" theme.
Who is that?
It's Yuminen.
- Iwase.
Ah so it's Iwase !
I'm pretty often on Yuminen's knee...
Or draw faces on her fingers
Fooling around ?
- Yes.
I also like to disturb her when she's playing games for example
As I pinched her cheek she looked
bothered and I love that, I think that's cute.
Kawaii~
So it's her face ?
"Don't bother me!" Hmm~
Like that right?
[Note: Himune - "ne" from onee-san, meaning Sister, which makes it Sister Himura.]
What do you think about Himune ?
How was it ?
"Hmmm~" like that, right ?
Ikoma Rina's "Fun" theme.
Uwa, that looks delicious !
- Really looks good.
I like ramen the most.
- It is really good.
Well, everyone loves ramen right ?
When it comes in front of you don't you feel happy ?
And this time I was super happy.
But what's this? Like Chashu
[Note: Ramen Chashu - ramen noodles that are in
taburin with roasted pork.]
That place in Kyoto, what was it ?
Shinpuku
Shinpuku saikan: located in kyoto, famous for its Black ramen
Shinpuku saikan
(Didn't get what he said, sorry)
Shinpuku saikan, the most delicious In Kyoto
In Kyoto!
It's quite famous
Looks great
It's been a long time since I've come to the ramen place-Ah so
Its delicious!
When it's about ramen you talk too much !
Speaking arrogantly like: "I've been wanting to go there for a long time"
Takayama Kazumi's "Angry" theme.
That's Takayama ?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Selfie?
I'm a bit shocked !
So this is not Takayama right ?
- It's not.
That's pretty random.
What breed is this ? It's cute.
This is a brown Toy Poodle.
You bought it ?
-Yes I bought it.
Actually my mother bought it,
and it isn't that cute but-
No it is cute !
- No...
Yes it is really cute !
It's all curly
- You don't think it's cute ?
The nose is pretty long...
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Is it not your dog... ?
I've never seen a poodle dog that is not adorable.
Perhaps it's because I was talking a lot when taking the picture, she looks angry...
But it's still adorable when you're alone with it, right ?
When alone with it ? Hmmm.....
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Is that your dog?
Takayama Kazumi's "Sad" theme.
What is this ? Did you eat that poodle ?
That is really sad if that's the case.
Please don't eat it !
No, it's not like that
And what's this all about?
[Note:  - Deep fried oysters.]
This is kakifurai !
Ah ! So this is kakifurai...
It's also curly looking so it looks similar.
And here we thought you ate it....
But why is this sad ?
- Well I really love fried oysters...
- It certainly is delicious !
It is !!
Delicious looking fried oysters !
I like them so much that I'm talking too much
I can understand your feelings
When it comes to fried oysters, you'll talk a lot.
-Yes
So, I bought a fried oysters bento box.
A bento ?
-Yes.
Usually, there's about 4 oysters in it.
Not a whole lot
- Yes, not much.
When I eat the first, it tastes fine. Then the second one...
But after the third one, you begin to feel the spicyness kick in.
I understand what you mean.
You told it that way
-Yes like that
And so this is the last one.
- I understand.
So that's why you look a lil' chubby.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Be careful.
Shiraishi Mai's "Fun" theme.
A music sheet stand ?
- Yes.
What makes you happy about this ?
There are lots of holes in it right ?
- Yes ?
the fact that there's a lot... it's fun.
What ?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Are you alright?
What is that!
According to me !
Eh~ !!
- Eh?
Shiraishi, so you're that kind of person?
Does that not look fun ?
There are lots of holes and this is fun.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Birth of a new character ?
Scary~ !
Not like that,
If there was only one hole, it'd be very lonely, right ?
Ah, so this hole here
it's like he's having fun with all the others
Yes, and that is the "fun".
Your imagination is wild.
- It is !
Why is Inoue crying ?
Inoue Sayuri's "Sad" theme.
Ah, it tore off.
That is really sad.
These belong to Noujo Ami,
Well, Ami's birthday was a few days ago,
After that, the next day, she went to school.
Then, her junior stepped on her foot from behind
Parts of her shoes were peeling off.
The day after your birthday ?
- Yeah... What a bummer.
How did you do after ?
I see, you dragged your ripped sole along
one legged Barefoot?
Well I carried the broken one.
-You carried it.
On the way I carried my shoes off and walked barefoot but obviously this was quite embarassing....
So I put it back on and carried on my way like this....
that's sad.
So this year for her birthday I plan to give her glue.
Give her shoes !
Just give her shoes !
But here ...
#On this occasion only,
\h\h\hInoue didn't send in pictures for the "Fun" theme.
Why didn't you send photos for this theme ?
We have not received your photo yet.
I'm sorry.
Because this is a Nogizaka group contest, I thought I wasn't allowed to enter with a picture unrelated to Nogizaka.
We won't forgive you, even if you cry.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Monster MC.
Crying is forbidden.
In this situation,
you have to answer the question,
while crying.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Cruel
Sorry Inoue, but have you brought us your "Happy" picture ?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Unstoppable
We're just joking, Inoue, it's fine, it's fine.
Forgive us Inoue !
When thinking about the photo, I thought that there is nothing that makes me happy.
Nothing that makes you happy ?
Are you okay now ?
I am sorry.
Well be more careful okay ?!
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Cruel until the end
Hashimoto Nanami's "Fun" theme.
This is a stage play ?
Some time ago ?
- Yes at the Parco Theater.
Who's on the picture ?
-Ikoma on the left and Noujo on the right.
- Ikoma and Noujo.
[Note: Boa Hancock - a character from One Piece.]
When I was in high spirits, I imitated Hancock.
When lifts his head up to the sky like this
From One Piece.
-Yeah from One Piece.
One piece, Ah ! You know it ?
- Of course he knows.
He ate the "Disgusting" fruit.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
His ability
I became like this after eating it.
Akimoto Manatsu's "Sad" theme.
Ah Kawaii~
That thing is cute
Himura-san ?
- it's not !
That's a cute pig !
This one's very important to me,
I've had it since elementary school.
You've had it for that long ?
- Yes.
I would take it with me wherever I was going.
But since entering high school...
I haven't given him much attention.
- Since you've grown older...
Yes, now I'm 19 years old...
I want to distance myself from this plush.
-You want to keep it away.
This is sad. Kinda like Toy Story.
Like Toy Story, yeah-
Have you given it a name ?
It... doesn't have a name.
If you have memories with it, please give her a name.
But,
I don't really "call" her.
- You rarely call her...
You just put it here.
Ichiki's picture will make the studio go wild !?
Ichiki Rena's "Happy" theme.
That looks good !
Looks so delicious~ !
I wanna eat it !!
What is it ?
It's not really about excitement or expectation.
At this time, I wanted to eat udon with my friends,
We walked around for an hour, trying to find an udon place.
And when we finally found it, I was very happy.
And so this is "Happy"...
Let's move on with the "Angry" one.
It's not udon ?
What does this mean ?
Oi, this is Udon, right?
Just before, that was udon, right ?
Yes it was udon.
First, this is-
Let's try to become the udon's feelings~
What are you talking about?
What are you talking about, Ichiki!
I'm a human !! Not an udon !
Right now, they're fighting.
That's quite peculiar.
Humans also fight sometimes, don't they ?
- Hah?
Humans also fight sometimes, right ?
But right now I'm an udon.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Now I am udon.
You guys too ! You're all udon !
You feel the same as udon.
This is the same as when people are fighting on the battlefield.
U- Udon War !
No, that's an udon war!
There's a fight in the plate.
- Yes !
Maybe all her themes will be udon.
Let's see what's next for the "Sad" theme.
Well isn't it Udon again !
The theme of "Sad" is also udon !
Right ?
What is it this time ?
When I had finished eating it,
Since they all fought because they hated each other,
They hated each other ?
The noodles had already died.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Mourning
the noodles.
What about the last theme "Fun"...
Isn't it already over ?
Usually it would be a picture of members during practice
Yey~
Let's have a look together at the picture for "Fun".
Udon, again.
What is the story this time ?
There you go again with the udon.
A new... noodle army...
Second battle ?
So is this new noodle army coming?
You just wanted more to eat !
You just ordered a second serving.
Noujo Ami's "Angry" theme.
That's cute !
That's Noujo ?
Yes.
At first I didn't think it was Noujo !
Really ?
To be honest I've never wore
such a twintail style in my daily life.
Like this
Yeah yeah
Asuka tied my hair
But that's cute !
It is !
No no no...
It's cuter than what you have now.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Take that back.
Hoshino Miiiiiiiiiinaaaaaaaamiiiiiiiii "Happy" theme.
[Note: My keyboard is not damaged, that's just how I like to call Minami.]
It's Iku-chan !
Ikuta with sunglasses.
That was when fiming the PV for Aitakatta Kamoshirenai
Does Ikuta even wear sunglasses during shooting ?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Always wears them ?
No !
Hello this is Ikuta~
One would think
"But why does she have to wear sunglasses ?"
She thinks "I'm the only one allowed to wear sunglasses"
Hoshino Miiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiinaaaaamiiiiiiiiiii "Angry" theme.
Hoshino and- ?
Is this Ikuta ?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Ikuta 2 times shoot?
That's not me ! Why ?!
Ikuta~
Hoshino, what's this?
In fact I like skulls.
You like skulls ?
Yes.
This one was super cute so I got a picture.
- It's cute ?
So you like skulls ?
Yes.
So how often do you go to the cemetary ?
I don't !
It's real.
That's a real skull !
Where is this "Angry" ?
This picture is not just "Angry".
I looked at the picture with Staff-san,
At that moment I was angry.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Determined by mood.
How can we know that !
TamamiCheeks.blogspot.com
Translator:Tamami-chan,Dozo
Timming:Sayuringo-Hime