Today is the 1st anniversary of this program.
Bananaman Himura will be shocked with members introduction.
Last year audition footage,
embarassing moment from members will be shown.
Is there any conflict inside Nogizaka46?
There are tears...
Am I going insane...
Nogizaka tte Doko?
This is a free fansub. Please do not reupload, sell, or stream.
DOOONNNNN!!!!
We are Bananaman....
And Nogizaka46 members.
Wow, today all member's here.
Ok Himura, say what we'll gonna do tonight.
1 Year Anniversary Special, "Back to 1 Year Ago !!"
- This show has been aired for a year.
- So fast...
And all of you already doing activity for 1 year too, right...
Lets flashback for this one year activity.
Hmmm... lets start from members last audition.
Nooooo...
Me, I am cuter now...
What?
No one talk like that.
Final audition held in August 11th, 2011.
Lets start with Ikuta Erika.
I'm Ikuta Erika, 3rd grade junior high, 14 years old.
I can play piano. I will do everything seriously.
In the first episode, Ikuta showing her skills...
I can name the capital of the whole provinces in Japan.
Nice to meet you.
- You can name all of them?
- What about Mie?
Mie is.... hmm.... now I can't remember ^^
If not now, then when?
And then, Inoue Sayuri.
When doing wind instruments extracurricular activities,
I was chosen as conductor,
I believe in my mental power.
In Nogizaka46 1st convention,
she showed her favourite Super Sentai.
Mahou Sentai! Magiranger.
Next, Itou Marika.
1st grade high school, 15 years old.
Lately people told me that my face is like Inoue Mao
when facing the side and smiling.
Next, Yamato Rina.
I like tomato very much,
Yamatomato. Yamato Rina.
I am gonna make it to become Nogizaka46 member.
so that I can return the favor to my parent
for their supports, and everybody else too.
Next, Itou Nene.
I had experiences
in gymnastic and figure skating.
I am really confident with my sports skill.
In Episode 1, she showed her backflip skill
with her proud face.
Cute!!!
Next, Saitou Asuka.
If I make it to be Nogizaka46 member,
I will do my best in singing, dancing, and acting.
I want to be an idol who is loved by everyone.
Next, Hoshino Minami.
2nd grade junior high, 13 years old Hoshino Minami.
If I make it to be Nogizaka46 member,
I will always smile and make people happy.
I want to be an idol who is loved by everyone too.
Ok, today we will talk about the members.
We have done the questionnaires and reports from members
about the attitude change of other members from 1 year ago.
- Ikuta!
- Yes!
About Ikuta, Saitou Yuri, please.
- In the group, we had a meeting.
- Oh, you don't like it?
- No, I like it.
- Really?
Yes!
At the meeting, I have some funny opinions for her.
When I expressed my opinions,
Ikuta said, that's not like my character,
I don't want it. She totally rejected my ideas.
But now, Ikuta introduced herself while singing a weird song...
Her character become weird.
I wanna see it. Do your PR (Introduction) now.
[SING] My nickname is Ikuchan. [SING] My favourite food, Udon.
[SING] Apparently cooking is not my specialty.
What is that?
- Comedy show Introduction?
- No.
You do that for PR?
I love to sing, so I introduce myself while singing.
- Udon is your favourite food?
- Yes.
You become weird, in this 1 year.
Next, Hashimoto Nanami.
I entered this audition because I want to exhance my abilities.
I want to look for my talent and skill.
Even 1st PR is so serious.
When I was in 4th Grade, I read Galileo Galilei biography.
- Because of that, not too much if I say
that biography help me to develop my personality.
- So serious.
Next, Hatanaka Seira.
I want to be respected,
I want to be someone who is respected by many people.
Next, Miyazawa Seira.
I have a 1/4 blood of France and Japan.
I used to study in Monaco for 1 year.
I understand a little of French language and I can do ballet.
In episode 1, she showed her ballet skill.
Next, Nakada Kana.
17 years old, read from the back or front, still Nakada Kana.
I love idol very much.
- Are you ready?
- In her 1st PR, she showed her wotagei skill.
Aaa Yosha Ikuzo.... Tiger, Fire, Cyber, Fiber, Diver, Viber, Jya, Jyaaa
Thank you.
Next, Nagashima Seira.
I want to be someone who can reaches my dream,
and my wish to get into Nogizaka46 isn't gonna lose to others.
Next, Wada Maaya.
My dream is to become an idol who can give smile
and happines to everybody.
In first PR, she doing salto jump in front of audiences.
Disgusting isn't it?...
Next, Nishino Nanase.
I want to be an irreplaceable figure in Nogizaka46,
to entertain the audiences and prove to them
that this group is great.
Saitou Yuri want to tell something about Hashimoto.
As we can see in the VTR just now,
we see Nanamin just like that.
Yes... a serious person.
Especially when she say Galileo Galilei,
we know that this person is serious.
But same like Ikuchan, Nanamin also start using weird PR.
- Hashimoto too?
- Yes.
Very weird one.
Oh yeah? , please...
OK, Born in Hokkaido...
19 years old ~~
Hashimoto ...
Nanami ~~
I will say my strong determination today
with The Matrix style.
Okay... Today I have a determination.
Hold on a second...
- Thank You.
- Wait... what the heck is that?
- Is this a funny PR contest?
- Are you serious?
It's not different, it's totally weird now.
Next, Nishino.
Shiraishi has something to tell about Nishino.
At first, I wanna get close to Nishino, I greeted her, but...
Na-chan didn't answer. More like making a wall between us.
Even one year has passed...you don't like Shiraishi?
- Shiraishi is hard to be approached.
- Shiraishi.
No...
- Like being in high place.
- A high place.
- Shiraishi is beautiful, maybe...
- I know that feeling.
To greet her... I feel a little bit uneasy...
- I usually like to touch everyone, like someone next to me,
but for Maiyan, I'm afraid she'll mad.
- Mad to you...
- Using this moment... Come on Shiraishi... go forth and...
- Ok, Ok
Closer to her side.
Usually we're fine.
Are you gonna hug her??
- I'm shy...
- Shy.
Na-chan, just touch me, don't be shy.
- Hashimoto, show them.
- What about Hashimoto?
- Absolutely fine.
- Wow, very close.
Like this...
- Hmmm... How's that...
- Very close.
- Okay try again, Shiraishi. Replace Hashimoto.
- Try again now.
- I will broke my heart...
- Maybe this time will work.
Come on, come on...
Umm... We're now...
Why did it end like this??
I think we don't have crying session?
Next, Matsumura Sayuri.
I'm from Osaka, Matsumura Sayuri, 18 years old.
I love to take a walk, when I have free time
I can walk all day long.
Next, Wakatsuki Yumi.
I will definitely become Nogizaka46 member.
I'll show my voice, dance, and smile.
Also I want to become an idol who can
give motivation to everybody.
Next, Nakamoto Himeka.
I believe with the power of my glare.
I want to become an idol who can
make you melted with my eyes.
My father says, kill those juries with your glare.
Next, Noujou Ami.
I'm strong when facing a problem,
I believe I can go through any problems.
People say, I resemble a collared lizard when running.
Looks like a serious PR, but her character
change drastically when she starts running.
- This is probably the most embarrassing.
- Next, Kawago Hina.
My specialty is karate and kendo.
In karate, I achieved Black Belt Level 1.
Because I'm from countryside, I love to
take a walk while looking at the mountain and sea.
Next, Saitou Yuri.
I love idol since child.
In her every PR, she always showed
her artistic balloon skills.
Wow great.
OK, it's done!
- Matsumura haven't changed at all.
- Yep, not changed.
- Yeah, I haven't changed at all.
- Still love to take a walk during free time?
- Umm, that time... Is it okay to say this now?
- Just say it.
That time, it's all just a lie ^^
Fukagawa, you wanna say something
about Matsumura, right?
At first I think Matsumura
is a quiet and shy girl.
- But all of a sudden, she have
this secret power "SAYURINGO PUNCH".
- What?
- "SAYURINGO PUNCH".
- SAYURINGO PUNCH!?
- Secret power?
- Yes, that secret power ...
Hmmm... why did you need a secret power?
Suddenly she start using her secret power.
- Is that related to your PR?
- Yes, of course. In my PR.
Ok, do it.
Ok, Sayurin start.
Sayurin Sayurin Sayurinrin.
Sayurin Sayurin Sayuringo.
Amaimitsu tappuri Sayuringo,
minna-san go-shoumi ikagadesuka?
Anata no ha-to buchinuku zo!
SAYURINGO PUNCH.
Wow great. This group is so cool,
there are many unique characters.
Each member has their own PR...
Even matrix style. Great, interesting.
Next, about Saitou Yuri... Sakurai.
Saitou Yuri, Sakurai Reika... from the name
we always sit next to each other.
She doesn't want to look at me,
No response either when I try to talk with her.
And now?
Now, we already start touching each other.
- Touching?
- What does that mean?
Reika always can't stop talking,
while moving her face closer to mine.
That's annoying, so I get rid of her with spit.
- Wait...
- That's so wrong.
- Seems like you're the only one who act sadist here.
- You're different with the others.
The way you communicate is unique.
Even before the show, we're all spitted by her
while saying some kind of spell.
Spell? Spit with spell?
Next, Takayama Kazumi.
The more nervous, the more I smile.
Umm... I'll read a poem.
"Unforgettable, this nervous and excited feeling,"
"Nogizaka audition on a cold day in summer."
OK, Thank you so much!
Next, Iwase Yumiko.
In freshness, I might lose to the young.
But, I have my own appeal that
young girls don't have, such as sexyness.
I'm always cool-headed and
I will not lose.
In first PR, she gives the impression of her sexiness.
Yumi-nee, Iwase Yumiko.
I grew up with your voice, Game simulation Nogizaka Iwase,
I want you to raise me up. OK.
- What the heck is that.
- Next, Higuchi Hina.
I always try harder than others, with strong determination
I wanna try a lot of new things.
Her first PR, she showed her kabuki skills.
Next, Etou Misa.
Things I was proud of, I'm not picky with food,
never have a toothache... rarely sick.
Next, Kawamura Mahiro.
Kawamura Mahiro, 16 years old, 1st grade high school.
I looked like this, but I can't stop talking.
My friends always told me to stop talking.
Next, Ikoma Rina.
Born and raised in Akita, Ikoma Rina.
- Heee, you've changed.
- Im born in Yurihonsou, Akita.
At first, don't know why she always
make a pose in the end of her PR.
From this day, meeting with fans,
I'll looking forward to it.
so first of all please come to my place.
Thank you.
- Then, Takayama.
- OK, Takayama.
Takayama, the way you talk are now different.
Aaah #$%%&$##.
What? What?
You're the one who become weird all of a sudden.
It's not like in the video.
Umm... At first, I really want to
become an idol like Yamaguchi Momoe.
Yes, you've told us before.
I want to be a cool Idol.
So... I decided to become an idol with
that kind of character. I tried so hard.
So now this is the real you?
Yes, now this is the real me.
- Now.
Yes.
So, you're trying so hard with
the way you speak before?
It is so hard.
A person who suddenly change their way of talk
in this entertainment industry, it's just you.
- Really?
- Yeah right.
- EEEHHHH!!
- Yes...
\(^o^)/ AMEJINGU (AMAZING)
AMEJINGU!? Sounds cool.
Give me that. AMEJINGU
Can we use this?
After this, Bananaman will be shocked by Shiraishi's PR.
Next, Shiraishi Mai's PR.
My favorite food is sweet potato,
my favourite sauce is mayonaise.
In Episode 1, Her PR is...
Coming from the 4th dimension, 19 years old
mayo-er planet creature, Maiyan... Shiraishi Mai.
I will work hard, nice to meet you.
Next, Fukagawa Mai.
I really like reading wise word.
My favourite wise word is from Shakespeare.
"There is no happy or sad, it is just a way of thinking."
- The one with serious PR is suspicious.
- Next, Saitou Chiharu.
I can give support from behind,
and unite the members.
Next, Ichiki Rena.
I had been a Japanese representative for dance contest,
and I can show my dancing ability in the world stage.
Not only in Japan, I want to become an idol
who loved by people all around the world.
Next, Andou Mikumo.
100 times lively , ANCHAN-MAN.
Anchan, Andou Mikumo. Nice to meet you.
I studied in America for 2 years.
And came back to Japan this June.
Her first PR, Showing her English ability.
Next, Sakurai Reika.
I always wanted to perform in a big stage
with the lights and many audience.
OK, from the video we saw,
Nishino will talk about Shiraishi.
Is it okay? u'll talk about Shiraishi,
is that okay?
Maiyan, her first PR are very Idol-ish,
like 'white skin is my charm point'.
But her PR now...
- Her PR is different?
- Yes, not like Maiyan anymore.
- Please...
- Come on, show it.
Why using a Baseball bat?
- To give you spirit, I'll do Air Homerun.
- Air Homerun?
OK... tararara...
Strike... DAMN IT
ok, tarara..tararara
KAKINNNNN.... HOWS THAT!
That's how it is ^^
The senbatsu election for Nogizaka46 4th single!!!
Translator: Rustyhand
Editor / Timer : Koala13th
English Translation by Jejedeath and Archykun
Visit www.nogizakanouta.blogspot.com for more !!