Tonight on NogiDoko, on sale on the 13th of March,
We’ll have the big announcement of the senbatsu for the 5th single!
Uwaa~ She made it in!!
Filled with ups and downs and surprises, what is the conclusion of it?
Nogizakatte, Doko?
DON!
Nogizakatte Doko has started, were you're hosts,
Bananaman, yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
YAY!
Now, here's Nogizaka-chan~
hai, douzo~
Clang~
Himura-san...
they've boycotted us.
If this is how it turns out, then we’ll do this by ourselves.
Please announce what we have today.
Understood.
Our plan for today…
Nogizaka46 big announcement of senbatsu members for the 5th single?!
Cling~
So that's why they're not here, Himura-san.
So, that's why.
Yes, actually…
Until now, we have gathered all 33 members in the studio
and then have the announcement, but…
if we do that, they’ll realize what’s going on.
That’s why this time, we’ll confuse them a little,
catch them off guard with a sudden 5th single announcement.
This one’s really…
I don’t have an idea about that, goes for you as well, right?
That’s right, I don’t.
On a certain day in December,
all members are gathered in one place without knowing anything.
And right there…
Everyone in Nogizaka46, good morning.
Good morning~
Everyone is gathered here today…
Whose voice is that?
…for this.
What is it??
Seriously?!
Very well, I will now explain how the senbatsu members will be announced.
This time, the announcement venue is divided into three rooms,
In the announcement room next to where the members are…
Cards with the names of all of the members are placed.
Once opened, if the number of the position is written, then she’s in the senbatsu.
I see,
up to 16 members, huh?
Unfortunately, if it’s a blank paper, it means she’s not in the senbatsu.
The members who made it in the senbatsu will move to the new senbatsu room.
And here's the formation this time.
Just like the last time, the eight members in the front will be the 8-Fukujin.
The order of who will open their card is not determined,
Acting with their own will, one by one from the person who wants to go, they will confirm their own result.
I see.
Furthermore,
the counter in front of you shows the number of remaining senbatsu members.
Ah, this one.
If this counter reached zero, even if there are still members left in the room,
it will mark the conclusion of the senbatsu announcement.
Very well,
From those who wants to go, please go to the next room and confirm.
Eh? Starting off with
those who wants to go?
Please go ahead.
Who will start this off?
This is so harsh.
Everyone’s spirit has departed already.
Who will go first?
Adding to the news about the sudden senbatsu announcement,
Scary.
is the strict rule that they have to voluntarily confirm their own result.
That’s why...
are they going to go?
The courageous member who raised her hand first is…
Oh?
Ikoma...
Ikoma breaks this open.
The first one to go to the announcement room is…
Ikoma Rina who has served as the center for all of the singles.
It has come to this, Ikoma.
Very well, Ikoma-san,
Please open the card with your name written on it and confirm the result of your position.
If a number is written on it, you made it in the senbatsu.
If nothing is there, you are not in the senbatsu.
Oh?
#2!
Ikoma Rina, for the fifth consecutive time is in Nogizaka46's center position!
It is a position filled of painful memories.
But...
responsibly...
I want to take the responsibility.
I'll do my best.
She's the center.
Ikoma-san's result is in.
Here it is.
Waiting for that countdown will make you numb.
Well then, the next person please.
It seems like they want to go but don’t want to at the same time.
Who will go next?
Oh, there she is!
Who is it?
Is it Matsumura?
Oh.
There she goes.
Second one to raise their hand is Matsumura Sayuri who gets everyone fired up with her cheerful smile,
her result is?
Not good. This is scary.
I see, Matsumura also entered
the 7-Fukujin and 8-Fukujin.
Oh?
She made it in!
Continuing from the last time, Matsumura Sayuri made it in the 8-Fukujin!
I see!
Matsumura-san's result is in.
Here it is.
That’s how it is.
That situation where someone went but the number didn’t change,
it haven’t happened yet…
Very well, the next person please.
So far, we have those senbatsu members who were selected every time.
Oh, there she is.
Next one to go.
Hashimoto, huh?
Hashimoto Nanami who has showed numerous great efforts with her peculiar sensitivity,
and the result is…
The members who were once
selected as a Fukujin went in first.
#5
Uwaaaa, she made it in!
Just like the last time, Hashimoto impressively made it in the 8-Fukujin as well.
8-Fukujin?
Going next is...
Oh?
Indispensable in Nogizaka for her composure and tolerance,
Captain Sakurai’s result is…
Oh, she made it in!
#4
Thank you very much.
Sakurai as well, continuing from last time, impressively made it in the 8-Fukujin.
omedetou~
Going next is Shiraishi.
She doesn’t look good coming in.
You’re right.
All-rounder Shiraishi Mai who has a sense of stability and unquestioned popularity and abilities,
her result is…
Are you okay, Shiraishi?
She’s in.
She’s in the 8-Fukujin.
We were suddenly told about the announcement today,
to be honest, I wasn’t really prepared for it, but…
It would be nice if I could be someone who can lead everyone.
Ah, Ikuta.
Musical talent and responses in variety,
she has demonstrated her diverse power, Ikuta Erika’s result is…
#1
#1!
Oh!
So far, six of the 8-Fukujin who entered the new senbatsu are determined.
10 spots remaining.
Very well, the next person please.
Won’t there be any
changes in the 8-Fukujin?
Given the situation, it’ll be hard for those at the back to come forth.
Those two at the front aren’t going yet.
-Because of their fear of not making it in the senbatsu,
the members couldn’t get up from their seats.
The next person please.
Ah, so strict. No one from the under has gone yet.
They’re scared.
-Those who think they’d make it since they did their best should go.
So far, everyone who went made it in.
Oh! There she is! Who is it?
-Who is it?
As expected, Hatanaka is the man~
That girl will do anything.
Admirable.
In the situation where no one can move because of fear,
she mustered up her courage,
Hatakana is the only one who stood up from her seat.
Will she make it in after making it in the 2nd single?
You can do this,
Go Hatanaka!
Eh? She didn’t make it
since the 2nd single.
Will Hatanaka’s courage be rewarded?
No way!
Seriously?
Please tell how you feel right now while facing the camera.
This is so cruel.
I'm frustrated but...
there are still parts where I’m lacking.
For the next single…
I’ll do my best in order to make it in the senbatsu.
So harsh!
This is so harsh!
Hatanaka-san's result is in.
Here it is.
The mood is gloomy.
For the first time, they saw firsthand a failure of making it in the senbatsu,
and the fear grows further.
In this situation, the one who got up from her seat is…
Oh?
Wakatsuki is admirable.
Wakatsuki has entered the senbatsu starting from the 3rd single,
will she make it for three consecutive times?
Cool!
Oh? There it is!
Wakatsuki who never lacks effort and always grinding out
made it in the senbatsu for the third consecutive time!
And then, the 9th member who got up from her seat is…
Oh? Uwaaa.
Who is it?
Oh?
Nakada!
Nakada.
Nakada who had experienced not making it in the senbatsu last time
mustered her courage and proceeded to the announcement room.
Will she make her way back to the senbatsu?
Will she be back?
Or will she taste the bitterness of not making it in the senbatsu once again?
The result is?
Oh? She made it in!
Nakada Kana impressively made her way back from Under,
Whoa.
She made her way back.
congrats for making it in the senbatsu!
Which means it is determined that someone from the senbatsu won’t make it.
-I see.
Kana, welcome back~
I'm back~
Good for you~
Nakada-san's result is in.
Here it is.
Under’s Nakada Kana making it in the senbatsu would mean that…
one of the current senbatsu members will go to Under for sure.
Very well, the next person please.
onegaishimasu
Fukagawa!
There she is.
Fukagawa fulfilled her desire to be in the senbatsu during the 3rd single,
will she make it in for three consecutive times?
the result is…
Thank you very much.
She made it in right?
The oneesan who motivates everyone with her innate cheerfulness,
Fukagawa Mai made it in the senbatsu!
Only seven remaining.
Going next is Hoshino Minami,
her result is…
She made it in!
She singlehandedly expanded the scope of their activities,
Hoshino Minami made it in the 8-Fukujin!
More surprises after this?!
10 members of the senbatsu are determined, 6 remaining.
In this situation, the one who got up from her seat is…
Uwaa, amazing!
Coming from Under.
So far, Ito Nene never made it in the senbatsu,
will she be able to have her most desired wish of being in the senbatsu?
Which one is it?
What did she get?
There it is!
Uwaa, she made it in!
She made it!
Amazing!
She made it in the senbatsu!
Good for her~
I can't believe this.
Her first one.
She even served as center in Under, everyone’s imouto,
Ito Nene impressively made it in the senbatsu!
Uwaaaaaaa!!! Nene!!!
omedetou~
Ito-san's result is in.
With this, two of the current senbatsu members are out.
I see.
With this, it's certain that two of the current senbatsu members won’t make it.
Right here, the one who got up from her seat is…
Ito Marika made it in the senbatsu once during the 3rd single,
will she make it in the senbatsu and turn the tables?
her result is…
Uwaaa. Nothing’s in it.
There's nothing in it.
Ito Nene had gone, and with that flow,
I went by it.
I went without having confidence.
Once again, as an Under…
I’d like to do my best.
Ito-san's result is in.
Remaining current senbatsu members
Takayama, Inoue and Ichiki hasn’t gone yet.
The next person please.
HAI!
She has voice and reaction louder and bigger than anyone else,
Nogizaka’s moodmaker, Nagashima Seira went to the announcement room to gamble for her first senbatsu selection.
How will this turn out?
UWAAAAAA!
She made it in!
She made it.
It’s her first one!
I’m really happy.
Finally, her most desired wish of getting in the senbatsu,
Amazing!
she’ll be able to perform with her close friend Shiraishi.
Three from the Under made it in.
Three of them made it in.
I’m so happy!
Good for you~
I'm so happy, what to do~
omedetou~
Thank you.
I’m really happy for you~
Nakada, Ito Nene and Nagashima
Nagashima's result is in.
the three of them made it in.
Here it is.
Only four people left, because of this.
It became difficult for the current senbatsu to go there.
Next person please.
Ah, Takayama?
Takayama.
From the current senbatsu members, it is certain that two won’t make it,
Takayama’s result is…
POSITIVE & AMAZING!
Takayama Kazumi impressively made it in the senbatsu!
Three remaining.
Going next is Nishino Nanase.
Can she fulfill her most wanted wish of getting in the 8-Fukujin?
There it is.
Her wish of getting in the 8-Fukujin didn’t come true,
Two left.
nonetheless, Nishino made it in the senbatsu.
And one of the 8-Fukujin.
Noujo, Saito Asuka, Inoue, Ichiki, Akimoto.
Among these five, it is certain that three of them won’t make it.
Very well, next person please.
Who is it?
Up to this point, Ichiki never fell off the senbatsu,
will she make it in the senbatsu for the fifth consecutive time?
Oh.
Seriously?
Ichiki didn’t make it.
I have been chosen up until the 4th single, so...
I’m really grateful for that.
Congratulations to everyone who became a senbatsu member.
Ichiki-san's result is in.
Here it is.
Very well, next person please.
Ah, Akimoto.
She finally moved, Akimoto.
Last time, Akimoto made a shocking entry in the senbatsu by being a 8-Fukujin all of the sudden,
her result is…
She made it in.
8-Fukujin
Akimoto Manatsu made it in the 8-Fukujin for two consecutive times!
omedetou~
I never really thought that I’d be chosen today.
Coming in here was really scary.
Akimoto-san's result is in.
Here it is.
Remaining current senbatsu members
At last, we’re down to the last one.
Will it end without them seeing the result for themselves?
Or will they muster up their courage and try?
There goes Noujo.
Last time, Noujo Ami impressively returned to the senbatsu,
will she able to achieve two consecutive selections in a row?
Too bad.
The result is out already,
and I’ll accept this result.
Once again,
from the start,
I'd like to do my best.
Noujo-san's result is in.
Here it is.
Last one.
Very well, the next person please.
There she is.
Saito Asuka
Last time, the youngest member, Saito Asuka fulfilled her wish of making it in the senbatsu,
will she make it in for two consecutive times?
UWAAAA!
Are you serious?!
Looking back…
I haven’t done anything in order for me to retain my spot in the 5th single,
I’d like to grow more with the opportunity in Under.
Saito Asuka-san's result is in.
Here it is.
Very well, the next person please.
Will Inoue go?
There she goes.
With her innate competitive spirit, Inoue Sayuri has challenged various things,
will she make it in the senbatsu for the fifth consecutive time?
Ah! There it is!
I see, Inoue.
So that’s how it goes.
Inoue impressively made it in the senbatsu,
with that, the 16 senbatsu members for the 5th single are finally determined!
Thus, a tough and long day finally came to a close…
This one, once again…
is different from the other announcements that we had so far.
It was harsh.
For Takayama as well, do you feel like you couldn’t go?
Truth is… since it is so negative…
Don’t put it that way…
Don’t say something like that!
Say something positive! Even if it’s half-hearted!
Say an inspiring cheer.
Positive say!