Tonight on Nogidoko!
Adult members are experiencing the adult's world!
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY www.zaka46sembung.blogspot.com
These four 20 year old members
will see the world of the adults!
They will be ecstatic because of the unexpected outcome.
And their change of appearances will make the studio excited!
Nogidoko is starting and we're the MC Bananaman...
And here's Nogizaka!
Amazing!
Today, you four who sit in the front...
... what did you do?
What happened!!
Obviously this is not something good, isn't it?
Adult Nogizaka46, experiencing the adult's world!
This year, these four members will
be having the coming of age ceremony.
Welcome to the world of adults!
Today, we will accompany them who've just grown up.
We're from TIM.
Pleased to work with you!
I apologize...
... he's getting a bit too excited today.
Just ignore him.
Being an adult means...
... someone who's 20 years old.
Got it?
You want to be an adult?
We really do!
This is our first place.
Adult's entertainment area.
Incredible!
First time being here!
I was looking forward to this day!
What can you do here?
Night horse racing.
This is a good place for a dating couple.
Basically, a grown up person
should try to visit this place.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
You want to be an adult?
We really do!
You're really excited about this today.
Without further ado,
they will experience the night horse racing soon.
Look at that, beautiful, isn't it?
Beautiful!
Do you know what it's called?
The first thing you do
when you enter a horse race track is...
Buying a newspaper.
Is this today's newspaper?
Exactly.
When you buy newspaper here,
you may get candies as a bonus.
Can we get it today?
After done buying newspaper...
... we will do one more thing.
Here it is!
A horse statue.
Matsuda Seiko.
No.
Hai Seiko.
When did they change the name?
What you need to do here is
praying for luck.
Pray for it.
Try to pray.
Onegaishimasu.
Actually you don't need to pray here,
anywhere is fine.
Eh!!
Moving on...
There's a lot of good food here, you know!
Where will TIM choose to eat with members?
What is this?
Here's the place.
Many delicious food here.
TIM invites the members to enjoy premium casseroles.
So smooth!
Delicious!!
You can't ignore this food
if you're visiting this place.
Next adult spot is...
This is big!
This is the entrance to the track.
Beautiful!
Amazing!
This place is beautiful!
Do you know what is that?
Now you know it!
Next, it's time to bet!
This is your first time doing this thing...
Surely you know nothing.
The newspaper we bought before...
... let me read the content.
Double circle mark means high chance of winning.
But it's all based on the journalists' prediction.
The way you bet is also important.
Like betting on Tosaki Keita as the jockey.
Betting on him has a winning ratio of 2/1.
We're talking about three racings.
On the next race, Tosaki Keita ...
... doesn't participate.
Surprising.
No Tosaki?
So Tosaki isn't there.
Pick horses you like.
For example, Nogizaka46, bet on no. 4 and no. 6.
Many options here.
After being carefully taught...
... they'll predict the winner.
Shiraishi is betting on 1 7 9.
This is according to my intuition.
TIM doesn't know intuition
Matsumura is betting on
no. 13, no. 1, and no. 8.
Unfortunately...
Hashimoto and Etou are still underaged.
They're not 20 yet.
Shiraishi and Matsumura will bet using their own money.
What?
Getting the wallet right away
So those are their wallets!
There could be five million Yen inside!
Of course not.
How much the money inside?
9000 Yen...
Commoner Idol
Matsumura?
800...
No paper money?
Unfortunately no.
It's all receipts here.
Full of receipts
Matsumura only has 800 Yen to bet,
this is not gonna be interesting!
Then I'll bet for 800 Yen!
You serious?
What if you lose the bet?
How will you live tomorrow...
One bet of 200 Yen,
so it's 600 Yen for three bets.
What do you think?
You agree?
Shiraishi too?
Go for 500 Yen,
so it's 1500 for three bets.
1000 Yen into 3000 Yen.
I'll place a bet of 500 Yen.
You're really gambling here!
Let's place the bet!
And so, they're placing bets for the first time.
However, Shiraishi makes a mistake here...
You have insufficient money.
But I put 1000 Yen.
What if you put 1500 there.
Eh! Hold on!
Each bet is 500.
( 3 bets =  1500 Yen)
I see!
I thought it's 500 Yen for all bets!
1500 Yen for all bets
I'm not betting that much...
Who knows, you may win it!
And so, with Shiraishi places a 1500 Yen bet and Matsumura with 600,
they're having a horse race bet for the first time.
Yatta!
2 people with different bets.
Buy us yakiniku if you win!
Important Dinner
So thrilling!
They'll start.
Ready, go!
No. 11, No. 13.
Ah, No. 13 is passing them!
Come on!
This curve is a crucial moment.
No. 7.
No. 1, 12, and 2.
No. 12 is pretty great.
Ah, No. 7 is catching up!
Then there's No. 13 and 8.
7 8 13
No. 13 is leading!
Where's No. 7?
No. 7 keeps catching up!
1 and 13!
I bet for 1500...
Aaahh! Too bad!
You must be kinda frustrated right now.
I am.
What if we play it again?
Let's do it again!
Addicted?
Matsumura has succesfully predicted the winner correctly.
How much will she get?
210 Yen.
2X2=4
420 Yen!
Eeeehh!?
She bet for 600 and she got 420.
There must be a mistake here!
Unfortunately, she got nothing.
Her first bet withdrawal.
Ready, go.
Ah, it came out!
Dancing over 420 Yen?
Shiraishi, you must feel pressured now.
1500 Yen gone
Do you still have the ticket?
I do!
Go check it!
There's something?
Insert wherever you want.
Is it okay?
Just in case.
This ticket didn't win.
There will be such notification.
Shiraishi?
I was so excited...
I thought there will be money pouring down...
Next, they will continue deeper to the adult's world.
What's the next adult experience?
Where are we going?
We're on our way...
Where does the elevator take them?
We've arrived!
What is this place? Scary!
Adult place?
This place seems dangerous.
Welcome!
Is this okay?
The four scared members are being guided to a table.
Scary...
What are you scared of?
This is adult's world!
Please have a seat.
Four Tranvestites?
Kawaaaii!
Beautiful!
Kawaaiii
We're in NewHalf bar!
(A bar where the hostesses are transvestite)
This is our first time here!
This is adult's world,
NewHalf bar PARTHENO.
But since these four members still seem afraid,
one of the trannies says...
I want them to introduce themselves.
Go ahead.
I'm from Hokkaido, 19 years old, Hashimoto Nanami.
19!?
She's still 19~!
....
There goes the tsukkomi!
I'm Shiraishi Mai, nicknamed Maiyan.
Maiyaa?
My nickname is maiyan!
My charm is my round eyes...
Are they laughing?
... I'm from Oita, Eto Misa.
Why did they laugh...
Your charm is your eyes?
Yes.
I've heard something like that before!
vs adult.
Scary, scary!
Alright, ready...
I'm Sayurin!
Where are we going?
We're not going anywhere.
Sayurin Sayurin Sayurinrin~
Sayurin Sayurin Sayuringo~
Do you want to taste the sweetness of "Sayuringo?
(*Ringo = apple)
Eh? Why not?
Crushed idol image
Thanks to the trannies talking,
the members don't feel awkward anymore.
Here we will change the seat formation
so they can feel closer.
Are you friends with others?
Yes.
Close friends?
We are!
You must've talked ill about others, am I right?
Is that true?
She must have talked bad things like your introduction.
There's no such thing!
What about Sayurinrin?
Sayurin looks worrisome.
End of friendship.
Why?
She's 20 yet she still acts like that.
Like Sayuringo for example...
- That name shouldn't be used anymore.
I think so too!
A session.
Do you want to talk like me?
Never ever!
I have something else too!
What's that?
Sayuringo punch!
Iwakong punch!
A smack to the face.
After the scare went away,
they're talking about something fun.
It's time for a performance.
How will it be?
Cute!
They're cute!
They look like idols.
[Seifuku no Mannequin]
What are you doing in the middle of the show!
What's with your terrible look?
You don't know?
This is like Nogizaka46.
46?
You don't have any resemblence whatsoever!
Who are they actually?
I am Matsumura Sayurin!
Why do you dress like that?
You don't know me?
Shiraishi...
The real person is there!
Where?
How unfortunate, this ugly person is copying you!
- Who are you?
- I'm Shiraishi Mai.
If you are the real one,
can you show the dance of the song just now?
I can.
Let's start dancing!
In the end, Shiraishi leads the dance on the stage.
What is this?
Embarassing!
Someone help me!
Eh!
You're a fake too!
Now go back!
The show goes on and on.
The four members are watching excitedly.
Then...
- Tip, please?
- Tip!?
At the end of the show,
members are tipping for the first time.
What will these two do?
Handing changes.
Giving a good impression,
members are tipping the trannies with coins.
The fun ended here.
How do you feel?
I think I'm not a kid as of now.
So don't you use Sayuringo anymore.
Perhaps I'll change it into something sexier.
Sayuringo Punch!
Sexy Up?
Seems a bit different!
Just a bit.
Members' changes make studio the go wild!
What is the next adult experience?
Now we'll change your appearances to look like mature women.
Appearance is very important, isn't it!
You still look like a kid now.
Look!
She looks like a girl!
She doesn't look like an adult woman!
Turn around.
Just like a girl!
You said it before.
And so, the place where they're doing their makeover is...
Mercury at Marui Jam Shibuya
Many elegant and mature designs
can be found here.
The makeover in this place...
... is also by stylist Inokuma Natsuko,
who has made clothing trends.
Please explain the concept for them.
To look mature and sexy.
Let's start from searching a good clothes for Hashimoto!
Since your hair is short,
you need to wear something white.
Looks good on her!
Look at the model here.
And it looks good coupled with this one!
Very nice!
She'll wear that?
Not wearing short pants?
No.
Looks like something to wear in spring.
Next is Shiraishi.
Cute!
I don't wear pink often.
I understand your problem.
Really?
She can show her beautiful legs
with this dress!
So she's not wearing short pants?
No.
Legging pants?
Next, Matsumura.
This one piece dress.
Nice color!
First time I'm wearing that! Embarassing!
With this jacket, the maturity will show.
This suits very nicely!
Incredible!
Really, I've never worn clothes with such color.
Lastly, Eto.
Eto Madoguchi!!!
No, no!
Since you possess a beautiful face...
... your maturity will show wearing this shirt.
Looks very good!
I rarely wear clothes like this.
With a bit of accessories,
you'll look elegant.
Combined with your beautiful face,
you'll look more mature.
Amazing!
Thank you very much!
This is what you wished for, right?
Let's blend in public.
7 Misunderstandings
You look
like models!
Alright! OK!
Ahh, so cold!
6 degree celsius
That was the first time I saw a sexy Mattsun.
I'm so happy!
Matsumura changed drastically!
Why did my face look like that?
But it's cute.
You look beautiful with that mature look.
That's cool!
Looks pretty mature!
Emotional face?
Honestly it wasn't like this!
I had no intention to strike such pose!
She did it on camera a lot!
Yes, she did that often!
There was also this pose.
Yes, there was!
Did you come up with this pose yourself?
This one was my own.
"The correct pose."
What's with this one?
Like I'm cleaning my lips.
What did you do?
That's nice!
You look more like an adult!
So you rarely wear this color?
I almost never wear pink!
This one looks just like an ad model.
Was that the poster?
Those 4 look like they've been waiting for this year.
You went to NewHalf bar.
Interesting!
The trannies were teasing you.
Shiraishi even did a performance.
Was it embarassing?
Seriously embarassing!
You even forgot a move there!
The tranny was wearing a very short skirt.
She was Matsumura.
But Matsumura also wears short skirt like that too, right?
These 4 members have experienced the world of adults.
And now they're having a coming-of-age ceremony!
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY www.zaka46sembung.blogspot.com