4th single campaign! Hit prayer in places that bring good fortune!
What they’re attempting to do is dangerous!
From all corners of the country, risking their lives, they’ll attempt rigorous ascetic exercises!
Considered as the harshest location shoot in Nogidoko’s history,
What kind of fate awaits for the members?!
Nogizakatte, Doko?
Nogizaka46's 4th single, Seifuku no Mannequin is on sale!
which means...
So, every time a new single goes on sale, in order for it to sell…
Campaign.
And this time, we’ll do it too.
Himura-san,
-Yes?
Just like a Mannequin, please announce what we have for today.
Let’s do the hit prayer in places that bring good fortune!
For this campaign, the members are split into four teams,
They’ll go to various highly regarded places that bring good fortune to do the hit prayer for Seifuku no Mannequin.
This is by far the harshest of them all.
I think it’s not on that level where it’ll just make you cry.
I think there’ll be a casualty.
Serious matter.
No one will die!
And the places where they'll do the hit campaign are?
Here it is!
JAN!
What is this all about?
The members will do a hit prayer on places related to these four categories.
Mountain
Fire
Cliff
Water
The place where each team will go is decided by Himura via draw lots.
First up, Ikoma-Nishino-Fukagawa-Wakatsuki Team.
Cliff!
Next, Shiraishi-Matsumura-Inoue-Saito Asuka Team.
Mountain!
And then, Sakurai-Hashimoto-Hoshino-Takayama Team.
Fire!
All that’s left for Ikuta-Akimoto-Ichiki-Noujo Team is…
Jyan! Water.
This time, as for the objective, every member has to complete the hit prayer.
I see.
Not just one, they all must complete it.
They must complete it until the end.
That is their objective.
The four teams will split up, departing to the prayer location.
DON!
Tottori Prefecture, Touhaku District, Misasa Town.
We’re Team Mountain, and for that,
we’ve arrived safely here in Tottori prefecture!
Yes, we’ve come to Tottori.
The place related to “Mountain” where this team is going to is…
Ready, set...
Eh? That one?
You're going there?
Here?
You are all going there to do the hit prayer.
Here is Mt. Mitoku, Sanbutsu-ji, Nageire-do.
Standing on the top of a cliff, this temple has 1300 years of history.
In the past, military commanders would go and pray here before the battle,
Having their prayers for luck at winning fulfilled,
it is said that this place truly brings good fortune.
However, to get there, they must go through a trackless path and a steep cliff.
There are a lot of visitors coming here,
and in the past, there were incidents of death due to slipping down.
Regulation which prohibits visitors to climb up alone was adopted.
It is called as the Japan’s most dangerous National treasure shrine.
They immediately changed into monastic attire and prayed for safety in their journey.
You're all properly
suited up for this.
Under the guidance of Sanbutsu-ji’s deputy chief priest,
for the sake of the big hit prayer, they’re headed to Japan’s most dangerous national treasure!
Woah, this is quite something.
Everyone has this same outfit?
Befitting of the nickname Japan’s most dangerous national treasure,
Immediately after entering the mountain area,
climbing up with both hands...
the steep mountain path continues.
And then…
This place is called Kazura-zaka.
If you make one misstep, you will fall to the bottom of the ravine, leaving serious injuries.
The first obstacle, Kazura-zaka
They must grab and climb the roots of a tree protruding from a vertical cliff,
If an accident happened, serious injuries are inevitable.
The danger level is: 7.
This is dangerous, indeed.
Maiyan! Ganbare~
The roots of the tree they’re climbing is along a steep cliff.
There are a lot of spots to step on,
You better grab on the roots tightly.
If they lost their footing, it will be a 10 meter drop.
Without assurance about their lives and with a great danger, they move along the mountain trail.
I’m scared, I’m scared, I’m scared. Wait up, wait up, wait up.
I think it’s better if you hold on to that root on the uppermost part.
Even though they overcame a dangerous spot,
one dangerous slope after another awaits for the members.
Do your best! For the sake of being a hit, do your best.
Hang in there! For the hit prayer.
It’s alright, please believe in yourself and come up.
An hour and a half passed since they entered the mountain area.
The paths were always like this?
All throughout?
The members keep on climbing the dangerous trackless path.
From the extreme nervousness of having their lives in danger,
Their tired looks has begun to show.
However, there are new difficulties!
Please wait!
This is not good.
This is the bottom of the ravine, right?
The second obstacle, Kusari-zaka
They have to cling onto the exposed rocks to climb up,
and while holding on to the chain, they will climb the cliff just like rock climbing.
An accident here would be life-threatening, so the danger level here is at the max of 10.
Once your feet slipped, you’ll be at the bottom.
Fear of death.
So be careful.
We have to hold on tight.
ganbare~ Maiyan~
Despair.
Clinging on a vertical rock is what it’s like,
Using both hands and feet to support their own body weight,
but aiming for the top.
I’m stumped.
Eh? Wait! What am I gonna do?
While being frightened by the fear of death accompanying them,
the members take on this max-level dangerous path.
Aa, I have arrived!
Thank goodness!
Shiraishi cleared the cliff with a length of approximately 15 meters.
Then, Matsumura, followed by Inoue, they have scaled this cliff!
Ashu, do your best! Just a little more!
How will I go forward~?
Left behind in the middle of the cliff is Saito Asuka.
Going this way?
Because you’re
too small, right?
This is your first climb, right?
Eh? I'll die, I'll die, I'll die...
I’m gonna die.
Really, I will die!
Saito Asuka looked at the bottom of the cliff and came into a panic about death.
The deputy chief priest is on the rescue.
And then…
You did great! Thank goodness.
Tears.
That was the most terrifying experience I’ve had.
-It is scary, right?
She got rescued.
It’s better if you don’t look down.
However, they have no time to cry. The next obstacle is…
Now, everyone will climb this rock.
Scary.
Clinging on to the chain, they have to keep their body upright and move in perpendicular to the surface.
That’s dangerous!
In order for Shiraishi to overcome her fear, she started to...
You started to say something,
Seifuku no Mannequin.
as the elevated train went by.
I tried reading your lips but,
Was it yes or no?
It’s really a nice song!
ganbare~
Just like that.
Sayurin, sing up!
Unsteady footing.
Are you okay?
Try to get your body steady then climb up gradually.
Where are you off to?
Ah, this is great~
-Okay, sing.
If you don’t try taking one step forward,
Nothing will start.
This is really a nice song!
Next is Inoue.
And then, even Saito Asuka who cried heavily earlier,
overcame her fear of the steep trail.
Everyone cleared the great obstacle, Kasuri-zaka.
And then, about two-thirds of the whole journey, there's a hall.
Here in the Monju-do, the priest performed a sutra chant.
Superb view.
Awesome. But it’s scary,
you might fall down.
It’s so beautiful!
So beautiful!
It’s beautiful but scary
at the same time.
No handrails.
From the recommendation of the deputy chief priest, the members will shout their personal wishes towards the mountains.
Here I go.
I hope I get to eat yakiniku every day!
Appetite comes first.
I hope we could meet Tamori-san!
then, I hope to become a lady with a nice body!
I want to eat yakiniku with all 33 members!
I hope to meet Gosei Knight-sama!
And then,
of course, I want to eat yakiniku!
Yakiniku sect.
Let’s eat!
We hope we could eat a lot of yakiniku!
After they finished their yakiniku prayers, they’re on their way again.
They move along the trail while holding on to the steep cliff.
The members will surmount a rock over a cliff with a height over 50 meters without any safety cables.
Devoted to climbing cliffs, three hours have elapsed. And then…
We’re here!
Ah! Great!
National Treasure Nageire-do.
This is it.
We’ve arrived. Finally!
Amazing!
-We did it!
Thank you for coming all the way up here.
Although along the way, I was wondering how many of you will give up..
Thank you for your hard work.
With desperation, they arrived at Nageire-do to pray for a hit.
All of Nogizaka46,
praying for the 4th single, Seifuku no Mannequin, to become a big hit.
We hope that Seifuku no Mannequin becomes a big hit!
Ready, set~
We also hope that Bananaman-san will sell more!
Since we’re doing a hit prayer anyway.
4th single hit prayer, finished successfully!
We're indebted.
You even did a prayer for Bananaman.
We mentioned it before your departure last time,
We asked you to pray for us too and you remembered that.
We're thankful for that.
This one's really incredible!
"Is that a cliff?” was what I thought.
-There are cliffs there, right?
The trail is always next to a cliff, all the way through.
This is really amazing.
-Right?
Those personal wishes in the middle, what’s up with those?
Shiraishi, what was that again?
I wished that I want to meet Tamori-san.
You wanted to meet Tamori-san
Then I want to become a lady with a nice body. Two wishes.
This one is likely to come true.
If you wait in front of Alta, you’ll meet Tamori-san for a while.
Studio Alta – studio in Shinjuku where Tamori-san’s Waratte Iitomo was filmed.
Waiting for him to exit.
That’s not what you meant, huh?
About that, you haven’t made an appearance on Music Station yet?
We haven’t.
On the next single, it would be great if that happened.
Let’s go to MSte!
After this, through a spiritual training, the members are beaten up?!
Sakurai team’s hit prayer related to “Fire”.
Let’s do Seifuku no Mannequin’s hit prayer!
Fukuoka Prefecture, Miyawaka City
Located in the mountains of Fukuoka Prefecture, Miyakawa City, the four members arrived in Fukoji.
And the good fortune related to fire that the members will be able to experience here is…
On the mountain, good fortune…
On top of that, it is related to fire.
Fire on a mountain will only make a terrible dangerous fumes.
Unpleasant premonition.
I’m guessing that because the autumn leaves are beautiful and resembles fire…
That is a nice argument.
That’s nice! I’m so happy.
Momiji manjuu.
Momiji – autumn colors
Momiji manjuu – manjuu shaped like a Japanese maple leaf.
What do you mean?
Eating momiji manjuu or something like that.
Setting the momiji manjuu aside,
The four of them went to the chief priest in order to know about the good fortune related to fire
We would like to ask if there is a good fortune related to fire.
There is. It is the Hiwatari Shinji.
Hiwatari Shinji – Shinto fire walking ritual
Saito Goma – Shugendo fire ritual
Then there is also Saito Goma, which is performed in Mt. Hiei and other different places.
What the four members will attempt to do is a ritual done once a year, Bishamonten Hiwatari Shinji.
Their wish are written on a piece of a wooden stick which will be burned.
It is said that walking over the fire will fulfill one’s wish.
Moreover, in order for them to participate as devotees this time, they have to undergo a ceremony.
First is…
Let’s do Zazen meditation in order for your minds  to calm down properly.
Zazen – seated Zen meditation usually in a cross-legged position.
This is my first time.
Place your right foot on your left… Ah, no.
Place your left foot above the right leg and then place your right foot above your left leg.
Ouch!
Too stiff.
If that’s not possible…
And then, we will commence the Zazen training to calm their spirit.
Sit still.
And then, without delay…
Frightened look.
Join your hands together.
Aims at Hoshino.
Hoshino is…
She's like "Why me?"
Fainting in agony.
And then, in rapid succession…
A shriek of intense pain came out after the blow coming from above,
However, coming from the chief priest…
Isn’t that a little lenient?
Finding flaws.
It's not something to be frantic about.
It really hurts.
Well then, I’ll do it seriously just a little.
Upgrade.
Bombardment.
That one's completely different.
And then, Hashimoto also received the same damage.
Okay, it have served its purpose.
Even after preparing their spirit with Zazen meditation,
In order to perform the Hiwatari Shinji, the members will continue even further in their training.
Right here, in order to form a connection with Fukoji’s primary deity, Bishamonten,
they must undergo a ceremony called Kechien-kanjou
Kechien-kanjou – a ritual to form a connection with deities.
A person can’t participate on the Hiwatari Shinji as a devotee if they didn’t go through this ritual.
Now then, for the sake of the hit prayer!
However…
Battling with drowsiness.
That expression is awful,
Takayama!
Right after this, they will challenge the scorching hot Hiwatari Shinji!
The Kechien-kanjou ended smoothly, so they can now participate in public as devotees.
The four members carried the wooden stick with their hit prayer written on them, which will be burned at the Hiwatari Shinji.
Finally, it’s time to challenge the Hiwatari Shinji! However, there is a shocking scene!
Shortly after kindling the fire, the smoke rises vigorously,
Spreading terror to the ritual.
Apocalypse?
While the fire slowly rises,
they will throw their wooden sticks with the hit prayer written on it into the fire. However…
I hurled it so hard it went to the other side!
It didn’t go into the fire at all. What do I do~?
What?! Who would have ever thought that this will happen?!
The precious wooden stick that Takayama threw never get into the fire.
Wooden stick out of bounds.
-Now It won’t be a hit anymore.
And then Takayama’s wish is left as it is.
Hiwatari Shinji will now start!
Is it hot?
It’s quite hot!
It’s so hot today!
The chief priest said that this year is likely to be the hottest of all time.
She even said “Seriously, be careful.”
In this record high temperature, the other devotees also have agony written all over their face.
A detestable path, Hitawari Shinji, the danger level is: 10.
We'll start with Hashimoto.
Praying for the 4th single to become a hit! It’s hot!
Was it hot?
Since I got to say the hit prayer, I think it’s okay!
Hashimoto, not letting up to the heat, impressively walked on fire while saying the hit prayer.
Next, Sakurai.
Motivate yourself!
Praying for a hit!
It’s hot!
Sakurai shouted for a hit prayer, but,
unable to bear the heat, she dashed all the way to clear it.
Next, Hoshino.
What to do?!
It will hurt if you jumped up and down, you just have to walk properly.
Jumping prohibited.
She’s dashing!
Hoshino forgot the advice about jumping up and down,
on top of that, she forgot about the hit prayer.
But somehow, she succeed in the task.
Last is Takayama,
Will she be able to walk properly and do the hit prayer?
It’s hot!
Takayama endured the heat while walking desperately,
although the way she walked was disgusting, she impressively cleared the hit prayer!
This part right here was really hot.
Minami’s legs are trembling like “gakugaku”!
And with that, the hit prayer of walking on fire,
Everyone finished it successfully!
Fire team, you walked on fire.
Actually, when you take a quick glance at it,
It seems that the fire died out, so it looks like it’s not hot at all!
Hashimoto you were really composed.
It was really hot.
You were walking normally, Hashimoto.
I thought that it was dangerous, but then,
everyone were doing like this after that.
Overreaction?
It’s because Hashimoto has a really weak reaction.
Isn't Hashimoto’s reaction right on the mark? What’s the truth?
It was really hot!
What about Hoshino? Didn’t you get any burn from that?
-Are you okay?
Yes, I’m fine.
Honest.
Look! She’s completely fine!
She’s completely fine!
Don’t make it exaggerated, Takayama-san!