In tonight's nogidoko, the June bride is decided! Members take on a test to see who is the most suited to be a bride!
The members challenge an ad lib drama!
They have to act as refined ladies in front of their "parents"!
But sudden happenings occur in the midst of each scene!
the members try to avoid the emergency situations!
Brought to you by IkomaSubs
For more subs visit www.Facebook.com/IkomaSubs
Translated by Jiaemi
Timed by Michael Soares
QC by ramenrider
BAM! Nogidoko has started we're your hosts Bananaman!
And here are the girls!
ready and .. TUNA!
As for the plan for today, Himura!
Yes!
Please announce it in a happy manner
Got it!
Oh! Happy manner!
Who is the most suited to be the June Bride?
Nogizaka46 Bride Test!
You girls are idols, but guys would think which one of you they would love to have as a bride
I see
Today, we check your aptitude as a bride
Yes
And other areas related to being a bride
But because you guys won't be getting married that soon ..
Umm, none of you are married yet right?
None of us are married
By law, you can get married at the age of 16
Marriage confirmation
For today, Manner Coach Igaki will be aiding in determining member's bride aptitude
The first test would be
The test of the choice of words
A fine lady will choose refined words to say
With that said, the girls take a test in which they have to edit a casual sentence into a refined sentence
Without further ado, the first question to change into a refined sentence is this!
「 Eat it while it's warm 」
Eat .. Eat it while it's warm
For this question, let's look at Wakatsuki's answer
Please enjoy your meal while it's warm
This sounds correct!
This is a model answer
As expected!
Amazing!
Please enjoy your meal
Next, Hoshino
Minami~
Hoshino should be okay
Even if you say that ..
Hoshino should be able to do this right?
Hoshino's answer is this
Eat it while it's warm okay~? ❤
Cute~!
Please understand that because you say that her way of talking is cute, the way she speaks becomes more unrefined!
Educational Guidance
That's no good I tell you!
What she's doing now isn't cute!
That's right, sensei this is incorrect right?
Yes that's right, the heart she put to mask something makes me wonder about her character
That's right
❤ Strictly prohibited
A heart symbol doesn't represent gentleness or anything you know!
Lets move to the next person, Matsumura!
Here is Matsumura's answer
Hahahaha!
Shock!
Please finish everything while it's hot!
You can't leave any food behind?
Forced eating
It sounds like an order right?
That's right, when you phrase it like that, it sounds like an order
Therefore it doesn't sound that good to the other party
Ahh .. I see!
It's like eating at a stubborn old man's stop, a gentle stubborn old man
Please eat it while it's hot!
It puts pressure on the other party
The next question is this!
「 Shall we go? How is it? Super subtle 」
This is difficult
This question is rather difficult right?
For this question none of you got it correct so there's no model answer
sensei, if you were to change this into a refined sentence how would you go about it?
This sentence means that it is difficult to decide on whether to go or not to go
The choice to go or not to go, a difficult decision to make
Umm .. Ikuta!
Ikuta you have the image of being refined
Lets have a look shall we? Here is Ikuta's answer
Shall we get going? No?  I'm very unstable
What is this?!
Somehow, her answer seems close
Initially I had the intention to change the sentence part by part into refined language
This is amazing~!
Sensei this sentence is wrong right?
I don't get what she's trying to say at all
Snipped
It sounds as if a maniac is talking to himself
Shall we go? No? I'm very unstable
Extreme monologue
The next question is this!
「 The pancake from that store is seriously badass right?」
I see
The word 'yabai' can be used in a lot of ways
That's right!
It can be used in many ways right?
Lets look at Hashimoto's answer, here!
The pancake from that store is very delicious, am I right?
This is the model answer we're talking about right?
This is the model answer
I'm relieved
This is what we're looking for!
Awesome!
This sentence seems like a given to get it correct
Yes, there isn't even a need to purposely make it sound refined
Ikoma!
Yes
Ikoma's answer is this!
I wonder what I wrote
The pancake from that store is seriously badass right!!
Where did it change? Which part of the sentence did you change?
Added an 「u」
consonant to the end
your answer is almost the same as the question
Right?
Changing it from "It's badass right? to "It's badass!!" sounds more ..
You added the 「u」 consonant to make it sound more impactful right?
That's right!
Nishino
Yes
Nishino you seem to able to answer such questions properly
Lets have a look, here it is!
The pancake at that shop is really "yabashiew"
What language?
What's with the word yabashiew!?
We sometimes say Oishu to describe something delicious right?
It's spectacularly delicious?
And then ..
But yabashiew is too ..
It seems like it would become a popular lingo
What exactly is yabashiew? It sounds like the name of a siew mai from some restaurant
「 Yaba 」 Specialty
Yabashiew!
Yabashiew right?
Sensei, this word yabashiew, is bad right?
Yes it's totally bad! really!
This is bad right?
Yes it is
Sakurai!
Sakurai you're the leader right? You have to properly answer such things or we would be troubled
Wait a moment .. what question is this?
Sakurai's answer is this
That pancake is so delicious that it would make you feel like you can reach the skies after eating it
Pancake that
makes you high
Are you okay?
Yabashiew!! Yabashiew!!
What the hell is this!
Yabashiew!
Well .. it might be a good answer but one thing's for sure is that you're strange
I understand what you're trying to say but ..
Right?
But such elaborate elaboration is overkill ..
That's right
It's so embarrassing...
Gradual shame
You had an 'oishi' moment
The next question is this!
Are you at home tomorrow?
How do you rephrase this?
The model answer is from Hashimoto
Would you be at your place of residence tomorrow?
EHHH?
Wow wonderful!
Oh she changed it to residence!
Isn't this answer wonderful?
This answer is splendid, it's quite rare someone manages to answer this question
Amazing, I couldn't think of that
Hoshino!
It's about time you gave an appropriate answer!
You aren't stupid
I have confidence in this answer!
You have confidence in this question?
She will be okay
You didn't answer with a ❤ symbol?
No I didn't!
She didn't!
I beg of you to get the correct answer
Hoshino's answer is this!
Are you at home the day after tomorrow?
EHHHH?!
She changed the meaning of the sentence!
Date change
Why did you change the date!
I think she thought it was rude to ask if someone is at home tomorrow so she changed it to the day after
When I tried to change the sentence into a refined sentence, I ended up with that...
So if we tell you in a refined way about tomorrow's plans, we have to tell you it's the day after?
I understand it now!
Mmm ..
Why did I answer it that way I wonder?
Hoshino's mystery
The test consisted of 10 questions, Sakurai scored the top with 8 points, Hashimoto and Wakatsuki tied at second with 7 points
The test is far from over, from here on we will be testing your practical knowledge
Oh practical knowledge!
The scenario is when you go to your boyfriend's house to make your first greeting
For this, please take it seriously and let sensei praise you for your good work
From here on, the girls would challenge this ad lib drama of going to her boyfriend's home to greet his parents
The parent's roles would be undertaken by actors while Himura will play the boyfriend role
And Igaki sensei would make the judgement whether they are refined or rude
There might be sudden happenings as a result of Shitara giving instructions to trip them up!
The members would also be judged based on their ability to adapt!
The areas of judgement are
1. How the initial greeting is done
2. Method of taking off shoes
3. The method of giving the gift
4. The way of eating
The first challenger is Sakurai!
Lets begin shall we?
The first meeting of your boyfriend's parents!
This is the first time you've been to my house right?
That's right! What should I do? What if I do something rude?
Are you okay?
But honestly speaking, my parents are really strict about proper manners
Eh!? EHHHH?
Lets go in!
I'm home!
Welcome back!
Ah! Welcome back!
Sorry for bothering you all
Why did you suddenly come back?
Nice to meet you
Nice to meet you both, I'm currently dating Yuki, I'm Sakurai Reika, I'll be in your care
It isn't good to use his first name, she should use his full name with an honorific like san or kun
Oh I see!
Why don't you invite them in
Please come in!
Excuse me
Somehow it's more nerve wrecking for us spectating
Oh, that's good
This step should be done right
Look at such a cute girl our son has brought home!
You're making me embarrassed if you say that!
Himura would you please say "What was that about?"
Mother what did you mean by that?
Eh?
Rebellious phase?
You see our son has brought such a cute girl home!
Thats right!
You heard what they're saying?
Say something like "What's with you both!"
Whats with you both!
You have never talked to us like that before! Right?
Sorry sorry!
Absolute obedience
to (Shitara's) instructions
Anywhere is okay, just sit where you like
Think of this as your own home, please sit at the place you like!
Then, I'll sit here
Sitting on the cushion is not proper
Have you all seen before people doing the New Year's greeting by bowing without sitting on the cushion?
Ah sorry, thank you very much!
She stood up again!
It is a no-no to stand on the cushion
Standing on top of the cushion is NG
The cushion should not be stepped on
Father how old are you currently?
Sorry it isn't much, please accept this if you would like
Thank you for taking the expense to present this gift
She passed the gift along with the bag but you aren't supposed to pass the bag along with the gift
Take it out from the bag and then present the gift
This is difficult!
What is this? Coffee and tea has been served
She shouldn't use her hand to hold the cup's sides
You shouldn't use your other hand to hold it?
For such cups you should only use one hand to hold it
What are you two talking about?
It's nothing! Quickly serve the dessert
Okay okay I get it
Seems like they're eating dessert
I bought these cakes from your favorite confectionery
You went all the way there?
And also, that delicious cream puff had only one left, Reika-chan you eat it
They gave the only cream puff to her
We've eaten it before so you eat it
It's okay!
There is a point to this action too
There is a point to it?
How should she go about it?
This is good stuff! Yuki you like it don't you?
I've never really seen someone eat a cream puff before!
Look at the way you're eating Yuki .. geeze!
This somehow seems ..
You don't use a fork?
You eat a cream puff by splitting it and dipping the bite sized portions into the cream
EHHHH?!
You can use your hands?
It's fine
The basics of eating it is to use your hands to split it and eat it
Ahh so that's it! This is difficult! Even at areas like these there's manners involved
Yes that's right
May I spark a happening?
Father, please keep saying that "This macaron is so delicious" towards the cream puff
I wonder how she would react
Please have a bite
It's delicious right?
Mmm!
Please say "These macarons are delicious!"
These macarons are so delicious!
I wonder how she would react to this
It's delicious right?
How is the macarons?
It's delicious, it's the first time I've eaten this, so it's called a macaron?
"But macarons are famous! Have you never eaten them before?"
Casual question
Aren't macarons famous?
But this is the first time I've had this kind of macarons, it's really delicious!
Macaron approval
You like macarons?
I love it
Sensei if she doesn't correct them is it okay?
It's good that she's going with the flow, but I would like for her to subtly correct it somewhere
Well then, Himura please say in a small voice "Is this a macaron?"
Is this a macaron?
Forcing the conversation
Ask if that is a macaron again
This is a macaron?
Yes it is
Do you have any specialty dishes?
Himura please whisper it to her again
This is a macaron?
KY Power
KY: Can't read the situation
Father please ask her to eat the macaron
Reika please eat the macaron
Thank you very much
Macaron pushing
Mother please ask her to eat the macaron too
As for cooking, omurice would be my best dish
Oh I see
Please eat the macaron
Okay, thank you very much!
Macaron storm
Reika .. Reika!
You should tell them that this isn't a macaron!
I can't say that!
Correction rejection
It would be better for you to do that
It's fine!
But this isn't a macaron!
It's fine! Keep quiet for a while!
It's fine
This isn't a macaron!
It's fine! This is a macaron!
"But it's wrong!"
But it's wrong!
"It's a mont blanc tart!"
Delicious!
THIS IS A MONT BLANC TART ISN'T IT!?
New dumb comment
Eh?!
This isn't a mont blanc tart
Then what is that?
It's a macaron
A macaron doesn't look like that
It's a macaron ..
Okay finish!
How was it?
It was scary! I definitely did alot of NGs
Over here, sensei said you were quite okay
You scored quite well!
Ehhh wow! I was really nervous
You did maintain your smile and properly handled matters
The way you replied was good too, from watching I thought that you were raised well
Ahh .. I'm relieved to hear that
And also that was a cream puff!
That wasn't a macaron okay
Macaron problem
But .. but!
What should she do in that kind of situation?
What should I have done?
When everyone around her says it's a macaron
Dumb family
Even though it's a cream puff
It would be better to subtly say that you think it's a cream puff
But, it was quite good right?
The atmosphere was good
It wouldn't be too good if you strongly rejected the claim that it was a macaron
From what we saw, you should score well
With that said, sensei how would you score her?
This is difficult to decide ..
Please give a score based upon 100, well this is going to be a benchmark for the following acts
She had some bad points regarding her manners but she carried the conversation well
On the whole, she scored around 90 points
That's wonderful!
90 points!
Right after this, a happening from hell attacks the members!
Next challenger is Ikuta!
I'm home!
Father, mother I'm home!
Excuse me
Welcome back!
Ikuta Erika is my name, please treat me well
Her self introduction was good
Right?
Excuse me
Please do
Ah! Showing your back is NG
It's wrong right?
Erika, think of here as your own home
Okay
Sit where ever you like
Okay, then I'll sit right here
Okay
She did another NG by sitting on the wrong place
I see
These sitting positions are quite hard to understand right?
Yes
The seat closer to the exit should be the Lower Seat
So she should sit at the seat nearest to the exit?
Yes
Seems like they decided on tea
Sorry we live in a rural area
Not at all!
At what point of time should she do her greetings?
She just bought it in a hurry
- When the mother is not sitting down would be a good timing to present the gift
If you would like, please accept this gift
Good timing!
Put it on the table?
This is good, it's supposed to be taken out from the bag
You don't present the bag along with the gift?
The bag's purpose is to act as a carrier and it's not something to be given
I see!
Here, Ikuta is presented with cake but.. !
Please eat the mille feuille
Thank you very much!
Father please say that "No that's a macaron!"
Mother, that's a macaron!
The macaron trap
Ah! It's a macaron, I'm sorry I got it wrong!
The macaron is delicious right?
The macaron is very delicious
Acceptance-type
The atmosphere seems good
Himura please say that it's not a macaron
This isn't a macaron right!?
But they said it's a macaron
Father please ask her if the macaron is delicious
But this isn't a macaron!
The macaron is delicious right?
Please say "Isn't this the Hagi no Tsuki?"
Hagi no Tsuki: Fluffy sponge cake from Sendai
But isn't this the Hagi no Tsuki!?
Problem complicates
Now for the complication, for this time the father would leave the seat
And when he returns his zipper would be wide open
We would see how she reacts to this
What's up with that Yuki
UWAHHH!
Lets see how she reacts to this
Riveted gaze
Is it delicious?
Ask her what is the matter
Recently ..
Yes?
I've been concerned about my stomach flab
Yes
"When I do sports which requires me to turn around, it's tough on my stomach"
It doesn't seem so at all!
Strategy to avoid looking
When I do sports which requires me to turn around, it's tough on my stomach
It would be bad if the others see this
I see
It would be best for her to tell him about the zipper as soon as she sees it
"My knees are hurting"
My knees are hurting
Ah your knees, I see!
Please take a seat then!
Please do!
Ouch ouch!
Are you okay?
Further emphasis
ow ow oww ..
This scene is rather tedious
Even imagining it is tiring
Please take a seat
Mother and Himura please come back
You two please laugh out loud when you discover that father's zipper is unzipped
What were you two doing?
Wait...
His zipper is!
What is it?
Please laugh out loud
Please laugh even harder!
What is the matter?
Eh what's the matter??
Dumb mother & son
Eh? What's the problem?
Your zipper!
Father please feel embarrassed
Father please say in an
embarrassed tone "What is this!?"
Wait a second!
Chaos
"Why didn't you tell me?"
You could have told me about this!
I didn't realize it at all! I'm sorry!
His zipper is open!
Disorderly state
Wait, please don't laugh!
Please don't laugh!
Himura please say "I think it's time for us to go home"
I think it's time for us to go home
I'm really sorry!
Go home?
Suddenly sane
It's time for us to go home
At the end where everyone laughed enabled me to have a very fun time!
What were we laughing about?
That's right
It was totally like a dream .. I can't seem to recall that memory currently
She doesn't want to bring the matter up right?
Mmm...
Himura please ask her if it's the zipper
It's the zipper right?
I don't know
"It's the zipper right?"
If you say that your father would be...
Say "His zipper was unzipped!" and proceed to laugh again
Father please laugh too
Laughter festival resumes
Father please laugh out loud too
Himura please fall and roll over laughing
Father please laugh too
My zipper was unzipped just now!
Ah! This is super fun!
Father please fall over laughing
Uwahh! This is fun!
Okay finished!
You decided not to say anything about his zipper right?
I thought it was best to pretend I didn't see it unzipped
You thought that was the polite thing to do?
Yes that's right
Sensei what should she do if the father's zipper is unzipped?
When you discover that, it would be better for you to tell him about it discreetly
There were many good areas too, lets hear your score first
You scored 75 points
Ah, she didn't seem to score quite high
The atmosphere was damp, it kind of irritated me
Ah, somehow it was...
Spicy words
It irritated her!
Ahh it irritated her!
I might have some responsibility to share too
Is that so?
For this round's Bride Test, we have done a lot of stuff
I'll announce the MVP!
Not all of you challenged the last segment, but I have watched it overall so the MVP is
Sakurai!!
Congratulations
Congratulations!
It was also due to her high score in the first test
For Sakurai, there would be a commemorative photo as a present!
Right after this, the performance of Girls Rule!
Brought to you by IkomaSubs
Visit us at www.Facebook.com/IkomaSubs for more!