Nogidoko tonight is, a joint event between the
1st gen and 2nd gen for the first time.
They will be together from now on, therefore
we asked 2nd gen to complete a question form.
A surprising survey results...
Show the power of the 1st gen.
The Senior loses their mind!?
[Nogizaka tte Doko?]
Translator : Rustyhand
Timer : fauzanrach
SUB-SHIRO (@subshiro46)
English Translator: Jejedeath
Follow @subshiro46 and stay update with Nogizaka46 subtitle release!!
Visit www.nogizakanouta.blogspot.com for more !!
DOOONNN!!! Let's start nogizakatte doko,
Your MC Bananaman! And Nogizaka-chan!
Ok, Thank you.
Himura, please announce tonight's topic!
Okay! Tonight, let's get to know each other
and become close! 2nd Gen awareness survey!
You guys haven't talked to each other yet??
Not yet.
Oh really?
We don't know the girls much yet.
Really? You take a lesson together, right??
No.
So you're not trained together!
Just say hello.
Oh?
That's why, let's find out how is 2nd gen impression for the 1st gen!
With this topic, let's make them know each other well.
How long the 2nd gen has been formed?
1-2 month.
Oh, still new.
It's one year for 1st gen already...
2.5 years.
2 years.
Really? This summer is 2 years already?
You're so close to maturity.
Not yet!
You act like a grandma!
1st gen! YEAH!
YEAAAHHHH!!!
It's been a while ^^
YEAH!
Yeah!
Weak.
Weak, weak ^^
Let's check out the question form. There's a
lot of topic, and the first question is...
Who's your oshimen in 1st gen?
Let's find out the reason first.
The first one is...
Pretty face, Stylish, good speaker,
I'm amazed by everything!
Who is this?
This is me.
No!
Matsumura.
Must be me.
This is most likely Matsumura.
It's all matched with me.
Which parts that suit you?
Face, style, my speech is interesting too.
Well, maybe it's really Matsumura, Who is this?
Let's find out, who is this??
Thank you very much.
Shiraishi!
It's Shiraishi!
It's about Shiraishi!
Shiraishi, you must be happy!
So happy.
Who wrote this?
Yamazaki!
Eeeeeee, Rena-chan!
Thank you so much.
Yamazaki Rena.
You think so?
Umm she's pretty, her style is good, but in nogidoko,
she's also great at speech. I admire her.
See? You've been admired.
Shiraishi, you get praised so much.
What should i do --<3
You must be very happy.
This is the first time i'm being told like this.
Have you never think of yourself pretty and stylish?
Never.
Really?
Now since Yamazaki said that to you,
you'll definitely remember her than the others.
Certainly ^^
Good. Let's continue it like this.
Now let's get to the next one.
Her face is my type, a good sense of humour, i really like it.
Who is this?
There is a sense of humour.
This!
Ummm... EEEE^^
My face.. isn't based on the general opinion,
It is just her personal taste.
So happy.
Who is this?
Ah!
Karin.
From the start, since she rubbed her elbow in the first event...
Eh!? Since that time?
Of course.
Even you're also lined up for the handshake right?
Yup.
Takayama, you remember her?
Yes, at 2nd gen first introduction,
Karin entered the room first.
Yup.
I think her face is familiar.. And when her name called,
Itou Karin, i was like EEEEEHH i know this girl.
What's your impression of Takayama's handshake?
When i came in, she greeted me "waaa Karin chan".
She remember you?
Just Sometimes... Maybe she's confuse
because there's too many people.
But, since you're together now, her charm
will going back to normal again for you, right?
Why? ^^
Right? All this time You're always
want to meet her but you can't.
Is there anything you wanna do with Takayama?
Well i love to talk too, i want to appear
in a Talk show together.
Talk show...
Yes.
Im not good at Talk show, actually.
Hey, this is your skill.
Heh! Not at all!
Takayama, please tell us an interesting story.
Nothing. Nothing. Nothing.
What? There is an interesting story just now..
Wait! Wait!
Show 1st gen power to 2nd gen!
Wait! Why end up like this? Wait!
Scary...
You're not so smart.
I really can't!
I think no one can handle that pass too.
Thank god.
Let's check out the next one.
Basically i love everyone. Even the lame Sayuringo punch.
Finally appear. Matsumura!
Who is this?
Yonetoku, so you think Sayuringo punch is lame?
Why? it's not lame ^^
Basically she's cute. Even her lame joke.
That character is cute?
Kawaii.
Kawaii but how about her gag "sayuringo punch"?
What "sayuringo punch"?
"Sayuringo Punch" is... SAYURINGO PU---NCH<3
Why?
You just saw "sayuringo punch" live, right? How is it?
I can feel the innocence image, like usual.
Can feel the innocence image...
So how is it? Good or lame?
We don't have to talk about that, right?
It's nothing to do with good or lame.
Is there anything else that you like from Matsumura?
Character, and of course.. her face.
How is this... I'm shy...
You're so happy when someone says
you're face are pretty.
Let's see the next one.
Her sing and dance is very good.
As a captain, she led and respected by the members.
Members doesn't respect her.
There is someone who think like that.
Eh, not respected by the members?
No.
No, they respect me all the time.
And she doesn't lead. It's all lie.
Members are often gathered by themselves, and she came late.
She doesn't lead the members.
Wrong!
Come late.
No, i escort the member to the destinaion
and then i go after them.
No, no, must be a lie.
It's true.
Who wrote this?
Yes.
Oh, Yada.
We have the same age, i can't be like her.
When i saw her on TV, she's so independent.
Independent?
Yes.
She doesn't lead in the right way?
But you respect her, right?
No.
What's this?
I respect her singing and dancing skills.
Her sing and dance is good?
Very good.
But, other than that there is nothing...
Right, in weak point episode, you're willing to be mocked.
Hmmm? Sakurai, You're not trusted by them?
They trust me. I always bear all the burden.
Why you all laugh...
But, members doesn't feel like that.
Even so, it's 2 years already.
Let's continue. The next one is...
Which member has the most gap?
Oh, gap...
Members who have distinct impression
when seen and encountered is...
Wakatsuki.
You do not seem to have a gap.
Alright Wakatsuki, so far how many members
that you've been bullying?
Wrong? You didn't do it?
No.
OK, let's see.
Who write that she had distinct impression for Wakatsuki?
Itou, what kind of gap?
When i saw her on TV, she looks so firm.
Eh, really...
Why...
But, during introductions, she's so kind.
She must be a very kind person.
I see.
I see, so it's a positive gap.
Anything else? Other gap...
When we showed up at principal, im so nervous.
And there is a snack and drink for members. It's so hard to grab it.
When im confuse, suddenly Wakatsuki come and said
"Let's grab it together".
Ah right.. you went there together.
And she asked "Is the drink enough? You're a member too, just take it."
I'm really impressed.
At that time, you must be so happy.
Yeah, so happy.
When you have no idea...
You have a good gap... isn't there anything else?
A good gap.
When we saw the rehearsal,
Wakatsuki come to our place at break time.
Oh, you even did such thing...
Come to your place.
And then with cheerful face she said, nice to meet you.
So, the other members doesn't come?
Ah, a few moments later they came...
Other members came too, but Wakatsuki came first.
Wakatsuki, What is this? Awesome...
But, Wakatsuki in the waiting room,
seems like she want to be liked by them very much.
Wrong, Wrong, Mattsun!
I see, this is the first time, so she want to be liked.
Yes, we don't know whether we can go there or not.
If you know it's allowed,
You would like to go there too for sure.
Yes.
Wakatsuki, you're exaggerate.
Wrong!
Seems like you want to hangout with 2nd gen
and be nice to them so...
Why end up like this...
But why?
Me too, i joined school club in middle shool,
I simply could not carry on a conversation.
Senior is senior, it's always like this.
This has always been a problem, and i know they feel it too.
That's why, senior should talk to them.
I always think that you're not such a good person.
EEEEEEHHHHHH although it's been 2 years...
Apparently you're a good person.
If compared to Matsumura...
You want to be liked by them.
No, no, i'm a good person, right? ^^
You know that, right? ^^
OK.
Next question!
1st gen members who are very had to be approached.
This is a problem. Members who are hard to be approached.
Who do you think?
Maybe Ikoma?
Ikoma? Why?
It's hard for me to open myself to the people
whom i first met. I just can't start it.
Coming up, Surprisingly, the name that called is...!!
Is Ikoma name will appear? Who's 1st gen members
who are very had to approached?
Wrong. Hashimoto!
Hmm... Hashimoto, I knew why she was so hard to be approached.
Hashimoto can not?
Who is this?
Hori speaks.
Hashimoto's image is smart, looks like she'll
give me a difficult words to understand.
Hmmm... That's Right.
I'm not too familiar with difficult words.
I'm afraid i don't get the conversation's topic.
I see, so it's the topic.
In the question form, maybe she will give
a difficult words or a proverb...
No.
Proverb, eh...
Hashimoto like proverb, right...
I never said that.
Needless to say but her image said so.
Yes.
That would be so hard to connect.
How old are you?
16.
You wanna give a proverb?
Next, we still have Members who are hard to be approached.
AKIMOTO!
Akimoto. Who is this?
Yes.
Nishikawa...
Nishikawa-san^^
Nishikawa is the same age as her.
Middle school, right?
Yes.
Same school and the same club.
This is awesome!
Cool.
It's true, right?
Right, in the school, we talk with everyday language.
Now it's senior-junior, im confused how to talk with her.
The position changed.
Right...
You haven't talked to each other, right?
Ah, we met in our latest show. At that time...
Wait. Please listen to me.
Um, at least now i'm the senior and Nanami is junior.
But in school, Nanami is in the funky group, while im in the ordinary one.
I see, There always such a group in school.
The funky group...
The funky group, and im in the ordinary one. That's why.
The group isn't talk much.
Who?
Manatsu san.
The plain group?
No!
So it's not the group that you know well.
Yes. I feel there is a little gap...
That's why, you're the one who worried?
Yes, i don't know what to do. But she called me just now.
I'll use this name to get close with her.
And then, the one who had junior-senior relation too.. Ah!
High School...
Your High School senior?
Yes.
It's quite interesting. She think, Manatsu-senpai...
She's student council leader. And when she became nogizaka member,
When me and my friend saw her at the station, "Look it's Manatsu-san"
In your hometown, everyone is like,
"Manatsu-san.. Manatsu-san"
I never thought I'd be noticed that much.
Manatsu-san had been washed down in waterfall.
You're being discussed.
Manatsu-san are going to do skydiving.
That isn't something to be proud of.
It's like degawa..
Yeah right!
Here we have the young one who became senior
And there we also have the older one.
How is it then? In one group...
What's the rules in the idol world?
Don't really know...
In comedy industry, if there's a young comedian but he
entered the industry before you, then he's your senior.
Comedy industry is like that.
Ah, right. Let's make it like that.
Nogizaka want to be like that too?
Ikoma-chan want to be senior too.
So even there's older one, you're the senior?
Yes.
So.. Ah please go on.
How do we call them? For example Matsumura-san,
should we call her Matsumura-san, Sayurin-san or Ringo-san...
Her name isn't Rino, right!?
So...
Ah, for the members who has a nickname,
Should we call them by their nickname or what?
Ah, actully i have a name...
Oh, there is!?
Finally i can say it.
I want all of you to call me Ringo-hime.
Errr... Sounds so wrong at this time...
Why!? It's the topic, right?
Ringo-hime?
So, everyone should call you Ringo-hime ??
Yes.
Is that okay? Even when you're 40-50 years old
and still called Ringo-hime.
Maybe it's better if we give the special name to Ikuta.
Ikuta is just like a princess.
Erika-sama.
She will be angry if you don't call her Erika-sama.
No, no, just .. let's be friendly.
Ok, the next question form...
I'm not confidence with my PR,
Please give me advice.
Who's this?
PR huh? Please show it first.
When i say Itou, You'll say Junna.
Konpeitou konpeitou konpeitou konpe ITOU!
Junna!
Thank you.
You like konpeitou.
This is just like before, even there isn't something
to think about, little things could work too.
Yeah right!
And later it will become a problem to yourself.
Yes, there will be an unexpected things.
Rrrr, is it Shiraishi? The one about mayonnaise...
Shiraishi...
Shiraishi, please do your first PR.
Wait wait... I can't. No no no no .
Shiraishi Shiraishi Shiraishi.
Do it!
Mayoer alien from 4D world. Maiyan aka Shiraishi Mai.
Nice to meet you^^
Alright, now...
Shiraishi, are you okay? Shiraishi from the 4D world?
Waaa... 3D 3D^^
Shiraishi, You never did this anymore?
Not at all.
What about konpeitou, is that okay?
Hmmm wait a second...
Let's try it first.
So let's use it for now? It can still be changed, right?
Yes, It can still be changed.
Apa banyak yang tidak mengganti PR dari awal?
Is there anyone who put their favourite food to PR?
Me.
Ah Ikuta!
What...
I'm udon.
Ah, the one that we made it here?
Yes, PR that made by Himura-san,
I'm still doing it till now.
EH! Until now?
Please show it.
DON DON IKUDON IKUTA DON UUUUUDONNNNN!!!
Ikuta, you're still doing the PR that we made here, Great!
Yeah right.
Because you like udon.
Yes.
But i haven't eat it much now, but im still doing it.
Because that's okay.
Ada yang ngomong tidak apa2 tuh.
Is there any food that you like beside udon?
Yeah, like Nikujaga...
Coming up, because of super blinking,
Something happened to Takayama.
The next one is!
I don't have any special skill,
What skills that are easy to do?
Oh, this is difficult.
You still don't have anything now?
Yes.
So when asked to show something, you'll just be quiet?
Yes, i'll just be quiet.
Ah so you're started to thinking about that...
Later i'll looks like a boring person...
Yeah, right.
Skills.. hmm you have any idea?
Is anyone forced to do it?
What did you do?
Me, toilet hand dryers.
I remember! Do it.
Please do it.
Ok...
It's been a while ^^
This is easy right? This...
That one?
Please try.
Ready? Go!
Too simple.
This is hard.. i can't do it.
She's shy.
Your upper lips should vibrate.
How could she know!?
Umm... Super blinking.. Who is it?
Yes.
Ok, Hori.
Special skill, super blinking.
Please do it. Go!
Awesome!
So fast...
This is great.
Anyone else can do it? Super blinking.
1st gen.
Oh there is!
Shiraishi, you can do it?
Ready, GO!
Fast, fast!
Takayama can do it also, right? ^^
Takayama, Super Blinking, GO!
I can do it.
Yeah you can do it.
Oh really? I did it ^^