Tonight on NogiDoko,
Announcement of senbatsu for the 6th single!
The new senbatsu members that were unveiled
at the national handshake event yesterday.
Whether you know the results or not,
witness the moment of this shocking announcement!
Nogizakatte, Doko?
DON!
Nogizakatte Doko has started, we're your hosts,
Bananaman, yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
Now, Himura-san,
Okay.
There's no one here.
Nogizaka46 absent.
No one's here.
This is where they're always seated right?
You got that right.
Well then, please announce what we have for today.
Nogizaka46
Big announcement of the senbatsu members for the 6th single!
That being said, this time,
we’ll show the moment when the senbatsu members unveiled yesterday were announced.
And with that, Nogizaka-chan are in a different room right now.
So, for today,
Saito Yuuri is absent because of a live radio broadcast.
Ah, is that so?
-Yes.
Her radio appearance coincides with our recording so she’s not here.
Then, this time, we’ll start the announcement from the 3rd row.
Furthermore, the formation is the same as the last time.
From the front it’ll be 3-5-8.
Those from the #1 up to the #8 position will be 8-Fukujin.
Now then, shall we start?
I'll start the announcement.
#9
The first senbatsu member for the 6th single is...
Ito Marika
It's Ito!
The first senbatsu member for the 6th single is Ito Marika,
She made it in the senbatsu after getting in the 3rd single.
Please go here.
Ito Marika, how do you feel right now?
To be honest, I'm happy.
Why? What's the matter?
You were chosen.
My stomach hurts.
Your stomach hurts?
-Yes, it does.
Because you were suddenly called, right off the bat, right?
Right?
But you were called, for the 6th single.
Please do your best.
I'll do my best!
hai, omedetou~
Shall we continue?
-Let's continue.
Then, I'll continue with the announcement.
#16
The next member for the 6th single is...
Saito Yuuri
Saito Yuuri made it in!
Saito Yuuri...
She's not here.
Uhmm, because she’s doing a radio appearance,
Wait, is she on-air right now?
Then, we’ll contact her and once it’s connected, we’ll inform her about it.
I see.
-We’ll inform her.
We’ll inform in the right timing!
We’ll tell her about it when she’s on-air.
They have no Idea about this, right?
She will be very happy about this.
#16 spot.
-Yes.
Saito Yuuri, huh?
hai, omedetou~
Then, let’s get to the next one.
The next senbatsu member, #10
The next member for the 6th single is...
Inoue Sayuri
Ah, Inoue, hai omedetou~
Inoue Sayuri, from the first single,
she made it in the senbatsu for the 6th consecutive time.
You were all smiles at the time you were chosen.
-Yes.
Up until now, really…
as I’ve thought, the feeling of frustration was enormous.
But, after a year of working in Nogizaka,
Even for someone like me, there are a lot of people giving their support.
So I will give it my best for them.
It seems like she has grown already.
She has changed a lot.
She has told us her frustrations right here.
omedetou gozaimasu.
-hai, omedetou~
#10, right?
-#10.
Very well, I'll continue with the announcement.
The next senbatsu member, #15
The next member for the 6th single is...
Fukagawa Mai
hai, Fukagawa, right?
Fukagawa Mai, starting from the third single,
she entered the senbatsu for the 4th consecutive time.
While being true to myself,
since I was chosen, I have to be responsible.
I’d like to do my best so that the 6th single can be a good single.
Do your best, okay?
omedetou gozaimasu~
Please go ahead to the #15 spot.
Four members have been decided.
Now,
please go ahead with the announcement.
The next senbatsu member, #11
The next member for the 6th single is...
Nakada Kana
It's Nakada.
Nakada Kana who served as a front member in the 2nd single,
made it in the senbatsu for the 2nd consecutive time.
Honestly, I never thought I’d get in.
I haven’t thought of anything to say.
I can’t say anything in ad-lib either.
Everytime, I can’t say anything funny in NogiDoko.
-What’s wrong?
Your funny expressions are good enough.
-It’s alright.
That’s why…
I didn’t really have any confidence,
but I’ll do my best.
Do your best.
-You were called, that’s why…
…do your best in your own way.
hai, omedetou gozaimasu~
The next senbatsu member, #14
The next member for the 6th single is?
Akimoto Manatsu
Akimoto?
From being a 8-Fukujin...
Akimoto Manatsu who has returned to Nogizaka during the 4th single,
for the first time, she is in the 3rd row after being in the 8-Fukujin.
She’s crying.
Why are you crying right now?
Even though I was allowed to be in the 8-Fukujin twice,
this time, my position dropped a little.
You were either frustrated or surprised, right?
-It’s frustrating…
But, I’ll do my best no matter what.
I’d like to do my best so that I can bounce back next time.
Congrats nonetheless.
-Proceed to the #14 spot.
Do your best, okay?
Akimoto is called right here,
which means that there are changes in the 8-Fukujin.
Akimoto is out of the Fukujin and went to the #14 spot,
there are now just two spots remaining in the 3rd row.
The next senbatsu member, #12
The next member for the 6th single is...
Wakatsuki Yumi
Wakatsuki made it in!
Wakatsuki Yumi, starting from the third single,
she entered the senbatsu for the 4th consecutive time.
Even now...
I’ve been saying that...
“Since I got in the senbatsu, I’ll do the things I can with my best effort."
From here on out,
I’d like to be able to do those things I thought I can’t.
To make everyone stronger, there’s someone there who serves as a replacement, right?
I think that it’s nice to have these kinds of feelings sprout.
There’s one person left for the 3rd row.
-Just one more person, huh?
For the 6th single, all that’s left in the 3rd row is the #13 spot.
The next senbatsu member, #13
Who will be chosen for the last spot in the 3rd row?
Hoshino Minami
Eh?
Oh?
Hoshino has always been...
-She has always been in the front.
That's true.
Hoshino Minami who has been mainly a front member for the past singles is now in the 3rd row.
How about this? How are you feeling right now?
To be honest, I felt relieved...
Eh?
Right now…
There are a lot of things where I get confused.
It’s like… the pressure, I mean...
This time… what number? I’m in the #13 spot,
but I’d like to give it my all for the 6th single.
Being in front means that you’ll be subjected to a lot of criticism.
You did all that while being under pressure?
We thought you couldn’t feel any of it…
but now that I’ve heard about it, I thought, “Ah, really?”
Do your best.
-I’ll do my best in the 6th single.
That’s nice, do your best okay?
-Nice.
Thank you very much.
Eh? So that’s how it goes.
Within the 8-Fukujin, it has been decided that two members will be replaced.
That concludes the announcement for the 3rd row.
Akimoto and Hoshino are out of the 8-Fukujin.
Furthermore , Ito Marika and Saito Yuuri from under made it in the senbatsu.
Right here, we’ll inform Saito who is currently on-air about getting in the senbatsu.
Someone’s on the line.
Hello?
Ah, hello?
Who is this?
This is Bananaman.
Which one of the Bananaman?
The one speaking right now is Shitara.
Ah, Shitara-san.
Yes, and then…
Hello, this is Himura, hello, pardon us.
Ah, hello~
On our end, we’re also in the middle of recording Nogizaka’s show, NogiDoko.
We have something to tell to Saito Yuuri.
You’re currently on-air, but could we have her for a moment?
She’s right in front of me right now.
Really?
Onizuka-san, please excuse us for a while.
Saito Yuuri here.
Starting from this spring, you’ll be doing a radio show?
-Yes, that’s right, it has been decided.
Yes, I am. I’m really really nervous though.
We’re currently on-air right?
-Yes, that’s right. We’re on-air.
Really?
What’s the meaning of this?
Ah, you see, right now, we’re announcing the senbatsu for the 6th single.
Eh? Why?!
Why didn’t they call me?
Wasn’t called.
The schedule is overlapping.
For the 6th single, Saito Yuuri,
you made it in the senbatsu!
Eh? Is that true?
That's great!
Amazing!
Onizuka-san, Saito Yuuri made it in the senbatsu!
Great excitement.
She made it in!
Is this a prank?
-She made it in!
omedetou!
Saito, please tell us how you feel right now.
Is it okay to say it here?
Say it!
It’s like… what is it? It feels like a prank,
I never thought I would be called.
Eh? What to do? I’m happy but I’m freaking out!
With that, sorry for the intrusion, that’s all we wanted to say.
Oh is that so?
Eh?
T-Thank you very much.
Pardon us for the intrusion. Saito Yuuri, do your best!
I'll do my best!
Bye bye!
-Goodbye!
After this, a great turn of events in the senbatsu announcement?!
Nogizaka46 6th single, next is the announcements for the 2nd row.
The next senbatsu announcement, #8
The first one who’ll get in the 8-Fukujin is…
Takayama Kazumi
Takayama! omedetou~
Takayama, 8-Fukujin!
Takayama Kazumi made her way back to the 8-Fukujin
after getting in the 2nd single four singles back.
During the time I've spent in the #16 spot,
I’ve had this feeling of wanting to go up front.
The amount of opportunities I had when I was in the 8-Fukujin,
I realized about it when I was in the #16 spot.
I’m really happy because of it.
You were wondering if you’re gonna drop from your position last time,
considering the various changes we’re seeing, right?
Is it…
enough already?
Is it enough already?
What do you mean by that?
I got you. That feeling of wanting to be happy also exists, that…
You don’t know how to explain it, right?
But still, you were chosen.
-I’m thankful.
You’re grateful, that’s nice.
Well then, please appreciate it.
omedetou~
Takayama entering the 8-Fukujin has been decided,
There are seven spots remaining.
The next senbatsu member, #4
The next one who will be chosen is?
Sakurai Reika
Oh, Sakurai, omedetou~
Captain Sakurai made it in the 8-Fukujin for the 3rd consecutive time.
I also graduated from high school,
the environment has also changed considerably for me.
For my personal charm to also increase regardless of being the captain,
for the fans to think that “We want to support you from now on.”
I want to work hard to become that kind of member.
We’ll look forward to it. Do your best.
6 people remaining.
The next senbatsu member, #7
The next member for the 6th single is...
Nishino Nanase
Nishino made it in!
Nishino Nanase made her way back to the 8-Fukujin
after getting in the 3rd single three singles back.
Ever since falling out of the 8-Fukujin during the 4th single,
I’m really frustrated, I’ve always been.
then,
gradually, I’ve become pessimistic.
Even while on the train, I’m only thinking about the comments when I dropped.
But you’ve made it in now.
I really like the #7, I’m glad,
so I'd like to do my best.
Nishino entered the 8-Fukujin.
The next senbatsu member, #5
The next member for the 6th single is...
Ikuta Erika
hai, Ikuta, omedetou~
Ikuta Erika who was a front member for three consecutive times
is now in the 2nd row, #5 spot.
Because I’ll be able to see a different view than before,
I’m really looking forward to the amount of hard work I’ll put in.
I’d like to give it my all.
Do your best.
I'll do my best.
Please go ahead. omedetou gozaimasu~
We’re down to just four spots.
Is this the last one for the 2nd row?
Yes, it is the last one.
For the 6th single, Hoshino and Ikuta who were front members in the last single are moved to the back.
Next is the last one for the 2nd row.
The next senbatsu member, #6
Who will be chosen?
Ikoma Rina
Ikoma
This is quite something.
You’ve always been the center since Nogizaka46 has started.
Is there anything you have to say?
I’ve always thought that there’ll be changes someday..
..that’s why I was always prepared for this.
The #2 spot (center) is the only world that I knew,
so I’ve also received words…
...that hurt me a lot.
But, these changes…
these changes right now, since it is the first time this happened,
It’s like.. I can’t understand it very well…
We were also surprised by it.
That’s right, it was surprising.
Ikoma was the center of Nogizaka after all.
But this is a fresh start,
it could be something different again.
It might take you some time to accept all this.
Ikoma Rina who has served as the fixed center since Nogizaka46 was formed,
is out of the center position for the first time.
After this, the big announcement for the front members!
Right now, up to the #5 spot were called, Ikoma, however, is resting for a bit.
We’ll continue without Ikoma here right now.
All that’s left for the 6th single are the three front members.
The next senbatsu member, #1
The next member for the 6th single is…
Matsumura Sayuri
Matsumura Sayuri who was in the 2nd row for all of the singles starting from the first single,
made it to the front position that she’s been longing for.
From the 1st single, I’ve always thought that “I really want to go up front.”
And then, even the fans at handshake events,
they were always telling me “Go up front even more!”
We’ve done 5 singles already, but I’ve always been in the 2nd row.
I’m 20 years old,
and among the members, I am one of the tallest,
I’ll get in the way of others when I go up front, so it’s impossible.
Don’t worry about those kinds of things.
I just keep on making excuses.
I’m a step closer to the place I didn’t get to go to.
I think this is where it really starts,
I won’t give in from this position.
I’d like to work with self-confidence.
There’ll be a lot of opportunities for you to see, so please work hard.
I will.
Do your best, okay?
For the 6th single, just 2 people remaining.
-Just two, huh?
The next senbatsu member, #3
The next member for the 6th single is…
Hashimoto Nanami
Hashimoto, hai, omedetou~
Just like Matsumura,
Hashimoto Nanami who was in the 2nd row for all of the singles starting from the first single, she made it to the front.
I was always in the same spot on the 2nd row, but…
honestly,
that spot has become a comfortable spot for me, in both good way and bad way.
This time, I was given this position,
It would be nice if I could build self-confidence and do my best in the 6th single.
I'll do my best.
-hai, omedetou~
Only one left for the 6th single,
the announcement for center.
The next senbatsu member, #2
The last one for the 6th single is?
Shiraishi Mai
hai, Shiraishi~
Shiraishi Mai who was in the 2nd row for all of the singles,
is selected as Nogizaka46’s new center.
Shiraishi, you are in the center position.
For me as well, I've always been in the the 2nd row,
rather than feeling relieved, it was more of “I’ll do my best in this position again.”
This time, I’m taking one step further.
There is a lot of pressure, along with the things that I have to be responsible of.
Since I was given this position,
I will work very hard and have a lot of people take notice,
I’d like to give my best effort in order to get acknowledged.
Do your best, okay?
-Do your best.
Proceed to the center position.
Thank you very much.
-hai, omedetou~
There we have it,
The 16 senbatsu members for the 6th single have been decided!
I think this is the biggest change we’ve had so far,
This coming summer,
Nogizaka’s activities will be more active than ever,
we’ll get to challenge a lot of new things, that’s why…
we’ll gather ourselves in this fresh start.
So that we could produce a single better than what we’ve put out so far,
We’d like to help one another,combine our efforts and work hard.
For the 6th single as well, ,yoroshiku onegaishimasu~