Tonight, Nogizaka46 2nd generation member that
just formed, finally gathered!
Because of their odd profile,
Bananaman had reached their limit!
Tonight, will there be a next generation star!?
Nogizaka tte Doko?
Translator: Rustyhand
Timer: Koala13th
English Translator: Jejedeath
Follow @subshiro46 and stay update with Nogizaka46 subtitle release!!
Visit www.nogizakanouta.blogspot.com for more !!
DANG!!!
Let's start Nogizaka tte doko, your MC, Bananaman.
Ok, please welcome Nogizaka... HMMNN!?
Himura, finally...
Finally Nogizaka46 has gone with the wind.
Now this show become "Nogizakatte, doko?", literally.
Wrong.
- Is that wrong?
- Wrong.
Ok Himura, please announce today's theme
like an amateur.
New addition! Nogizaka46,
Lets make 2nd generation's profile!!!
In audition that started in December 2012,
2nd generation member are finally chosen.
Tonight with Bananaman, let's make
2nd generation member profile.
And that's why,,
Finally,,
Please welcome,,
- Give a lot of enthusiasm.
- Give enthusiasm.
Nogizaka46
2nd gen, please come in!
Hmmm... They're so calm.
From now on, each member will show
their own character. 2nd gen!
And as kenkyuusei, we hope that they keep
their spirit on and be able to become senbatsu,
and appear in nogidoko.
That's why, Pleased to meet you!
Pleased to meet you!
Let's get to the point, this is
your first time appear on TV, right?
Yes!
So basically, most of you didn't have
this experience before, right?
You must be nervous.
A lot of people watching!
Hey hey. Don't make them more nervous.
They look so nervous already.
Everybody's watching, right?
Don't tell me, you guys will be a
troublesome to Nogizaka46!
- They're Nogizaka46 too.
- Oh yeah!
- Nogizaka46!
But that's true, right?
Why are we bullying them...
Let's check them out.
First one is Itou Karin.
Born in Kanagawa, 19 years old, Itou Karin.
Nice to meet you.
- Itou Karin chan.
- Itou karin.
- Ah... KarinÜ
- Ah so it's KarinÜ
So the tone is KarinÜ. Not Karinv...
Just like Mirin and Kirin, KarinÜ
Kirin, Mirin, Karin...
No, Karinv...
- KarinÜ...
- Yes.
- Weird... KarinÜ is weird.
- Karinv right!?
Karinüv
- I've been called like that for 19 years, so please...
- What's the letters?
Hiragana.
Eh! Hiragana but KarinÜ...
Karin Ü
Must be Karinüv... In our whole life
we always think it's Karinüv.
- Your parents read it like that, too?
- Yes!
- Your friends too?
- Yes.
- KarinÜ?
Yes, but in hospital they called me Karinüv
That's the normal one, right?
- KarinÜ is weird.
- In general, 'down' is the normal one.
- But you're Karinüv right?
- KarinÜ
KarinÜ... What a name.
I'll just call you Itou, then.
- Oh wait... Karin.
- Yes.
Thank you.
- Are you taking part in Nogizaka46 first audition?
- Yes!
- But you failed?
- Yeah, failed.
Since then...
- You became a Nogizaka46 fans?
- Yes.
- Since failed.
- Usually you'll become a hater...
- Yeah it will turn you into a hater.
At first i have that intention too.
But then i came to their event.
- So you watched them?
- Yes.
I think i will hate them so much,
but after i saw them... KAWAII!!
- Really?
- People who make her failed,
she wonder how their faces looks like.
When she saw them, they're so cute.
- Really cute girl, eh?
- Yes! I love them.
Takayama oshi.
Oh, Takayama.
Have you met her?
- Yes! She remembered me...
- How?
- I went to akushu event.
- Really!?
Lie...
You must be lying.
Im not lying, Errr... Karin-chan,
that's how she called me.
- There's now way she could remember you!
- I always...
Takayama never remember a thing!!!
No comment.
- Really?
- Maybe.
Everytime i went to akushu, she be like 'Karin-chan, it's been a while'.
She always greeted me like that.
So you lined up in Takayama's line?
Yeah! Always lined up.
Cool...
Great...
- Her skill is, can guess the name of perfecture only by its form!
- Cool!
- Only by the form?
- Yes, the form.
Really?
- Cool!
- Leave it to me.
This?
... Chiba.
This is Hokkaido.
- How could she know? also it's different from the original.
- It's in the question.
- Oh, in the question?
- Ready?
- OK!
- ... Ah OK!
- You know it already?
Yes ... Can i answer?
Go on.
- Okayama.
- How?
Right!
- Awesome..
- Yeah.
- Is there any particular form of Okayama? I don't know.
- Isn't it looks like Tochigi?
Yeah, but Tochigi is a bit flat.
- A bit flat? Which part?
- Here.
- So this part is more sharp ,right??
- Yeah right.
Because it located in the seaside.
Next 2nd gen Member is Itou Junna.
Her hobby is.. groping someoone.
Hey you can arrested by the police!
Why groping?
It's because... Girls are smooth and soft, right?
- Yeah right!
- I know right!
But isn't that a man's feeling?
So you like soft things?
I'd rather hug than groping, actually.
Feels good, huh?
Everyone wants to do it...
Especially old man.
Favourite food...
Konpeitou (sugar candy)
What's konpeitou? From all kinds of food in this world..
KONPEITOU!
Alright, number one favourite?
- Yes, number one.
- Really?
- Yes, i like it.
You like it more than Chuutoro (Tuna Sushi)?
Konpeitou! It's Konpeitou!
- Really?
- Yeah!
So when you're at the sushi resto, at first...
Ootoro...
Uni...
Steak...
Konpeitou...
- You will get the konpeitou?
- Yes, i'll get the konpeitou.
Lie. Even if you're hungry?
Yeah, konpeitou tastes good.
Weird...
Btw, 1st gen had also been making an answer like this,
And now they regret it.
Why do you like it?
Hmm.. It's cute..
Yeah, konpeitou is cute..
And also sweet.
Haha... What kind of reason is that.
- Calligraphy!
- Yes.
- Dan 7?
- Yeah right.
- Cool!
- Do you bring your calligraphy now?
- Yes i bring it.
- Let's see!
Dan 7 level... Itou Junna's calligraphy,
Please show it.
Hahahaha.
She wrote konpeitou.
You must be relieved after wrote it.
Next, let's check out the profile of Kitano Hinako.
Born in Hokkaidou, grow up in Chiba,
2nd grade high school, 16 years old.
Kitano Hinako, call me Kii-chan, nice to meet you!
- What did you just say?
- Born in Hokkaidou, grow up in Chiba and then?
What did you just say?
- 2nd grade high school.
- And then??
16 years old...
And then?
- Kiichan...
- That's it!
What's that?
- Kii from Kitano?
- Yes!
Kii from Kitano are different from Kitano Kii.
- That wouldn't be a problem, right?
- There is Kitano Kii.
(Translator note : Actress Name)
- Skill.. Wow cool.. Ripping a magazine?
- Yes.
Ripping a magazine? Can yo do it?
Yes, i can!
Ok, please rip it.
Awesome!
Cool!
What's this? Since when you can do that?
In the audition, there are parts that require you
to show your skill.
And then my father told me to do that.
Next 2nd gen is Sasaki Kotoko.
- Skills, Sleep anywhere.
- Anywhere ?
Even in the muddy place?
Umm.. yeah as long as there is a bed.
Favourite food, Mentsuyu (soup/sauce)
This is also....
From any kinds of food!?
Any kinds!?
I like to drink mentsuyu that has been diluted with water.
That's why... I'm talking about compare it to Chuutoro.
It's Mentsuyu right? Mentsuyu!
Yes!
Ok, in belt conveyor, if there is Ootoro, Uni,
meat, konpeitou, mentsuyu...
- You'll take mentsuyu?
- Yes, mentsuyu.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Why the food list is like that?
- Yeah, it's this kind of restaurant!
- It's the same as the previous restaurant.
Do you like to draw?
Yes...
What did you usually draw?
I don't draw.
A confusing answer.
I like to picture it in my mind.
What is it?
A Line...
- Line?
What the hell are you saying?
Next, let's check out the profile of Shin'uchi Mai.
Oh, her skill is cool.
No surprise, she's the oldest.
- Can tell the name of all Tokyo Metro colors (Underground Train).
- Yes.
The sign, right? For the underground train.
Ok, here's the document.
- So, you wanna guess the name or colors?
- I can do both.
- Oh, both?
- Colors and track?
- Yes, no problem.
Ok, let's start with the easy one.
- Marunouchi Line.
- Red.
I know it too.
Ginza Line.
Orange.
- You know it?
- Yeah of course.
- Yeah, this area...
- Yeah that area...
Touzai Line.
Light Blue.
Hahaha, so there is also dark blue.
Yes, Mita Line.
- You can go to Touei Line?
- Yes.
- Really?
Really.. Who are you? Go to Touei?
Hmm... Who?
How could you memorized all of them?
I just like Metro.
- Ah, You like it?
- You like underground train?
Umm.. Colors and Line, im not
really interested with the train, actually.
It's on the top, right? (route map).
I always see it.
So, from here to here is shortcut. You like it?
Yeah right.
So far there's still no member who like train...
Not train, i like Metro.
Coming up, why is Bananaman angry?
Next 2nd gen member is Suzuki Ayane.
From Akita?
Yes, Akita
- Same with Ikoma.
- I see.
- You're Ikoma's junior.
- Born in the same place.
Things she love.. All kinds of Airplane.
No...
- Eh, No?
- NOOO, not wrong, but...
- Wrong?
- Not Wrong.
Wrong!?
At the announcement day, from Akita to Tokyo, Haneda.
At first i was going to get on Boeing 787 but it's cancelled.
Finally take off.. I like Airbus than Boeing.
Really like it!
Why don't you tell from the start?
You have one favourite Airplane, right?
Not all kinds of Airplane.
- Yes!
- What type of Airbus?
Airbus A380, like this.
What you just did?
- Because it's big.
- Which part do you like?
Because gooo and waaa, and then hihihi.
What the hell are you doing?
- Why do you like it?
- I don't know.
There must be a reason.
If you don't know anything,
how could you know about that Airbus type.
Why do you like A380? Must be a reason.
No it's just.. "Pon"
I suddenly like it.
No way!
There must be something.
Like when you see it fly or whatever.
Nothing!
This damn kid!
Akita... since in Tokyo,
You have a red on you.
- Yes...
- Hey, Ikoma also got it.
- Must be the air, water..
People... You don't like it.
The water is not good.
Ikoma said that too.
But she has changed.
Next, let's check out the profile of Terada Ranze.
- Terada Ranze.
- Yes.
- Ranze?!
- Unique name, cool.
- What's this.. her weakness is stupid.
- It's not really a weakness.
Is there any story about your stupidity?
Lately, in science lesson,
there is a formula calculation.
My teacher said, the fromula is right,
but the multiplication is wrong, so my answer is wrong.
You're bad in multiplication?
Multiplication and others... All subjects.
But there are worse person, right?
Like the one who can't tell the difference
between teacher and student.
- I did not come to that.
- Then it's not really a weakness...
Your small, eh?
- 155 cm
- Oh, 155cm?
Ah, yes.
Her face is tiny.
- But we also have...
- Saitou Asuka.
Have you met Saitou Asuka?
Yes i have.
- Her face is tiny, right?
- Yes.
But you also looks like ikuta...
Err... Lately...
Which one is better?
No need to answer.
Next, profile of Nishikawa Nanami.
Nishikawa, i saw you on the news.
- So you're an AKB48 ex-member.
- Yes.
Ex-kenkyuusei, right?
But it's only for a very short time.
I can't count that as an ex...
I see... Let's forget that from now on.
- Oh! You went to the same junior high school
with Akimoto Manatsu, same year!
- Yes, right.
- Even in the same extracurricular.
- Really? What?
Cooking club.
You can cook?
But, when i saw nogidoko, and saw
Manatsu-senpai cooking...
Right, from the same year, now become a senpai.
- Yeah right.
- Complicated.
You're friends, right?
- Yeah, we're friends.
- This is interesting!
So you talked to each other at school?
Of course, we're on the same club.
Like what?
- Like Manaccha~n
- Like that, right?
Now in Nogizaka46, it become...
Now, ah excuse me Akimoto senpai...
Next, profile of Hori Miona.
Favourite food... Meat.
She wrote the best 3.
No. 3 Salt Tongue (TanShio),
No. 2 Kakuteki (Turnip Kimchi)
Kakuteki?!
Kakuteki is not meat.
But this... BBQ Restaurant, right?
No. 1 Senmai Sashi (Sashimi)
That's plain!
That's so Plain!
How about Karubi and Harami (Meat name) ?
I still prefer the Senmai.
Plain, right?
It's senmai plus kakuteki and tanshio...
Isn't that finished already? After that is BBQ.
- Ah, i repeat it again.
- This?
- Yes.
- Why?
- It's so plain. Why do you like it?
I like the crispy flavour of senmai sashi.
Ah, crispy....
And what do you drink?
Umm... Tea.
Eat senmai sashi and drink tea. Awesome!
Her skill is.. Flash Blink.
Yes.
- Can you show it?
- I wanna see it.
Ok, Start!
Fast!
At first her face is so serious but it slowly relaxed.
Is there anyone who can do it too?
- Yamazaki.
- Come on Yamazaki!
Wait, Hori, do it again.
Ah, she's faster.
Hori is faster and smooth.
After this, Akimoto the Legend will appear again!
Next 2nd gen is Yada Risako
Yada!
- No way!
- You went to same Highschool with Akimoto?
Who is Akimoto actually?
Really! Same Highschool?
1 Year above.
- Ah, you're her junior?
- Yes.
But really, there are 3 people from there.
Yeah, Akimoto as the center.
What the hell is this...
- Is Akimoto cute at that time?
- Yes, really cute.
Since she was accepted, when all the junior including me
saw her at the station, We always like, "Manatsu-san!"
I see, since she was in Nogizaka46 right?
Great.. so if they saw her at the station,
Look it's Manatsu-san!
You saw her in the waterfall episode?
- You saw it?
- Yes.
Manatsu-san.
- Also, the Skydiving. You saw it?
- Yes.
Hahaha, Manatsu-san... like Degawa-san.
(Wiki: Degawa Tatsuro)
Next 2nd gen is Yamazaki Rena.
Wait a second...
- Skills, Chaplin's speech.
- Yes.
What is that? Chaplin's speech.
I was in english club for one year in junior high.
There was a contest so i memorize it.
Now it become my skills.
- Oh! You can do that?
- Yes i can.
- Please do it.
- Sure.
Yes, start now!
- This is... Cool!
- Awesome!
What did you just say?
I don't know.
Eeee... Really?
I forgot...
When you started talking in english
Your face was like.. what's that?
Seems like you're go deep into it?
Yes.
Next, Yonetoku Kyoka's profile.
Oh, you're so good at swimming,
even participated in junior olympics?
Yes, right.
Olympics level?!
4 times...
- Yes.
- Awesome!
Favourite food.
Udon and Mochi.
Why do you like udon?
I like the chewy taste from the noodles.
Your dream is, eating noodles while
riding the adrenaline rush.
Why is that?
Usually we eat udon while relaxing.
Why?
- I think it's exciting to do two things that we like at the same time.
- Oh, you like adrenaline rush?
I love it!
No no no, it's better to eat after you ride it.
No, i want to do it at the same time.
With hot soup?
No, only the noodles.
Without the sauce?
Only noodles.
If you get the chance, how about the sauce?
How?
But... It will spill to my face...
- Yeah, that's it.
- That's the problem.
You like mochi too. Tell us about it.
I like mochi poured with shouyu.
How much can you eat?
In new year's eve, in 1 day i can eat about...
5 pieces.
Wow, a lot.
Next 2nd gen is Watanabe Miria.
Cool...
You're still 13...
Awesome...
Only two years different from my child. Wow.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You look so mature.
- Everyone said so.
Everyone said so, right?
Because you're so calm?
- Oh, her hobby...
- Touching people's cheek.
What does it mean?
Umm, i have my own rank...
Water
Mochi water.
Water mochi for the softest, mochi for the hardest and elastic.
And i love touching it to observe.
Water, water mochi, mochi...
- There are 3 level.
- Yes, 3 level.
What about Yonetoku?
This is Mochi.
It's hard?
You're mochi.
Well, i like mochi...
Awesome!
What about Himura?
- Ah, this is 100% wat...
- A rat, right?
It's water.
Water?!
But maybe water mochi..
It's between water and water mochi.
Between water and water mochi? Tell me what is that?
Water water mochi mochi.
Which one is that?
Hard or soft?
- Not both, it's unique.
- How about Shitara?
- This is water
- Water?
Im water.
What... Why im water water mochi mochi?
Next, member's blog will be checked all-out!
Last week, members managed to succeed the musical
"16nin no Principal deux" in Tokyo.
The Osaka show will be held soon!
Highfive event will be held on May 31th.
Also on June 1st and 2nd, there is a 2nd gen
announcement and bye-bye event.
Check official website for more info.
Next week, there will be member's blog checkup!
For idol, blog is the place thow show themselves.
Here, Idol master Arino will check them out all-out.
Translator: Rustyhand
Timer: Koala13th
Disclaimer:
SUB-SHIRO (¡subshiro46)
Barang siapa yang ingin mem-posting ataupun menterjemahkan ke dalam bahasa apapun
hubungi Rustyhand/Koala13th/part2gee di Facebook Group ataupun AIF.
English Translator: Jejedeath
Follow @subshiro46 and stay update with Nogizaka46 subtitle release!!
Visit www.nogizakanouta.blogspot.com for more !!
Who's shameful past that will be revealed now?