アイDOL
www.myAidol.net
On tonight's Nogizakatte Doko, we'll be having Quizzes about the members' insecurities!
There'll be an outbreak of bad mouthing as the members have their eye on the prize!!
Your face is round!
That's so mean!!!
Your [?] is weird!
That's mean!
Will we have members fainting?
Nogizaka tte Doko?
[What was supposed to be a quiz on insecurities turns into a bad mouthing tournament!?]
You have small eyes.
Your makeup looks gaudy.
Really?
Banana Man
Himura Yuki
Shitara Osamu
DON!
Here we go! This is Nogizakatte Doko? We're the MC, Banana Man. Great to have you here!
And here is Nogizaka-chan!
Let's quickly get into it and introduce what we'll be doing today.
- Okay!
Himura-san.
- Yes.
Go with a menial manner today.
Let's resolve issues with our hidden insecurities...
...Nogizaka Insecurities Quiz!
Let's Resolve our Issues with our Hidden Insecurities
Nogizaka Insecurities Quiz
That was in a menial fashion, right?
- Yep.
The chosen member will put their insecurity up for guessing,
while the other members try to guess it.
By exposing the insecurities hidden within themselves,
they'll aim to mature even further!
For the first question we'll have Sakurai's insecurity up for guessing.
Akimoto, Matsumura, Ikoma and Saito Yuri will be the ones guessing.
Okay, guessers...
It'll be good if you guess it right.
- That's right.
Don't be afraid to guess.
- Yeah, no need.
Say what their insecurity is.
- Yeah.
Got it?
And for the person that guesses it correctly, we have this as the prize!
Here it is!
Oh, what's this?
Dancing Wildly!!
I want to eat it!
Please be generous with the guesses!
m 0 0 l 350 0 l 350 40 l 0 40
Strawberry Shortcake Serenade
m 0 0 l 250 0 l 250 40 l 0 40
Berry Angel of Spring
m 0 0 l 240 0 l 240 40 l 0 40
Shiratama Milk Berry
m 0 0 l 220 0 l 220 40 l 0 40
Chocolate Devotion
The correct guesser will get to choose 1 of these 4 desserts from Cold Stone Creamery.
It's only the winner,
that gets their ice cream made for them over there.
Because after recording, you won't have any chance to have it.
Correct Guesser's Privilege
Obviously.
Then guess it correctly!
- Yeah, get it right.
I want to get it.
Just keep on throwing guesses our way.
So just what insecurity is Sakurai self-conscious about?
Oh, is that so?
- Oh, I see.
Oh, really? But that's cute.
- They won't have a clue.
I really hate it.
- Well, I guess if it was you.
Okay then, Insecurity Quiz... START!
So fast!
- Here we go!
Her chin, her chin is long!
Oi!
It's sticking out!
Her chin is long!
- It's not long!
That's not right. Ikoma!
You're short!
Well, that is true...
- Being short.
That's wrong. Oh here's Akimoto.
She has a chiseled face!
- A chiseled face!
Well it is a bit...
Please don't put it back yourself.
Go.
She's not good at talking!
- What!?
What?
She can't really wrap up an MC performance.
Saying whatever they like.
What!? No way! Do you really think that?
We now have Matsumura!
The parting of her bangs go back too far.
That's not it.
Will it be okay, with such an assault from everyone?
Oh, Matsumura.
Her nose is a bit too prominent.
Oh, I wonder if it is.
- Her nose is fine!
Wrong!
Okay, Ikoma!
- Okay.
Er...
Her cheeks are thick!
- What?
An Insult?
Thick cheeks...
Are my cheeks really?
Wait a minute. Hold on a second.
Let's stop for a moment.
This person can't take anymore if you girls continue saying harsh things.
At her limits?
I'm sorry, Reika!
Akimoto's guess was good. "She has a chiseled face."
Okay, here's a hint.
- A hint?
This one is above the neck, I'd say.
I've got it.
- Okay, let's resume.
Ears!
What?
Her ears are tiny... kinda... big... kinda...
Which one is it?
- Her ears...
...I'll go with her ears being huge.
Ah! Wrong?
- Her ears are...?
Oh, here is Akimoto.
Her ears are badly shaped.
Just wanted to say it?
Oi, you!
Please give a specific answer.
Here we go.
- Be more specific.
Her ears...
Um... are small?
Nope!
Okay, here's Matsumura.
Her ears are pointy?
Which means...?
- Her ears are?
I've got it!
Oh here we have Akimoto!
Her earlobes are small!
I feel so embarrassed!
- It is, isn't it.
Her ears... her ears are...
...weird?
Like I said... these kinds of...
General statements like that...
Her ears go red easily.
No. It has to do with the shape of it.
Her ears point forwards.
Which means?
Oh, here's Akimoto.
Her ears droop forwards.
Drooping?
Drooping...
The expression is different, but...
Correct Answer!
But it should be fine!
Yeah, that's fine.
Okay then, why don't we show the answer.
- Okay.
Her ears are...
The fact that my ears stand.
Wait, isn't that cute?
It is cute, isn't it?
No, it's...
- Show us how it is.
My ears stand.
- Your ears stand?
It's like a monkey's.
Which means that you'd prefer it to lie back more?
- Yeah.
There's nothing wrong with it, though...
- Yeah!
No, when I wear hats...
- Yeah.
My ears get squished.
- Oh, I see.
I see. So they are weird ears.
You got that right, Himura.
We were scared none of you would say anything...
...but you said way too much.
Was Mostly an Insult Tournament.
Sorry.
But because you got it correct, Akimoto...
Please have your reward, Cold Stone ice cream!
Have a mouthful, Akimoto!
I'm all wounded so can I have some?
The wounded Sakurai cannot have any.
BURN.
Why?
You'll get your chance when you guess another person's.
- Please guess it.
So can we please have the others return to their seats?
Please sit down.
Akimoto, what'll you have?
I'll have the Shiratama Milk Berry.
Ah! The Shiratama Milk Berry.
There's no doubt that's going to be good!
- Please make your order.
Good day to you, and welcome to Cold Stone Creamery!
[T/N: This is sung when buying
ice cream from Cold Stone.]
na na na...
la la la...
Yay!
Thank you very much.
Oh, here's the Shiratama part.
Do you like Shiratama?
I love it! With all its chewy goodness!
- Ahh~
I want to eat it!
I want it!
It looks just great!
This is too good to resist!
Thank you for waiting.
Let's eat!
Have a bite and tell us how it is.
- Thank you very much.
Have a bite and tell us.
- Please have it.
Here I go.
Have a bit of the ice cream as well.
This is awesome! I'm so happy I won!
Eat the ice cream as well.
Shiratama...
It's Japanesque!
"It's Japanesque!" Is it good?
Okay then, you can go back to your seat and eat it there.
You can't give it to anyone else.
Yeah, you can't do that.
Don't come here!
Next up is Hoshino's insecurity.
The guessers are Nishino, Hashimoto, Takayama and Inoue.
Are any of you girls confident that you can guess Hoshino's insecurity?
I'm very confident!
- Oh, Hashimoto, you are?
I think I might get it in one go.
- Seriously!?
Oh, you have some examples?
- Stop it!
That's fine, you can get it right with your first guess.
How about you, Takayama?
I think Minami is just too cute, so I have no idea.
How about you, Inoue?
I have no idea, but I want to eat it!
Not confident?
- Want to eat it, right?
Yeah.
Nishino?
Um... I'm not confident, I think.
Then Hashimoto has the advantage.
- She'll get it right straight away.
What? Can I really?
- Yeah, sure.
So what in fact is the hidden insecurity Hoshino has?
Hoshino's insecurity. Ready... start!
Here we go, Takayama!
What? Kazumin?
Being told that she doesn't work hard, even though she does.
That's wrong.
Let's see.
Okay, Nishino.
The fact that she eats only sweets.
Nope.
- That's not close at all.
Oh Hashimoto hasn't had a chance yet. Okay, Inoue!
Um...
Her face is round!
That's so mean!!!
That's wrong.
Ah, here she comes!
Hashimoto, will she get it? You can get it right.
- No! This is bad!
She can't decide on how to arrange her bangs... each day.
Oh?
Her bangs...?
Nice one, that was close.
That's in the right direction.
Do you know, Shiraishi?
We were discussing it just now.
Kanarin's got it.
If you get it right Shiraishi, I'll give you the ice cream.
- What!?
What? That's no fair! I'm the one that knows.
Ah! Inoue responded first.
Inoue.
- Er...
Her bangs are...
...are thin.
That's not it, right?
- Yep, not it.
The last one wasn't bad.
Okay, here's Hashimoto.
Her bangs easily have gaps.
Having gaps... argh! That one's also good!
Was that one close?
Her bangs get into her eyes.
She's annoyed.
Nope.
Um...
Okay, Inoue.
Her bangs curl up.
Waaa~... which means...?
Takayama!
Her downy hairs are bothering her.
Correct Answer!
That's right!
Let's show them what you wrote.
In the parting of my hair here... Can you see?
Yeah, we can.
Oh, that?
This, here.
- Cute!
It's long, my downy hair.
Ah, I see.
Cute.
That is cute.
But because this is what is bothering her...
...Takayama guessed correctly!
Prize Obtained!!
Takayama, over here.
Takayama selected the Strawberry Short Cake Serenade.
That looks so good!
Here I go.
How is it?
So GOOT!
It's good!
What did she say?
- What does she want to say?
This is good!
"This is good!"
Next up we have Ikoma's insecurity.
The guessers are Hoshino, Sakurai, Shiraishi and Wakatsuki.
Ikoma's insecurity. Please guess it. Start!
The shape of her eyebrows differs from each other.
Nope.
- Oh, it's not?
What?
When she wakes up, she looks like a Sunday dad.
What do you mean?
I meet her in the morning before she applies her make-up, and she has ruffled hair with glasses on.
Which really looks like a Sunday dad.
It's not good because she looks like a dad?
Yeah, not good.
- That's wrong.
Here we go!
The sizes of her pupils are different from each other.
That's a bit freaky.
What?
Wait, what is it?
The size of her eyes are different from each other.
Correct Answer!
You've got it!
OMG!
[The sizes of my eyes are different]
They're the same!
But, they're not different at all.
- Yeah, they're the same.
They're the same!
So we can't see it.
- Why don't we ask?
Do you really think that?
I don't see it at all.
No, well first off...
Whenever I look, one looks bigger...
The gap in my double eyelids are also completely different.
Yeah.
- What?
But the faces of humans are generally asymmetric, right?
- Yeah.
But these parts here are really gross.
It's not at all.
I'm jealous of it.
My face is what I'm insecure about.
Even though you're this cute!?
Right?
You're cute!
Makes me want to just grab and throw her!
Can we have everyone else return to their seats?
- Ah, I want some!
I'll go with the Chocolate Devotion!
I want some!
[T/N: This is also sung when buying
ice cream from Cold Stone.]
Looks good!
Oi!
She hasn't finished commenting, you know!
Wakatsuki is giving her impressions about the dessert.
With the worst possible timing.
- Kazumin!
You're the worst.
You had to do it at the best part...
Okay, Wakatsuki, have a bit and tell us what you think.
- Okay.
I'm sorry.
Next we have Nishino's insecurity.
And for the guessers we have Ito Marika, Fukagawa, Takayama and Nakada.
Nishino's insecurity. Guess it right! Start!
- Let's go!
Push the button!
Go for it!
- I have no idea.
If you say it, you'll win... Okay!
Here we have Takayama!
The fact that she cries very easily.
Cries very easily....
Wrong.
What is it?
Okay, Ito Marika.
Being shy?
Here's Takayama.
When she smiles she gets dimples here on both sides.
But isn't that cute?
That's cute!
She has it on both sides.
Hint: it has nothing to do with her appearance.
- What?
What is it?
Okay.
Body odour?
- What!?
What is it about her body odour?
- She has none.
What's with her body odour?
Please don't just say whatever pops into your head.
Oh, nothing, nothing.
Yeah, but...
What? I didn't say anything.
But her body odour?
Uh, nothing at all.
Please don't push it down yourself.
- Ah, I'm sorry.
Hint:
Hint: When she speaks...
Okay, Takayama.
She seems quiet, but...
...but she really is funny...
...and people don't get that.
Too long!!
If no one guesses correctly, there won't be any ice cream given.
- No!
Good luck!
When she speaks...
Here's Nakada.
She speaks differently, like when she blogs and other times...
That's not it.
She speaks with a lisp.
Not bad.
Not a bad guess.
She can't speak very clearly.
Ah, not bad.
- What?
What is it?
Go ahead.
She speaks with an Osaka accent?
Ah! You've gone colder, I think.
Okay, Takayama.
She can't say the things she wants to.
That's wrong.
- What?
When she speaks, her mouth...
Takayama.
When she speaks, her mouth gets dry.
What!?
- Nope.
Okay, Fukagawa.
Her mouth stays small when she speaks?
Which means?
Time's up!
I want to eat some!
I had no idea.
Okay, here's the answer.
When I speak, my mouth doesn't move.
- Yeah.
What!?
You really think that? I really don't think that's the case, though.
- No...
Whenever I see myself on TV...
- Her mouth is moving.
...the shape of my mouth doesn't change.
And... like with Ikuchan, her mouth goes like...
It moves quite a bit, right?
- Yeah.
My mouth always stays horizontal.
- Oh, now that you mention it.
And I really don't like that.
But that's fine.
- Yeah, shouldn't be worrying about that.
Next we have Hashimoto's insecurity.
The guessers are Fukagawa, Matsumura, Shiraishi and Hoshino.
Do the participants have any thoughts? Any confident ones?
Well, she's seems like one with a mature insecurity.
- Oh, yeah.
It's written down.
- Okay!
Please show it to just us.
I see...
I wonder what it is.
I see. It has to do with her appearance.
- Appearance?
Let's get rolling. What's Hashimoto's insecurity? Quiz, start!
Here we have Matsumura.
Her make-up looks gaudy.
Really?
She always says that.
Okay, Shiraishi.
Her posture being too perfect?
But that's a good thing, right?
She doesn't seem to think so.
Fukagawa.
She has a very prominent nose.
Correct Answer!
What!? No way!
It's fine, though.
She has a prominent nose.
- In what way!?
It's perfectly fine!
I'm jealous of it!
It's way too big compared to my face.
Your nose?
- My nose.
There's nothing wrong with having a prominent nose, right?
- Yeah.
The size of everyone else's nose perfectly matches their face.
Oh she does say a lot about people's noses.
Like, "You have a nicely shaped nose."
- Yeah.
Well, I can't tell. I think it's perfetly fine.
Her nose is real cute.
But it seems that when you put make-up on you end up looking gaudy, right?
No, no!
Yeah, that's why my make-up today is light.
Really? But you do seem gaudy, was what someone said, right?
No, that's not true!
It wasn't me!
"It wasn't me?
It was you.
Okay, Fukugawa got it right.
- Yes.
Please go receive your reward.
- Ah, so lucky.
Can the others please return to their seats?
The arrangement of her teeth!
Whaaat?
Coming up... The members say all they have to say to Takayama!!
m 0 0 l 180 0 l 180 27 l 0 27
Ikoma Rina
m 0 0 l 225 0 l 225 27 l 0 27
Matsumura Sayuri
m 0 0 l 200 0 l 200 27 l 0 27
Shiraishi Mai
m 0 0 l 180 0 l 180 27 l 0 27
Sakurai Reika
Quiz on insecurities. For the last one we have Takayama.
And we have these 4 members as the guessers.
Okay, time for the quiz on Takayama's insecurity. Start!
Oh, here's Matsumura.
Up until now she believed that she was fair-skinned, but Maiyan is in fact the fair-skinned one.
That's a good one.
Her ability to speak clearly.
Is bad?
- Yeah.
Nope.
That is true.
Okay, Shiraishi.
Square shoulders.
That too is true.
Okay, Matsumura.
She has a hard time preparing her bangs.
Ah, that's not it.
Will Sakurai have a chance?
Ah, here she is.
Her eyes being small.
"Her eyes being small."
Okay.
She has thin-shaped eyes.
- Thin-shaped eyes.
Oh, but...
Yes?
- Is it with her eyes?
Huh?
What about her eyes?
Her eyes...
- Her eyes...
Her eyes... are kinda intense-looking.
- Her eyes are intense-looking.
The fact that she has double eyelids.
- Double eyelids!
Sorry, but it has nothing to with her eyes.
- What? No way!
Not her eyes.
Nothing with her eyes!
Here's Matsumura.
She easily gets those smile lines.
That's true, but wrong.
Not her smile lines.
What could it be?
Shiraishi.
She's bothered by her frizz.
- Ah, there's that. But it's wrong.
The hair that sticks up?
- Yeah.
Nope.
This insecurity can't be fixed.
I've got it! I've got it! Um...
She has a stiff back.
There's that, but that's not the one.
Well, I do have a stiff back.
Her nervous laugh.
Ah, that's not it.
- What?
Nervous laughter... that might be the closest one yet.
- Uh, yeah.
Come now.
Ikoma.
The arrangement of her teeth.
- Arrangement of her teeth.
Whaaat?
- What's it about her teeth?
She has a bad set of teeth!
Oh, is it really?
Yeah, it is.
But it's not.
- Yeah, it's not.
Okay, next.
Shiraishi.
She sneezes like a middle-aged man.
- Ah, that's not it.
Nope.
It's not that she sneezes like a middle-aged man.
This part of her... is weird.
AHH! That's so mean!
- Too far.
What? How is it weird?
Kazumin keeps saying, "This part of me sticks out...
...right? It's gross, isn't it?"
That part is weird?
I see.
Which part of her would she be unconfident about?
The fact that her hands are big.
That is true, but that's not it either.
- Big hands?
Hint? Hint?
The hint is...
It's between these parts.
It's around this area, under the nose.
Okay, Shiraishi.
Her philtrum is deep?
A deep philtrum.
- Nope.
It's surprisingly not that kind of thing.
When she smiles her chin disappears from sight.
When she smiles her chin disappears?
It's still there.
It's in this region.
What is it?
She personally dislikes the shape of her nose.
Her nose...
Yeah, I don't like my nose.
Okay, everyone? It's not just the outside, there's stuff inside this region as well.
Inside?
I'm not sure, but the mole over here.
She hates the mole there?
She does.
You hate it?
- But, like...
Whenever she laughs, she opens her mouth too wide and reveals the insides.
You don't see that much.
That's wrong!
She has large tonsils?
Ah!!
Yeah, they are big, but yeah...
That guess was the closest so far!
What is it?
She... has an Adam's apple!
Ah... I don't have any!
Everyone has one.
Nope, no Adam's apple, right?
Go ahead.
Her throat easily gets hurt.
- Oh, that is true.
But, that's not it.
Sakurai.
She can't produce her natural voice.
That's real close!
Her natural voice is weird!
In what way...
...is her natural voice weird?
Her natural voice is deep and weird.
Correct Answer!
That's it!
Please show us what you wrote.
My natural voice is deep.
That is her insecurity.
But she has a great voice!
That's not true.
My natural voice is incredibly deep.
- I see.
When I went up for candidacy for the student council in junior high...
...my voice was so deep...
...that it was surprising.
Let us hear it.
Natural voice... What voice do you have now?
Right now I'm talking with a produced voice...
Then, show us.
If I were to speak in my natural voice...
It really tires my throat, though.
I'm Takayama Kazumi.
It's like that.
Your name?
- "I'm Takayama Kazumi."
Hello, I'm Takayama Kazumi.
Really?
- Yeah, it's really deep.
But that other one sounded like the weird one.
- "I'm Takayama Kazumi!"
No...
Your natural voice...
My natural voice is weird.
I'm not sure how to say this... but the future seems tough for you.
Yeah...
You'll have to be burdened with that.
- Yeah.
Coming up next... we'll be having that CM song being shown for the first time!!
Next time on NogiDoko, we have the members lecturing all over the place about stars.
Monday 29th, April Pacifico Yokohama
5th Single Kobetsu Handshake Event
From Ando Mikumo, who announced her graduation from Nogizaka the other day...
...we have a message of thanks to her fans.
m 0 0 l 200 0 l 200 45 l 0 45
Ando Mikumo
Hailing from Shonan, 100 times energetic! I'm Ando Mikumo a.k.a Anchanman!
I have announced that I'm going to graduate from Nogizaka.
From now on I won't be a Nogizaka member anymore,
But I'm going to do my best on my own to move forward.
So please keep supporting me!
I love you all! Thank you so much!
Please keep up your support for her!
Thank you all so much!
The lecture on stars!
Next week, we'll be having Nogizaka46's Stars Lecture!
Realising that you should aim to be a star in the entertainment industry,
we should be learning about the profiles of the big stars accurately.
But by continuously forgetting the details...
will a new star be born?
[In order to become a star you've got to learn from the stars themselves!!]
[The Nogizaka members present their Star Lectures all over the place!]
Panda.
Giant Panda.
Antonio Inoki!
I have no idea what you're saying.
Ready, and...
Komanechi!!!
With such confidence in incorrect details, what'll become of the stars' profiles!?