Tonight, we will show the behind the scene footages
of Nogizaka46’s participation
in the match between Rakuten and Nippon Ham.
The members were appointed to get everyone fired up for the match,
In this important match, they need to challenge this nerve-wracking ceremonial first pitch!
I’m nervous right now, but I’ll manage somehow.
That superstar will also have a sudden participation!
This fateful ceremonial first-pitch, how will it turn out?
Study meeting about certain happenings!
Furthermore, tonight,
Large Idol Family study meeting about certain happenings, final part!
It is falling down from the moment I put it on,
In front, you were saying bye bye, but the zipper at the back is…
The troubles of being in a large family,
then will resentment erupt tonight as well?!
Nogizakatte, Doko?
DON! Nogizakatte Doko has started, we're your hosts, Bananaman, yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
and here are... Nogizaka-chan~
Now then, Himura-san,
Please announce what we have for today.
Understood. Tonight’s plan is…
Let’s support Tohoku Rakuten Golden Eagles!
I heard that the Tohoku Rakuten Golden Eagles...
offered these girls to keep the crowd fired up and throw the ceremonial first-pitch.
Really?
It seems we have compiled footages of it.
We wanted to see the highlights. Douzo~
Let’s support Tohoku Rakuten Golden Eagles!
And for that…
The Annual Rakuten Group Day Game will be held on the 9th of July,
The group is offered with the ceremonial first pitch and various events
for the game between Tohoku Rakuten Golden Eagles and Nippon Ham Fighters.
In order for the members to inform their participation in the game,
With all of Rakuten’s employee present at the weekly morning assembly, the members got the privilege of expressing their determination.
However…
Eh? You’re going here?
That’s nerve-wracking.
Speaking of Rakuten’s company official language, English is their standard.
Moreover, the morning assembly where the members will say their greetings
is relayed towards all Rakuten employees around the world.
This is not good!
They received advice from one of Rakuten’s employees,
Now, let’s go to that morning assembly!
All people of Rakuten all around the world,
They barged into the assembly for this important match.
Will they be able to ace their English greetings?
That’s nice.
Positive response.
They got a warm reception.
Senkyuu berii macchi!
They somehow cleared the English greetings garnering favorable impression.
However, the relief from nervousness is just for a brief moment.
They all did another greeting to the president of Rakuten, Mikitani,
And right off the bat…
Your English was really good!
Praise.
We practiced a lot, right?
-That’s right.
Aim towards being international idols.
On the 9th of July, yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
Having received words of encouragement from Mikitani-shacho,
This offer have to be a success!
So, with that…
The ceremonial first pitch’s... ball throw?
Amazing!
Sloppy right from the start.
Ball throw?
Ceremonial first pitch.
Who will deliver
the first pitch?
So it’s just throwing the ball, huh?
Okay, okay.
Do over.
So, with that…
Appointment suggestion for the one who will deliver the first pitch.
A do over?
Let’s take a good look!
What do we do? Who should it be?
Right here!
Announcing candidacy.
Ah, double Sayuri.
Can you really do it?
-I can do it.
Both of you are a little bit questionable.
Okay then, I get it.
First, I will throw the ball, then Sayunyan will catch it midway and throw it to the catcher.
Everyone’s talking all at once.
First attempt.
I’ve never seen anything
like that in my life.
Nanamin, how about you?
No, no, I’m good.
Keeping distance.
Various proposals are made for this important ceremonial first pitch.
They can’t afford to make it look like a farce!
What if it became…
Someone who has experience with throwing will do.
Someone with experience?
Ah, softball.
Experienced with softball.
I wonder if it will reach~
If you’re going to practice throwing for several times, I’ll definitely go with you.
Then, somewhere like a batting center.
Plans on strengthening batting skills first.
Then, do your best.
There we have it, under the condition of having a practice,
Shiraishi who has experience in softball will deliver the ceremonial first pitch!
Several days later, as preparation for tomorrow’s match, the members are…
…not in a batting center, but in Tokyo Dome.
So, for tomorrow’s match between the Rakuten and Nippon Ham,
I was given the opportunity to deliver the ceremonial first pitch but,
We are here right now and we're waiting for a player of the team.
That’s right. My heart is pounding right now.
Could it be? You're kidding.
I’m so nervous.
That legendary… pitcher.
Legendary?
The members feel nervous, who is this player?
Konnichiwa
Uwah, that’s great!
Are you serious?!
That’s right, the one who turned up is a pitcher who represents the baseball world,
Tohoku Rakuten Golden Eagles’ pitcher, Tanaka Masahiro
Konnichiwa
Ready, set... We are Nogizaka46. yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
Smile.
Ah, he's smiling.
This is awesome,
as expected!
So cool~
Raw impression.
Although they are feeling sorry for having troubled Tanaka, they asked them pitching tips for the ceremonial first pitch.
That's nice.
There’s no point in saying anything that is hard to do.
So, throwing it in the easiest and simplest way is the best thing, I believe.
In reality, the mound is actually inclined,
and the timing is different when throwing from a flat ground.
This is amazing,
he's considering a lot.
Maybe because
he’s the ace, right?
If you can throw it around here with caution, I guess it will be a success.
I see. Thank you very much.
In addition to that, they kindly asked a request.
Can you please take a look at my pitching?
Yes, no problem.
Comfortably OK.
yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
Awesome!
How luxurious!
Tanaka played catchball with Shiraishi to see her pitching.
Totally looking good.
You can do it!
sugoi~
At that point…
Great, you can even
catch the ball.
It seems like we can use the mound in the stadium for your pitching.
Surprising development.
Awesome!
That’s the best!
Let’s practice over there.
onegaishimasu~
To practice on the dome’s
mound is quite something.
That’s true!
What a development!
In order to grasp what the real game feels like, Shiraishi will practice throwing in the dome’s mound.
You raise your legs and throw it hard.
Because there’s an inclination right here,
the timing is different than on a flat ground,
of course it’s easier to plunge forward.
You have to throw so that your body won’t plunge into the ground.
What was your position
in softball?
Second base.
Understood.
Because there’ll be a lot of fans attending the game,
In that situation, you’ll get nervous.
You’ll be caught between “I want to throw it” and “I can’t throw it.”
There’ll be a lot
of fans for sure.
To get used to the inclination of the mound,
and to overcome nervousness in the game are the important advice she received.
Looking at her on the mound for the very first time…
From here, you look so far!
It’s far~
Renewed sensation.
It's so far.
By just standing and looking at it, the large distance can be felt.
From the middle of the diamond, Shiraishi’s first pitch is…
Awesome! Really?!
Strike!
I did it!
That one’s a strike!
Isn’t this good enough already?
An impressive strike from her first pitch on the dome’s mound!
In addition to that…
Go!
Two in a row!
Seriously?!
Yey!
It’s already perfect then!
Moreover, she has quite a
control on her throws.
I wonder if I could do this.
As expected from Shiraishi who has experience in softball,
She has shown pitching that is close to a strike.
If you were to throw just like in this practice...
Practice.
-Yes.
With this, you can do no wrong.
Shiraishi received an approval from Tanaka,
With confidence in her heart, she’ll challenge the ceremonial first pitch!
And then, the day of the match between Rakuten and Nippon Ham has finally arrived.
Rakuten’s starting pitcher for that day is Tanaka.
Confident as expected, he will challenge to get his 12 consecutive win in this important match.
Furthermore…
There he is!
Ohayou gozaimasu~
Manager Hoshino
You’re doing the ceremonial first pitch today?
Yes.
Did your pitch reach the plate with this distance?
Yes, it did.
Oh, is that so?
You are more amazing than I am!
They even reported to Manager Hoshino for the ceremonial first picth. And then…
Awesome, right?
What am I gonna do?
I just thought of telling that we’re doing something extremely incredible right now.
Approaching gradually towards game time,
The nervousness is up a notch.
And for this day, there are 43,000 in attendance,
she’s under pressure even if she didn’t like it.
Because I think there’ll be a lot in attendance,
I'm really nervous
Of course, because there are members and players around me,
I’m nervous right now, but I’ll manage somehow.
Can Shiraishi overcome this nervousness?
And will she be able to deliver a successful ceremonial first pitch?
Finally, the fateful ceremonial first pitch.
I’m nervous right now, but I’ll manage somehow.
Rakuten bestowed a ceremonial first pitch offer for this important match.
In order to make that task successful, Shiraishi did a complete preparation.
The nervousness before the match,
and the pressure from the big crowd is overwhelming.
Will Shiraishi be able to make this important ceremonial first pitch a success?
The fated moment has come.
Next, Rakuten Group Day Fans Thanksgiving 2013
We’ll conduct the ceremonial first pitch!
To deliver today’s ceremonial first pitch is Nogizaka46’s Shiraishi Mai!
Awesome and frightening.
This is really amazing!
Ah, everyone’s
cheering her on.
Well then, please go ahead.
I’m quite nervous but,
After a few days of practice,
and because I was taught how to throw,
I’m sure that everything will be alright.
With this, you can do no wrong.
To what extent do you have confidence?
I have confidence!
With Tanaka who oversaw her practice and Manager Hoshino,
along with baseball stars representing the baseball world,
and with the big crowd watching attentively,
Challenge the string of fate!
Where will the ball really go?
You're kidding, right?!
What happened?
What an ending!
The ball pitched by Shiraishi is a wild pitch which bounced twice.
You lost your strength?
You were knocked
down completely.
Sinking.
Dealing with a lot of shock,
she crouched down on the mound.
It was really frustrating.
Really..
Just plain frustrating.
There’s too much frustration that she shed a lot of tears right after the ceremonial first pitch.
However, after seeing that, on Tanaka’s blog is…
I saw her disappointed appearance,
But I think she seriously made an effort for it.
It was fun, wasn’t it?
Such kind words…
For Shiraishi, it was a ceremonial first pitch where regrets will remain.
Game’s all good, playball! And then…
Here's Sakurai Reika.
yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
Batting for Rakuten Eagles is…
Stadium announcer?
What’s up with that?
That’s awesome!
Ok, #7.
#7, Shortstop, Matsui~~~~ Kazuo
Just like how they did it
in the Major League.
They even performed
their song.
You even did this?
That's amazing!
It was fun.
Live performance, stadium DJ and cheerleading, Did their cheers somehow reach the players?
Tanaka achieved his 12th consecutive win with an unblemished record.
Remarkably, the Rakuten Eagles had a complete game victory!
Whether it contributed to the victory or not, the Eagles cheering plan finished safely.
That was nice.
-It was amazing, right?
I’m so jealous of you.
-Not just the ceremonial first pitch but you also did a lot of things.
Having Ma-kun to teach you is the best.
It’s just that, it was frustrating, the pitch…
Yes, it was.
What happened? How did it turn out like that?
When I saw the crowd, I got completely nervous.
I was even taught how to grip the ball.
But I don’t remember it anymore when I stood right there.
But I exerted not much force, and the timing is off.
Embarrassing, right?
Yes, it is!
That’s why you jumped and crouched.
Losing Pitcher.
But it wasn’t supposed to be like this!
Yes, it was something like that.
But it was good, it was a great experience, right?
After this, Large idol group study meeting about certain happenings… Final part!
Previously, we had “Large Idol Family study meeting about certain happenings.”
My grandmother often says “Nogizaka appeared right there, huh?”
I didn’t sing! Moreover, I didn’t even appear!
From the worries they accumulate day by day came an unexpected roar of laughter.
These situations can't be covered with just one episode.
With that, continuing from last week, this week too..
Large Family Happenings, Start!
Let’s move on…
The next happening is this.
Similar casual clothes.
For casual clothes, this is unacceptable.
Who wrote this one?
Ah, Akimoto, what do you mean?
In handshake events, having similar clothes is acceptable, but…
Even with everyday casual clothes, there is someone who wear quite similar clothes with others.
What do you mean?
-Something like doing imitation of others?
Copying others’ fashion.
Hhmm, well, there’s also that…
Is this really happening often?
There’s only one member who often wear quite similar clothes with me.
Ah, similar with Akimoto?
Who is it?
It's Sakurai.
Something like your tastes have the similar look.
Basically, I’ve always been wearing the same type of clothes, but,
Sakurai is a bit different at first, she is somewhat a cool type.
Ah, she’s the type who imitates other people!
Reference.
I wonder if she’s getting closer to me.
I see.
Wait. Are you wearing clothes same to that of Manatsu?
That happened quite a lot.
After all, with the amount of money that people our age can spend,
then there is a trend to consider as well,
and the places to go shopping are also limited.
Are you doing an imitation of Manatsu-san?
No, I’m not!
Just a coincidence?
-I’m definitely not!
So Manatsu-san is just an excessively self-conscious person, right?
Excessively Self-conscious Person.
That’s not true, you know!
I don’t think that it really matter but,
But to be frank, if Himura-san showed up to work with the same clothes I’m wearing,
I would hate it.
It’s fine but…
If you really hate it then, tell the shop clerk that “If any Nogizaka member came by, don’t ever sell this to them.”
Uramawashi
Uramawashi – skill used in variety. To sum it up, it is a statement that sets up the mood for easy follow up.
Why don’t you just go shopping together?
With the person who has similar clothes.
So that you won’t end up having similar clothes.
What if we wanted the same thing?
Decide it by janken.
That is the power balance.
But I bought this!
Having similar clothes, does this happen often?
It seems so, but I haven’t experienced it.
Could it be because of...?
Why?
Well, the fit is kinda…
The fit is kinda.
That was really funny.
Let move on, this is the next one.
Quick change during live shows
Is there some incident about this? Who wrote this?
We have high hopes.
For example, it does happen during live, right?
For example?
Yes. For example: live concerts and such.
Not just during live, we have to change clothes quickly.
Because the outfits are not always the same right?
Then, really, for about 40 seconds, we have to finish changing. Is it forty?
Well, it seems that we have to finish changing with that time limit, something like that.
During the live performance, on the stage,
Because I was in a real hurry,
On my way, my clothes came off, and I thought that it was no good.
I was holding the zipper firmly on my back.
Right on the stage?
It is falling down from the moment I put it on,
In front, I’m saying bye bye. It was during the encore.
In front, you were saying bye bye, but the zipper at the back is…
Greetings ignored.
That’s awesome!
While being sociable,
I’m saying bye bye a lot.
This part came down and opened up.
Because there are a lot of people, I can’t turn around.
-Because she can’t zip it on her own.
You have to acquire a technique to do it.
Certainly, there’s a great difference between being near close to the crowd and away from them.
Basically, those in the front row will gather together.
Then those at the back are like…
You don’t have to wave your hands, just hurry up!
No consideration.
That’s enough! It’s unnecessary!
Wait a sec, idols have to wave their hands.
That would be a big deal for the fans.
Most people, they’ll do this.
That’s enough! Just get going!
There is no one like that!
There is.
Who?
Serina?
Serina is the type of person who can’t help but stop.
Then everyone else is like…
Enough of this Serina talk!
Let’s move on to the next one, here it is!
Obsession with food.
What's the matter, Noujo?
Uhhmm...
-Obsession with food.
For example…
At someone’s birthday…
Cake?
Yeah! Cake.
Yeah, that one.
another case of tameguchi (casual talk)
Hold on for a second,
He is your senpai!
Ah, I messed up.
Yeah.
I was wrong, senpai.
It's alright, it's alright.
Uhhmm...
Yeah...
For example, when the cake has arrived,
someone will invite everyone to gather and eat, then everyone will come.
-They’ll come.
They’ll say “Aa~ Strawberry~ ♥”, but,
Everyone’s faces are serious.
“Aa~ Strawberry~ ♥”
Pride of lions aiming at their prey.
So it won’t get eaten away.
So it won’t get eaten away, because there’s a lot of you, right?
Yes.
-Strawberry.
We’re doing kawaii faces but our obsession for food is too much.
You also like eating huh?
When idols pig out, they also get fat, right?
In the case of AKB48, everyone got fat so they banned it.
Supply of provisions banned.
The supply of provisions.
It was banned.
-Banned?
Eh? Why?
Because everyone do nothing but eat, then the innocent ones eat more.
Our brains are fat, therefore,
I will want it by just appreciating it visually!
-I know how you feel!
”Just a piece of this, and also a piece of this.” I’ll do something like that.
Then I’ll say ”I will eat this with everyone!”
But I’ll end up eating most of it.
Stealing food from others’ share.
I get that!