In this evening's Nogidoko there will be a bungee jump for the 6th single campaign!
Just before the dreaded jump
Something unthinkable will happen to Captain Sakurai!
Will the 6th single campaign really end in success?
[The do-or-die bungee jump campaign]
[Will Sakurai really be able to jump? And if not....]
DA!!
Sorry about that. Nogizaka tte Doko's started, we're your hosts Bananaman, enjoy the show!
And heeere's Nogizaka-chan!
Here we go, look that way!
[T/L: This comes from a more advanced form of janken]
Oh no, I lost
I lost
Today we're going to
Well, last week was just the first installment
We only discussed who was going to perform the bungee jump for the single campaign
Now we're finally getting to the sequel
We get to see who really did the bungee jump
Who was it really?
Not "Who was it?", we already decided on Sakurai
OK, let's get on with it
Sakurai, today you do the introduction
-Yes!
OK, video footage, go!
What was that?
The 6th single campaign was announced last week
And the activity chosen was
Promoting the single through a bungee jump!
From among the front row members, one was chosen as a representative
Isn't Kazumin trying to hide in the background too much?
You need to jump and train your nerves!
The members took place in a heated discussion
And then all 16 senbatsu members voted for the representative
And the one chosen for the famously horrific jump was
Sakurai!!
The one taking the challenge will be the captain, Sakurai
And Takayama was chosen as her backup
Tsubokura Yoshiyuki
Watabe Jun
And so, we're here at Minakami, Gunba prefecture!
[T/L: The guest hosts are from the comedy group Wagaya, they were guests on Nogizaka tte Doko early on]
It's been a long time since we saw you
It's been a long time
You guys really seem like top idols these days
You all seem completely different to when we first met
One person here looks weirdly underdressed though
-What's up with that?
Why are you wearing that?
There is a good reason, I have a nasty allergy to insect bites
There you go; the drama emerged
-She's a real diva actress!
She's a real diva actress!
-The special insect bite excuse
The special insect bite excuse
Out came the special treatment!
And so this time we're going to be doing a bungee jump
The height of the bungee jumping spot next to us is an eye-watering 42 metres!
Shall we take a quick look?
This would be scary if you looked down
Looking down before you jump...
I've done this before, if you looked down first it would be really hard
This time the single campaign is a bungee jump from a bridge
The height is the same as a 12 story building: 42 metres!
If you compare it to the previous skydiving campaign
It's scary because you need to jump yourself
Now the single campaign will swing into motion!
Nowaynowaynowaynowaynowaynowaynowaynoway this is impossible!
-Captain!
-What's wrong captain?
-This place is scary
What's wrong?
Actually, if you want to have a hit, this is the place to come
Famous people who jumped here include Ninety-Nine
[T/L: Japanese comedians]
Exile
Kanjani Eight
[T/L: Boy band]
And your rivals, AKB48
Eh?! Did they all really jump here?
That's right
[T/L: Sugiyama is the third member of Wagaya, who didn't come today]
-By the way Sugiyama tried this and he retired
Sugiyama Hiroyuki
By the way Sugiyama tried this and he retired
"Retire"? He just wussed out
But if you guys can perform a bungee jump here, your single will definitely become a big hit!
Right?
Isn't it good that you were chosen by everyone last time?
How is your mental state right now?
Well, because such harsh things were said about me
I need to show all the other members that I have my dignity as captain
-You can see her resolve
-It's impressive
So I'm going to try my best!
First to challenge the jump will be the appointed member, Sakurai
But if Sakurai is unable to jump, Takayama will be forced to substitute
By the way, if the worst should happen
You're covered by our insurance
What do you think is going to happen to us?!
In the event that Sakurai dies
You're covered for 10 million yen
[T/L: It's not that much, about £60,000]
Oh my god, it's actually written down!
And if you're injured your hospital fees are covered
If you invest that 10 million yen into the single it'll probably sell
Wait, stop, this is insane!
This time, Akimoto will return Sakurai's favour from the previous campaign and support Takayama and Sakurai
However, Tsubokura has an unsettling message for the wavering Sakurai
In an hour and a half ordinary customers will start using this spot again
We've only rented it for that long
In an hour and a half people will start showing up
So if you don't jump then this will all have been futile
Wow, the pressure!
The engineer who had to come 3 hours from Tokyo
The feelings of the staff who got things ready
And the money spent on renting this place
That's right!
Think very carefully about the effort that was put in while you jump
This is weird, you are you pressuring me so hard?!
Feeling pressure from all sides, Sakurai prepared to jump
This looks super scary right?
The other members wait under the bridge, waiting and believing in their captain
If Sakurai fails to jump, a compulsory jump awaits Takayama
With the weight of the success of the single on her back
She looks down from the 42 metre high jump platform
Wah, wait, wait, this is too scary!
-Woah, amazing
Jumping from here, you'd really mean it
-Sakurai, how's the view?
Sakurai, how's the view?
It's scary, scary, way too scary!
No, I can't do it!
-This is properly scary
This is properly scary
But you'll all have to do this at some point
Come on, you can do it Reika!
After this, please go in your own time
In your own time, please step forward
And then, make sure to say
"To make Girl's Rule a massive hit!"
And then jump!
What are the members going to do for Sakurai, who can't seem to jump?
Everyone raise your voice and let's help her out!
Yes!
-What's up with this old geezer?
What's up with this old geezer?
Who is he trying to be?
-We could say "Go for it captain!"
We could say "Go for it captain!"
And then how about "Hop, step and bungee!"?
Let's go!
Go for it captain!
Hop, step and bungee!
However, Sakurai who was receiving this support was...
Wait, this is scary, what should I do, I can't do this, wait, I can't jump, I really can't do anything!!
As a result of Sakurai being stuck like this for over 20 minutes
Tsubokura had to speak up
A lot of staff are working on this
I'm sorry, I know
If you don't jump, Nogizaka46
Might have to break up
No way!
Come on Reika!
Reika~
If the worst comes to the worst
Takayama is standing by and ready
Do it for me Reika!
Reika!
Don't forget, everyone believes in you!
She's never really solved any of our problems
Captain Sakurai, up until now no-one can say they trust her absolutely
If Nogizaka's going to change, the captain needs to do this
I see, I see!
This bungee jump is the perfect chance to show a captain's abilities
Will she be successful, and win the member's respect?
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, Bungee!
I can't do it, I'm going back!
I can't, I can't, I can't!
I can't, I can't, it was impossible after all!
It's scary, it's too scary!
Sakurai, who couldn't overcome her fear, collapsed and couldn't get back up
What happened?
-It's scary~
It's scary~
-Is it impossible for you?
Is it impossible for you?
It's really too scary
-Really too scary?
Really too scary?
-It's really too scary, way too scary!
It's really too scary, way too scary!
-Well, it definitely looks scary from here
Well, it definitely looks scary from here
What should we do then?
Reika~
-Can you try one more time?
Can you try one more time?
Nnnn, I can't
Is it impossible?
-Nonono
Shall we get Takayama to substitute for you?
If Sakurai abandons her duty here, the dreaded jump will pass to Takayama
What will Captain Sakurai's decision be?
Do you want to substitute?
No way! Is this for real?
-That tiny nod! You gave up so meekly
That tiny nod! You gave up so meekly
REIKA!! THIS HAS TO BE A LIE!!
Sakurai's spirit cracked and she quit, now it's Takayama's turn!
Was it scary?
It was really scary, even though I know I should have gone
When I was supposed to jump off I could let go off the hand rail
It was scary?
-Too scary
When she was asked to switch with Takayama she just gave a tiny nod
I don't believe this
Even though it was a good opportunity for her
It was her chance to act like a captain
She really should have done it
Because the captain wussed out, Takayama headed to the platform
How did this happen?
Hah, isn't this too scary? I can't do it!
Takayama, can you perform this jump and make the single a hit?
No, wait! I can't!
Go for it Kazumin!
You're even worse than your captain
Reika! Why you...!
How is it?
-Reika, this is horrible!
Reika, this is horrible!
Well, it is really scary
I think anyone would be freaked out by that
Just a bit further forward, the assistant's right behind you
My legs, my legs won't stop shaking!
In your own time, please
You really need to jump yourself
Wait, wait, aaargh!!
Takayama's amazing isn't she
Yaaah, what the heck?!
Tell me this isn't real
Takayama's screams were filling the air
But no jump came, and time was fast running out
I can't do this with one leg shaking
Takayama, there's no time for this
.....No, I can't do it!!
I can't believe this, is everyone going to back out?
What are you people doing?
You can do it!
-Reika, Reika!
Reika, Reika!
-What, what?
What, what?
Nonononono, make it stop!
She just completely collapsed there
After an even shorter time than Sakurai, Takayama just collapsed and gave up
Takayama, what happened?
-Yes
But while I was watching you
I thought that your captain looked more likely to jump
It looked like your lower body had turned to jelly
Honestly, after watching Kazumin
I was thinking that maybe I could do better
Seriously though, there's no time left
Then, I'm sorry Reika, but
Can you try again?
Just once?
How about it?
I guess I'll have to try again, right?
Well then, Sakurai will challenge one more time!
-Go for it!
And if you can't do it
We'll just have to go with Akimoto!
Her reaction just arrived
She has no idea what's going on
Want to give it a shot?
Uh, what are you talking about...?
OK Captain, please try one more time
And if you can't
We still have Akimoto!
I hope I just misheard that
The bungee jump for the sake of the single campaign
What will be Sakurai's fate this time round?
Picking up a spirit that seemed broken
Captain Sakurai is going to take on the bungee jump once more!
(Staff member) It looks like Sakurai's going to go
-Reika!
Reika!
Reika, you can do it!
-Sakurai-chan, this is awesome!
Sakurai-chan, this is awesome!
And if Sakurai's not able to jump
Akimoto's preparing by filling out her insurance
-Wait, wait, this is just weird
What's with this?
This is totally unfair!
He~h, this is really harsh, it's so scary
OK, make your statement and jump
-I knew it, this is horrible!
I knew it, this is horrible!
Ah, she changed out just in case
It's just weird!
You changed just in case, right?
Isn't this "just in case" just weird?
You might be needed, though
Ugh, come on then captain
Last time, Captain Sakurai
It's so tall
Failed to jump
If you don't jump Reika it'll suck to be me!
That's for sure
1, 2...
Come on captain!
Now, once again please prepare yourself, captain
Ha, scary, wait a second
Look, you've already let go
See, you can do it!
I can't just yet, this is just practice
Yeah, yeah, I know
Come on captain!
Why are you suddenly cheering so much harder?
But this is scary....
Anyway, if you yell "So that Girls' Rule will be a big hit!"
If you yell it out loud it should help
Use that feeling
Nogizaka46's 6th single!
To make it a big hit!
It's hopeless!
It's no good!
Do you even want the single to sell?!
Facing her frantic fears for the sake of the group, Captain Sakurai
But what about the other members?
Reika!
-Look, a train!
Look, a train!
Cool, a train!
Pff, a train
Shouldn't you be more interested in Sakurai-chan than a train?
Captain Sakurai, is it really impossible?
Is she going?
Go for it!
There's no time!
Since this morning
Lots of adults have been working on this
Even I woke up at 4:30 in the morning
4:30?!
-They came here wanting to be shown your courage
They came here wanting to be shown your courage
The camera operator also had to carry a lot of heavy equipment
All the way here
We've stretched this out long enough
All there is left is for you to jump
Come on Reika!
Jump, you can do it!
Go for it!
Go on!
Jump
Will she give up?
Does Sakurai's nod mean she's made a decision?
Has she decided as captain, to jump for the sake of her comrades?
Or perhaps she's decided to pass the responsibility on once again?
Go! Oh, she looks like she's going
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
-Here we go!
So that Nogizaka46's 6th single will be a big hit!
-She's really going for it!
-She's so cool!
-She really did it!
She really jumped!
-I can't believe it!
Reika!
You look like you're going to cry
The members said they thought she was lacking as a captain
But when it came to the feeling of loving Nogizaka46
She believes she wouldn't lose to anyone!
And most of all she wants this single to be a success
With that strength of that feeling she conquered the fearsome bungee jump
For the sake of her comrades, and her self-belief
Sakurai took a massive step forward
It was awesome!
So awesome
And scary too!
She still going
This is excellent!
Reika!
-Yes~
Yes~
That was amazing!
You might not like it now, but that was seriously amazing
She's still crying
Are you OK?
Mmmnnnn
How was it?
Your first bungee jump?
It was horrifying!
Do you feel more confident than before?
She's cute!
-It was scary right?
She really is cute
What do you think of your captain now?
She's really cool!
You all look moved
You really did well
What did you all think?
It was so moving!
I thought I was going to cry when I did this too
You were great
Did you all feel your captain's greatness?
We felt it!
Has it changed your view of her?
Up until this point
That image of a capable captain
She never had it
But today was really different
She really tried her best for all of us
And when I saw her jump for the 6th single
I felt that I can be relaxed and trust her from now on
The 6th single "Girls' Rule"'s campaign was...
A total success!
Yee-ay!
That was awesome!
I thought you'd do it, but well done!
You gave it your all
It must have been scary though, standing up there
It was really frightening
It really looked that way
I felt a strange pressure
Before you jumped?
-That's right
That's right
-When you're about to jump your body starts feeling heavy
When you're about to jump your body starts feeling heavy
That was scary, I don't ever want to do it again
First time round though, you gave up and passed it on to Takayama
You still don't get why?
I was already terrified
-There are people who can't do it
There are people who can't do it
-I thought I probably couldn't
I thought I probably couldn't
But there was still time so I went
Your legs just freeze up, right?
-That can happen
That can happen
You're just staggering like this, up to the last moment
If you stumble even a little, you'll fall
That's actually what we wanted to see, though
That would have been good
We should have recorded that
The thing is the longer Reika took
The more I understood her fear
And I wanted to share what she was feeling
Was a new bond formed between you two?
Next time should we send you somewhere haunted then?
Coming up, the 6th single's coupling song will debut in the studio
The new single coupling song
"Sekai de Ichiban Kodoroku na Lover" is debuting now!
[T/L: "Loneliest Lover in the World"]
Coming up next, a familial squabble will boil over!
Nogizaka46's midsummer national tour
As soon as this episode is finished, the ticket allocation will start on the group's mobile site
Please check the site for more details
Next week, a great meeting of all the members!
Former AKB member Noro Kayo
Will give this familial meeting a lecture on surviving showbusiness
Huh, it should be Marika
And the group's anger will be dragged out!
[Is this what it means to be a big idol family?]
[Do a lot of members mean a lot of problems?]
Noro-sensei will show them the demon's path!