m 0 0 l 0 27 l 2 27 l 2 0 l 0 0 m 2 0 l -4 0 l -4 6 l 16 6 l 16 4 l -2 4 l -2 2 l 0 2 m 2 2 m 16 0 l 16 27 l 18 27 l 18 -1 l 16 -1 m 22 0 l 22 0 l 24 0 l 24 11 l 19 11 l 19 9 l 22 9 l 22 2 l 15 2 l 15 0 m 6 18 l 6 12 l 12 12 l 12 14 l 8 14 l 8 18 l 6 18 m 12 18 l 12 20 l 6 20 l 6 18 l 10 18 l 10 14 l 12 14 l 12 18 m 5 7 l 8 9 l 7 10 l 4 8 l 5 7 m 10 9 l 10 9 l 13 7 l 14 8 l 11 10 l 10 9 m 3 24 b 3 24 3 23 3 23 b 7 21 11 21 15 23 b 15 23 15 25 15 25 b 11 23 7 23 3 25
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
Nogidoko tonight,
continuing the previous episode...
Let's continue Amachan!
Show your love for your hometown!
Then, confessions using members' local dialects!
Because of the love confessions in local dialects,
Himura is having a high level of delusion!
BUCHI SUKI JAKE~!
(I LOVE YOU SO MUCH~!)
Plus, with laughters left and right,
her Seitanshai will be started!
Nogizakatte, Doko?
- Hashimoto said "lame" just now!
- Why?! Why?!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Let's talk about your hometown! Preserve the LOVE
for your hometown! Love confessions in dialects!
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
- I'm going to claw you!
- I'll claw you!
Can I hold your hand now?
I want to hold hers.
Let's continue Amachan!
Show your love for your hometown!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Judging by Amachan's popularity, we will explain many things
from the [Dialects] to [Local Specialties] of members' hometowns!
Show your love for your hometowns!
Because of the Amachan's success...
... people have been paying attention more
to local dialects and products!
Based on that, we've gathered Nogizaka members
from various areas.
They are going to explain more about...
... events and distinct words
that people of Tokyo don't know.
BANANAMAN
Himura Yuuki
Shitara Osamu
Okay, here's next.
- Ah, this?
- This is the same.
Does it only exist in my hometown?
[Peculiar Word Category]
Peculiar word category.
Lots of words will be revealed here.
When your name gets called later, don't explain it right away.
We will try to guess.
Here's the first one!
Does it only exist in my hometown? [Peculiar Word Category]
JonJon
JonJon?
That's what we usually do,
we let our JonJon out.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Words only my hometown knows
[JonJon]
- Whose is this?
- Whose hometown?  - Me!
- Ah, Shizuoka!
- Yup!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
m 0 3 b 0 3 0 3 0 3 b -7 -2 -10 -5 -10 -8 b -10 -11 -8 -13 -5 -13 b -2 -13 0 -11 0 -8 b 0 -11 2 -13 5 -13 b 8 -13 10 -11 10 -8 b 10 -5 7 -2 0 3
Wakatsuki Yumi
asal Shizuoka
- JonJon? Why is there JonJon after DonDon?
- No, this one is different!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Local ad of Shizuoka
[ DonDon Obento ]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
The meaning of a word only
Shizuoka knows [JonJon]?
Perhaps it does sound similar with DonDon,
but this JonJon is actually different.
- JonJon?
- When do you use this?
JonJon has nothing to do with time.
- Toilet! Toilet!
- Obviously not toilet.
- It must be, usually we say "Finally I'm JonJonning!"
Is that the sound?
No?
On what condition do you use this?
For example...
"Ah, this is troublesome, shall we get the JonJon?"
"Is JonJon good?"usually it's like that.
Bicycle?
- Nope.
- This is something people wear.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Fukagawa Mai
from Shizuoka
It's the name of the thing.
- Shirt!
- Nope.
- Shoes?
- Close...
- Sandals!
- Correct!
- Sandals?
- Yes, sandals.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Sandals = JonJon
In Shizuoka
- So it's called JonJon?
- Yes.
- The ones you wear inside the house.
- House?
There are slippers you wear only in toilet, right?
The name started from there...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Shizuoka's distinct word
[Sandals] = [JonJon]
... and it got simplified like that.
- So, Benjo sandals? (Toilet/bathroom)
So those are called JonJon sandals?
- No, because "JonJon" means sandals!
- The pronounciation changed.
- JonJon sandals means sandals sandals.
- True.
Same meaning.
- Did I say JonJon Sandals just now?
- You just did.
- So it doesn't mean toilet?
- Benjo JonJon, right?
- At the beginning...
- So Benjo JonJon means toilet slippers?  - Yes!
- Benjo JonJon?
- Yes, Benjo JonJon.
Dad is wearing Benjo JonJon in the living room, you know!
Dad, that's Benjo JonJon!
A daily thing habit in Shizuoka?
Ah, but that's how it usually is.
- Like that?
- Yes.
- Interesting, isn't it?
- Indeed!
Alright, moving on. Here's next!
Does it only exist in my hometown? [Peculiar Word Category]
Sunrise
Sunrise?
- Is this a local dialect?!
- This is English, isn't it?
- Who?
- Me.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Nakamoto Himeka
from Nagashima
Who? There we go!
Your hometown has a lot of stuff!
- Yes!
- But sunrise is clearly different!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
The meaning of a word only
Hiroshima knows [Sunrise]?
- Not really.
- Is this in your local dialect?
- Other places have a same name for that thing,
but it's called this in Hiroshima.  - Sunrise?  - Yeah.
- What is this sunrise?
- It's a thing.
A thing?
- So no other place uses this name but Hiroshima?
- Yes.
This is its specific name.
- Don't tell me it's sunglasses.
- No, not that.
Isn't it lame to call sunglasses sunrise?
Common mistake.
Hiroshima doesn't call sunglasses sunrise.
Interior! Interior of a house!
- This is a food.
- A nice interior!
- Eh! It's a food?
- Food, huh?
Vinegar! Vinegar!
- Minami loves it!
- Bread! Bread!
What bread? What bread?
- Melon bread?
- Correct!
Eehh!? So it's melon bread.
- Melon bread's nickname?
- Yes, it's sunrise.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Melon bread = Sunrise
In Hiroshima
- You've gotta be kidding me!
- It's real.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Hiroshima's distinct word
[Melon Bread] = [Sunrise]
Why?
- Wait a second! Hashimoto just said "lame" just now!
- Why?!
Spontaneously
from the bottom of the heart.
Why?!
You should not have say that!
- I'm going to claw you!
- I'll claw you!
Quarrel arises!
I'm getting the JonJon!
Nothing to do with sandals.
Those are sandals!
You can't claw with sandals!
- This is JonJon!
- JonJon is sandals.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Bakery in Hiroshima was inspired by the image of a sunrise
and use [Sunrise]  as their brand
This is the product, where the bakery got inspired
by the image of a sunrise for the brand...
... and it has become a common name for them.
This is our next topic.
Does it only exist in my hometown? [Peculiar Word Category]
Kurottsu~
- Kurottsu~
- Kurottsu?
- Who?
- Me.
- Where?  - Nagasaki again.
- Nagasaki?  - Yes.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Kawago Hina
from Nagasaki
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
The meaning of a word only
Nagasaki knows [Kurottsu] ?
- Kurottsu~?
- Kurottsu.
What is this?
Does this exist only in your hometown?
- This is a living thing.
- A living thing?   - Yes.
Living thing?
- Do we know this thing?
- Certainly! Everyone knows this!
Cockroach! Cockroach!
- Cat! Cat!
No! It's cockroach.
- That's correct?!
- Yes.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Cockroach = Kurottsu
In Nagasaki
It's called Kurottsu?
Ah, because it's kuro (black)?
Because it's kuro (black) and it's ttsu (crawling)?
That quite makes sense.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Nagasaki's distinct word
[Cockroach] = [Kurottsu~]
Goki means bowl for us.
- Eh?!
- Goki?
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Cockroach = Kurottsu
Bowl = Goki (of Gokiburi/Cockroach)
In Nagasaki
Goki means bowl?
So gokiburi (cockroach) means bowl...
The meaning becomes bowl.
Kurottsu means cockroach,
while goki means bowl.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Nagasaki's distinct word
[Cockroach] = [Kurottsu~]
- So you can say this, "There's a kurottsu
next to the goki!" ?  - Yes.
- "Orubai!" (there is!)
- Orubai!!!
[ Orubai from Iru/exist (for living things) ]
- Quick, get the JonJon!
- What are you talking about!
Kurottsu~ vs JonJon.
Why did it go there?
Was the usage correct?
Why? That was correct!
What's with you and JonJon?
- All these distinct words are interesting.
- They are something new.
Let's get to the last theme, here it is!
Talk about love in your dialect!
Love Confession in Local Dialect
Love confessions in local dialects!
Finally, they will act where they confess their love
in their own local dialects.
Himura here will be the guy whom members will confess to,
in their local dialects.
The theme is "After School".
The stories and the scripts are decided by members themselves.
First challenger, Etou of Oita.
The plot here is being together with a classmate
when it's raining after school.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Oita dialect
Etou Misa
Let's get prepared!
Ready, start!
What a heavy rain.
Himura-kun didn't bring an umbrella, did you?
What if we use this together?
- Let's head home together.
- Sorry for the trouble.
Alright, I'm in.
Hei...
There's something I've always been dying to say to you.
What?
Truthfully I...
... have been loving Himura-kun ever since.
Huh?!
I can't hear you because of the rain!
I really love you!
I'll be waiting for your answer.
Here!
- Bye bye!
- You...
... are getting soaked!
Alright, CUT!
Hey, you're getting soaked!
Oita dialect is so cute.
You said "Suki yatta ni."
"Suki yatta ni", also "Suki ya ni"
(been loving you ever since)
Oita dialect is so cute.
But does Hatanaka's hometown have a really similar dialect?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Hatanaka Seira
from Oita prefecture
- It's totally different.
- What do you use as determiners besides "cha"?
Like "Souccha".
(that)
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Oita dialect
Etou Misa
For example, this is "Uuron Cha" (Oolong tea),
how do you say that?
- This is "Uuron Chaccha" (Oolong tea).
- I see.
Too many "Cha".
The result is so funny.
Himura-san, what do you think about Oita dialect?
One can say this Oita dialect sounds cute, but...
... even though this was just a drama,
I actually am happy but also embarassed!
Because he's a suddenly popular guy.
Embarassed because there are two people involved.
Since you'll be the guy until the end of the segment...
- ... Himura-san, please lose such feelings!
- Sorry, I'll hold it in.
Position yourself as a support cast.
Next, Hashimoto of Hokkaido.
Love confession while walking home
from school to the station.
Ready, start!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Hokkaido dialect
Hashimoto Nanami
Sorry I'm late.
The reason is...
- ... I was shining my shoes...
- I understand.
Nothing to be worried of.
Let's go!
The train has left.
Kisha (train)? Oh yeah.
It means we're going through more distance
until the station.
But also...
... we can be together for longer.
Why did you say that so suddenly?
You're being very weird today.
You know...
... at this moment,
I want you to know one thing...
... but please don't have any Hankakusai thoughts!
I...
Actually I...
... love Himura-kun veeeery much!
Hankakusai!
His answer is [Hankakusai].
Okay, CUT!!!
CUT!
He said it!
- Himura-san's words were cruel!
- Exactly!
- What is "Hankakusai"?
- "Don't have any Hankakusai thoughts", what is this Hankakusai?
It can mean absurd.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Hankakusai = Absurd
In Hokkaido
So it means absurd!
- Is that so?
- Poor girl!
No, no, that wasn't the case.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Hokkaido dialect
Hashimoto Nanami
What did you mean by "Na~nmara"?
"Nanmara" means very, like...
- ..."Na~nmara" with such intonation, it means "veeeery"  - So the voice is lower.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Hokkaido dialect
Hashimoto Nanami
Even though she "loves him veeeery much"
but the answer was "That's absurd!"
Man of no feelings.
I didn't know that!
- I do know.
- This is good.
Although it was in local dialect,
the situation was very good.
- The acting skill of a prime time actress is clearly different!
- As clear as day.
She moved like this, then she spun like this.
The result was "Wow!!"
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Hokkaido dialect
Hashimoto Nanami
Experienced as a prime time actress.
- It was different when she was doing it.
- You're good, Hashimoto-san!
Next, Ikoma of Akita, but...
- This will be my first confession.
- There it is!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Akita dialect
Ikoma Rina
Himura-san is your first everything.
Fated.
- Started from Valentine's Day, confession...
- Valentine's Day, confession, all of them were Himura-san.
Viewers, I apologize.
I'm sorry.
Ikoma chose a love confession story in Akita dialect,
titled "A Promise to Meet A Classmate!"
Ready, start!!!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Akita dialect
Ikoma Rina
Sorry!
- You waited?
- You're so slow!
- It took long, didn't it?
- Oh you, how long should I wait you for?
I better go home by myself.
- You...
- Why? You're angry? I'm sorry.
Nah, I was lying!
Come on!
So cute.
Hey...
- ... can I tell you something
that has been bugging my mind since forever?   - What?
- What is it?
- You know...
... actually I always liked you!
Please be my boyfriend!
But...
I guess you can't go out with me, can you?
okay, CUT!!!
So sweet!!!
- She was embarassed when she was acting.
- Because...
- Because you never said that?
- Never!
I never said that!
- I will accept it!
- You can't!
First confession ACCEPTED.
You said many things, huh?
That "Soretomo watashi ja dame desuka?"
"Ndadomo...oredaba damedabeka...?"
She's so cute when she said "Damedabeka..."
You're good, that was cute!
Next, Nishino of Osaka.
Love confession in local dialect
to a childhood friend!
Alright, start!!!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Osaka dialect
Nishino Nanase
Aaahh~
I'm seriously hungry!
Where should we go?
- The Kushikatsu is delicious at Tsutenkaku!
- Kushikatsu, sounds good! That's delicious!
[ Tsutenkaku = Landmark tower of Osaka ]
[ Kushikatsu = some kind of skewered pork with leek ]
But here's the catch! In Osaka's Kushikatsu,
we're not allowed to get the pickles twice!
What are you talking about?
Hey...
... what does Yuuki think about me?
Well...
... I see Nanase as...
... just as my close childhood friend, perhaps?
That's Yuuki's stupidity!
Is that how you see my feelings as?
What do you mean "feelings"?
Seriously, Yuuki is insensitive!
It's helpless!
Honestly I love Yuuki since forever!
- Huh?
- Really really love you!
What?
Huh?
You...
... you're not allowed
to hear my love confession twice!
ALRIGHT CUT!!!
- WHOAH WAIT WHAT?!!
- AWESOME!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Osaka dialect
Nishino Nanase
It felt like watching a work of director Izutsu.
[ Izutsu Kazuyuki = a famous Japanese director ]
Nice performance.
Nishino, you really pulled that off amazingly!
A nice usage of "twice!"
She started it casually,
then she ended it brilliantly. Amazing!
I was confused when she said "twice" in the beginning,
but it turned out to be very wonderful in the end!
"You're not allowed
to hear my love confession twice!!"
Himura-san gets influenced because of
an amazing love confession in local dialect!?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confessions
in local dialects
We've seen some now, and...
... as expected, I think Himura-san is very annoying!
What did you say?
Himura's dialect.
- What did you say?
- Since Himura-san is very annoying...
... some members will give it a go after this...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession
in local dialect
... while facing the camera,
so the viewers will feel like they're the boyfriend.
Ah, got it.
This certainly makes the viewers ecstatic.
First, Fukagawa of Shizuoka...
... will confess on the way home,
in the cold of winter.
Ready, start!!!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Shizuoka dialect
Fukagawa Mai
Hey, Himura-kun...
... since it's cold,
can I hold your hand now?
Thank you!
Himura-kun's hand is warm!
You know...
... I...
... actually...
... am deep in love with Himura-kun!
Okay, it's over!
That's so sweet!
Whenever a girl confesses her love...
- ... it turns out to be sweet, huh?
- Very!
With local dialect added,
the atmosphere is even more solid.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Shizuoka dialect
Fukagawa Mai
When everyone was saying sweet,
Kawago was having a reaction more than the others!
Kawago = Fukagawa's fan
- You like Fukagawa so much, don't you?
- Yes!  - Which part was the good one?
When she was holding hand...
- ... I want to hold hers!
- You want to hold?!
Instantly fell in love.
After this, a confession in Wada Maaya's local dialect,
a 15 year old girl from Hiroshima.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Hiroshima dialect
Wada Maaya
Start!!!
Hey, hey...
Can I say something special?
I, honestly...
... like Himura-kun so much!
I like you before I knew it...
If Himura-kun also feels the same way...
... I'd certainly be happy...
- Okay cut!
- SO CUTE!
That was pretty great!
Very nice!
- That was seriously cute!
- Indeed!
Hiroshima dialect is dangerous!
- That was great!
- Cute!
The lines were good too.
"If Himura-kun also feels the same way,
I'd certainly be happy." How did you say it?
"Himura-kun mo isshon koto
kangaettotara ureshiin jakedo..."
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Hiroshima dialect
Wada Maaya
Very cute!
BUCHI SUKI JAKE~!
(I LOVE YOU SO MUCH~!)!
Imagination runs wild.
NOPE!!!
Next, the excited Kawago...
... will confess in Nagasaki dialect!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Love confession in Nagasaki dialect
Kawago Hina
Start!!!
Hey, Himura-kun,
what do you think about me?
Well I always feel I...
... love Himura-kun so much!
That's why, perhaps it'd be better for us if we're dating, yeah?
Okay, CUT!!!
Very good!!
"Yoka" very nice!
"I always feel I love Himura-kun so much",
then...
"Gougi suito~to sa"
- "Gougi suito~to sa"?
Then "Tsukiatte hoshikacchakedo..."
(I want to date)
"...perhaps it'd be better for us." So...
"Yoka?"
So "Yoka" in the end?
After this,
a ridiculous Seitansai full of mistakes!
This week's episode is not over yet!
- Himura-san, what are we going to do?
Please announce it.   - Okay!
Not Everyone Is Done Yet!
Nogizaka Seitansai!
Okay, we had commemorated everyone's birthdays here,
however...
The last one was Nagashima, wasn't it?
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
After the forgotton to be broadcasted of Nagashima's birthday,
every member's birthday is done!
Actually she said, "My birthday hasn't been commemorated yet",
then we did it.
And after Nagashima's birthday,
it's all done, right?
- That's what we thought.
- Because a week had passed.
But then, suddenly, someone cried...
A complaint by tears.
When she was asked,
"What's wrong? What's wrong?"...
Turned out, we haven't commemorate
one member's birthday.
And she's that member.
- Please raise your hand!
- Me!
There she is, Manatsu-san!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Born on August 20th
Akimoto Manatsu (20 years old)
I'm sorry!
No need to. Since Akimoto joined us late...
- The commemorate had been started  that time, so it's
quite messy to organize it.  - Because of her sudden joining.
So...
... let's see, Akimoto's VTR.
Here it is!
Ah, how cute.
Akimoto Manatsu.
Agustus 20th, 1993.
She was born in Akimoto family.
When she was a baby up until she was a kid,
she cried a lot because of her gentle character.
Cute.
Just like her name...
Since she went to kindergarten,
she joined a cheer team.
When she was in elementary schoo,
she started to be able to fix the button of her father's pants.
Although she was still 7 years old,
she could make a perfect sewing.
Ah, this is awesome!
Aside from that, she started to have an interest
in making cakes.
She also started to cook in her house.
Your face hasn't changed.
Your little brother?
You finished it.
Her cuteness is same!
Identical!
Without realizing it, this has become her hobby
and a way to relieve her stress.
Impressive!
She could make that,
amazing!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
In the middle school, she joined a cooking club
and passed a Nation-wide cooking test
Akimoto Manatsu
Nogizaka46 Kenkyuusei
Nishikawa Nanami
When she's in middle school,
she joined a cooking club.
She was able to pass a nation-wide test
for homemade cooking when she was 14 years old.
So young.
Even though it's just a hobby, her cookie-making skill
will surprise even the professionals.
You made this?
You're amazing!
Moreover, the collection of dishes
she's able to make is countless.
She even replaced her mother's job
when she was busy.
And then, she also had this kind of skill,
that many people don't aware.
What?
Violin?
Don't say that
The princess!
Clearly the princess!
You're good at it.
Because of her tiny body,
when there's a school festival...
... Akimoto always got a task
to climb her friends' bodies.
Akimoto's on top?!
Because you were small?
Yes, I was so small.
That time, huh...
You did this?
That's terrifying!
No one helped you?
You were always on top!
Why didn't you try
to be a bottom?
Wonderful!
Interesting,
she kept being on top.
She's not good at all in sport.
When she was in a sport team,
she always dragged her friends down.
Even today, this no-good-at-sport
still can't ride a bike.
What is this?!
Sport match.
Now she's fully back as a member.
And to handle her special position,
she's determined to be an idol with a super reaction!
To be an idol with a super reaction!
Thank you very much.
I see.
That's a rarely known moment, huh?
Let's say nothing has changed since the elementary days.
- That's right!
- She has many interesting things.
Totally not a reaction she was expecting.
- But everyone was laughing at me.
- Interesting indeed.
That was good. This is the birthday commemoration
you asked to the point you were crying.
- But that was funny.
- Not as I thought...
Not as I thought...
Did you think this would be cuter than that?
- I thought it would be a melancholy video.
- That's what we wanted at first, but...
There's one where you molded some batter...
... how old were you?
Maybe I was around 7.
- About first or second grader?
- Yes.
- Your face hasn't changed, huh?
- From the video, yeah.
She could cook at 7...
- ... she's also good at making cakes.
- She's  good too, here's her work...
You have it?!
- Here!
- Wow, amazing!
Her handicraft when she's 7
She made this when she was 7, that was impressive.
- You made this when you were 7?
- Yes.
- And then... was your body that light?
- It was quite light...
- I was the skinniest back then.
- So you're on top.
She's always on the top when they're doing a pyramid formation.
Others might think "Why always her?"
- It wasn't me all the time...
- In her whole life, was she always there in a pyramid formation?
Then at the same sport event,
on the pyramid formation category...
... I became a substitute of one kid
who was having bone fractures.
So after I climbed one pyramid, I went down
and I headed to another one.
Double roles.
That is a fact!
- So you climbed another pyramid?
- Hence why I could be seen a lot in the VTR.
- Maybe since no one else could do it.
- Really?
- Two jobs? You were awesome!
- I climbed again...   - Was that even a thing?
I see now.
- That's her job, she provided a pyramid formation service.
- She was contracted for that...
Her service was selling like hotcakes!When her shift ended,
she went right away to another one.
Pyramid worker.
- So funny.
- "Ah, I've been booked to make another pyramid..."
That's amazing.
Maybe it'd leave a deep wound if she said no.
- So your birthday is on Agustus 20th?
- Yes.
Actually we were gonna broadcast this
for August's birthday commemoration, but...
... we apologize, since it was all over the place,
it gets broadcasted for an early September episode.
Unfitting time.
Why?
Because there's a lot of things going on...
... so it kinda deviated from the schedule.
It's because we need to arrange this and that...
... and when we were about to put Manatsu-san's segment,
the schedule deviated...
I want them to work harder for that!
One-on-one battles of Nogizaka46!
Nogizaka46 Zenkoku Tour FINAL!
The show in Yoyogi National Gymnasium is going to be held!
Ticket reservation for mobile members
has been opened!
More information on the official website.
Next week, Waruzaka46 arrives!
Members are divided between Team Kanto and Team Countryside
and they are going to have a battle!
An accident happened in a heavy clash using their bodies?!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
The fighting spirit and guts of Nogizaka46 are off the roof!
... that's what they say, but cries explode in a close match
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
Don't you dare looking down
on the countryside fellas!
Hey you! Don't underestimate Tokyo!
Stick your hands out!
You can do this!
Non-stop fighting spirit, Yoroshiku!