GG
VOZ48
Your names! Even though you’re doing this for 2 years,
I don’t even remember a single one!
Tonight on Nogizakatte Doko,
The members will try to leave an impression
on our guest in this Pressure Self Introduction.
Heading to the special guest’s green room,
the members desperately promote themselves.
Will our special guest be able to remember all of the members’ names?
Who is this special guest?
Credits to guringurin for the original Indo-sub and timesetting
DON!
Nogizakatte Doko has started, we’re your hosts, Bananaman.
-Yoroshiku Onegeshimasu
and they are...
Nogizaka-chan~
Saito Yuuri, what’s wrong? It looks cool.
Injured.
Because it is fashionable.
Released on the 3rd of July, the 6th single, “Girls’ Rule”
set the record as the group’s highest-selling single.
Taking on the ride this summer are Nogizaka’s members.
You guys are doing well.
Eeeeee no no no...
I saw Hashimoto on a TV drama.
Monday Primetime Actress
Thank you very much.
Your character is a bit of a mysterious girl, right?
I also saw someone like Shiraishi, for example.
Thank you ve-
Shut your trap! All of you!
Great Fury!!
This is so sudden, why…
-Shut up!!!
-Why is that?
Recently, you are all suddenly in the rise!
That kind of occasion is okay.
I really want you to sell, but…
Your names! Even though you’re doing this for 2 years,
I don’t even remember a single one!
Shocking truth?!
Too rude!
That’s a bit of a problem for Himura-san too.
That’s right.
For those in a large idol group,
The amount of people who will remember your name
after one self-introduction is important.
This time, with a special guest offered with Nogidoko’s fake project,
the members are headed to the special guest’s green room for greetings
There, they’ll introduce themselves one by one.
Afterwards, the plan is revealed to the special guest.
GG
Who among the members will leave an impression?
It will be checked through a verification segment.
Finally, the special guest offered with the fake project is…
Our special guest… is this person.
Who is that?
-I don’t know.
What is he doing?
Ah, reading the newspaper?
Even with all these different camera angles, we still don’t know who it is.
-Amazing
-Amazing.
Perfectly unknown, huh?
Ah! senpai, senpai
It’s our acquaintance, Degawa-san.
With 28 years in the industry, one of the biggest names, Degawa Tetsuro.
The person himself thinks that he’ll be teaching reaction skills to the members.
By the way, who here have worked with Degawa-san in the past?
Ah, Ikoma and Shiraishi.
We talked quite a lot.
-Have you?
He’s sitting beside me and talked a lot.
Ah, he might still remember you. It may be an advantage.
That’s an advantage.
Even for Shiraishi, right?
Can they leave an impression on Degawa Tetsuro?
Finally, here’s the green room greetings.
The preparations are done, let’s start the green room greetings!
Excuse me.
Yes?
Sorry for bothering you. Nogizaka46 is grateful to have you today,
Can they have the privilege of greeting you?
Sorry about that.
That’s how Degawa-san is in the green room.
sumimasen, onegaishimasu~
Will he be able to remember them?
Good morning. I’m the captain, Sakurai Reika.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
Born and raised in Akita, I’m Ikoma Rina, yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
Actually, I’ve been on a show with you in the past, called “TORE!”
Yes, I remember.
Really? Thank you very much, yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
That is a tough one!
It is not easy to remember all of them!
Good morning, I’m Shiraishi Mai, yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
He thinks that it’s already over with just two people.
I’ve also been in a show with Degawa-san
-Ah, yes.
Thank you very much.
White skin corresponds to refuban Shiraishi, please keep that into mind.
Refuban – reflector board used in photography.
Eh? Shiraishi is?
I am often called as reflector board…
-Ah, reflector board.
Reflector board corresponds to Shiraishi. I’d be glad if you remembered it.
-Ah, Reflector board Shiraishi-san? Okay.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu~ I’ll excuse myself.
Thank you very much.
He thinks that it is over already.
Pardon for the intrusion, good morning.
May I introduce myself?
-Okay
Here goes Sayurin~
Sayurin, Sayurin, Sayurin Rin
Sayurin, Sayurin, Sayuringo~
That’s troublesome!
full of sweet honey, Sayuringo.
Degawa-san, would you like to taste it?
-Well…
-Thank you very much.
Good morning~
We’re still at the 5th person.
I wonder if everyone will come one by one.
Born in Hokkaido, 20 years old, Hashimoto Nanami
I’m thinking of doing a response with you.
It will go like “Born in Hokkaido”
”20 years old”
”Hashimoto”
”Nanami”
What is she doing?
What is she suddenly saying?
That’s not a greeting!
Born in Hokkaido
20 years old
Hashimoto
Nanami
Okay, thank you very much.
It is rude of her!
This is being rude to her senpai!
Good morning.
What is she saying?!
Currently in 2nd year of high school, I’m Ikuta Erika.
My nickname is Erika-sama
Erika-sama
I am Nogizaka’s Don.
What kind of Sawajiri-san is she trying to portray?
Yes, I’m a Don.
it’s not Ikuta but,
She is doing Sawajiri-san, right?
Please remember me as Ikuta Don.
The 7th person is Nishino. During the 8th person, Takayama’s appearance..
the special guest felt something unusual about this.
I’m Takayama Kazumi.
-Ahhhhhhhh~
Do you think he somehow figured it out?
Degawa-san is suspicious about this.
I don’t understand what the purpose of this plan is.
He thinks that something’s up.
Excuse me, Good morning.
I am Nogizaka46’s Wakatsuki Yumi.
It’s the same as Wakatsuki Chinatsu-san but…
Little by little, I saw this coming!
I can’t do this! I can’t! This is impossible!
Up until now, I don’t even remember a single person!
Ah, he gave up!
I understand it now, this is hopeless.
Degawa Tetsuro-san completely noticed the purpose of this plan.
From this point on, Degawa-san is in
a challenge of flipping his “memorizing mode” on.
”Ido NO UE no SAYURI” Please remember that.
-Then, Degawa, Fukagawa, I’ll remember that.
-Ah, Thank you very much.
Da-Saito Yuuri, please remember it.
Ahhhh.
Dasai – uncool
MarikaMarikaMarikaMarikaMarika marika rika rika......
Read from top to bottom or bottom to top, Nakada Kana.
Read it sideways, DA!
This is her usual self-introduction right?
My nickname is Kanarin, I’m Nakada Kana.
Read from top to bottom or bottom to top is Nakada Dakana,
there’s nothing when read sideways.
Read from top to bottom or bottom to top is Nakada Kana.
Ah, that’s what you meant. Na-ka-da-Ka-na-chan.
That’s right!
Ah, I’m sorry, I’m sorry.
Thank you very much
Nakada Kana, Nakada Kana
What number are we in now?
Excuse me~~~
Too fast!!
15 years old, Hoshino Minami, Yoroshiku Onegashimasu
Please remember Minami.
Minami, Minami chan, Minami chan, Minami is easy to remember.
Do you remember my name?
If you would do something Minami chan-like..
Eh? What for?
So that I can remember your name.
Something Minami chan-like.
I don’t know.
Eh? You don’t know?
Then I’ll remember Minami-chan with that “I don’t know”
What exactly is Minami chan-like?
I’ll excuse myself, thank you very much.
Is it over already?
Thank you very much. If you would excuse me.
Everyone’s finished.
I have to do this right away!
How many of the members’ names are remembered?
Degawa-san is called to the studio to finally start the verification.
He’s probably aware of what’s going on.
Ah, doumo~ Sorry to have kept you waiting.
For starters, I’d like to say this is impossible.
I’d like to say this from the start..
douzo~
This is impossible.
Today, we have Degawa-san to teach you all about reaction skills.
No, no, no.
That’s not right!
That’s not right, right?
Okay, Nakada Kana-chan!
Wait a minute.
What are you looking for?
Finally, the verification started.
Choose the number of the member in mind,
and announce the name of that member.
Who is able to do this with me but bothered by it?
-Hai, hai, hai.
Nakada Kana-chan!
That’s no good.
Please choose a number
They won’t say anything.
Eh, wait a minute, Nakada Kana-chan....
Nakada Kana-chan, right?
Who here is Nakada Kana-chan?
You had just met her earlier..
You’re kidding, right, Degawa-san?
No, no, you’re wrong.
I really don’t want to do this, I don’t know anyone.
There’s really something strange with my brain.
This is really…
-That’s not true!
That’s not true, Degawa-san
Should I give you a hint, then?
Degawa-san
Degawa-san found something!
Lock-on!
Degawa-san have decided already,
That’s not Nakada Kana-chan.
Wait a minute, what’s with that?
Number 13?!
Nakada Kana chan..
Okay!
But which number will stand up?
Number 13, please stand up.
Okay, number 13.
Minami-chan!
Wait a minute.
Suddenly… Wait a minute.
Degawa san....
Why, all of the sudden… Hoshino..
All this time, you were looking for Nakada Kana
I’m sorry, but when I saw her face,
she is Minami-chan, I remembered.
However, when I asked her to do something
she’s like “What’s Minami-chan-like?!”
What she did remind me of her.
-It suddenly came to you, huh?
-That’s amazing.
You did it.
Yay! Thank you very much.
Anyone you remember with confidence?
Don’t you know anyone in the first row?
Because she co-starred with me…
That’s great! Then, say it quickly.
Co-stars at a different TV station.
Number 3, please stand up.
No, it’s wrong, wrong, wrong.
Cowardly
it’s not that.
Wait a minute, we were talking quite a lot,
you were sitting beside me, I remember about it.
Ah! There it is!
-I might be wrong…
Yukino-chan?
That’s not it, it’s wrong!
I’m sorry!
Back then there’s this Yuki Yuki.
Verification results
Names that are remembered  from the self-introduction:
1 out of 16 members.
At this rate, this will never end, right?
Let’s start over again!
Revenge!
Thank goodness.
This time, you can memorize from the start.
Thank goodnesss.
everyone as well.
More self-introduction revenge after this!
Pressure Self-Introduction Challenge.
For Degawa-san who is motivated from the beginning,
Will he be able to remember the members this time?
Now, let’s take a look at the situation in the green room.
He’s already memorizing.
Super serious
He’s preparing for this match, right?
Degawa-san?
Yes?
For the second time, please remember them all, okay?
Please do it slowly.
-Here we go.
-Yes.
Onegaishimasu!
This is the second time,
will he finally be able to remember them?
Douzo.
Nogizaka46 is grateful to have you today…
Enough of this!
Yes, yes, please go ahead.
Good morning~
I’m Nogizaka46’s captain, Sakurai Reika.
Mr. Children – Japanese band
The vocalist of Mr. Children is?
Sakurai-san
My name is Sakurai
Leader, Sakurai.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
onegaishimasu~
Did you get that, Degawa-san?
It’s all good.
I’m Ikoma Rina.
Ah, it’s Ikoma-chan.
Ikoma-chan. Because a lot of people are calling me that,
just Ikoma-chan, please remember that.
Ikoma-chan, just Koma-chan would be..
Ikoma-chan
seems Koma-chan, I think?
Because you’re small and cute, Koma-chan.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
Ikoma-chan, Sakurai-san...
Ikoma-chan, koma-chan, koma-chan
Sakurai-san, Ikoma-chan
Kobo-chan, Kobo-chan, Kobo-chan
Stop that!!!
Sakurai-san, Ikoma-chan, Sakurai-san, Ikoma-chan
Pardon for the intrusion, good morning~
- I’m serving as Nogizaka46’s center, I’m Shiraishi Mai.
- Ah, as expected from the center,
as expected, you are cute.
My white skin is my charm point
This time, I’m also wearing a white uniform.
And on my name Shiraishi, it has ‘shiro’ in it.
Reflector boards are also white.
There are silver-colored ones, right?
I wonder if reflector boards appear as white?
That’s right.
-Yup, closer to a silver-color.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu~ Thank you very much.
-Sakurai-san, Sakurai-san, Ikoma-chan, Shiraishi-san
-There are silver colored reflector boards too, right?
There are silver colored reflector boards too, right?
That’s right.
Rather than white, it seems to appear as silver-colored, right?
That’s right!
Reflector board and then white skin,
Forget about the reflector board.
White skin.
Reflector board is ditched
But they all have white skin, it’s what they have in common.
But hers is really amazing.
Shiraishi-san
Do you remember Kobo-chan?
Ah, Kobo-chan.
There’s no one named Kobo-chan!
Koma-chan, Koma-chan, Sakurai-san, Shiraishi-san
Koma-chan, Sakurai-san, Koma-chan, Shiraishi-san
- Next person please~
Good morning.
Ah, you’re cute.
Matsumura-san, I’ll remember you as Ma-chan.
Seriously?
For some reasons, this cute girl is Ma-chan.
I have a close friend, Matsumura Kinihiro,
because you share the same surname…
I have a catchphrase but, is it okay without doing it?
Please do it, I might remember you because of it.
Okay, here goes Sayurin.
Sayurin, Sayurin, Sayurin rin
Sayurin, Sayurin, Sayuringo
full of sweet honey, Sayuringo.
Degawa san, once again, would you like to taste it?
Wow, you are like a talking doll.
Thank you very much.
I don’t remember what you did just now.
Was not particularly…
I’ll remind of you as “Ma-chan despite of being cute.”
Next, the way of remembering Hashimoto Nanami…
Hashimoto, the professional wrestler, Hashimoto.
Hashimoto Shinya-san?
It’s okay if you remember me as Hashimoto Shinya’s daughter.
Hashimoto Shinya’s daughter
This had gone weird.
You’re next to “Ma-chan despite of being cute,” right?
That’s right.
Next to cute Ma-chan is,
Hashimoto Shinya’s daughter.
That’s right.
Doumo~
Ah, after Hashimoto Shinya’s daughter is..
I’m Erika-sama
Ahh, Erika-sama
This girl’s folding up her arms again
My hair is black, right?
Ah! That’s right.
Please remember “Black Erika-sama”
Okay, okay, I’ll remember that.
What number is Black Erika-sama assigned to?
Front row? Back row?
Front row?
But the seating arrangement have nothing to do with the sequence of self-introduction.
That’s no good Degawa-san!
Ehhhhhhh this is impossible
Big Miscalculation
Doing that is useless!
My hair color is black.
- Degawa-san?
– Eh?
-Who said that the seating arrangement and the sequence of appearance is the same?
- Ehhhhhhh
Please remember their faces and names properly.
Next up, number 6 is Nishino.
what kind of impression will she make?
My nickname is Nanasemaru, but..
if we could do a catchphrase of it together…
Okay, let’s do it.
When I do this..
you’ll say Nanasemaru.
Okay.
Born in Osaka
Nanasemaru!
Let’s do it one more time.
Born in Osaka
Nanasemaru!
- Thank you very much. Is it okay?
-Onegaishimasu~  I’m Takayama Kazumi.
- Takayama Kazumi-chan, Kazumi-chan
- Yes
Philtrum – midline groove in the upper lip
that runs from the top of the lip to the nose
Among the members, I have the most prominent philtrum.
Please look at this line and this character on my name..
Okay!
This is what I’m most thankful for!
Kazumi-chan, Kazumi-chan
In reference to Kato Cha
- Kato-chan Pe
- Kazumi-chan
Kazu-chan Pe
-It’s going well, huh?
-It’s all good.
Because that was Kato-san, huh? Just now.
The 9th member, Inoue Sayuri
Sayuri-chan, how can I remember you?
With my bangs
What’s up with your bangs?
Please remember my precisely done bangs.
Precisely done?
Why is that? Sayuri..
It’s true, this part here…
Sayuri-chan who really likes nori.
Likes nori?
After that,
Wakatsuki Yumi
Akimoto Manatsu
Fukagawa Mai
Saito Yuuri
Ito Marika
14 members are done,
Last one is Nakada Kana
Read from top to bottom or bottom to top…
Uwaaaa, Nakada Kana
Our eyes should’ve met more!
Well, about my appearance...
Because of my hair, please remember "Black Kanarin"
Black II
It already appeared earlier,
Black Erika-sama
My white skin is my charm point.
White skin also appeared earlier!
Bye bye.
-We’re finished!
Degawa san, please proceed to the studio.
Finally, how many members were able to make an impression?
Verification Take 2!
What number?
Number 1
Sakurai-san
Please take it off.
Okay, amazing.
Number 3
Ikoma-chan
Center, I know this one, Number 5
Because of her white skin, Shiroi-san... Shiraishi-san...
Yatta! Yes! Yes! Yes!
It is always Degawa-san’s turn.
What number?
Number 4
Despite of being cute… Matsumura-san
Woohoo, so amazing.
This is pretty amazing...
Ah, yes.
Let’s go.
Short hair and yet…
Ah, wrong.
Hashimoto-san despite being a short hair.
What’s that?
Pro-wrestler Hashimoto-san’s daughter.
You remembered quite a lot, Degawa-san.
Uhhmm, the girl who did this.
What was that again?
yabai, yabai, yabai.
Number 7, please stand up.
Do that one again.
Ahhh! I got it!
Please do it again!
Nanase!
Ah! This one!
Nori, nori nori.
Number 10, please stand up.
What was that? She really likes nori…
No, no, no.
You really like nori, right?
Eh? Wait a minute.
She really likes nori… Matsuzaka-san..
She really likes nori, who was that? I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
Read it from top to bottom or bottom to top, Nakada Kana-chan.
From this point on, Degawa-san displayed his forte.
- Yumi-chan
- Yes
Manatsu-chan
Dasai is Saiito-san!
- Saito-san!
-Okay.
Thank you very much.
Marika-chan?
Mai Degawa, Mai-chan
Yatta!
With that, there are three members left.
Ikuta, Takayama and Inoue
Just three people remaining!
Degawa-san, there’s not much time remaining.
Ah, wait, wait.
Which one is Black Erika-chan?!
Black Erika-chan!
Searching for Black Erika-chan.
I figured out who Black Erika-chan is.
Number 2 is Erika-chan!
I’m begging you, I’m begging you.
Two remaining.
After this, a miraculous perfect achievement?!
Ah! You’re not doing this! Because you’re not doing this!
Number 8
with the most prominent philtrum, Kazumi-chan!
Ahh, amazing!
It’s amazing!
Last one.
I’m begging you.
Will the last one be safe?
It’s not “Matsuzaka-san who really likes nori” after all?
Who is that?!
Matsuzaka-kun?
She really likes nori.
She really likes nori, who was that again?
You had a lot of doubts after all, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Time’s up!
I’m sorry!
Sorry!
Sorry! I’m really sorry.
I’ll give you a last chance.
Last chance, get it right, then it’s safe
There’s only one shot however.
Her favorite is nori.
Eh, wait a minute.
There’s only one shot.
Her favorite is nori…
Akie-chan?
Who is that?
We’re finished!
Number 10, please show the answer.
Inoue Sayuri
Ah, it’s Sayuri-san, Sayuri-chan.
Ah, it’s Sayunyan, I’m really sorry.
Matsuzaka-san who really likes nori,
please think of a new self-introduction!
Terimakasih sudah memakai sub dari guringurin.com
Maaf banyak kesalahan dan Typo dalam mengartikan