Nogizaka46 Staff's Ranking!!!
Tonight, will we see some of Nogizaka46's "behind the scene" face?
Nogizaka46 Staff's Ranking
Member who has lame fashion style is?
We conduct an research with behind the scene's staff.
A lot of members who feel down? What is the real voices of their staff?
There are some staff who don't like your "AMAZING"
[Nogizaka tte Doko?]
[Translator: Rustyhand
Timer: Jejee46
Disclaimer:
SUB-SHIRO (@subshiro46)
If you want to share or re-translate this fan sub to another language, please contact us.
Visit www.nogizakanouta.blogspot.com for more !!
DANG! Your MC Bananaman! Lets begin the show tonight!
And Nogizaka-chan
Ok, lets start this. Himura announce the program for tonight! Do it like a backstage staff.
Oookkaaayyy lets start! What is backstage staff's thought about them. Nogizaka46 Staff's Ranking!
As an idol, you have to be loved not only by your fans, but also by your backstage staff.
And we conduct a research about backstage staff's thought
regarding nogizaka46 and announce it with rank style.
Hope that they can accept this and make an improvement in the future.
The 1st topic is this!
Member who grow up the most is... This is a definite topic,
you people already doing this for more than 1 year.
And in this year, the one who make significant grow
and became closer to entertainment and cute, like that.
Firstly, no 3 is this person!
Nishino!
Ah Nishino...
Her style is obvious, her personality is also changed, she has grown.
I thought she is a delinquent when i saw her at audition,
there's answer like this and we have her photo at audition... THIS!
It's very different.
Her face still have a thorn.
Yes... This is 2 years ago right...
Yes, but it isn't that long ago, only for 2 years, her face is changed.
Yes, i agree with you. I think my personality that time is worse than now.
Oh yeah? How is nowadays?
Nowadays, my way of thinking is different.
Heee, so last time you just kick a wild cat if you found one right...
I didn't but...
- You didn't do it?
- She won't do it right.
Ok, member who grow up the most no 2 is...
Sakurai
Her lame style is disappear.
So until now, someone think your style is lame.
She became more like a girl.
I see.
There's opinion like that also and we have her photo. HERE!
- Wow, she's completely different!
- She's very young.
Only in 1-2 years you became a very different person, look at your face, so different!
Sakurai at that time, I can't imagine her to do bungee jump.
Even in my dream.
Yes, that girl is a definite change.
So do you feel any differences?
Yes, I try to be more girly.
I see.
Yes, you are innocent at that time, not even make-up.
I rarely did make-up that time.
Ok let's go to no 1.
No 1!
Member who grow up the most no 1 is this person!
I knew it!
Ikoma!
Ikoma is more shining now if you compare it with audition time.
I see.
She's maturing everyday. And her face is changed better.
Her hunchback is cured. And so on. Let us see her photo at that time.
She's cute but...
When i went to tokyo 1st time, i don't get the meaning of hunchback.
So you mean that you can't see the person who said that right?
No! I'm not that bad.
So you cured it by yourself?
Last time, i thought this pose is my natural pose, then...
Our staff said that is a hunchback, so i better fix it and they just pushed my back.
And you see yourself on TV or PV, so you became aware of it right?
Yes.
What do you think of Ikoma? Shiraishi. Do you think she changed a lot?
Yes, i do think she grow a lot in Nogizaka46.
I see, members also think that way too....
Her outer beauty is changed into better one.
I'm happy <3
I see.
- Can we go to the next one?
- Ok, lets go!
Next topic is this!
Member who has lame fashion style.
At handshake event, you all go by your own dress right?
Yes.
So, because it's an event, you might give some effort so that you wont be recognised as a lame one,
But for staffs who see you everyday, they just think "that person just so lame."
They won't say it in front of you right?
Yes!
It's a definite answer. No one said that in front of the person.
Maybe they just "KAWAII" but in fact "Wow... So lame..."
I agree.
So who is she?
Let's start with number 3, the one who has a lame fashion style is this person!
Ikuchan!
For real?
She's just a bit retro.
I think you wear a dress properly right? Whenever there's staff around.
Yes, I do wear dress properly.
I see.
But at 16, you should be buy a lot of fashion mags and read it shouldn't you?
I just dont get the point of that kind of interest.
So, even you are choosen here, you dont feel anything like a curiousity about it?
Yes ^^
I see...
But she will change!
- I agree.
- Maybe...
She's just 16.
Like wearing whole branded costume like prada!
That's possible!
Right now, Himura is wearing whole vuitton costume.
That day will appear.
I don't know what's wrong with him.
He just like a rich chinese.
Yes.
Next one... No 2 is this person.
Takayama?
You are called here, Takayama!
Im shocked...
I bet.
You are not considering yourself wear lame fashion right?
If you see per item, they are cute but she can't mix them.
And, you wear brown too much.
And, that rucksack is a no!
Firstly, my dream is became a stylish!
That's one of the reason and...
- So you are confident with your style.
- I see.
Yes I do.
I see, that's shocking right. Being told as lame.
And last time, after recording, when it's aired.
At private item corner.
The fact is, I got that from my mother.
And at mail, my mother just apologize for it.
That's too sad.
And she said, if you don't like it, don't wear it.
What's that? Too sad.
Then lets sent it back to your mother!
It's still alright that you wear brown a lot.
And someday you will be called mole.
But if they call you a mole, this is a sign that you are already being hated.
Next one... The one with lame style no 1 is this person.
All of you just agree with this right?
Sometime, she came wearing some sort of pajamas.
Almost all the time, she wear big dress...
Like one size bigger...
You wear it like someone from a village and wear worn-out shoes.
The truth, i just don't like to go out, so i rarely go shopping.
So i buy my dress once every 2 months.
But you still buying it.
So i wear the same dress over and over again, easy to wear.
You just overwear that one dress?
Yes. I wear same thing over and over.
That kind of person do exist.
Matsumura is only wearing pink.
Are you Hayashiya Ichimon?
Even Hayashiya have other colour.
And the reverse, the fashionable best 3 are...
Hashimoto, Nishino, Itou is the 1st!??
She is not catching the trend but make her own style.
Not the expensive one but the fittest one that she wear.
Thats good.
Do you have any photo of her dress? Lets see her fashion.
- This is blog?
- Yes, this is blog.
The middle is made by my mother.
Ah, your mother is someone in the apparel business?
My mother is an ex-fashion designer.
I design my dress and my mother make it for me.
What's that!
What a daughter-mother! So cool!
So your mother made those?
Then, you all just order from her mother.
Yes, especially the cute design.
Lets go to the next one. Next topic is this!
Member who love mirror.
This means that you are a narcist or love yourself.
No 3 is this person!
You, the one with lame fashion, what are you doing?
Everytime she just see a mirror and saying cute!
Is this true?
.... Yes it is.
You just see upper side from here right?
Aaa, like this line...
You have to see your lower parts.
Lets see no2. No 2 is this person!
She won't move from mirror.
That's true, because our job is being seen, if you dont always see mirror
and do checkup... I will get warnings...
Like, your nosehair is appearing?
Because my face is a bit hard, they always say, make a soft face or change your make-up or... And my Photos isn't that good, they said I should do more research. So i always see a mirror.
So you done it conciously.
But you don't do your own make up right?
Eh, there are members who did it by yourself?
So there are members who did and didn't?
The one who did it? Oh that's a lot. Why?
The one who can and can't!
Because there are lots of person, so the one who can do it, will do it by herself.
I see...
I can't do it!
So you are make up-ed by other?
Yes.
If you do it yourself, how is it look like? Is the lipstick will be like this?
It's not like that but...
And you make this pale blue and red lipstick.
We haven't announce no 1 yet, i never think she will be in. This person!
Hashimoto!
- Is it true Hashimoto?
- So different with what i imaged.
She check mirror every several minutes.
Glass, windows, she also see other reflecting things.
I, like Reika, are not good in the media.
What's that means?
Even from starting, my picture on photos and videos is not good.
And everytime i see myself, I just think it would be better to do this and that.
So, now before any recording or photoshoot, i will see myself first.
Do you decide your own make-up and hairstyle? Like this and that?
Yes.
Especially Takayama, you changed it alot.
Yes I do. Which one is better?
Are you going to do that conversation here?
Because it affecting your appearance....
Lets go to the next one, next topic is this!
Member who always late.
This is  not good!
This is not good!
Let us see no 3, no 3 is!
Itou Marika.
You are stylish though...
She will wake up if someone call her, and even she's late, she never apologize.
This is bad!
The staff have this kind of image!
I'm weak at waking up in early morning...
Everyone is!
Everyone is having difficulty to wake up early!
Indeed!
And you never apologize?
EH! I am apologized...
It's not reaching them!
It's scary...
This is important! If you already apologize but it's never reaching them, it is same with not Apologizing!
This is causing a problem between your manager and their talents!
Lets go to no 2, no 2 is this person!
Captain!
- Captain this is not good!
- As captain you should not be ranked here!
I just waiting for other member to ...
LIAR!
You always say that you are waiting and confirming other members right...
You never did that!
I am slow at everything... I am not reasoning myself but being so slow...
As a captain, this is not a good thing!
Be quicker! But there is no 1!
The one who always late is this person!
Matsumura!
YOU what are you doing, since the begining...
I didn't do it lately...
You took all no 1 today...
HAPPY^^
She won't be there every morning and she always have a wake-up hair when she came.
Yes... Thats true...
- But there is 1 more person...
- Yes, other one...
There is no.1 !?
The real no.1 ?
Who is she?
There she is! The actress, Hashimoto!
What are you doing? Like "PLEASE!!"
That's amazing...
So is it because you already became an actress?
It's not like that!
So you already bored?
No, back then I won't even wake up from emergency alarm!
Then my manager wake me up!
But I rushing out in 3 minutes!
Ow, our perparation is short!
Yes, so maybe staffs...
I see! I SEE!
So it means that no one know about this...
But i can't commenting about others...
So, everyday what are you doing at morning?
I do go early every morning!
It's hell!
Don't say it's hell! What do you mean by it's hell?!
Because i have responsibilities with my jobs.
But Himura is very precise about time! And I feel anxious because of that!
And I just gone mad and said WHY YOU NEVER LATE?
That kind of madness is impossible right?
When he see me at waiting room, he just yelled WHY ARE YOU HERE?
Next is this! The topis is...
Member who is troubling as lil sister.
Staffs also answer for this kind of question...
No 3 is this person!
Why? Because she will be a great lil sister i think.
Smart... Cute...
Her parents' education is good and she has no opening.
She will be in hyper mode when it is night time.
So at night, you will be overactive?
Yes, from 10 PM my mood is became strange...
The starting point is at 10 PM right?
Why?
I don't know, maybe i am a nocturnal.
A nocturnal?
It would be dangerous for you to attend a live night TV show.
Yes...
Like waaaa... Yeeeaaaa...
I am no 1!
Ikuchan!
Shut up!
You can see her like that, audiences.
That kind of sister isn't needed.
No 2 is this person!
- EEEHH why?
- Takayama!
Why is it?
Her way of speaking is infectious.
And, if we go out together, and she suddenly shout "AMEIJINGU" it make me feels awkward.
There are staffs who don't like your "AMEIJINGU".
No 1 is unexpected! I do think she is the lil sister. This person!
This is unexpected.
There are lots of thing she can't do. This is so lil sister.
She will ask for something unexpected with that cuteness.
If she said something selfish with that voice, i can only follow.
So, they will feel pressure as big sister/brother.
Is this a good thing?
I don't think so!
It's very burdening.
Cute face rank?
After this, announcement for cute face ranking?
Next, i will announce the topic later.
I will announce the rank first! This!
No 1 is Matsumura! 2 is Ikuta and 3 is Nishino!
What kind of ranking is this?
Matsumura, what do you think?
Cute face ranking?
I know you will say that!
Do you know it, Nishino?
Eating...
That's possible!
So what is this? Lets see the topic!
I see.
Gluttonous ranking!
No 3 Nishino. She always watching snacks...
You always watching foods?
Yes.
What kind of act is being observed!
Ikuta is ranked in...
Ikuta do eat!
Yes i do. If i don't eat, i feel upset.
She has obsession with foods.
Like, for lunchbox or onigiri, after she take one, she will take another as a spare.
They know it!
Of course they will know!
They do think you are a gluttonous.
I don't think that they know it ^^;
No 1 Matsumura is always take away lunchbox or snacks.
You always said it on TV... So you do so?
Yes! I love it.
Like, for someone's birthday, there will be a cake on the buss...
And everyone just swarming, but for me, I took all the leftover.
Yes, when everyone finished eating, I go and eat all of it.
Are you just confessing to me?
After this, because of Himura's ranking, members feels disturbed!
The last topic, i will announce parts of it. THIS!
According to Himura! Member who xxxxxxxx!
What's this?
And the rank is ready there!
3 is Nishino, 2 Ikoma, 1 Takayama.
What do you think? Inoue.
Like... Himura?
Himura...
Like eh @.@
Eh, are you confessing to me?
Yes, that kind of expression is like confessing!
You say "like.... Himura"
She deny it with all her power!
So what is the topic? Let us see it.
Member who like me!
- It's reversed...
- Yes it is! You all almost get it.
For Nishino, it is Bananaman that she like.
This means she like me right?
Do you like Himura?
I do...
Eh! What do you mean by that?
No 2 is Ikoma.
She's very honest with her feeling.
I just can feel it.
Not like other members, she just entered my personal space.
But... I...
BUT no 1 is different!
I'm sorry, but no 1 is...
Takayama!
For Takayama, if you see her face, you'll understand!
Like... Like now!
She's in love.
There's lovy eyes right?
Yes! She just show it whenever she's not catched by camera and just see me.
This is the truth!
So Takayama how is it? You are no 1!
I respect him!
Yes I know it...
You respect him as a comedian?
That too, and her character...
You notice it from my sense of humour and character right?
Yes yes!
And slowly you just...
EH!
Just say it!
Why do you want me to say it all for you?
WHAT!!! I do like you!
Eee... What's that mean?
After this, members will tell their scary experiences.