Tonight, all members is here!
There will be a fullblast about the unknown problems
regarding being in a big group.
Bananaman is ROFL, what is the truth
that has been told by UG?
And then, the real story from ex-AKB48
made members burst into cry.
[Nogizaka tte Doko?]
[Translator: Rustyhand
Timer: Jejee46
Follow @subshiro46 and stay update with Nogizaka46 subtitle release!!
Visit www.nogizakanouta.blogspot.com for more !!
DOONNN!!!! It's started, and your MC, Bananaman!
And Nogizaka-chan!
The usual member... whaaa...
Today, all nogizaka46's members are here.
All here?
That's great, a lots of it. And UG is also here.
- That's great, what happen?
- For some members, it's been a while...
Hmmm? Who is that, the one on the 2nd row? Third person?
Wait... 2nd row huh? Who are you?
2nd gen? Today 2nd gen aren't called isn't it?
So, who are you?
Noujou Ami!
- Your hair is very different!
- Noujou?
Your hairstyle seem different...
Is it?
Himura, please announce the topic tonight
with a loud voice that all can hear!
To be able to survive a harsh entertainment world,
big group idol's group learning of "happenings".
Tonight, doesn't matter whether senbatsu or UG, as a big group of idol,
They have to tell their happenings that they experienced, to make a tighter union.
And tonight's guest is...
Start the topic?
Yes, I think we should ignore the guest this time.
Ok, lets start!
It's cruel. Please call me!
It's starting, so please be quiet.
I do think I am important guest for them.
You should call me.
So the guest is that oldman?
Wait a sec, that person is my manager.
A big manager.
Big manager?
He's called Demon Hama.
Demon Hama?
Demon Hama, please forgive us.
Tonight, she will act as a teacher. Noro Kayo-sensei.
Please pardon me.
You Know a lot of happenings right?
I've been in 2 group.
Ex AKB48 and SDN48, further more, she was a captain in SDN48.
Yes, thats why I know all your feeling.
I intent to help you all.
That means you will give a lot of advise for them right?
But, please talk only if I give the chance.
AAAA, like that huh!!??
So, the 1st happening is this!
Wrong name...
- This is very plausible.
- Who wrote this?
Thats me!
- Oh, Wada!
- Wada Maaya. It's been a while!
- Yes.
- What is this mean?
At event, fans calling" Maaya Maaya".
Oh Maaya Maaya.
I am so happy and wave my hands for reply.
That's good!
But when I observe more, they are not waving their hands for me
and when I see my side, there is Maiyan, Shiraishi Mai.
Not Maaya but Maiyan!
So I made a mistake.
If you see from fans' point of view, they wont understand your action.
"Maiyan Maiyan" and you waving your hand to them.
Too bad for you... Only because you have a similar name.
So this kind of happening is occuring a lot in a group?
Yes! And if you are in the front row, you wont notice
whether they wave their hand for you or at back person.
I see.
Especially for non-senbatsu, this matter is an "issue" for them.
So you should make a confirmation first
by seeing your surounding first.
Confim and reply.
Yes, confirm that it's for you then reply.
Fabulous it is so correct.
And there's alot of same family name right?
Yes it is.
"Saitou" problem.
Saitou... Theres 18 Saitou(s) right.
Is there any problem?
Kanji for "SAI" in Saitou is different one to other.
But in the script, i never see my name is written correctly.
So it would be better if I said "that SAI".
- Yes.
- That's correct.
I see, a small problem but...
A small problem but it hurts.
As for me, my name is Noro(v) but they always said Noro(^).
EH! so the correct one is Noro(v)
- Yes the correct one is Noro(v) Kayo.
- So it's same with "NORO" Virus?
When we say norovirus is noro(v) right?
Yes that noro(v).
Like "norakuro"' nora? (Wiki: NORAKURO)
That's completely wrong!
Boro Car? (Boro = wrecked)
Noro(v)
The correct is Noro(v).
Why you all doing this gesture?
Its like saying "NODO"(NODO = throat)
Yes...
Nodo!
Not Nodo.
NODOKAYO (Just Throat)!!
Other name?
Name problem...
Itou!
My Itou's character is same with Nene.
So is there any mistake?
Usually the work schedule is sent by mail,
and i will go according to it.
At that time, I was back at Gifu,
and for work I need to go to Tokyo.
And the staff just "EH! It should be Marika..."
That's cruel!
So they called different person.
This is the staff's mistake!
That is cruel!
Schedule is being told by mail. Usually they use our first name
"Marika" but that time it's different.
And then?
They called Marika in a rush and me at my Tokyo house.
But... I feel uncomfortable with Nene... What to do?
Only for name there are lots of happenings, today we have alot!
Next happening is this!
Hmm? Trying hard to wrap legs together.
I don't understand...
Who is this? What's the meaning?
If you sit like this, your legs will spread wide open.
STOP it... Wait a sec, it's not captured by camera.
Reply it from closed condition.
So what is it?
Sit like this and...
You are closing your legs right?
They just loosen.
And, I do understand that we have to keep it closed but...
That's right!
But, is it only your problem? not for all right?
This is a private problem...
your legs are easily to get loosen right?
And then when we sit at Nogidoko for senbatsu announcement,
we sit with 2, 3 rows right?
Senbatsu will be sitting on 1st row
and we UG are sitting at 3rd row.
So when they're called, your legs is being shot.
we are betting it all on the legs.
I want to show beautiful legs.
I understand!
But it's opened?
When I watching the show on TV...
How is it?
WHAM!
This happening, you all feels the same?
Yes.
So female also open their legs?
Yes...
So you are now keeping your legs together?
With all power.
That's correct, if it's break time,
you all showing your panty right.
NO NO NO NO
So this is a common thing?
Yes. Especially the one who is sitting on the back row.
You have to close it?
Yes. Cause it won't even be a fanservice.
So we have to try harder?
Yes, try harder.
Why don't you tie it with a skin-coloured gumtape.
Lets go to the next thing, next is this!
You appeared as Nogizaka, didn't you?
What's this? who's this?
Yes.
Whats the meaning?
My hometown is a village, so whenever I get back, my grandma
always saying, you appeared as nogizaka didn't you.
- She always said that.
- It's happy thing!
I didn't sing, moreover I didn't appeared.
No no no, you don't know it right!
You maybe appeared.
No, she said "Hina-chan, you appeared as Nogizaka, it's good"
She always praising me.
But... I didn't!
No no, you just don't know.
You don't know that!
Maybe you did appear.
No, COMPLETELY DIDNT APPEAR.
I see. This is a very likely UG problem...
UG is good.
UG's good.
US's GOOD!
I do understand that.
I usually see Nogizaka46 at CM and Mags.
Wait a sec...
You are NOGIZAKA46.
You are NOGIZAKA46!
Yes I do but, I see it alot, like cover page
and I just think "This is great!"
Just lately right...
Nishino is doing solo gravure at mags.
Yes, I do think she's cute...
But I just... "It is good..."
I see, but this can't be helped.
But, not only UG, we also, when we are called
for a TV show, they wont put mic on us.
Ah! Pin mic...
Understand that...
This is, not only in the group,
this thing also happened to us comedians.
Yes it is.
Like, why he got a mic and I'm not.
That's common. I do understand!
So, in that case, we shouldn't talk? or should we talk?
This is complicated.
Yeah it is complicated.
The truth is, our management just said,
do it, that's a chance, why don't you do it!
Yes, they said that things.
But the reality is... no no we can't do it.
We, UG, every recording is a life bet.
- That's right!
- I agree.
You get your shoot when performing songs or PV, but when the camera
is coming at me, and if i did a mistake, that shoot won't be used.
Ah, because of nervous.
Yes... Always like that at the important timing.
This is our true story, there's time when we only
could appear at TV once in every year.
Then whenever there is a chance, Like batting, I just put
all my strength holding the bat and aiming for the coming ball.
But, the one who did that, won't hit the ball. In other word,
the one who put all their strength will miss it.
That's why, that person will go against the mood, like when you just only needed to say delicious, that person just saying, what's this! Fried shrimp that I ate yesterday is WAY BETTER!
This is do happened.
All young and inexperienced comedians will do this!
They all think this is a chance and play it wrong.
You have to be carefull with this...
but you must have the will to hit the ball.
I also learned from you just now.
I do things like you said before.
I did it with my fullest.
The important thing is the will.
- May i said something honestly?
- Please do!
I'm selected as senbatsu in all 6 singles.
That's great!
But, my scene time is...
If you count the total, it's only around less than 1 second.
It should be more than 1 second.
I really don't have any screen time
But, this matter, if you're in a group, sometime when you see PV on tv, some people just have a blink, and if you want to see certain member, she's very unlikely to appear.
Acting like a panorama...
Panorama?
They won't give the focus on us.
Wow, you people are very talkative today.
Today is great!
But... But...
Here she come!
Senbatsu member still have screen time on nogidoko... UG have nothing!
They wont even call us.
For us, being a senbatsu member is a jealous thing!
This is heating up.
This kind of learning is rare, this is a good chance.
It can't be helped right?
Yes it is. If you dont appreciate for being selected,
member like Inoue will be replaced by others.
For front members, 8fukujin, I dont think there will be
a large movement. Only a difference in the numbering.
But for the back members (senbatsu) if you show any opening,
you will be overtaken. Furthermore there are 2nd gen.
Yes. I dont know about them in details but when I see that side (UG)
and comparing with that side(senbatsu), you people have no big differences.
I see, but I do have big differences (sarcasm for Noro).
I do have big differences. No, not like that!
I see.
I agree with you.
I feel something big today.
Excuse me, Yuttan is crying because she feels the same.
And I didn't get the mic also...
I don't think it will be like this.
If you said that, we already doing this for 20 years.
You people only in your 2nd year!
That's right! You people are being selfish!
You have your own TV show!
After this, don't know why but Himura is victimized!!
Let's continue, the next happening is this!
What's this. I did research about myself over net. who is this?
I did that research by entering my name or nogizaka,
and it will shows alot of things.
When I search it, the result is...
Anything that make you shocked?
You see something that attacking you?
Yes..
But, I think you all search it right,
like the impression of certain tv show.
And like love photos, or any witnesses...
I think some of you lready search this kind of things.
And there are other person's entry and lots of it is not correct...
This is frightening. You have to make sure
the information is correct or not.
There's a lot of entries of Himura, aren't they?
Yes, correct.
Like, he's eating with his foolish face.
And like, acting cool... There's alot of
entries with acting cool bla bla bla.
Now he's at 7-11 posing cool.
Acting cool at gasoline station.
Yes, I feel the same with you about this matter.
Like, when I just want to make payment, others just
why you take out your wallet like that!!!
Lunchbox... When he queueing for buying lunchbox,
it said "he queueing with acting cool".
This is my character's problems right...
But I... I just... Yamato Rina is..
Why? Are we friends? (hes reacting for her way of speaking)
That's fine.
I am really troubled.
When I search "Yamato Rina" it just shows
"YAMATO RINA HIMURA YUUKI".
Me too!
And, it seems Yamato Rina and Himura Yuuki is similar.
- Your chin shape.
- The chin shape?
And according to that site, we are similar.
Me too, that site also appear.
Your face is similar, something like that? So sorry.
And there's polling about yes or no.
Ahhh Understand!
I choose "NO"!
wait a sec...
You choose "NO"
I click "NO" but 79% people choose "YES".
I see. Right now you are hurting Himura's feeling.
You don't like it do you?
After this, because of Hashimoto's comment
Noro is become speechless.
Next! the next one is this.
Tan oshi...
Tan oshi?
When I think that person is Tan oshi, he went to other lane...
Who is this?
Yes. Tan oshi is, you only have one pushed member.
So only pushing one member is called tan-oshi.
Yes, and...
For me, there are fans that always supporting me from 1st single.
That time, when Manatsu is restated back as Nogizaka46,
her lane is next to my lane.
Oh, so at handshake all of you is standing next by next?
Yes.
That time, the fans who always pushing me is standing at her lane.
Ah, so you already know that person is
the same person that always pushing you.
Yes, the sad feeling when you see that person
on other lane... lonely feeling.
So you remember your fans? like always coming...
Yes I do.
We remember, I want to say something for fans,
you think that members not watching you, we did watch you.
Even though you queue at a very far lane,
I'm like "ah that person queueing at that lane!"
It's like that?
Maybe that person doesn't realize,
but I do want to make that person realized.
And there's someone that change their clothing and queueing at other lane...
- That's...
- That person just considering your feeling.
It's so sad...
Then give a tan-oshi fan a special service.
I agree with that.
Like giving your hair.
No way!
We do want IT!!! YOUR HAIR!
Wait wait, what happen? that thing is mine to do.
Yes, if there's nothing...
If there's nothing, ITS NOT FAIR! GIVE US YOUR HAIR FAST!
Stop it Himura!
But if you don't act like that...
It's like a trust.
If fans always coming to our lane,
we can trust that person and we feel safe.
So this thing is common?
Completely common. Like AKB's Fans, especially my fans, there's fans that always pushing me and that person give me a letter stating that he is supporting Nogizaka46 right now.
Only a part of your fans?
Yes.
A farewell letter?
Yes it is.
What to do if this thing happen...
But it's free to change your fave right...
At the last handshake event,
"I up until now, I always pushing Noro Kayo".
That person.
That person must be the same person, so he just give a word
and apologizing for pushing Noro Kayo.
His manner is good but...
You won't win against Hashimoto.
I won't win against you.
I do think he did the correct thing, but please say
"left some of her in the corner of your heart" to him.
Don't forget about Noro Kayo.
Just left some of me in his heart...
Interesting.
He said, he really liked you.
In that case...
Why he said so much about this.
I think it is not a bad thing to move into
next generation, we are getting older...
- So from you to them is OK
- Can't be helped
So from here to here is...
Yes, you're all about the same age right...
Same group...
A fans of Mayuyu from AKB48 just came to my place
and reporting to me that Mayuyu like Ikoma.
That kind of excitement is also possible.
Like a pigeon post...
That's a bad example...
It means that a lot of people just go to a lot of places.
Yes, so a lot of girls in same group...
why you are laughing?
There's still more...