m 0 0 l 0 27 l 2 27 l 2 0 l 0 0 m 2 0 l -4 0 l -4 6 l 16 6 l 16 4 l -2 4 l -2 2 l 0 2 m 2 2 m 16 0 l 16 27 l 18 27 l 18 -1 l 16 -1 m 22 0 l 22 0 l 24 0 l 24 11 l 19 11 l 19 9 l 22 9 l 22 2 l 15 2 l 15 0 m 6 18 l 6 12 l 12 12 l 12 14 l 8 14 l 8 18 l 6 18 m 12 18 l 12 20 l 6 20 l 6 18 l 10 18 l 10 14 l 12 14 l 12 18 m 5 7 l 8 9 l 7 10 l 4 8 l 5 7 m 10 9 l 10 9 l 13 7 l 14 8 l 11 10 l 10 9 m 3 24 b 3 24 3 23 3 23 b 7 21 11 21 15 23 b 15 23 15 25 15 25 b 11 23 7 23 3 25
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
Tonight on Nogidoko,
hometowns of the members special!
Let's continue "Amachan"!
Show your love for your hometown!
A surprising event that only happens in member's hometown
will be revealed!
How could she get there?
Moreover, they get flabbergasted
by local ad that doesn't make sense!?
So the songs were overlapping?
Nogizakatte, Doko?
They walk for about 20 kilometers...
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Members will talk more about their love for their hometowns!
A miraculous revealing of the mysterious [Gourd Quiz] ?
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
- That's harsh.
- Elementary students too...
He really said something about gourds.
Since there was no big gourd in Osaka...
Wasn't that Takayama's teacher?
Bananaman
Himura Yuuki
Shitara Osamu
DON! Alright Nogizakatte, Doko is starting,
we're the MC Bananaman, Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu.
And here's Nogizaka-chan!
Huh? Huh?
Here, here, here!
Lots of them!
Ayaya Gayayoyo!
What was that? What?
- What was that?
- What did you say?
- Let's do the best until tomorrow!
- I see.
- Almost all members are here today, there's a lot of them.
- That's right.
- What are we doing to do today, Himura-san?
- Okay! Today...
Let's continue "Amachan"!
Show your love for your hometown!
It means, like an effect made by Amachan...
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Looking at Amachan's popularity, we will explain many things
from [Dialects] to [Local Products] of members' hometowns!
Show your love for your hometown!
... like local dialects, delicacies,
and places which have become very popular.
Based on that, since we have many members
coming from many different areas in Nogizaka...
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Nogizaka members hail from various places, so show new amazing things from your hometown and talk about your love for your hometown!
Show your love for your hometown!
... we will give them a chance to show their love
for their hometowns to their heart's content.
And that's our theme.
This time, we have chosen members who aren't from Kanto area.
[ Kanto = Tokyo and its surrounding areas ]
They will try to...
... tell about events exist only in their hometowns,
which isn't Tokyo, as much as they want.
Let's start with the first theme.
Here it is.
- Does it only exist in my hometown?
Local event category.  - There must be a lot!
Does It Only Exist In My Hometown?
[ Local Event Category ]
Like festivals that only exist in your hometowns, right?
Alright, let's start with this one.
Does It Only Exist In My Hometown? [ Local Event Category ]
Elementary School Trip Was A Physical Trip
Elementary school trip was a physical trip.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Elementary school trip was a
[Harsh Trip]
- What?   - Physical trip?
- This time, we already knew the summary of the theme but we don't know the details at all!
Whose hometown is this?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Etou Misa
from Oita Prefecture
- Me!
- Oh, Etou!   - What's this?
- It's from Oita, and in Oita, everyone knew this.
- Yeah, everyone.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
The regular event of Oita prefecture
[Harsh Trip]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Hatanaka Seira
from Oita Prefecture
Really? Did Hatanaka actually know this!?
- You knew it, right?
- She obviously didn't!
- So everyone in Oita knew this?
- It's really famous.
- This physical trip is...
- Hold on!
[ Etou is talking with Oita dialect here, using "-cchuu" suffix ]
Don't use your dialect so suddenly.
Enjoying the theme too much?
In this physical trip, we walk as much as we can,
the distance is about 20 kilometers.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Trip usually done in a special event where
the participants walk through a quite long distance
Oita's Physical Trip
Students aren't treated in a special way.
They also aren't allowed to bring snacks.
They just have to keep walking.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
The regular event of Oita prefecture
[Harsh Trip]
Where's the end?
Like, where are you heading?
The regular event of Oita prefecture
Walk as far as you can in [Harsh Trip]
Deep into the mountains.
Unclear destination.
Deep into the mountains?
The distance from home to that place
is about 20 kilometers.
So the round-trip is 20 kilometers?
When did it start?
Is it just for elementary students?
Up to sixth graders...
Eh? The first graders take part too?
Yes but the distance is closer.
The 20 kilometers one is just for sixth graders.
Very difficult.
How marvelous!
And snacks are not allowed too?
- I think we're not allowed to bring some. Not even a banana.
- But maybe we're allowed to only buy the 300 Yen ones.
There are snacks after all!
Snack issue arises.
- So you're allowed to bring some.
- Etou didn't bring it?
Did Hatanaka just bring it as she liked?
Soul of Yankee.
- That's Hatanaka for you.
- Which is why we need to adapt.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Additional Information Regarding Oita's Physical Trip
An event to train students' physical strength, especally
their legs and waists, everyone in Oita has experienced this
So this is the detail about that event in Oita.
It's to train their physical strength.
Ah, this is an event to train their legs and waists, and...
... the local government called this "Physical Trip"...
The shocking thing is, the government also supports this event
called [Physical Trip] to be held in Oita Prefecture
... and they were surprised because people in Tokyo don't do this.
- Unbelievable.
- This is very Oita.
You can say, the government people there are awesome!
Because although they're adults,
they said "You don't know?!"
"JeJe" in Oita.
[ JeJe = shocked expression of finding something,
said by the main character from the drama "Amachan" ]
Alright, moving on.
Here's next.
Does It Only Exist In My Hometown? [ Local Event Category ]
Getting A Lot of Snacks With Rousoku Dase!
(Get The Candle Out!)
Getting a lot of snacks...
... with "Rousoku Dase?"
- What is this?
- I have no idea!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
With "Rousoku Dase!
Getting a lot of snacks
This sounds like a folktale!
Get the CANDLE out!
GET THE CANDLE OUT!!
- Then you receive snacks.
- Whose hometown is this?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Hashimoto Nanami
from Hokkaido
- Hokkaido?
- Yes.
- What is this?
- This is a Tanabata Festival in Hokkaido.
[ Tanabata = a traditional festival on July and August ]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Tanabata event in Hokkaido
Getting snacks with Rousoku Dase!
- Tanabata?
- Yes, the festival takes place on the 7th of August in Hokkaido.
I guess it's similar with Halloween.
So it starts on the 7th of August?
We do it only on August 7th.
It can be said that this is only done by elementary students,
in a place where they live, they will...
Get it out~ Get the candle out~
otherwise we will "Kacchakuzo"...
... plus, we will bite you.
Wait, what's "Kacchakuzo"?
What's a "Kacchakuzo"?
- Clawing?
- Ah, so clawing is called "Kacchakuzo"?
- Yes.
- Surely we don't want to get clawed.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
According to Hokkaido's dialect
Kacchaku = Clawing
Don't claw us! Don't!
"Doesn't want to get clawed" group.
- I've never wanted to get clawed!
- Maybe we have that too.
- Akita has that too?
- Tohoku?  - Correct.
[ Tohoku = northeast region of Japan ]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Ikoma Rina
from Akita
Yamato, you have that too?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Yamato  Rina
from Miyagi prefecture
When do you say that?
For example, to my little sister...
... I'll claw you!
You claw me, I claw you back!
Claw war.
Her little sis is very scary.
Normally, there's no such thing!
- Eh, then after you say that...
- After that...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Tanabata event in Hokkaido
Getting snacks with Rousoku Dase!
Someone will come out from that house and says
"Ah, you're here this year too..."
- Halloween?
- Maybe it's like Halloween.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Rousoku Dase Hokkaido!
On Tanabata, the elementary students sing in front of houses
trying to get snacks and candles from every house
- Hokkaido's own Halloween, huh?
- Most people...
... prepared a lot of snacks before August 7th.
- Any snacks?
- Yes, every house provides that...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Tanabata event in Hokkaido
Getting snacks with Rousoku Dase!
However, for house that doesn't have any snacks,
they'll give money instead.
The correct house.
- Amazing.   - They will say some thing like
"Since we don't have any this year, you go buy it yourself."...
... then they give 100 Yen!
If you say get the candle out,
will someone give you a candle?
- They might.
- They might?!
For example, an old couple who doesn't know anything,
they will mutter...
... "Okay, we understand",
and they give a candle instead.
The wrong house.
Are they okay?
Then they actually knew the history behind it, didn't they?
It's famous in Hokkaido.
Everyone knew it when the Tanabata Festival is being held.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Additional Information Regarding Rousoku Dase Hokkaido!
In Hokkaido prefecture,
this is the most popular part of Tanabata Festival
The story goes like this: the children are included in Obon, then they
are asked to gather the candles needed for the offering
At Obon, kids are being told to gather some candles...
[ Obon = the lantern festival or festival of the spirits ]
... they're also traveling around while carrying lanterns
and playing some music.
- I see!
Then after a while, together with the candle,
the children also receive snacks to make them happy
- So that's how it is!
After a while, together with the candles,
they're also given some snacks to make them happy.
- That's very nice!
- So the candle is the important one.
- Yes!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Tanabata event in Hokkaido
Getting snacks with Rousoku Dase!
But there's even a song about it, huh.
Get it out~ Get the candle out~ otherwise, I will claw you!
I'll claw you~ I'll claw you~
I'll claw you!
Conductor of Kacchaku song.
I'll claw you! I'll claw you!
- Don't claw me!
Okay, I won't claw you!
Next, here it is.
Does It Only Exist In My Hometown? [ Local Event Category ]
The Mysterious [Gourd Quiz]
- What is this?
- Quiz? Gourd Quiz? Whose is this?
- That's mine.
- Eh, you have this in your place?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Takayama Kazumi
from Chiba
- Really?
- I had this in my elementary school.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
An event in Takayama's elementary school
The Mysterious Gourd Quiz
Takayama is from Chiba, right?
[ This segment is about traditions outside of Kanto.
Chiba is still in Kanto region ]
I am from Chiba, but it was an outskirt area...
- Eh, there's nothing like this in Kanto?
- No!
Everyone is strongly rejecting.
Wait... Wait...
I think this gourd quiz is special just in your area.
Like it only exists in your area.
- What's a Gourd Quiz?
- Back in my elementary years...
Twice a year, from first grade to sixth grade...
... we had a Gourd Quiz when it was the gourd season.
And to smoothen the quiz, we had a meeting...
A meeting about gourds.
So there was a meeting?
Then, one by one...
... we carried a gourd located on the first floor...
... and we were asked to "Guess the weight!",
it was that type of a quiz.
- So you looked for a big gourd...
- The gourd was quite big...
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
The Gourd Quiz in Takayama's Elementary School
A quiz where all students of her school try to predict
the weight of the big gourd the school has
... about this big, there was always one gourd that big every year.
We only had to guess the weight of the gourd.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
An event in Takayama's elementary school
Quiz to get the heaviest gourd
And then you wrote it on a paper and showed it?
Then, about five students with the most correct answers,
would get some award...
.... in the school ceremony.
A special right as an honor.
- Well...
- What was that?
I guess your school is the only one who does that.
Not a local specialty.
Certainly just your school!
But that's sweet, though!
Then...
Eh, what? What's wrong?
... there's some detail about that.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Additional Information Regarding The Gourd Quiz
Takayama's school has combined with another school.
The school does not exist anymore today
- Takayama's school has combined with another school,
so it doesn't exist anymore now.   - That's true!
- That's so true!
- How unfortunate.
Sad, isn't it? We've been searching for more detail
about this Gourd Quiz, but...
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Additional Information Regarding The Gourd Quiz
We can't contact the said teacher to ask for his whereabout
With such condition, the information regarding this thing is unknown
... her teacher back then was not there anymore,
and we couldn't make a contact with him either...
... so the Gourd Quiz is still a mystery now.
Still a mystery.
This sucks!
Ah, hold on. What?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Matsumura Sayuri
from Osaka
-  In my elementary school...
- What? Don't tell me...
Back on a teacher exchange, there was a new headmaster,
it happened when I was a fourth grader.
Suddenly my headmaster got changed, and...
... he told us
"Actually, that teacher can guess the weight of a gourd...."
Since there was no big gourd in Osaka...
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
The Mysterious [Gourd Quiz]
Matsumura also has a similar experience
He told us to guess the weight of the dirt instead.
Wasn't that Takayama's teacher?
The gourd teacher got transferred?
Kyaaa! Awesome! Unbelievable!
- Do you remember his name?
- Ah, I don't.
What do you mean with the weight of the dirt!?
Now it's The Dirt Quiz.
- I don't get it at all!
- They used that because there was no gourd.
- Like a handful of dirt...
- He said, "Normally we use gourd, but let's just use this in Osaka..."
So that was the gourd teacher?
That's for sure!
- Amazing!
- I remembered so suddenly...
Wasn't our story so scary just now?
- Let's send this to "Tantei! Naito Scoop".
- Yeah, let's do that!
[ Tantei! Naito Scoop = a show where detectives
solve problems the viewers had sent to them ]
Legit investigation.
- Your teacher might get found.
- That's right.
Okay, let's continue, here it is.
Does It Only Exist In My Hometown? [ Local Event Category ]
All-You-Can-Eat In Someone Else's House
EEHH!!!??
- What is this?
- All you can eat in someone else's house?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
All you can eat
in a stranger's house
- What is this?
- I don't understand. Whose is this?
- Where?  - Who?
- Me.
- Nagasaki? Kawago!
- Nagasaki?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Kawago Hina
from Nagasaki
Yes. There's a festival
called Nagasaki Kunchi back in my place.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A festival of Suwa Shrine in Nagasaki
A name of the dynamic (Dragon Dance)
Nagasaki Kunchi
On the day of festival, we can go to someone's house
and eat as much as we want.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A festival in Nagasaki
All you can eat in a stranger's house
- You gotta be kidding me!  - No, it's real.
- Isn't that creepy?
It's just for children, right?
No. There were quite some old men I don't know
came to our house.
Strangers are coming to eat.
No! That's creepy!
Was it okay for them to came into your house?
So a bunch of old men came to your house?
- Yes! I don't know any of them.
- Seriously?
- Yes, and they ate as much as they wanted
in my house and went home.  - That's very bizzare!
Area of crime risks.
That's so creepy!
But we all understand each other...
- At least you knew who they were, right?
Like they weren't total strangers?  - Ah, well...
- ... since it's a rural area, everyone was close
and befriended each other.   - I see.
- So on that festival, everything in that area
is available to be eaten?  - Exactly.
Unbelievable!
Ah, here's an information about Nagasaki.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Additional Information Regarding All-You-Can-Eat In Someone Else's House
On Nagasaki Kunchi (especially Karatsu Kunchi), there's a local custom
which is providing anyone with meals which was the start of this tradition
Nagasaki Kunchi is a custom to receive anyone.
So it's...
So it was a custom, then it became a tradition.
In the area where the festival is taking place, the local women
cook the luxurious [Kunchi Food] without stopping
Because of that, when the festival is going on,
the women stay inside the house and keep cooking.
Keep cooking? That's very tiring!
Pretty interesting!
Next segment, there will be a mysterious local delicacy!
Alright, next topic.
Does It Only Exist In My Hometown?
[ Food Category ]
Does it only exist in my hometown?
Food Category!
So we have this too!
Alright, here's the first one!
Does It Only Exist In My Hometown? [ Food Category ]
BABAHERA
Babahera?
- Wait a second!
- What is this?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Special delicacy of Akita prefecture
[BABAHERA]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Ikoma Rina
from Akita
Ikoma? It's in Akita?
First thing first, what's a Babahera? Wait...
- We'll try to guess.
- Alright, got it.
- It's like a Miso.
- I'm thinking about the same thing too!
- Baba (granny) does this using Hera (spatula).
- But there are Baba and Hera.
- There are Baba and Hera.
- No way!
Okay, tell us what it is. What is this?
Ice cream.
So it's ice cream?
Here it is.
- So pretty!
- This is Babahera...
... because a granny uses a spatula
to make such ice cream.
The rose shape can only be done by professionals.
- Wait, what are those made of? The pink and the yellow,
are those ice cream?   - Correct, those are ice cream.
They use strawberry and banana flavor there...
It's very good, Baba with a Hera...
- So only a Baba makes this?!
Just for Babaa (Grandma).
Yes. The ones who sell this...
- I wanna see a Jiji (grandpa) making it too!
- There are moments where Jijis make it instead.
But mostly grannies.
Baba with a Hera.
What is she doing there?
They're doing business in a place like this.
Lonely.
On the side of the road, near the mountains.
How did she get there?
She lives here?
They have a method!
- There's a Babahera company...
- There's a company?!
When the grannies are going to work...
... they get picked by a car,
and they get dropped at some spots.
Seed-sowing strategy
A bunch of grannies are being picked up by a car at once...
... then they'll get dropped off at each points?
I see.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Special delicacy of Akita prefecture
The mystery of [BABAHERA]
Then when their work hour is up,
they'll get picked up one by one.
So that's how it is.
Well so while waiting for the car,
they'll just keep making the Babaheras forever!
A sad work system.
Precisely!
- How much is this?
- About 150 Yen.   - Eh, that's very cheap!
- That's cheap.
- You can certainly find them on a festival.
A while ago when there was a festival in Akita,
Babahera also came to that festival.
Actually, they just came as they want.
Just as they want?
So right after a Babahera got dropped off...
... all she does is this.
Zero Complain.
Why?
Shall we continue?
Here's next!
Does It Only Exist In My Hometown? [ Food Category ]
What Do You Call This?
What do you call this?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Kawamura Mahiro
from Osaka
Ah, me!
- We call that Obanyaki or Imagawayaki.
- Maybe it's different.
[ Obanyaki/Imagawayaki = snack with red paste fillings ]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Osaka Prefecture = Kaitenyaki
- We call that Kaitenyaki in Osaka.
- Kaitenyaki, huh?
Even though we call it Kaitenyaki,
that's not the case in Tokyo.
- There's Kaitenyaki too in Kyushu!
- Maybe it came from Osaka.
- But it's different in Hiroshima.
- What is it? Okonomiyaki?
[ Both of Hiroshima & Kyushu are located on the southern part of Japan ]
[ Okonomiyaki = Hiroshima's special delicacy ]
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Nakamoto Himeka
from Nagashima
Usually it's called Obanyaki in Tokyo.
Nijuuyaki?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Hiroshima Prefecture = Nijuuyaki
Eh, I don't really know.
But maybe it's called Nijuuyaki.
- Nijouyaki?
- Nijuuyaki. But perhaps that's...
Eh, it's okay, let's go with that.
So, Nijuuyaki?
- It's alright compared to the "Gourd Quiz" story earlier.
- Why?!
A very trusted local information.
- Others? Ah, Akita.
- Ajiman.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Akita Prefecture = Ajiman
Huh? Ajiman?
Where they sell this Ajiman, they also sell Takoyaki.
So Ajiman? Are the others different too?
Hokkaido?
We call that Oyaki.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Hokkaido = Oyaki
Well, Oyaki...
Oyaki, Shinshu's original product
[ Shinshu = another name of Nagano prefecture ]
[ Takana = pasta made from mustard plant ]
- ... there's a lot of fillings...
- Like Takana too.
But it's just in my place it's called Oyaki.
Basically in Kanto, this is called Imagawayaki or Obanyaki.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Kanto  = Imagawayaki  Obanyaki
- But it's different in my place.
- Eh, no way!
What? Hyoutanyaki?
(Hyoutan = Gourd)
Inheriting the name of Miss Gourd.
- Takayama, what about your place?
- It's called Amatarou in my place.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Chiba Prefecture = Amatarou
- No! No!
- What a difference!
I thought it would end with "Yaki",
but actually it's "Tarou".
- Amatarou?
- Yes, Amatarou.
Alright, moving on.
Here's the next theme.
Does It Only Exist In My Hometown?
[ Local Commercial Ad Category ]
Does this only exist in my hometown?
Commercial Ad Category.
There must be some ads that only broadcasted in their hometowns.
This seems interesting.
Okay, first is this.
Does It Only Exist In My Hometown? [ Local Commercial Ad Category ]
The Poppo Ojisan Song
The Poppo Ojisan song.
- What is this? Whose hometown is this?
- Me.
- There's a lot of things there.
- From Oita.   - Oita.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Hatanaka Seira
from Oita prefecture
- Does everyone in Oita know this Poppo Ojisan song?
- Certainly!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A popular ad in Oita region
The Poppo Ojisan Song
I see.
This is a song of Karaage shop.
This is a drawing song!
Then I'll try to draw it according to the song on a paper.
We'll try to draw it.
- You draw it too.
- Draw the correct answer.
Before they see the actual ad,
we'll try the drawing challenge based from their singing.
Okay, I will draw it for real.
- Please start.
- Go!
Poppoojisan no Uta
Poppoppo~ on the Onigiri~
[ Poppoppo = Onomatopoeia of something puffing like steam from hot food ]
Put two Umeboshis and wrap it in Nori.
[ Umeboshi = dried plum ]
Sprinkle some sesame and salt, it's Poppo  Ojisan.
What was that? Eh!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A popular ad in Oita region
The Poppo Ojisan Song
That sounded scary!
Hold on, you were too fast!
The tempo was too fast.
Here's mine.
I thought the song would be a bit longer.
Now please watch the real Poppo Ojisan ad here.
Poppoppo~ on the Onigiri~
Put two Umeboshis and wrap it in Nori.
Sprinkle some sesame and salt, it's Poppo Ojisan.
How cute!
Oita Karaage!
- So that's Poppo Ojisan?
- It's been a while since I saw that.   - That's cute!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Poppo Ojisan
Isn't Poppo Ojisan weird?
It's red from here on!
- Seriously!
- So this is Oita's Karaage!
- We didn't know this.
- That's true.
- Oita itself is famous for its Karaage.
- Ah, I see.
Moving on, here it is.
Does It Only Exist In My Hometown? [ Local Commercial Ad Category ]
Long Term Relationship
[ Nagai Otsukiai = long term relationship, the company is trusted
and gives the best service over a long period of time  ]
Long term relationship?
- Who?
- Me!
- Osaka?   - Yes.
- What ad is this?
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Matsumura Sayuri
from Osaka
It's an ad of the Bank of Kyoto.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A popular ad in Osaka region
Long Term Relationship
- And it's seriously long.
- Yes.
- Literally.
- Everything is literally long.
Let's check it out.
Long~~~~~~~~~~ Term Relationship
Ah, the nostalgia.
I see.
Bank of Kyoto
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A popular ad in Osaka region
Long Term Relationship
So that was the "long"?
- This feels so Osaka.
- It does!
Bank of Kyoto Long Term Relationship
Toast Category
Toast?
Ah, there's more?
What is this?
Eeeehhhh???!!!
- Awesome!
- That's weird!
Long~~~~~~~~~~ Term Relationship
Bank of Kyoto
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A popular ad in Osaka region
Long Term Relationship
What ad is this?
- There are many?
- Yes, about 20.  - That many?
There's more!?
Mop?!
Bank of Kyoto Long Term Relationship
Mopping Category
Let's start together!
- Ah, that's nice.
- Cute.
Long~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Term Relationship
Bank of Kyoto
I see.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A popular ad in Osaka region
Long Term Relationship
So that's how it is.
So it's a series of a long-shaped things.
After this, there will be an illogical local ad!?
So the songs were overlapping?
Okay, let's continue.
Here's next!
Does It Only Exist In My Hometown? [ Local Commercial Ad Category ]
Tokugawa Okonomiyaki
- Tokugawa Okonomiyaki.
- Okonomiyaki ad?
- Who?
- Here! An ad from Hiroshima.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A popular ad in Hiroshima region
Tokugawa Okonomiyaki
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Wada Maaya
from Nagashima
The concept is old...
... the drawings are old...
... well... everything looks old...
Too many "olds".
I seriously have no idea!
- Wada, all you said was "old".
- Everything is old.
The atmosphere is classic...
... the classic atmosphere can always be felt...
... well... it just looks old!
No relation whatsoever.
- Let's just see it, what did she mean by old?
- Let's check it out.
Quickly, quickly, mix it quickly
Ah, this is old.
Let's make it round
I see now.
Talking about Okonomiyaki,
it's Tokugawa
With your friends...
Toyokanko Group
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A popular ad in Hiroshima region
Tokugawa Okonomiyaki
What was that? Like...
That was bad!
- Why did it overlap?
- So the songs were overlapping?
- Was it like that ever since?
- It was, huh?
Suddenly "Toyokanko!"
- Let's see it once again.
- What was that?
Must be scary to be there.
Quickly, quickly, mix it quickly
Let's make it round
Talking about Okonomiyaki,
it's Tokugawa
Let's make a lot with your friends
Toyokanko Group
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A popular ad in Hiroshima region
Tokugawa Okonomiyaki
Why?
The "Tomodachi..." hasn't ended yet
but there's "Toyokanko." What was that?
What a timing!
Actually...
- ... it's "Let's make a lot with your friends."
- That's what he said, right?
But then "Toyokanko" suddenly got in,
I wonder why?
Maybe because of the time limit,
since ads have 15 to 30 seconds of duration...
... perhaps they thought "Not enough time!"
Then they just said
"Put it in! Just put the Toyokanko in!"
Forcing it too much.
Shouldn't be like that!
Okay, let's continue.
Here's another!
- Mysterious...
- Another quiz.
Does It Only Exist In My Hometown? [ Local Commercial Ad Category ]
The Mysterious Bento Quiz
The mysterious bento quiz?
- An ad from Shizuoka!
- Shizuoka?  - Yes.
- Certainly everyone in Shizuoka knew this ad.
- Seriously?!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A popular ad in Shizuoka region
The Mysterious Bento Quiz
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
Fukagawa Mai
from Shizuoka
- Was it that famous?
- Very!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
m 0 3 b 0 3 0 3 0 3 b -7 -2 -10 -5 -10 -8 b -10 -11 -8 -13 -5 -13 b -2 -13 0 -11 0 -8 b 0 -11 2 -13 5 -13 b 8 -13 10 -11 10 -8 b 10 -5 7 -2 0 3
Wakatsuki Yumi
from Shizuoka
- Maybe this is a very old recording.
- Yes, this is so old school!
Well then, let's see.
It's a quiz, isn't it?
Here's the question
If you have to say
Happy Gourmet Bento now...?
What is this?
Ebi Katsui!
So old!
Don~Don~?
Obento~
What?
Instantly makes you Happy!
Don Don?
Obento Don Don.
- It's Obento Don Don.
- I think I know this.
- So it's Obento Don Don's ad?
- Yes!
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A popular ad in Shizuoka region
The Mysterious Bento Quiz
- Do the stores that sell this Obento Don Don
exist only in Shizuoka?   - Perhaps yes.
When fans come to the handshake event...
... if they say
"If you have to say Happy Gourmet Bento now...?!"
We'll answer it with "Don Don!",
and the atmosphere becomes like "Wah!!!"
Humor Shizuoka people definitely know.
That was awesome!
What was that...
"If you have to say Happy Gourmet Bento now...?!"
- Happy Gourmet Bento!
- Happy Gourmet Bento?
But the cut just now,
it was here at the beginning...
... but the girl answered it from this direction.
What's with the glasses.
Let's see it one more time.
- That was all over the place, even the cuts were messy.
- True that.
Here's the question.
If you have to say
Happy Gourmet Bento now...?
Ebi Katsui!
Don~Don~?
Obento~
Instantly makes you Happy!
Obento Don Don.
- Her pose was good!
- Yeah.
m 466 -175 l -469 -175 l -469 19 l 466 19
A popular ad in Shizuoka region
The Mysterious Bento Quiz
- It was kinda erotic, wasn't it?
- Like alluring?
Like "DonDon"
Her breathing makes a difference.
That was it, though.
And they had Donburi (bowl) on their heads, yeah?
Maybe they wore it since it's DonDon.
That's right!
Why did they shoot it outside
when the weather was that bad?
Cloudy...
What's next?
Is that as far as you know how my feelings are?
Love confessions using local dialects,
everyone is shrieking!!
"Members turn to Mofi characters"
for UFO Catcher reward has been released!!
By autumn of August,
the products will be released at game centers.
To know the places where you can get these products,
please check Sega Prize on the official website.
Sekai de Ichiban Kodoku na LOVER
November 9th,
Gekijou DAN Bad Boys J will be released!
The ticket reservation for art performance
Nogizaka version has been opened!
For more information,
please visit our official website.
Is that as far as you know how my feelings are?
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
There's still more discussion about love for hometowns
Something we've been waiting for! Love confessions using their local dialects
MANUALLY TRANSLATED FROM INDO SUBTITLE
ORIGINAL SUB BY MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
USE IT AT YOUR OWN RISK
Um... may I say something I've been holding all this time?
But...
... I want us to keep being together like this, okay?
Since it's cold, may I hold your hand now?
I want to hold her hand!
This is a bit different than what I thought...
A ridiculous birthday party of Akimoto!