Tonight is the "Nogizaka46 Haloween Party"!
Tonight is the "Nogizaka46 Halloween Party"!
Each member appears in a costume!
For some reason, members' sexy phrases causes a huge laughter?!
The heated up party game has a shocking outcome!
Translated by Jiaemi & Eytr
Timed & Typeset by Michael Soares
QC by ramenrider
For more subs visit www.Facebook.com/IkomaSubs Brought to you by IkomaSubs
DON! Nogidoko has begun! We're your hosts Bananaman!
Good evening! Treat us well!
As for today
Yes.
The members are not here
The members were all hospitalized
No, they weren't!
That was you.
Oh, it was me.
You're wrong.
Without any delay, Himura-san
please do the title call like a monster pumpkin.
Your monster pumpkin impersonation is good.
I haven't really done this before.
Nogizaka Halloween Party!
First, just like last year, members will appear in costumes they chose.
And they will say a sexy phrase fitting their costumes
However, the phrase they choose must not be too obvious as to what character they are portraying
Understood.
Wearing a police costume and saying "I will arrest you!" is no good
Last year when we said this, Hashimoto said something like
"No Left Turn"
As long as you say it sexily it's fine.
Ah~ She said "No Left Turn".
So, without further ado!
let's call them!
OK.
Come on in!
Who is it?
Ah~
Oh Kawago
She came out.
-What's this?
-Isn't that Tinker Bell?
Is it?
"Don't become an adult!"
-Ah~ It's Tinker Bell
-Tinker Bell
Nice
Let's keep going.
Wait a minute!
Here she comes.
Matsumura
Some kind of monster?
I see.
"I'm hungry! Can I eat you?"
Nice
Your Kansai dialect was used at the right time
Who?
It's Saito Asuka.
What is this?
-It's cute, Devil-chan.
-Some kind of demon?
She will say a phrase.
Bite~
Suck~
"You are blood type A, aren't you?"
Hold on
It was a mosquito?
It became a gag.
Nice
Keep it coming.
It's Hori!
Ah! The Arabian Nights
Nice.
"Come riding on a flying carpet to meet me~"
Nice~
"Come riding on a flying carpet to meet me"
It's good.
Ah~ It's the policewoman. "I will arrest you!" is forbidden you know.
I'm counting on you
"Wait, You!"
"You are going over the speed limit~"
Haha nice! Nice~
I wonder what was speeding
I see.
Here she comes.
It's Himetan
Maid
"Moe Moe Kyun~"
Himetan is always like this.
"Moe Moe Kyun"?!
I liked that phrase
It's here!
Cheongsam! (China Dress)
She is holding a panda.
"Chinese Cabbage~"
Why Chinese cabbage?!
-It was stupid!
-Next one is here.
-It's fine. It was sexy.
She is here.
It's a nun.
Ah nice
Fukagawa is looking good
"Amen~"
She summarized what she wanted to say in one word
Please sit over there.
"Amen" is good.
Yes.
Next one.
Ah~
People who like this kind of outfit won't be able to resist this.
You're right.
"Oniichan,"
"play with Manatsu~"
She knows how to seize people.
Next one!
She's cute!
"L... O... V... E..."
"Love Yu-ki~!"
She said "Love Yuki"!
Me. It's me.
I'm sorry.
She's completely making fun of you
No, she's not.
She is here.
Ah! What's this?
Lolita
Ah~ It's lolita!
It's goth lolita style.
So, it's goth lolita.
Ito Marika
"You can do whatever you want with me~"
She said an amazing one!
I can do whatever I want?!
It was great!
Isn't this one a little weird?
Will this be okay?
The theme was supposed to be Halloween.
"Shoulder it~"
What's she saying?
It was good Takayama. As expected of you.
She certainly has that knack for making people laugh
What's she saying?
It's the next one.
Ah! It's a nurse!
It's here.
This one is good.
"20 ml"
20 ml of what? Where are you injecting I wonder?
It was good.
The way it makes you imagine is good.
It's the next one!
Ah! Race Queen!
It's a Race Queen?
Race Queen!
This one is really cute!
"Pit stop, OK~"
This one makes your imagination run wild too!
Is it alright, doing pit stop?
It's fine. It's OK.
The next one comes.
She's appeared! Je je je!
It's good. This one is cute.
Didn't this one already come out?
Yes. Wasn't there one similar to this?
"Je Je Je~!"
Ah, I said it already.
Sorry.
It's the costume party of Nogizaka.
It has been a year since the last time.
Time flies so fast.
Yes, it does.
Matsumura got first place the previous round right?
Yes.
What was your phrase?
"P-l-a-y with me~"
Right.
"Play with me~~~"
You said something quite perverted
Matsumura, this time too.
This time "Is it OK if I eat you?".
This "to eat" part...
Monster.
It's a monster?
Matsumura is a man-eating monster, right?
Yes. This year I'm a man-eating monster.
Yes.
Everyone's phrase sense, compared to last year
was a little more on the offense.
There were many on the offense.
Hori!
Right, Hori!
What was it? Was it "Buy a carpet"?
CARPET SHOP?
What was it?
When you wear a different outfit than your usual ones it gives off a different vibe
Yes, it does.
Usually you have a more childlike vibe but in this outfit you look mature.
See, like I said.
Arabian Nights?
What kind of a setting was this?
A Dancer Girl.
That's a little...
Roughly
You are saying it the way it is.
There are many types of dancer outfits in the world, you know.
It's good. It was great.
It gets weird from here on.
Eto?
Eto is sexy. Stand up.
The slit on your skirt is great.
This one is good.
It's nice, isn't it?
I went on a little offense.
It has a China feel. You are holding a panda too.
And what you said was "Chinese Cabbage".
Isn't this a dirty joke?
It's not!
It is!
I just like it.
Ah, Chinese cabbage. It's a vegetable, right?
Yes, it's a vegetable.
Manatsu-san.
Manatsu-san did it.
Manatsu-san as expected.
"Play with Manatsu"
Even though you're 20 years old~
Even though, she is 20 years old!
You are mean!
It's fine isn't it!
People get fished by stuff like these after all.
No that's not true, this is my true self
Your true self?!
THAT'S A PROBLEM
That would be bad, those kind of "onii-chans" would come and find you
He will do it.
I'm onii-chan.
ONII-CHAN RUSH
It will be like that.
Nishino.
What's this Nishino? Explain it a little.
She divided the phrase into 6 parts.
Eh?
"L.O.V.E"
"Love Yu-ki"
See!
What do you mean by that?
There are many people called Yuki.
There is Himura Yuki.
Amami Yuuki-san
There is Amami Yuuki-san.
BROAD EXISTENCE
Takayama is weird.
Takayama that's enough out of you!
Even though it was supposed to be a Halloween festival,
you came wearing the outfit of a different festival.
WRONG FESTIVAL
Right.
Show the whole outfit.
It suits you though
You look like a woman portable shrine bearer. It's cool.
At first,
I wasn't sure about it.
But everyone said it suits me.
Right now it really feels like a festival.
IT FEELS LIKE A FESTIVAL
Next one is Shiraishi.
Shiraishi is a Race Queen.
Yes, Race Queen.
It was a good phrase.
"Pit Stop, OK"
Yes.
That's dangerous.
It's dangerous.
You shouldn't say that.
It's the changing of tires at the pit stop...
It makes you think what kind of a tire is it, you know.
CAN CHANGE AS MANY AS YOU LIKE
The more you say it the worse it becomes.
It's useless whatever you say.
We are thankful though.
This kind of thing is for us to say
And the last one, Ikoma.
I said your phrase before you, I'm sorry.
You know the recent Amachan craze
I am told a lot that it suits me.
You appeared in the show before right?
It suits you to the extent that it wouldn't be strange if you were to be added to the cast
I'm a huge fan so today I will only say "Je Je Je"
"JE JE JE" DECLARATION
After this, a heated game tournament.
Let's heat up the party by playing various party games in those costumes.
Let's play the first game. Himura-san please announce it.
First game is "Nogizaka Fruits Basket"!
One member will be "it" and others will be sitting,
"it" will read the paper she picked out of the box
and the members that fit the description in the paper will change seats.
The one that is unable to sit becomes the "it".
After playing for 10 times, the member that has been "it" for the most time will receive a punishment
The first "it" is?
Are there anyone that wants to be "it"?
Yes.
That's good.
This will count as being "it" once too
THINK BEFORE YOU ACT
Were you surprised?
Oh! That's good.
Je Je Je~
It's not good to say "I'll do it" to everything.
Then, let's start. We will search for the ones that didn't move even though the description fits them.
Because it's not fun if you don't move.
Yes.
It could end with Ikoma being the "it" for 10 times in a row.
ENDS WITHOUT ANYONE MOVING
Please, not that.
Please change your seats with all your power.
Then let's start with Ikoma being "it".
"Nogizaka Fruits Basket" start!
Yes.
Read it.
The ones that can't study.
Here it goes.
So it's like that.
Who is not bad at studying? The ones that didn't move raise your hands.
The ones that didn't move raise your hands.
Ah, Matsumura definitely should've moved.
AREN'T YOU BAD AT STUDYING?
No, it's not that.
What's not that?
Everyone moves faster than I thought so I couldn't move.
That's the point of this game you know.
I was shocked.
Please turn your switch on.
You are really bad at studying, right?
Well, not good.
If it happens next time, I'll count you as "it" once as a penalty.
I'm sorry.
This time let's watch out for the penalty and start the 2nd round.
After you pick and look at the paper,
you can check for people that might move.
You can read after checking.
Let's start the 2nd round.
Get ready to move right away.
But only if it fits you.
The ones not from Tokyo.
Who is it? Who is it?
Matsumura!
It's Matsumura!
At the end, your fight with Kawago for the chair was hard to look at.
Next is the 3rd round.
And the topic is...
Ah~ I see.
Takayama's outfit is the easiest to move in.
You have the advantage.
She is waiting with her legs open.
Close your legs for now.
I'm reading.
The ones that are frequently late!
Hashimoto moved.
Oh, that's bad. That's bad
Eh, I can't believe it.
Even though many moved.
The one closest to you moved. Why didn't you sit there?
That's not it! When I saw this,
I thought of Nanamin.
I thought about going to Nanamin's seat.
But Reika was really fast!
She was really fast!
The ones that fit the topic moved?
Who moved? Raise your hands.
So these are the members that are always late.
To the 4th round with Matsumura as "it" 2nd time in a row.
Then, I'm reading.
The ones that can't cook.
Attention
Why are you holding me?!
What are you doing?
I was sitting there from the start.
Ah! It was your seat.
Even though Ikoma couldn't move at all.
Wait a minute. I was able to get a seat but,
somehow,
when I was getting ready, it felt like someone was holding my sleeve
I thought it was my imagination and started running but,
Shitara-san was sabotaging me.
Were you surprised?
I was shocked.
I was suwrprwised.
AAAARRRGGH~!!!
EVOLUTION OF "JE JE JE"
Continuing on to the 5th round. And the topic is...
The ones that take off their socks right away.
Go!
Hold on!
It's nice~ Things heated up.
That was dangerous.
Ah! 3 people moved.
We already knew about Nishino. She talked about it on the show before.
She would take them off as soon as she comes home.
Matsumura is like that too?
Maiyan is
famous for sitting in her underwear in her room but actually, I don't wear clothes in my room either.
Eh?
Yes.
So when you are home...
I remove everything.
Naked?
There are many times I'm naked.
Are you serious?!
Why is everyone like that?
But right now we will be playing the 6th round and Matsumura has been "it" 3 times.
Most of the topics fit Matsumura.
On the other hand, Takayama is sitting the entire time.
What is this? Are you from the festival's management committee?
What are you?
Like an old man sitting in the tent.
We move on to the 6th round with Matsumura at a slight disadvantage.
The ones that loves money!
OK. She is out.
Hold on!
Who moved?
They are honest.
Are there someone who knows a member who loves money?
Right.
Don't you all say "I want money" all the time?
They say it all the time?
Takayama you moved because you love money.
I really love money!
I want money!
Next round, with the topic "the ones who are taller than 155cm" Shiraishi became "it".
At the 8th round, Akimoto became the "it" with the topic "the ones that like Shitara more".
9th round is starting with Matsumura in the lead.
Ah~
Please proceed!
I think there will be many people moving.
Wouldn't it better to come a little more to the front?
The ones that have lied!
GO!
Not many moved.
What's this?
Wait a minute!
Kawago.
I've been watching Kawago for a while but it seems she can't move freely because of the wings.
BIG HANDICAP
They are in the way.
Hold on. The ones that didn't move raise your hands.
Who didn't move?
There were some weird movements in that section.
You three! Isn't it unfair? Didn't you just change seats between yourselves?
-We didn't.
-At the last moment Mattsun said,
"let's change seats"
Eh?!
So I told them to let me onto the plan too
This is penalty.
Sakurai you stood up and sat down back to your own seat, right?
IN ANY CASE IT'S A FOUL
I didn't stand up.
Sakurai gets a penalty.
Yes.
Who else didn't move?
Really? You don't lie?
I've never lied.
Himetan you are lying, aren't you?
Wait! I'm not lying!
Himetan!
You can't shoot "Himetan Beam", can you?
I can shoot it.
I can shoot the "Himetan Beam".
You can't shoot a beam!
Shoot the "Himetan Beam".
"Himetan Beam~"
It doesn't come out.
NO BEAM
Himetan gets a penalty.
OK.
Who else?
Hori.
You've never lied.
While thinking about it I ended up not being able to move.
Here it comes.
That was honest.
It was?
I thought about it but I didn't notice.
Then Hori gets special treatment.
HORI IS SPECIAL
Shut up!
We decide the rules!
The words of Bananaman are absolute
Shut up!
Do you have a problem?
Hori gets special treatment right~
Hori, do your best~
Shut up!
After this, a shocking development in a new game.
With Matsumura at an absolute disadvantage we move onto the last round.
Get ready for the last round.
Go ahead.
The ones that are actually black-hearted.
NO ONE MOVES
No one moves.
Eh?!
There is no black-hearted person among you?
If you had to pick the most black-hearted one among the members here who would you pick?
Manatsu-san?
Manatsu-san is black-hearted?
And?
Aren't there anyone else?
Only Manatsu-san.
This is weird. You guys are so mean.
Conversely, Matsumura looks like the most black-hearted person here for saying Akimoto's name.
Because she already has 3 penalty points
Matsumura gets another penalty here.
It's decided that she will be the one to get the punishment
What is the punishment?
A mini repentance about something that you haven't told the members until now.
I see.
Can I do a real one?
Of course.
If not, I have another one.
To whom?
Fukagawa Mai-san
Mai
What is it?
Did something happen?
Well...
When we first entered Nogizaka46,
I borrowed a manga from her
and I haven't returned it yet! I'm sorry!
I remember! I remembered now!
Eh?!
What is it Hashimoto?
What happened Hashimoto all of a sudden? It looks like an emergency case came.
EMERGENCY PATIENT?
Did something happen?
What happened Hashimoto?
I too
borrowed a DVD from MaiMai last year and haven't returned it back yet.
We're sorry!
Just because Fukagawa is a good person, don't steal her stuff.
LET'S BE MORE CAREFUL
Then, please announce the next game.
"Halloween Yamanote-sen Game"!
We will pick a subject and
you will say words matching it.
The ones that miss the rhythm
or the ones that says words that doesn't match the theme are out.
They will receive a punishment right away.
Himura-san will announce the first subject.
"Nogizaka Halloween Yamanote-sen Game"!
Yay!
Subject is "What comes to mind when you think of Shitara-san".
Non-Stop!
Cool!
MC!
Funny!
Kind!
Smart!
Great!
Ai ..
Hold on.
Stop!
Just now...
Hashimoto should be out according to the rules.
Hashimoto how far are you going?
Takayama was too slow.
I'm sorry.
Because everyone here is red.
No. No.
Why "because of red"?
What do you mean by "because of red"?
Because they are all wearing red you decided to treat them as one entity?
No way.
I was thinking I would go after the one wearing red but all 3 of them are wearing red.
Don't do that!
So Hashimoto gets punishment.
Please check.
Please read it.
Himura-san imitation.
Himura imitation.
Do the imitation of
Himura-san.
She is imitating me?
Himura-san doing something or the regular Himura-san either one is fine.
Either one is fine.
Are you ready?
The punishment, Himura's impersonation start.
Hashimoto,
I've seen your gravure photos in FRIDAY.
You did it alone, right?
It was good. It was beautiful.
Was Himura such a producer-like person?
Hashimoto, I've seen FRIDAY.
It was great.
Really? I'm happy!
Yes.
Yes, it was similar.
IT SOUNDED LIKE HIM
The party is reaching its climax!
Next game is "Halloween Russian Roulette Cream Puff"!
The last game is the person that eats the spicy cream puff loses.
However order is by volunteering.
Going first or waiting,
you can decide for yourself.
Anyone that wants to go first?
Me!
Oh~
You are great!
Je Je Je~! Je Je Je! JeJeJe!
Eat right away after you pick please.
Delicious~
It's delicious!
Hey!
It was fine.
If you wanted to do it twice you can go again.
1 MORE TIME?
Once is fine.
Once per person after all.
Now there is 14 left.
Me!
Good.
Today for some reason
you keep getting penalties
But this one should be fine.
I'll be fine
I'm eating!
Delicious!
Yay!
After that, Sakurai, Eto, Nishino all succeeded one by one.
And...
Here comes Himetan
Good.
I'm eating!
Mmm!
Yay!
Eh?!
WHAT HAPPENED?
What was that?
Time lag?
It's spicy?
Out? No good?
Himetan is out!
This is new.
Eh?!
While going like this, suddenly...
That's new.
Can't believe you could pull that off!
Have you ever seen something like that?
Nogizaka46 1st photobook which was just released
"Nogizaka Ha" got 1st place both in
"Rakuten Books Daily Ranking" and "Amazon Shoseki Yakubumon".
Furthermore, in its first week sold more than 100,000 copies.
Check Nogizaka right now!
What is the reason for Shiraishi's scream?