アイDOL
www.myAidol.net
On tonight's show, we'll be deciding who Nogizaka46's Gang Leader is.
With Kanto region vs. the Countryside
Who is the 'baddest' person in Nogizaka!?
However the studio becomes a storm of shrieks and screams!
Furthermore...
How will the crazy One-on-One battle between Ikuta and Matsumura turn out?
Nogizaka tte Doko?
[Ikuta vs Matsumura's battle of willpower is a must see!]
[Showing their delinquent sides]
We won't lose to some hillbillies!
Nice one!
Don't mess with the hungry spirits of the countryside!
This is less than I usually eat with!
It's quite a lot, don't you think?
Here is Noujou!
DON!
Banana Man
Himura Yuki
Shitara Osamu
Here we go! This is Nogizakatte Doko? We're the MC, Banana Man. Great to have you here!
Okay now, Nogizaka-chan... is not here...
Dead Silence.
The set today is also a bit different.
Okay Himura-san, please announce today's theme.
Let's do this!
Let's change our image! The Battle to decide who Nogizaka46's Gang Leader is!
[Sign: Nice to see ya!]
[Sign: Bring it!]
[Sign: Gang Leader/Boss!]
Oh, here they are.
What an appearance.
Oh? What are they doing?
What was that just now?
My, my, my.
Oh.
Nice!
Let's do this!
I'll do my best!
Oh, "I'll do my best!"
- Nice.
Right?
- Oh.
They look different today.
They're doing well, strutting like that without cracking a smile.
Smile!
Don't you feel like smiling?
What's going on? Oh, that's scary.
And then here's...
Ohh.
The hell?
The hell was that?
What was that about?
That was the opposite of cool.
What was that?
What just happened?
They're giving off a different vibe today.
Oh?
- What is going on?
This bunch is weird.
What's with them?
Isn't something off with them?
Oh.
My, my.
Ah, I see.
Wow.
Okay then~
The hell is all this?
And so, as you can tell, things look different today.
Right, everyone? Did you guys give up on being idols?
Stopped being Idols?
What's with that?
In preparation for the release of the movie version of BAD BOYS J and to hone the Nogizaka girls' versatility as idols...
...they are going to showcase more of their delinquent sides. And so!
Split into the Kanto team, led by Shitara.
Meanwhile, Himura leads the Countryside team.
They will determine who is the baddest through a series of battles.
Although everyone's attire is all over the place, this Countryside team is quite unfashionable.
A vibe of the countryside.
This other side seems more suited.
- I get what you mean.
Don't you get that?
Yeah.
Hatanaka, did you prepare that outfit yourself?
Genuine Attire
I didn't.
But you're all fired up, right?
Go and express our desire to not lose.
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 25 l 0 25
Kanto Team (Kanagawa Prefecture)
Sakurai Reika
We won't lose to some hillbillies!
Nice one!
I'm always impressed by someone able to say that!
Someone from our team, get back at them.
m 0 0 l 335 0 l 335 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 335 0 l 335 25 l 0 25
Countryside Team (Hokkaido Prefecture)
Hashimoto Nanami
Don't underestimate the hungry spirits of the countryside!
You've done it now.
- The hungry spirit of the countryside?
Okay then.
Think you can do it, Hoshino?
m 0 0 l 355 0 l 355 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 355 0 l 355 25 l 0 25
Kanto Team (Chiba Prefecture)
Hoshino Minami
Can you do it in a very aggressive fashion?
- Okay.
Oi, you hicks!
Don't mess around with Tokyo!
Nice one. Nice one.
Misa-senpai, let it out! Come on out.
m 0 0 l 295 0 l 295 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 295 0 l 295 25 l 0 25
Countryside Team (Oita Prefecture)
Eto Misa
Oi! Inoue!
Choosing Inoue?
- You!
Why the hell are you in the Kanto team when you come from the boondocks of Saitama?!
m 0 0 l 355 0 l 355 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 355 0 l 355 25 l 0 25
Kanto Team (Saitama Prefecture)
Inoue Sayuri
The hell!?
Since you've been singled out, go on and return the favor.
Let it out!
H-Hey you!
What's wrong?
Keep it up!
You.
Don't mess with Saitama!
Hang on.
She has a sore throat.
She's from the countryside, right?
- That's wrong.
Okay, so the first battle will be...
...the Electric Shock Russian Roulette!!
Going in alternates, the members will one by one select a pen from the ten that are laid out.
The team which gets the electric shock pen will lose.
If they’re aiming to be the baddest, clicking an electric pen should be no big deal. Even more, they should aim to win!
By the way, through rock-paper-scissors, the Kanto team will be going second.
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 25 l 0 25
Countryside Team (Oita Prefecture)
Hatanaka Seira
Electric Pen
First off is Hatanaka from the countryside team.
Okay.
- Hatanaka isn't scared at all, right?
Yeah.
- Alright. Now face the camera and show your appeal.
I've got this!
Oh, she really does sound like she does.
Let's do it.
Ready, set, go!
Yay!
Safe!
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 25 l 0 25
Kanto Team (Tokyo)
Saitou Yuri
Next up we have Saitou from the Kanto team.
Which one will you pick?
Isn't she taking her precious time choosing?
- The middle part is sticking out.
Not choosing one.
- I haven't decided yet.
Decide already!
"I haven't decided!"
Okay, face the camera and give it your all! Ready, set, go!
We ain't losing to some country folk!
Go for it!
Alright!
Safe!
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 25 l 0 25
Countryside Team (Shizuoka Prefecture)
Wakatsuki Yumi
Next for the countryside team is Wakatsuki.
You've gotta do better than that.
Ready, set, go!
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 25 l 0 25
Kanto Team (Saitama Prefecture)
Nakada Kana
Then we had Nakada from the Kanto team.
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 25 l 0 25
Countryside Team (Nagasaki Prefecture)
Kawago Hina
Kawago, from the countryside team continued their success.
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 25 l 0 25
Kanto Team (Saitama Prefecture)
Akimoto Manatsu
With 5 pens left, Akimoto takes the challenge next.
This ain't scary at all. But you wouldn't know that, city girl!
What? Don't mess around!
- It ain't scary at all!
Let's do this, Manatsu!
- Okay.
Which one will she choose?
Oh, the middle one!
Okay, now face the camera and tell them how psyched you are!
I'll show you how to give hillbillies electric shocks!
- Go for it!
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 300 0 l 300 25 l 0 25
Countryside Team (Oita Prefecture)
Eto Misa
4 left. Eto, from the countryside team, will be up next.
Don't go around wearing weird, flashy outfits!
The hell are you wearing?
The hell is with that coloring!?
You can sense the seductiveness, can't you!?
- No, none at all!
So which will you choose?
- This one.
The leftmost one.
Okay now, face the camera and show how psyched you are.
- Use Oita.
Don't go underestimating Oita's potential!
Go for it!
Safe!
Oh, there's only 3 left.
What shall- Oh, you're volunteering for this one?
m 0 0 l 355 0 l 355 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 355 0 l 355 25 l 0 25
Kanto Team (Kanagawa Prefecture)
Ito Marika
What!?
- Timing is important!
What the? What a gutsy one!
- Will she be fine? I wonder.
I've got this!
How cool.
I'll go with the middle one.
- What? The middle one!?
Okay, face the camera and show how fired up you are!
- This will be fine!
I may look childish, but I'll show you my mature side!
- Alright! Go for it!
You guys see that? Why don't you guys have a go!?
We were already doing it before!
They were doing it before.
We were!
- Okay.
Amazingly, there are only 2 pens left!
m 0 0 l 335 0 l 335 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 335 0 l 335 25 l 0 25
Countryside Team (Hiroshima Prefecture)
Nakamoto Himeka
m 0 0 l 355 0 l 355 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 355 0 l 355 25 l 0 25
Kanto Team (Saitama Prefecture)
Inoue Sayuri
For this one we'll have Nakamoto for the Countryside team and Inoue for the Kanto team.
For this last round, the both of them will have to click at the same time.
[Yankee = Gangster ]
She's not a yankee!
- Are you a yankee?
She's actually the baddest of them all.
Yeah.
- She's the real leader.
What the?
- Bad, isn't she?
'Badness' Pose?
See? Bad, right?
Okay, which one?
m 0 0 l 335 0 l 335 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 335 0 l 335 25 l 0 25
Countryside Team (Hiroshima Prefecture)
Nakamoto Himeka
Okay then. I'll choose this one.
Okay.
Well then, face the camera and show how fired up you are.
I told you not to mess with Hiroshima!
- Don't click it yet!
Then we have Inoue!
- What's with her pose?
Inoue, face the camera and say what you like!
m 0 0 l 355 0 l 355 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 355 0 l 355 25 l 0 25
Kanto Team (Saitama Prefecture)
Inoue Sayuri
Kanto is actually strong!
Nice one!
"Kanto is actually strong!"
[Hiraizumi Sei-san (Japanese Actor) ]
Hiraizumi Sei-san.
- Imitation?
Okay, line up there.
Now, face the camera and hold out your pens to get ready.
With your thumb.
- Don't lose!
Ready, set...!
Countryside Team Wins!
The next battle is...
...The Extremely Spicy One-on-One Battle!
One person from each team will sprinkle the blend of seven spices on the udon. Then, they'll have a taste.
They will take turns doing this until one is unable to eat.
If they are truly bad, they should be able to take the spiciness without faltering.
Okay then, who will represent the Kanto Team?
Ikuta will!
m 0 0 l 355 0 l 355 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 355 0 l 355 25 l 0 25
Kanto Team (Tokyo)
Ikuta Erika
You'll do it?
- I totally got this!
Nice, Ikuta.
m 0 0 l 335 0 l 335 50 l 0 50
m 0 0 l 335 0 l 335 25 l 0 25
Countryside Team (Osaka Prefecture)
Matsumura Sayuri
And Matsumura will represent the Countryside Team.
Let's do this!
- You can do it, right?
Through rock-paper-scissors, we'll decide who gets to choose who'll go first.
Ready, and...
Rock-paper-scissors!
What will you do, Matsumura?
You won.
I'm going second!
She must be scared. She chose to go second.
If you don't go all in, you'll lose!
- Uncool!
I can look if I want to!
Okay, let's do this.
First off is Ikuta, how much will you put?
She's just getting warmed up!
- Well, it is the first one.
What's up?
This is less than you usually eat with.
- Oh.
No, no, it's quite a lot, don't you think?
More than usual?
- It is just the first one.
It's the first one.
- She's scared, but that's fine, right?
Please take a bite now.
Gonna eat it now.
- Oh, "Gonna eat it now."
You can't just go eating your favourite udon, got it!?
Not spicy? You lose if it's spicy, right?
How was it, Ikuta?
- It was nothing.
Okay!
Obviously!
That udon looked delicious.
Next is Matsumura, how much will you put?
Show them, show them!
Show them!
Show them how it's done.
See, see? This is how it's done.
How's that for ya, Ikuta?
- See?
Well, that's still not much.
- What!?
Not much!?
Smells so good!
Please eat it.
- Okay.
Tastes great!
Brilliant, as expected!
With a nice start...
...there will be an epic life-or-death struggle coming up!
If we keep this up, it won't end.
Therefore, I'll put more.
Okay. Why not remove this here?
What in the world!?
Can you do that!?
Yeah, I can!
- What did you say?!
Oi!
Superb! As expected of Ikuta!
Nice one!
Do it!
No problem!
After that, Matsumura did the same.
Very cool!
Let's do this!
Don't go mixing it around!
I am mixing it!
You freaking out there?
You're the one freaking out!
What's wrong?
- That might get mixed.
Gulp that part down!
- Let's do it!
Oh, she's going for it.
You can do it!
Show them what you've got!
What in the world!?
Go! Go!
What the hell!?
What will they do? Things are escalating rapidly!
Let's do this!
- Go for it!
Do it!
C'mon!
You can do it, right?
Safe!
Not spicy for her at all.
But after this, Ikuta's body starts acting weirdly...
Look carefully.
Look here.
Ikuta-san please put your tongue back in.
Put your tongue back in.
- Oi! What are you doing, sticking your tongue out?
Alright!
Let's also get you girls to drink the soup from now on.
- What!?
New Rule Added.
What? Why?
Are you okay with drinking the soup as well?
No worries!
You can eat that one as it is.
Okay, I'll do it then.
- Okay.
So you're going with that.
You can do it! This is easy for her!
Safe!
Let's do this!
Can't handle the spiciness? Weren't you sticking your tongue out just a while ago?
- Not spicy at all!
My tongue stuck out on its own!
Stuck out on its own.
[ Doberman (a dog breed) ]
Same as a Doberman!
Are you a Doberman?
- Yeah!
Let's finish this thing here.
- Yeah.
Go for it!
Good luck!
Going for it?
She looks like she's enjoying the food.
Okay, now she'll have the soup.
- Can you handle the soup?
She has to drink the soup.
If you were to drink it, it might be too much for the other.
Spicy?
- Delicious, right?
Delicious, right?
Delicious.
Safe!
Did you all see that?
See that?
[HaaAaaaA~~~]
What was that just now? Why'd she open her mouth?
- What?
Isn't this crazy?
[Qigong is an ancient Chinese health care system that
integrates physical postures & breathing techniques.]
She's currently doing Qigong.
You're doing Qigong?
- You've gotta quickly eat, or she'll smash you.
This is bad, Matsumura.
Next up is Matsumura.
Incredible, Matsumura-san!
This is where the real challenge of willpower starts!
The challenge of willpower between the Kanto and Countryside team!
Alright, bring on the One-on-One battle!
Ikuta-san, are you okay?
Looking into the distance.
Isn't she done for?
- She's fine.
It's the other team's turn, right?
- She's going unconscious.
Ikuta!
- Okay, let's go, Matsumura!
Wow, looks good.
- Go!
The prize is expensive ice cream, do it for the ice cream!
Go! Go for it!
Too spicy?
- Go!
You'll never see a princess with a redder face than this!
Matsumura?
- The soup!
That's gotta be hot!
Safe!
The battle of willpower between these two will finally conclude.
This might be too much to handle now.
This looks way too crazy!
Come now, let's have you eat it.
Somehow...
- What's up, Ikuta-san?
It's going 'crunch'!
The Udon is going 'crunch'.
It's like sand.
It'll probably be over if you eat this.
Leaving the udon there makes it look like it's on the ground.
Ikuta, you can do it!
Do it! Do your best!
Very cool!
Please drink a mouthful of soup.
Where's the soup?
When you tipped it, all of it moved.
There's no soup.
Try getting out something which looks like the soup.
Let's go with this then.
Let's go with this.
Will she- Will she eat that!?
Don't underestimate Ikuta-san!
- Yeah!
Don't underestimate me! Let's do this!
Do it!
Utter Gutsiness!
She went for it!
If you finish eating that, then it might be over.
Don't give up!
What will you do?
Give up?
Which is it?
Oh, what's with that face?
Her eyes have flared up!
What in the world?
- Is she...?
Safe!
Well done!
You'd have no problem if she gave up now, right?
Don't overdo it.
"Don't overdo it."
- What will you do, Matsumura-san?
Let's do this!
What did you say!?
There's none left!
Absolutely none left!
Ikuta-san is standing, watching you.
You can do it!
If you win this, it'll be over!
- Ikuta-san, watch her.
Okay...
You wouldn't mind if she gave up, right?
- Yeah.
You can give up here.
What will you do, Matsumura?
I'll do it!
Ikuta?
Look at her, oi!
Look, Ikuta-san can't wait to fight!
Preparation for War?
Okay, Ikuta-san, please sit down here and watch.
Alright, let's do this, Matsumura!
- Oh, Ikuta, didn't she pick up a little less?
What's up, Ikuta-san?
Go for 2 strands of udon!
"Go for 2 strands of udon!"
Go all in!
She can't stop.
Ikuta-san, please sit first before preparing.
Ikuta-san, please calm down.
Go for it, Matsumura!
Good luck!
Wow, she's going for it.
YOU'RE OUT!!!
Kanto Team Wins!
Countryside Team vs Kanto Team
1 win - 1 win
Now we head off to the final battle.
The "I Can Grab a Frog Myself!" Relay Race!
Okay then.
This is the frog we'll be using for today.
Tada!
What is it?
That looks freaky!
Shaking.
5 members from each team will participate in the relay.
We’ll be timing how long it takes for them to move the large frog into the other tank.
Will they be able to touch the frog without freaking out?
The Kanto Team will be going up first.
I'm going to announce the members.
Shiraishi!
- Let's do this!
Wow! What an entry!
Noujou!
- Okay.
Oh?
- What? No way!
Can't do it?
- Don't be acting all scared!
Takayama!
You can do it, right?
- Can't do it?
Absentmindedness.
Can't do it? Get fired up!
Hoshino!
Me?
Let's do this!
And the final person is...
Manatsu-san!
- Oh! Manatsu!
Leave it to me!
Kanto Team
#5. Shiraishi ← #4. Noujou ← #3. Takayama ← #2. Hoshino ← #1. Akimoto
And so, the Kanto Team will relay in this order.
Ready!
And start!
It will be jumping so please watch out.
Block it before it jumps out.
Let's go.
Be quiet.
Ah! It'll get out!
Escapes.
Grab it!
Nice!
Hoshino also escapes.
Hold on!
Alright. Alright.
The two of them are panicking!
Hoshino! Quickly!
Wait!
- Quick!
How about putting it down for a moment?
If I put it down, I won't be able to pick it back up.
Hoshino, go for it!
Ah! Wait!
- Don't drop it.
Here's Takayama!
Don't face it towards me!
- Wait, wait.
What do I do?
- Nou-chan!!!
It's fine.
- Here's Noujou!
Noujou!
- You can do it!
It's a frog!
Let's calm down.
- Noujou.
The frog might drop.
- It'll be fine.
Alright!
- Nice, nice!
Noujou!
- Ah! What should I do?
Noujou, Holding Up Everyone.
Come and grab it from the top of my hands.
- Okay, got it!
Okay?
- Yes, it's fine.
-  Got it!
Noujou!
- Ready?
- Let's do this!
Noujou! What the hell?
This is bad!
- No! No!
Nnn!
- It's fine, Noujou-san!
What's with the "Nnn!" just now?
A sudden "Nnn!"
It's like a balloon.
It's fine.
That's weird, calling it a balloon.
A balloon. A balloon. A balloon.
Oh, she managed to grab it?
- Yes, she did!
Don't drop it! Don't drop it!
Oh! Shiraishi is good!
We did it!
The hands which made contact
with the frog are off-limits.
It's over!
"I Can Grab a Frog Myself!" Relay Race
Kanto Team: 2 minutes and 16 seconds
Noujou, you were the one who hindered the progress, right?
That was impossible. There's no way I'd touch one!
Coming up, the studio will be in a greater panic!?
Countryside Team
#5. Ikoma ← #4. Wada ← #3. Eto ← #2. Hashimoto ← #1. Kawago
Next is the countryside team. Will they be able to best Kanto team's time?
Hashimoto, are you okay with these things?
I've– I've–
- You've got this, right?
I've got this...
You scared?
- You scared or something?
Kawago, how about you?
I've got this in the bag.
Wada?
No worries!
Alright then! Let's do this!
Get ready, countryside team!
Start!
Go for it quickly!
Do it quickly!
It's easy to hold!
Just do it in one go!
You can do it!
- Do your best!
Grab it!
Second Escape.
Quickly!
Quick, quick!
Grab onto it!
Grab it! Nice!
Go for it!
Wada!
Wada in a panic!
Wada's not coming over!
Wada!
After continuously refusing to even touch the frog, Wada Maaya gives up!
Nogizaka46's Gang Leader Deciding Battle!
Kanto Team Wins! (2 wins vs. 1 win)
And so, the Kanto team wins.
The last concert for Nogizaka46's National Summer Tour...
...will be held on the 6th of October at the Yoyogi National Gymnasium (Tokyo).
We're currently only accepting reservations from the Mobile Members.
For more details, please check out the official site!
Next week, we'll be revealing the details of surveys given to the family members of Nogizaka members!
The members' faces will redden from their affectionate parents' answers.
[Their families know everything!]
[A big revelation of the members' hidden and surprising talents as well.]
Akimoto's mother reveals her daughter's evil side!?