Tonight is the Senbatsu member
announcement for the 7th single.
This time there will be many surprises.
Then, the new Nogizaka46 journey begins!
Nogizakatte, Doko?
Timer: Mukaichi-G  |  Translator: WA Mirakuru, KimKim  |  Typesetter: WA Mirakuru, NiL.  |  TLC & QC: WA Mirakuru, NiL  |  Encoder, Hardsubber, Uploader: NiL | IndoToEng: weeabookstore
DON!
Nogizakatte, Doko? has begun.
I am the MC Bananaman, Shitara Osamu.
Then, this is Nogizaka-chan...
Okay, I'll announce tonight's theme.
Nogizaka46's 7th single Senbatsu announcement!
Therefore as announced, this time the
7th single Senbatsu announcement will be held.
First, the formation this time is...
First, I will announce the formation
this time for the 7th single...
The 7th single formation.
- Here is the formation.
What's this?
Is this possible?
Seventeen members?
Seventeen?
Usually there are only 16 members, but...
Kikuchi-san...
There are 17 members in Senbatsu this time?
That is correct...
There are now 17 Senbatsu members.
Now...
The Senbatsu which usually contains
16 members now contains 17.
The leading members are now the Fukujin 8 + 1.
All right, let's get started.
Okay, I'll begin announcing from the third row.
The first is...
Number 17.
The first to enter the Senbatsu is...
Takayama Kazumi.
Takayama.
First, Takayama Kazumi. Although she was able
to make Senbatsu this time, she was moved from the Fukujin 8.
We've just started and you're instantly called,
your feelings also must not...
You're not overly...
But this is the second time I've been in this position.
Although I was chosen for Fukujin 8 before...
I always wondered if I deserved to enter Fukujin 8, but...
Maybe I'm positioned in the back
because I still have many shortcomings.
Still, being placed in position 17 of 17 available spots,
there must be some reason.
That's true...
Still, being placed in position 17 of 17 available spots,
there must be some reason.
That's true...
Being in the 17th position...
My grandmother told me that I was
in the most vulnerable position, and that surprised me.
She also often forgets my position in Senbatsu.
Your position...
She's always said that.
I see.
Still, try to stand out more.
That's right. I will fight to get back into Fukujin 8.
- Keep working.
Takayama, please stand at the 17th position.
Hai. Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Well, let's continue...
I'll continue the announcement.
Number 10.
The next member to enter Senbatsu is...
Itou Marika.
Itou Marika...
Has successfully re-entered the Senbatsu.
This time, I managed to enter Senbatsu again.
In the 7th single, I will continue trying to show my character.
That's right, you're able to make it back in.
Continue to work hard to overcome all challenges.
Hai, the 10th position.
Dozo.
Arigatou gozaimasu.
Okay, let's move on.
Position 16 in the third row.
The next member to enter the Senbatsu is...
Kawago Hina.
Kawago Hina who always gives warmth to the members
managed to enter Senbatsu for the first time
Well, Kawago.
It's your first time entering Senbatsu.
Hai, this is the first time.
How do you feel?
All this time, I've always been working in Undergirls, but...
This time is the first I've made it into Senbatsu. Ureshii desu.
Finally, I can repay the kindness of the fans and my family.
Having been chosen, I will try to throw away my laziness
and work hard toward making the 7th single.
Your grandmother also wondered
if you were performing on Nogidoko?
You answered, "I did not appear."
This issue has been discussed before.
It seems, I will be featured more in this 7th single.
Hai, I will work hard.
Keep working hard.
With this, Kawago enters Senbatsu for the first time,
but with the entry of Kawago that also means...
Well, let's move on.
I'll continue the announcement.
Number 11.
The next Senbatsu member is...
Etou Misa.
Etou Misa, she also enters the Senbatsu
for the first time, following Kawago.
How are you feeling now?
All this time, I've always been in Undergirls.
I've thought, "Is there any reason for me to be in Nogizaka?"
But I always think to try my best at every chance I get there.
So even though I'm not always chosen for Senbatsu...
Because Nogizaka daisuki, I will keep fighting.
I've already made up my resolve.
As such, I can't believe I've been chosen.
Work hard because you have been chosen.
Ganbarimasu.
Hai, that's the 11th position.
Two people have entered Senbatsu for the first time.
Let's continue.
I'll continue the announcement.
Number 15.
The member who will enter the Senbatsu next is...
Nakamoto Himeka.
Nakamoto Himeka, she also got into Senbatsu for the first time.
How do you feel now?
I am also like both of the others,
doing their best until now as Undergirls in Nogizaka.
Surely...
I've wondered if Nogizaka is the right place for me.
I'm always thinking of things like that...
Although many things are painful. But definitely...
I always trust the fans who always support me.
I am really grateful for the support they provide.
You've also made it, Himetan.
Hai.
You got in.
Hai, omedetou.
Arigatou gozaimasu.
If Himura-san were here as usual, he would be surprised.
"Lot's of Undergirls are entering Senbatsu."
This is pretty sugoi, isn't it?
Three people from Undergirls
got into Senbatsu for the first time.
The 7th single is surprisingly sugoi, right?
Of course with the inclusion of Undergirls members, this means
there will be previous Senbatsu members who have not made it.
Well, let's move on.
I'll continue the announcement.
Number 12.
The next member to enter Senbatsu is...
Saito Asuka.
Saito Asuka, she makes it into Senbatsu
as she did in the 4th single.
Because right now I am the most insecure...
I will try to work with confidence in this 7th single.
Work hard with confidence.
There are a lot of members entering Senbatsu
for the first time, so I feel really relieved.
Really, yokatta desu.
You must be worried about not being chosen.
But you must also be happy to see
the other members chosen, so you feel conflicted.
Yokatta ne.
Ganbarimasu.
Your face is very small.
Omdetou gozaimasu.
Arigatou gozaimasu.
- Hai, the 12th position.
This time it's sugoi, there are so many changes.
With this, there are four positions
that changed from the 6th single.
Okay, let's move on.
I'll continue the announcement.
Number 14.
The next Senbatsu member is...
Fukagawa Mai.
Fukagawa Mai, she's made it into Senbatsu for the fifth time.
In the 6th single before, I always made
everything troublesome for the members.
Although I still have many shortcomings, still...
I will work hard to fix them.
Arigatou gozaimasu.
- Hai.
Ganbatte ne.
Now is the last position in the third row.
I'll continue the announcement.
Number 13.
The eighth member to enter Senbatsu is...
Akimoto Manatsu.
Akimoto Manatsu, she's always entered
Senbatsu since returning in the 4th single.
When I returned in the 4th single, I was glad
for being entrusted once as Fukujin 8.
But I moved out of Fukujin 8 during the 6th single.
So I've been thinking about working hard
to get back into Fukujin 8.
Though this time I've failed, I'll be more confident
to try to get back into Fukujin 8 for the next single.
It's okay, isn't it? Work to become confident again.
I look forward to many interesting reactions from you.
Hai. With that, the 13th position. Dozo.
Now, the third row is fully occupied.
There are two rows left.
After this, more and more surprising things will be announced.
Nine positions remain,
the announcement starts from the second row.
I'll continue the announcement.
Number 6.
The first person in the second row is...
Sakurai Reika.
Sakurai Reika, as captain of the leading members,
has made it into the Fukujin 8.
I am ureshii to be re-entrusted into Fukujin 8.
Because this time there are many changes
and differences that have occurred...
With these changes...
I will try to push this group to change for the better.
Support them as captain, yes?
Ganbarimasu.
- Hai. Ganbatte kudasai!
The 6th position.
Well, eight people remain.
Let's continue.
I'll continue the announcement.
Number 9.
The next member selected is...
Wakatsuki Yumi.
Hai. Wakatsuki.
Wakatsuki Yumi, she's made it into
the Senbatsu Fukujin 8 for the first time.
This is just your first time entering Fukujin 8, right?
How do you feel now?
I always try to do well at all the work I receive...
In order to be a useful person in Nogizaka.
Hai. Omedetou gozaimasu.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
The 9th position.
Wakatsuki has entered Fukujin 8,
and there are now seven people left.
Okay, let's move on.
I'll continue the announcement.
Number 7.
The next member selected is...
Ikuta Erika.
Ikuta Erika, though in the second row, she re-enters the Fukujin 8.
How are you feeling now?
In accordance with my position,
I will work hard to my best ability.
This time there are many changes.
Despite the concerns within me...
I will work hard with all my body and soul.
Ganbatte, you've been chosen as Fukujin 8.
Arigatou gozaimasu. Hai.
- Please work hard.
The 6th position.
Six people left, now is the last in the second row.
I'll continue the announcement.
Number 8.
The last member in the second row is...
Ikoma Rina.
Ikoma Rina who has been a five-time center
since debut is in the second row this time.
Ikoma, how do you feel?
Actually, there is a feeling of joy.
But even as I say that, it seems that isn't a good thing.
Why?
(Being selected as center) until the 5th single was,
of course, really very heavy.
Hmm, as the center, yes?
Then in the 6th single, I was in a different place
for the first time. I felt free.
It was really fun.
Yes, but that's no excuse for not ranking higher, right?
Right, now I'm going to do everything with all my strength.
I see.
With that in mind, I'm not complaining too much about what's there.
But I'd rather be able to do something
with all my might and be happy in that position.
- You've matured, haven't you?
But I'd rather be able to do something
with all my might and be happy in that position.
- You've matured, haven't you?
You used to hide your face and cry, right?
Yes, I'm always troublesome.
No, this position is good for Ikoma
after what you've said, continue to grow and ganbatte.
Ganbarimasu.
- Hai.
The 8th position.
Well, the five people in the first row remain.
Let's continue.
Hai, now position 5 on the first row.
Finally arriving to the front row members, the first person is...
Matsumura Sayuri.
Matsumura Sayuri, she returns as a front row member,
continuing the previous trend.
This time, the formation has changed again.
I thought, "Will a new Nogizaka be formed?"
I'm looking forward to what Nogizaka will become.
You are also a figure who helped push Nogizaka forward.
No! No! No!
I'm always saying things that aren't necessary.
Things like that are also okay, aren't they? Ganbatte kudasai.
- Hai.
Okay, the 5th position.
Four people are left.
I'll continue the announcement.
Number 1.
The next member selected is...
Nishino Nanase.
Nishino.
Nishino Nanase, for the first time,
has gotten a position as a front row member.
As it's my first time standing in the front...
I'm worried.
It seems like there are a lot of people
who do not think I can rise from the bottom ranks.
But no one really thinks like that, right?
It makes me very frightened.
However, I am ureshii to be once again chosen as Fukujin 8.
Because of that, I want to do my best
in all these 7th single activities.
After this, the center position will finally be determined.
Well.
Three people are left.
I'll continue the announcement.
Position 4 of the first row.
The next selected member...
Hashimoto Nanami.
Hashimoto Nanami, just like Matsumura,
she returns as a front row member as before.
At the 6th single announcement, I was offered various jobs.
My feelings when possible were to try
to be more patient when struggling behind.
Then I understood that anything can have a positive impact...
For both yourself and the people around you.
And that makes me happy. Therefore,
from now on I think I will continue to work hard.
From now on various job offers will surely come. Ganbatte.
Hai. do your best.
- Ganbarimasu.
Hai, the 4th position.
Two people are left.
Okay, let's move on.
Position 2 in the first row.
The next selected member is...
Shiraishi Mai.
Shiraishi was elected to this position.
Shiraishi Mai who was previously trusted as center
for the first time is a front row member this time.
Oh, Shiraishi.
Though you have entered Fukujin 8...
That's true.
- Before, you had the center position.
Yes, for the first time I stood as center.
Many things happened to me.
Things that aren't shown also exist.
Being in the center position, I had to take on more responsibilities.
Although there are many things to think about...
Thanks to the support of everyone, I tried my best for the 6th single.
Until now, we've all grown.
Everyone wants to be who we are, and now with all our strength we have started to pass our target.
Because I was re-elected to the front.
I will put this result aside...
And work hard to do a good job alongside everyone.
Shiraishi is definitely...
Once you become a center, many things
must be done and other job offers appear.
You must have become the face of Nogizaka now.
So start working harder now. Ganbatte kudasai.
To the 2nd position.
In this 7th single...
The center is neither Ikoma nor Shiraishi.
After this, a surprising new center will be unveiled.
With this, it's time for the announcement of the new center!
There is one more person remaining, the center of the 7th single.
Please announce it.
Number 3.
The one chosen as the new center is...
Hori Miona.
From there?
Hori, please come here.
This is sugoi.
A member from the Kenkyuusei, yes?
She is the 7th single center.
How do you feel now?
I just entered as a member...
I also can't dance like the others...
Because I'm still Kenkyuusei...
Such an incredible path...
I never once suspected it.
You're surprised, aren't you?
Usually, you must feel something when you come here, right?
But since you were selected in the 7th single...
Ganbatte!
I will work hard with all my might.
Arigatou gozaimashita!
- Omedetou gozaimasu!
This is very surprising, isn't it?
This time, there is a message from management
regarding the Senbatsu announcement.
Well, allow me to read it.
To all members of Nogizaka46...
You must be surprised by this Senbatsu announcement.
Various feelings are mixed in here.
But we ask everyone to guide Hori Miona
the 2nd Gen center who is still very inexperienced.
For the brighter future of Nogizaka46...
Nogizaka46 Management.
It's true, you have to support each other
for the future of Nogizaka46.
And that's these 17 people, right?
The 7th single is really surprising, yes?
Why isn't Himura-san even present?
I think he'll be very surprised.
Therefore, with Himura's return next week...
We try to get closer to the new 7th single center, Hori Miona.
Then, we'll learn the warm feelings of the members
who have entered the Senbatsu for the first time.
Timer: Mukaichi-G  |  Translator: WA Mirakuru, KimKim  |  Typesetter: WA Mirakuru, NiL.  |  TLC & QC: WA Mirakuru, NiL  |  Encoder, Hardsubber, Uploader: NiL | IndoToEng: weeabookstore
So can Hori's charm be realized?!