In this week's Nogidoko, the member's families take a survey without them knowing!
Things only their families would know, the hidden charm of the members!
Or so it was supposed to be ..
The members tyranny behavior at home are exposed!
Translated by Jiaemi, Timed & Typeset by Michael Soares
For more subs visit www.Facebook.com/IkomaSubs | Brought to you by IkomaSubs
DON! Nogidoko has begun and we're your hosts Bananaman!
Today we have a lot of members!
Yes we do
Here is Nogizaka!
There they are, oh theres more!
Oh?
The undergirls are present too!
Today, the undergirls are present too
The 2nd Gen members are also present
2nd Gen observing
They look really refined and ladylike
They are really sitting properly, thank you all very much
Well then, Himura-san, like a parent watching over their child
Please do the title call in that way
Okay I got it
A secret survey by the families, "My child is actually OOOO"
What the?! UWAHHHH!!
This plan is evil!
Without the knowledge of the members, their families take a survey
Areas of a members that only their families know, to find out the members hidden charms
To determine the members future endeavors
After this recording, any complains you make to your families would automatically come here
EHHHHH?!
Complaints will be included in the next survey
That kind of system has already been in placed
We don't need this kind of system!
This is the system in place here
First survey question is this!
Family Members Survey
An area where my child is better than all of the other members
Why did you ask them?!
We haven't say what its about
We haven't even called out the names yet!
Wait till we call you
We haven't even called any of you yet
YOU ALL REACTED TOO FAST!
Please wait till we call your names!
First question! An area where my child is better than all of the other members
Lets go with the first person, here she is!
Nooo! Wait wait .. Nooo!
Ohhhh!
Hoshino's father
Yes
Hoshino Minami's father's answer to the question is this
Her voice is cute ❤
Cute voice!
Your father said that
He said that ~
Umm .. Hoshino, your father, while watching Nogidoko
Feels that your voice is the cutest among all members!!
Since you were born, did your father ever tell you that your voice was cute?
I don't really talk to him much but ..
Mmm .. Teehee ~
NOT BAD?
Her voice is cute
Cute voice right?
Why don't you talk more with your father?
Wouldn't it be embarrassing if I talk to him about this at home?
Its embarrassing
Yes it is
Its okay, just ask him if he thinks you have a cute voice
Yes thats it
EHHHHHHH?!
Its okay to talk about such things to your father
Ehh? I think I'll do that today
EHHHH?! Cute!!
Cute! Cute!!
Good!
Shall we move on to the next person? Here she is!
NOOOO! I didn't know about this for real!!
From Nakada's mother
What is her good points? Here is the answer!
The nape of her neck is beautiful ❤
Wooooo ~
Its true!
We want to see!
This isn't something worth talking about!
We want to see this right?
We want! We want!
Could you show it to us like this?
Wooooo ~
Its beautiful right?
Yes its beautiful!
This is good
There are no baby hair, its clean and smooth
And above all, its of the same beauty as me
Yes thats it! My mother just wants to praise herself!!
Casual Self-boasting.
When you went to a beauty salon, the staff there praised you for having nice skin
Thats good
Her forehead is also pretty and smooth
Your forehead is pretty too?
On a whole, shes has a face like a freshly peeled egg. That makes her very cute  ❤
Ahhhh! Woooo ~
Thats great
If you say such things I'll blush for real!
Why? Its good that you're praised
It don't want such praise
She said that you're pretty
Cute ~
Everyone stop saying that!
Cute~
This is great
Lets continue! Next is this person!
Inoue
Wonder what its about
Here it is!
By far the first!!
What is this about? What is this answer pertaining to?
What is she first in?
As to what she is by far the first in
We have asked your mother, according to her answer to the survey ..
Both her looks and her style is by far the first
OHHHHH!!
She is definitely meant to be an idol though it might just be a parent's bias but
I feel that she is the cutest among all Nogizaka members
You're happy right ~?
This is a good thing
Even if she doesn't eat, or if shes crying, or when shes not doing anything, shes still cute!
Please stop this for real!
Ohhh this is wonderful!
Why not? This is good!
Yeah!
She says that likes AKB48's Mayuyu and Shinoda Mariko
From my point of view, compared to them, Sayuri is by far cuter!!
I'm really sorry!!
Please stop it I'm begging you!
Not me, its your own mother's opinion
Its your own mother's opinion
Why not? Thats good to hear
I'm sorry, my mother is really DUMB ..
Your mother isn't stupid
Your mother isn't stupid!
Why did you say that?
I Inoue Sayuri, am her daughter that lives with her, even despite that
My mother purposely goes to convenience stores, to buy Nogizaka46 trading cards like what a fan would do
She also would purchase Nogizaka46 official goods
Thats good ain't it?
Shes kind
Is that sold in stores?
But I'm the real Inoue Sayuri!
Yeah, its sold in stores
Anyone can purchase it from 7-11
Wow!!
My junior spent around 50,000 Yen on the trading cards!
EHHH?! Who is this person?
Core Nogizaka fan
He really collects the trading cards
Who is this person?
Then he got obtained a foil card!
A FOIL CARD!
This is awesome!
We're so happy!
Thank you!
Everyone is doing that!
Its a given for a parent to do that!
But that junior of mine is Himetan-oshi
He was like .. Himetan's card isn't appearing!
Himetan Oshi
He really likes you a lot!
EHH ~
He really likes you for real
He got your card after buying so many cards
Ohh ~ thats good to hear!
And then he went "HER CARD FINALLY APPEARED ~!"
That makes you happy right?
Theres still more, here is the next person
This is still continuing ~
Kawago's mother
What did Kawago's mother say? Here is her answer!
She has good luck in lotteries
Why did she say this!
The topic seems to have been changed a bit
Kawago you have good luck in drawing lots?
Yes, I have very good luck at that
Kawago, your mother said that instead of saying you're cute or something similar
"The bottomline is that her lottery luck is good!"
Did you win something from the lottery before?
From what we heard from your mother, at a festival you won an oven
Right? Furthermore, on that same day, she participated in a janken competition and won more prizes
You have also won before in a magazine's contest
Yes
I was thinking of asking her to buy a lottery ticket for me this time
Yes, when my parents buy a lottery ticket, they told me to hold onto it because I have good luck
And I held onto the ticket even as I slept
To borrow her luck.
You did that seriously?!
Theres still more! We will move on to the next theme, here it is!
A member who has changed from when she just joined Nogizaka46
Ahh, I see
Your parents would be able to tell
Lets start off with the first person, who she is?
Don't worry you haven't changed
From your mother
Her taste buds became 1st class
Why did she say that?!
What is this about?
Your mother thinks that you all eat high class snacks or souvenirs frequently
You lost interest in the snacks at home, you don't even bother about them
And next point, this is amazing ..
Yes
Don't say anymore I don't want to hear it!
She can't stop when shes talking about Yakiniku
I didn't even talk about that!
How many grams is this meat's weight?
UWAHHHHH!!
I DIDN'T SAY THAT!!
This is definitely made up!
Your mother's survey answers certainly did come here
I really didn't say that! For real! For real!!
I'll definitely call my mother after this studio recording!
What you say to her would come back to us
It would loop one round and come back here
Opposite Effects.
I won't do it anymore!
Scaryyy!
If you complain to your mother, it would just ricochet back and the news would come to us
I won't do it!
Lets move on, the next member who has changed since she became an idol is this member!
Oh Nishino changed?
Here is the reply!
She now hates sunlight
What is this about?
What this about that you now dislike sunlight?
It sounds sad
You're afraid of getting sunburnt right?
"After she got in Nogizaka, she started to have a strong dislike for the sunlight"
"When the family travels in car, she will always sit at the rear seat"
Ahh! I see!
"She has completely become like an actress"
That .. I'm not sure about the way your mother phrased it
Because the children always love to sit in the front seat right?
Yes, I used to always sit in the front seat but
Because the sun's rays are really strong
Yeah it really shines through
The sun's rays shine onto my legs
Thats why I turned to sitting in the rear seat instead
But this is only for summer time
I think when winter comes I'll move back to sitting in the front seat
You'll move back infront?
Yes
Oh I see
Lets move on, this person is next up
EHHH?! MY SISTER?!
Sister?! Is this for real?!
Its from your sister
Yes, they are siblings, Saito Chiharu's sister's answers for the survey, here is it!
She has turned into a tyrant
This is weird!
Did you become a tyrant?
To get an idea of what you did, we have asked your sister and she said this
She eats the snacks I bought without asking me
Thats not true!
When I ask her about it, she tells me "It is mine!"
Again .. we had bought a pair of commuter tickets
You both had pairing commuter tickets
Chiharu you lost your commuter ticket
And then you pointed at your sister's ticket and told her "Thats mine right?"
This is amazing!
"After saying that, she snatches the ticket from me and uses it"
And then she broke it
You're such a tyrant, at the end you even broke it!
"My sister is such a tyrant at home"
Thats not true!
So you treat her stuff as your own, and whats yours is yours. You're a tyrant
Wait a moment! Because I lost it, I thought I would borrow it, and told her I'll borrow it before doing so
Like I said, thats being a tyrant
Tyrant Logic
You're scary!
You returned it to her broken right?
Umm, before I realized .. its the stretchable type, and before I realized, it snapped
So I was like "Ahh Sorry" and returned it to her
Tyrant's Modus Operandi
Thats bad! You shouldn't do it!
Thats cruel of you!
So you would tell her "Theres a concert so lets go!!" right?
Forced Recital?
Do you do that?!
You have definitely said this before!
I don't say such things!
Next up is this person!
Manatsu-senpai!
Manatsu-san!
EHHH?!
Manatsu-san, its from your mother, what is it about, here!
You bully your mother
What is this about? You bully your mother?
You shouldn't do that!
I won't do that!
You dont?
You sure?
We live in harmony together
She pretends she herself is tired, and asks me to massage her shoulders
UWAHHHH!!
You ask her to massage your shoulders?
No way I would do such a thing
Really?
Lets ask your mother to confirm!
Hello ~ ?
EHHHHHHH?!
Right after this, unexpectedly Akimoto's mother reveals a huge scoop!!
You're Akimoto's mother right?
Thats right, thanks for always taking care of her
HUH?! HUHHHH?!
Hello, thanks for treating us well, we're Bananaman
Manattan~
What is she doing?!
Do you frequently watch Nogidoko?
Yes, I always watch Nogidoko
Thank you very much!
Right now, we're talking about her asking you to massage her shoulders
She said she did not ask you to massage her shoulders before, what is your take on this?
She always tells me "I'm the only one tired, would you massage my shoulders?"
EHH?! She said that?
Yes she frequently says this
Manatsu-san, this is your mother's side of the story
Why did the phone call even connect!?
I'm First Mentality?
You're concerned about that instead?
Thats where I'm concerned about!
How long do you massage her shoulders for?
I massage her shoulders for at least 10 mins
Wait a minute, you're kidding me right?
But after that, she would massage your shoulders in return right?
Nope, when I ask her to massage my shoulders, she would say "I'm tired so theres no way I'll massage your shoulders"
This is cruel!
Wait a moment, that shouldn't be how things go
But if your cute daughter asks you to massage her shoulders you would do it right?
Yes, she always treats me like a servant
Ararara, such a poor thing
I didn't do such a thing!
What do you think of Akimoto's recent activities, the waterfall, skydiving and going to scary places
I think that she has really become an idol but I didn't expect her to be compared to Degawa Tetsuro
Thats right
I didn't expect that so I'm got a little surprised
Currently, Akimoto is close to becoming like Degawa-san
Thats not true!
Next Topic
Member's unrevealed special talents that would definitely be received well?
Special talents which has not been demonstrated on TV yet, why didn't you demonstrate it?
Shall we begin? First up is this person!
Oh! Your older brother!
Itou your older brother submitted this, here it is!
Back flip and cartwheel
Thats amazing!
You have did it before in live performances but you have yet to show it on TV
No I didn't
You should do it, spin more!
To Itou's brother, she has never spun around so much on TV before
He must be watching today and thinking "Why isn't she spinning?"
Thats not it, but I didn't know about this talent of yours
Oh I see ..
Now then, please show us your backflip and cartwheel
The special talent that your brother said that you should demonstrate more often right?
Itou Nene, cartwheel followed by a backflip
If you would, please begin!
WAHHH! COOL!!
You did it!
Cool!
And heave ho!
You did it, you're amazing!
Your form was beautiful, you should do it more often
Amazing, Takayama why don't you try this too?
Catastrophe Premonition.
Takayama-san
Lets move on! Next is this person!
Thank you to Nakada's mother for cooperating with us
What what what?
What kind of special talent does she have? Here it is!
A Waist-Rhythmic Dance
What does it mean? Theres something to it right?
Its a type of exercise right~?
Erm, this is ..
Every night, she would do this dance while brushing her teeth
What is that?!
We want to see you demonstrate this~
Is there a toothbrush?
The demonstration of Nakada mother's favorite, the Waist-Rhythmic Dance!
Please do it as you usually do
We do not know what is it about
Now then, please demonstrate your Waist-Rhythmic Dance
If you would begin!
Whats wrong? Nakada were you like this all along?
Please wait a minute! This is really ..
Do you do this at home?
Yes I do this at home
What is the purpose of this?
Because I'm not moving my neck so I move my waist
Everyone lets follow her and do it too!
How do you do this?
This is gonna be interesting!
You don't move your upper body
Do you spread your legs to shoulder width?
Spread it slightly beyond shoulder width
Towards the right
Oh, bend down slightly
Bend down a little and towards the left
Right~
Left~
And just rotate around
Nakada could you turn around to show the members?
Nakada can you walk while doing this?
When I try to walk its like this
Right after this, a mass reveal makes all members blush!!
Next theme is this!
Areas in which lacks in being an idol, areas for improvement
For this segment, we would stream through all members at a go
All at a go right?
And after that we would focus on the interesting ones
What what what what~?
It would stream through fast okay
With that said, lets proceed to "Areas which a member lacks in being an idol, areas for improvement"
A poor speaker
Oh I see
Wada
Areas for change
Unladylike
Eh? Shes ladylike~
She doesn't want to be a girl?
Perseverance & Desires
Perserverance
Desires? What kind of?
She lacks in her desires
Itou Nene
Self Confidence
Ahhhh, you lack confidence
Fukagawa
Confidence & Aura
Aura?
AURA?!
Confidence and aura
Kawamura
She can't act cutesy
She cant act cutesy
Ahhh .. so I see
She can't act cutesy
Such things are okay~
Wakatsuki
Aura
Aura!!
Saying she lacks aura is kind of strict
She is exuding a lot of aura!
Kawago
Lack of idol awareness
Is that true?
Its because she sometimes part her legs
Shiraishi
Decide on character portrayed
Whats that about
Your character is already quite awesome
Eh? Me? What what?
Nagashima
No sex appeal
What the hell?! You're kidding me right?
Matsumura
Singing skills
This answer pierced through you!
This answer is interesting!
Noujou!
Girlish gestures
Ahhhhh!
What is that for!?
Hashimoto!
Too many to answer!
Too many areas of improvement to answer
You were super surprised at this right?
Yeahs, this was unexpected
Ichiki
She can't act cutesy
Ahh, because you're too serious
Takayama
Rival mindset
Oh I see ..
Saito Asuka
An idol's naturalness
An idol's .. naturalness?!
Naturalness?!
She has that naturalness right?
She has plenty of it!
Manatsu-san
Hunched posture
No! You're fine from the front view!
It might not be okay if you're filmed from sideways
Lacks her own view
Eh~ I don't get the meaning of this, what is this about?
After hearing that, you would go eh too
Nishino
Lack of self confidence
Expression when filmed by the camera
Stop that seriously!
Right now you're showing that!
Awareness as an idol
You lack awareness as an idol
I have awareness as an idol! I do! I do!
Something which she needs to find in order to make fans feel happy
Too long! I don't understand what is being said!
Ikoma!
Using 'uchi' to address herself
Ahh .. I see
I've got found out!
Yamato!
Self-conciousness
Self-consciousness! There seem to be a lot of self-consciousness as answers!
Ikuta
Off guard face
You show an off guard face, do you?
Looks & Style & Plain clothes fashion sense
Nakamoto
Thats not true!
That isn't it!
What is this about?
Its saying you need improvement on the whole!
Itou Marika
Singing technique &
Self-confidence & MC Skills
Singing technique, self confidence ..
MC SKILLS?!
Every area is lacking
Self-improvement is a never ending journey
Higuchi
Every area is lacking, self-improvement is a never ending journey
So cool!
So strict!
Nakada!
Visual from behind character
What the hell does she mean by that?!
Suppress your appetite &
Honor promise to your sister
To suppress your appetite and honor your promise to your sister
Ahh! Your sister answered!
Attitude of self before others
Your attitude of self before others .. I see
Hoshino!
Weight management
Hey! You shouldn't say that!
Thats weight, not height!
With that we conclude this segment!
I don't get the meaning of saying that!
Because its your own families that answered the questions, some of the answers might be quite strict
Thats right~
Hoshino!
I really don't get the meaning why my mother said that!
You don't get the meaning of that?
The answer, weight management came up
My mother's height is 148cm, so her weight is very light
My sister also has around the same height and weight as my parents
Thats why, they are always gossiping about my weight
They are worried about you
They are not gossiping about you!
For Wada, the answer was that you're unladylike
Eh? Shes feminine and acts like a girl
The members think that way of you right?
But at home you're more "released" and you just become more tomboy-ish right?
Yes, I run around the house barefoot, thats perhaps what my parents are talking about
Eh? Naked?
Barefooted!
Where do you run barefooted?
Outside
EHHHHH?!
Wild child.
I only do it in my hometown!
No thats not it! Even if its in your own hometown ..
Local barefoot life?
I would still understand if you were a small kid
Its like at our front porch
What do you do there?
We like to have relays there
You all have relays there?!
Barefoot relay family?
Thats cute!
This session is far from over!!