Survey Festival!
Tonight, we will be releasing surveys for this show that have piled up!
This is how she answered this question...
We will be presenting interesting answers to scrapped surveys and some unscrapped ones as well!
Also, for some reason, the studio roars in laughter at the presentation of that person's new performance art!
\hpoji-peace.tumblr.com\h
m 0 0 b -2 0 -4 0 -6 0 b -7 0 -8 0 -8 -2 b -8 -2 -8 -2 -8 -2 b -8 -3 -8 -4 -6 -4 b -4 -4 -2 -4 0 -4 b 2 -4 4 -4 6 -4 b 6 -5 6 -7 6 -8 b 6 -8 6 -8 6 -8 b 7 -10 9 -10 10 -9 b 10 -7 10 -7 10 -6 b 12 -4 13 -3 13 -2 b 13 6 13 4 13 7 b 12 8 10 8 8 8 b 7 8 6 8 5 8 b 4 8 3 8 1 7 b 0 5 0 3 0 2
DON!
And Nogizakatte Doko has started. We're your hosts, Bananaman. Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu.
And here are Nogizaka-chan!
Let's go!
Ready, go.
Gao~
Alright, gao~
Alright then. What will we be doing today with so many of the members here?
Himura-san. Do it like a national census official.
A national census official?
Please do the announcement.
Alright.
Well then, they weren't used, so to clear our inventory we've gathered them to present them.
Nogizaka Survey Festival!
Considered indispensable in creating this program: the pre-surveys.
There are interesting answers that are collected and presented as part of an episode's activity.
Unfortunately, there are many that have been scrapped as well.
And so this time, we've selected interesting ones from the scrapped survey answers and we'll discuss them!
First. From a survey whose deadline was on March 28, 2013...
That's quite some time back!
This is from around spring this year!
Spring!
So from that survey, it's this.
Yes. What do you think is your own charm point?
So there was something like this.
It's what YOU think YOUR charm point is.
This is it.
Normally, when it's decided that this is what we'll do, after receiving the surveys...
Most of the time, staff will pick interesting people and you'll have a casual meeting about how it will be.
But today, you haven't done that, right?
We haven't.
So, if you get picked and we talk here...
and after hearing the conversation it's decided that it's boring after all, that part will be cut out.
Merciless editing.
Do your best.
This is my only chance!
I don't have any chance other than this, really!
You've said it, this is a good chance to appear for unders, right?
The only. Yes!
By the way, Nagashima. What do you think is your charm point?
My smile...
If you say it now, then it's not going to be used there.
So Nagashima is out for this survey, huh.
I'm sure I'm not there at all!
You just got told right now that there aren't any more of your survey answers here.
End of appearance for today?
Alright. Then let's move on. First is what you think is your own charm point.
First is Akimoto.
This is something you said yourself.
I have no idea what I said.
Right. It's this.
Alright. "My approachable appearance"
No way.
This is embarrassing!
Your appearance?
Your entirety?
Do you think you're approachable?
I do.
She said it.
When do you think this?
When shy-looking girls talk to me...
I think "Ah, I really do look approachable..."
I see.
So you think like everyone's talking to you?
Is there anyone here who thinks she won't lose in terms of being approachable?
Step forward! Step forward!
So Saito Yuri too?
Yes.
Is that so?
I'm really. Really. I'm actually the opposite and I never get shy around people.
So 100% for sure I can get along with anyone I've just met.
That's quite clever.
When I first talked to everyone in Nogizaka when the group was just formed...
Yuttan wasn't very...
Eh?
Lie episode?
Ah so she was hard to approach?
Yes.
Like...
So Yuttan is lying?
Yuttan isn't lying!
I didn't think she looked very approachable...
Why?
She looked quite headstrong?
Just wait.
Just after it was said that you don't get many chances like this...
It's the worst when you get told something awful, huh?
Let's move on.
Matsumura.
Do you remember this?
I don't remember at all.
I see. Matsumura's answer to this question is this.
My chest as seen from the top when I'm wearing a bra.
Eh!!
Why... I wonder why this wasn't picked?
Eh, this... Really... Well, we wear bras right.
Then I peek inside my clothes from the top like this.
And my chest as seen from the top like that is really cute.
Cute?
So it's cute.
I see.
This is quite an answer, isn't it?
It's true. Shiraishi Mai-chan also always says it's cute.
Eh, so you show her? You said it was cute?
I did.
So because she said it, you wrote this?
But she usually says so.
Yes. I kind of really... I kind of really like looking at myself from the top like this.
So, usually, I...
No, no. It's not like that...
What's that like?
Eh, how do I say this...
But Sayurin, you're quite flat, aren't you?
No!!
Sayurin is cute because she's flat.
Eh, so you're flat? This seems like something that someone more endowed would say though.
Actually, I really am just a tad bit small...
It's not a tad bit.
Is there anyone here who would say they won't lose in terms of chest size?
Ah, as expected, it's difficult to assert yourself with this topic.
Then maybe I should assert myself first.
No need.
It's true. It's true though.
So, how do we... Can we have camera 2 take a peek?
Since we're already here...
No, no, that's not allowed.
No, no.
Then, shall we continue? Next is Hashimoto.
Hashimoto thinks this is her own charm point... Here.
I can do three different voices depending on what work I'm doing.
Amazing.
That's true!
What is this? So when you say work, I guess there's... Variety.
And well, there's when you're singing songs, and aside from that I guess your actress voice?
No, no.
Well, there's three...
Tell us the three types.
One is for when I appear on TV shows like this.
Another is for handshakes.
That's different?
For handshakes.
And the next is for narration? For voice-only jobs.
Actress?
Voice only? Like when you need to act with your voice?
No, no.
So, then, your voice right now is your TV voice.
Yes.
Right? So when you're doing handshakes, it's different?
Fans actually say this a lot to me...
They tell me that my voice is actually higher when they talk to me personally.
Do you do that consciously? Like you tell yourself I'm going with my handshake voice now?
It's probably more unconsciously...
Ah, so you do it unconsciously.
But well, we have to talk to a lot of people for a long time then.
Kazumin also says this. In order not to hurt our throats, we make our voice a little higher, it's not falsetto, but...
Eh? Can you do it? Like "Hello." Hello.
Wait, it's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing.
Hello.
We're not asking you.
You're always so cute.
Do you really think that?
Ah, it's high!
Okay do your usual voice. Usual voice.
Hello.
Ah, it's lower.
Wow.
You're always so cute.
Ah, thank you very much.
So for handshakes... Hello.
Hello.
You're always so cute.
You're just flattering me.
Cute~
So for narration?
When I do narrations, I try to make my voice higher in a good way.
So it's even higher?
How was it with narrations you've done in the past?
Can you do something like
"This is something something" for us?
Yes.
Ready, start.
Coming out of the bamboo thicket, what comes into view is, yes, Kinkaku-ji.
Oh, sounds good.
Ah, I see.
Coming out of the bamboo thicket...
He's, he's making fun of you.
Hashimoto, you're being made fun of.
It didn't sound like that, did it?
It's like in Spirited Away.
Coming out of the bamboo thicket.
Wait, they sound alike? It's similar?
Similar?
It's similar!
So that's how you do it.
Is there anyone else here who do things differently for different situations?
Hatanaka.
Eh?
Completely unprepared.
You... Just now, you absolutely thought you won't be called, didn't you?
You've done it.
So do you have anything, Hatanaka?
No... I really don't do anything different. Like, for handshakes too...
Like, I do it really normally. Just like talking to people.
We're all people.
No, no, everyone... Everyone's like that.
Hm? I mean, is there anyone here who talks like they're not talking to people?
Next survey question is...
What is another member's strange habit that you find difficult to understand?
Just to inform you...
This is... The answers for this ended up focusing on a certain member. Then let us look at the next answers.
First is Hashimoto. Here.
Iku-chan.
When she gets stressed she hugs and attaches to you with great strength.
Next, Matsumura.
Alright. Iku-chan.
When she catches your leg, it's the end. She won't let go no matter what.
Do you remember these?
I do. This is still true now.
Even now.
So she does that. How strong...?
How strong? Can you...
What, what, what?
So you don't let go like this?
Yes. I keep holding on.
So if you try breaking free, you can't?
I can't. Ow, ow!
Hashimoto, break free and run!
Wait, wait.
Wow, Ikuta's...
What? Ikuta Tightening? That's amazing.
What's with that? Ikuta Tightening.
Yes, I end up doing this.
What is this? So you do it when you're stressed?
Like when I'm irritated...
Venting stress?
So when you're irritated and there's someone there, you just go for her?
Yes, I usually just do it to whoever's in front of me then.
But lately, Iku-chan has a new... should I call it a new trick?
So you catch them.
Trick?
Yes, it's new... She's into singing songs at a different pitch and all.
She's changed!
What is that?
Like she harmonizes.
Yes, she's kind of addicted now to harmonizing. Like for Girl's Rule...
Can you... Can you do it for us?
Like when there's someone singing at the right key, I forcibly join in and harmonize my way.
Ah, nice. That sounds fun.
Can someone sing?
Maiyan~
Maiyan.
Ok.
Amazing, amazing, amazing.
Go, go.
Shiraishi, Shiraishi, can you do it?
Can you? Try it again, you might've lost the key.
Wait, wait.
We can't hear Shiraishi.
Um... What is this? What, what is this?
Scary, scary, scary. Wait just a minute.
Shiraishi can't be heard anymore.
Amazing!
No, I...
Fun.
Were there two singing?
I guess we can't tell unless you're lined up and closer to each other.
Shiraishi, if you don't sing more strongly you'll get drowned out and we can't hear you.
Find... Find your key.
Find your key.
Super passionate singing!
Her face!
Who's the main one here?
Wait, wait...
What was that?
So you're into that lately.
Yes, I usually do it when we're in the bus and all.
Really fun.
So you forcefully harmonize and make your own arrangement?
Yes, forcefully in a way that makes me feel good.
Can't you do that on your own even without someone else singing?
But... Well, singing together feels more like an ensemble.
Can you do a solo version?
Girl's Rule, solo version.
Ahh...
Can you do solo harmony?
I can...
Like a rearrangement.
Yes.
Find your key.
Find your key. Alright?
Sing strong alright?
Ready, go.
Splendid!
Amazing!
That was some amazing harmony!
Nice.
You did a perfect harmony there.
Really good.
So you can harmonize with anything?
For example, like, Donguri Korokoro (Rolling Acorn)?
So you can go along with anything?
I'm good with anything.
Can you harmonize even with Himura-san singing?
I can totally do that.
Then Himura-san, will you?
Then I...
What should I sing?
Anything is fine, really.
Then let's go with Donguri Korokoro.
Okay.
So what's the first note?
Himura-san, acorn... Is acorn alright, Himura-san?
Can you do it?
Okay.
Then, Donguri Korokoro. Please.
Wait, just wait!
What was that? Wait a minute!
Completely satisfied.
No, no, wait. No, no.
At the end you just went ru~ ru~ didn't you?
Thank you, thank you.
No, wait. What are you doing?
What are you doing, really?
Next is a selection from a survey whose deadline was on September 29, 2013.
It had a question like this. Here.
What is a question you find difficult to ask another member
but would like to ask if you can do so anonymously?
Anonymously, huh.
Yes.
As such, we won't reveal who wrote it since it's supposed to be anonymous.
Who wrote it won't be revealed, only the contents will be shared.
I see.
Who does she want to ask? It's Hoshino.
She wants to ask her this.
To be blunt, how many kilos do you weigh?
By the way, I was 53 kilos at my peak.
But you lost weight, didn't you, Hoshino?
Yes, I did. Yeah, Yeah, Yeah. I lost weight!
How many kilos did you lose?
Around 2.5 to 3...
Oh, 2.5 to 3... That's significant, isn't it?
Yesterday, she ate a bento her mom made her for lunch.
Lately she's been bringing her own bento, right?
Yes, like counting calories...
So your mom calculates the calories in it?
My mama said that if I was going to do it anyway, I might as well include lunch.
Ehhh? That's amazing.
Nice.
That's wonderful.
This... So 53 kilos...
Takayama... Is this on the heavy side?
I think it is. Um...
Eh? So Takayama, what's your weight right now?
Well... From my peak... Um...
So how heavy were you at your peak?
At my peak... At my peak I was 53 kilos.
Huh?
Wait, exactly the same?!
There was no point in making this anonymous~
There's no point making this anonymous.
Eh, was it you who wrote this?
Yes, it was!
Confession of the criminal.
Oh my. So this was you, Takayama?
Then let's go to the next one.
The next one is for Sakurai.
Alright, here.
When we meet outside like at train stations and surely you should've seen me, why do you just keep walking as if I were a stranger?
Maybe you don't want to be disturbed in your private time?
This... What is this?
Is there anyone here who gets this?
Scary...!
She listens to music while walking, so, she's really, like...
Ah, I see.
Like she's in her own world. I thought of saying hi but decided not to.
Ah, so that's how it is.
I see.
So you're listening to music and you don't notice much around?
I don't look at people's faces much outside.
So most of the time you're listening to music?
I'm usually fiddling with my phone while walking.
I see.
Eh, Noujou, you've experienced this too?
Yes... I have.
Where?
Where did you meet?
Like...
At stations...
Huh? Station?
Exactly the same again.
No way!
So at stations?
Eh, was this you?
Y... Yes.
Crime solved.
There's no point!
Is that so?
So it's not like you were ignoring her, right, Sakurai?
It's best if you go and tap me like boink boink.
She just said boink boink.
Hey, who you calling a pig?
You're overly self-conscious.
No, no. You're too sensitive.
You're too sensitive.
Then let's do one more.
This one is for Kawago. Here.
Okay.
You like girls for real, don't you?
Scary, scary, scary!
Ah, there it is.
So this was asked anonymously...
That means there's someone here who wants to confirm whether you really, for real, like girls.
Everyone's scary.
Like Fukagawa.
You're always saying you like her.
Well, it's true, isn't it?
Um... Just wait. When a cute girl comes, like, to handshakes, I do get happy and all, but...
It's like I like collecting pictures of cute girls...
You collect them?
It's amazing. Like the whole time, like on the train, when we sit together, like the whole entire time...
She's keeps going "This girl is cute, isn't she?" "I think she's cute too."
The whole time she shows me pictures of cute girls.
Isn't that kind of a bit overboard?
Doesn't that count?
No, no, no.
Eh, but that's like...
That's like if Himura-san was collecting pictures of cute boys.
Dirty old guy.
Yes.
What now?
It's the same as that.
That's true. What do you think now?
Scary.
What do you mean scary?
It's like if we were commuting together he'll go "This boy's cute, right?"
"Cute, right?"
But, that's the same, right?
That's the same thing as earlier.
So there's probably some romance going on between members, huh?
No, no, no.
Then, what was that?
But, there are worries that some romance will bloom.
I see.
But I... There's...
This will probably sound kind of creepy, but there's something I've always wanted to ask everyone just once.
Oh, okay, okay.
If it's alright, I'd like to have this portion of my face mosaic-blurred.
Is there a point?
Well, well. Alright, we'll do that as a special favor.
Her voice as well?
If... If everyone here had a chance to peek into a bath, would you peek into the men's or the women's bath?
Women... We're all women here, right?
But if we could peek into a bath, I'm sure everyone here would say they would peek into the women's bath.
Yes, women's.
Why?
No way. I mean if Himura-san had to pick between the women's and men's-
Stop bringing me up!
Don't do that!
I'll be a pervert no matter which I pick!
Whether I peek into the women's or the men's bath, I'll be a pervert!
I just, well, we're our own group here.
We're a group here so just to answer that question too. For me I'd definitely peek into the women's.
Just wondered which Himura-san would pick.
This question is bad, it's bad for men. Like if I say I'd peek into the women's bath, that sounds bad, right?
Coming up. Ikuta and Inoue's hilarious stories.
Next is a survey whose deadline was on August 13, 2013.
From the Nogizaka Hilarious Stories survey.
So there was a Nogizaka Hilarious Stories survey?
So there was something like that.
There was. Right.
The people who answered this question said they have a hilarious story, a really funny one.
Ikuta.
Uwa, I knew it.
Ikuta, do you remember this? You wrote it.
Do you?
I do...
Then can you share this story?
Oh nice.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu. Go ahead.
Wait...
Um... This is...
Um, so you're getting up?
Super willing?
While walking?
So you'll do it in front?
Ah yes, just here.
This is a dream I had when I was in 4th grade.
A dream?
A dream.
Yes, a dream. That's right.
Neko Hiroshi-san appeared in that dream.
Neko Hiroshi?
So Neko Hiroshi-san was there, and
he told me, "Erika-chan, I have a new gag."
Eh?
That's what he said. Then he asked whether I could take a look at it and he showed it to me.
And that gag was like this...
Neko Hiroshi! Neko Hiroshi! And turn!
Come on~
No wonder it was a scrapped gag.
Nee~
Ah, the end?
Eh, wait a minute, was that the end of the story?
Yes.
Really, geez, this sucks...
So cute!
No, no, it wasn't so bad.
It was good.
Next is Inoue Sayuri's hilarious story.
Inoue's hilarious story.
So first, we have my mother.
And my mother and her older sister are siblings, and... their voices are really similar.
So people always mistake them for each other.
And one day, my grandma was supposed to go out with like my uncle and everyone from that older sister's house.
We have a bad feeling about this...
And when she tried calling...
Huh? That's not right... Wait... The older sister's mother... Mother...
My mom and her older sister's voice are really similar, and...
Since continuing to listen here would be a waste of time, we'll just skip it.
So, the older sister
Stop!
Alright, that's enough. Thank you. Please go back now.
Coming up. We'll be presenting the music video of their new single, "Tsuki no Ookisa."
The coupling track from their 7th single, please enjoy the music video of "Tsuki no Ookisa".
The Magnitude of the Moon
Lyrics / Akimoto Yasushi
MusicArrangement / Furukawa Takahiro
The Magnitude of the Moon
Credits
Cast
For some reason, the moon tonight is one size bigger
Ikoma Rina
Self-proclaimed Strongest Swordswoman
And it's shining more brightly than usual
Wakatsuki Yumi
Aloof Genius Swordswoman
I hunch my back and trudge back home
My allies are always there
Hashimoto Nanami
Beautiful Swordswoman
If only I could just cry without saying anything
Sakurai Reika
Swordsmistress
Town Girls
Nakamoto Himeka, Akimoto Manatsu,
Saito Asuka, Takayama Kazumi
And when my tears dry, it'll be all over
Stronger, I must become stronger
Sadness is one step towards standing on my own
Ninja
Eto Misa, Ito Marika
Fukagawa Mai, Kawago Hina
How many times do I have to get hurt to forget the pain?
Ikuta Erika
Princess
Matsumura Sayuri
The Princess's Attendant
When I shed red blood, I'm reminded of life
Nishino Nanase
Best Dancer in Town
As I collapse spread-eagled on the road
Shiraishi Mai
Strongest EnemyEvil Swordswoman
I look up at the sky and think
True solitude lies with those who have no past
Hori Miona
Mysterious
Beautiful Girl
Those who know nothing but the present
Next. Nogizaka makes an appearance at Waseda Festival!
Nogizaka46's first ever Nippon Budokan concert. Ticket preorders are currently open!
For details, please check the official website!
And at the match between Vissel Kobe and Kyoto Sanga FC that was held days ago,
for the "Rakuten Group Day" event,
Saito Yuri, Noujo, and Kawamura took on the challenge of doing the opening kick.
They splendidly made a goal and brought excitement onto the pitch!
Nogizaka also appeared at the Waseda Festival.
The members make an appearance in two events this day.
They brought excitement to the place along with the students. Both events were a big success!
Next week is the 7th single campaign. What will it be?