m 0 0 l 0 27 l 2 27 l 2 0 l 0 0 m 2 0 l -4 0 l -4 6 l 16 6 l 16 4 l -2 4 l -2 2 l 0 2 m 2 2 m 16 0 l 16 27 l 18 27 l 18 -1 l 16 -1 m 22 0 l 22 0 l 24 0 l 24 11 l 19 11 l 19 9 l 22 9 l 22 2 l 15 2 l 15 0 m 6 18 l 6 12 l 12 12 l 12 14 l 8 14 l 8 18 l 6 18 m 12 18 l 12 20 l 6 20 l 6 18 l 10 18 l 10 14 l 12 14 l 12 18 m 5 7 l 8 9 l 7 10 l 4 8 l 5 7 m 10 9 l 10 9 l 13 7 l 14 8 l 11 10 l 10 9 m 3 24 b 3 24 3 23 3 23 b 7 21 11 21 15 23 b 15 23 15 25 15 25 b 11 23 7 23 3 25
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
weeabookstore.tumblr.com
Autumn Art Inspiration.
Recommend Movies with 4 Illustrations.
- Isn't that great?
- Really?
However, some presentations instead
create a disturbance!
Takayama's is ugly!
Don't say it like that!
Does this girl exceed Spielberg's work?
Unexpectedly her new character
makes everyone surprised!!!
Nogizakatte, Doko?
Original Indonesian subtitle by Mastoppu.blogspot.co.id
English translation by weeabookstore
It's a turtle coming out of its shell.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Let's recommend a movie with 4 illustrations!
Storm of fury because of odd characters and unclear presentation
It's not!!!
So you don't show everything, but
you can draw Ten-chan there.
- No!
- It's better you not.
So you say, "Let's change the style"...
...with your drawing level
like that?
Sugoi!
DON!
BANANAMAN
Shitara Osamu
Nogizakatte, Doko has begun,
I'm your MC, Shitara Osamu from Bananaman, and...
GUEST
Shimada Shuhei
Hello, Shimada Shuhei, the hand-reader!
Yoroshiku Onegaishimasu.
Because of asthma, Himura-san
cannot be present today.
Because of asthma, Himura is absent from recording
Instead, Shimada Shihei will become a guest star
Ah, sadly...
He's too noisy. He can't keep quiet.
Therefore, today there is our old friend...
- ...Shimada Shuhei will appear.
- Thank you very much.
- Onegaishimasu.
- It's sudden, so please help me.
And here they are, Nogizaka-chan!
Yay!
- Hmm... Pa!
- Autumn Art Inspiration.
Autumn art inspiration, good word choice.
All right, Shimada-san,
for our segment today...
...try to announce in the Osugi-san style
from Osugi & Piko.
[Osugi & Piko = twin celebs and
famous Japanese film critics.]
Autumn Art Inspiration,
Let's recommend a movie!
Sugoi, he can do it!
Yay!!!
- Nostalgic.
- You can do it too.
Shitara-san, my armpits are constantly sweating.
Minimum experience in this position.
When it comes to Autumn Art Inspiration,
many things come to mind. Film is one of them.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
With a theme appreciating film masterpieces, members will make
a presentation to encourage everyone to watch
while explaining the movie
- You guys have all watched the movie
that you've selected, haven't you?    - Yes.
Then, with just this theme...
...when we hear their explanations,
we'll be able to know more, and will want to watch.
Therefore, when you maybe
come to have work similar to this...
...you can describe
which parts to look out for.
This could be your talent.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Members will make their recommendation of the films
within 30 seconds with 4 drawings of their own illustration
that will show which scenes are important.
They will recommend a movie they've
already watched with 4 illustrated images.
Of course, they drew which
scenes were important in the movie.
For the best work, there is also the best prize!
Then, for the best presenter...
Shimada will read your palm.
Best Prize
Hands-on readings and luck predictions from Shimada Shohei
Thoroughly read.
- Sugoi!
- I want that too!
Recommend The Best Movies
With 4 Picture Illustrations!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Takayama Kazumi
The first film will be presented by Takayama.
First, what movie have you watched?
"Lupin III...
...The Castle of Cagliostro".
- Isn't that a great movie?
- Yes.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
"Lupin III : The Castle of Cagliostro" released in 1979
The film debuted under director Miyazaki Hayao, who
announced his retirement a few days ago...
...the story of Clarisse, a princess
living in a small country...
...and within that country there is a
big conspiracy to seize power.
Lupin stops the plan...
...and ultimately saves Clarisse.
Then at then end, there's an important dialogue in the film...
On the contrary, he manages to steal
something you did not expect...
...your heart.
- Okay, are you ready?
- Yes, I'm ready.
The mic can catch your voice,
so don't get so close.
Please move to the middle.
- She got close to that!
- Sugoi.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Takayama
Kazumi
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film title
"Lupin III : The Castle of Cagliostro"
Ready? 30 seconds starting from...
...now!
Lupin accepted the princess's ring.
The princess left the ring for him.
Because the ring is important
and he wants to return it.
Lupin and this beard man...
Jigen* = beard man.
[Daisuke Jigen, Lupin's criminal partner.]
...go there.
And they tried hard...
And Goemon* also came to help.
[Ishikawa Goemon XIII = swordsman, Lupin's partner.]
There are a lot of interesting things going on.
Fujiko-san* also came to help.
[Mine Fujiko = thief and rival to Lupin.]
Then, Lupin and his friends,
try to defeat the bad guy...
TIME'S UP!
Wait! Just a little more.
Her picture...
- ...is pretty good, yes.
- The picture is good!
But the whole 4 pictures are only
of characters in Lupin, it's little bit...
Everything is just character introduction.
Wait... but, after all...
This Fujiko-san, unexpectedly...
- What did he bring with him?
Roasted Onigiri?
Is he eating?
Sugoi! It's similar!
It's not! It's not!
He was carrying pistols and bombs.
That's a grenade, isn't it?
He had a grenade in his hands.
If, The Castle of Cagliostro is...
- ...there's a woman named Clarisse, right?
- Yes, the princess.
And in the last scene, when Zenigata...
...is doing something, that's the climax.
If only there were 6 pictures
I could draw him and Clarisse...
...but, since there are only 4 images...
Then why did you make
one picture per person?
Useless protests.
That's quite a lot, huh?
Maybe you should put
Lupin in each picture.
Why does that tall Doraemon even appear?
Lupiemon?
The one on the right, yes?
It's not! That's not him!
This is a castle! A castle!
That's not what I'm talking about!
If I can't distinguish
a castle and Doraemon...
It's the most different thing today.
Then how? How about this?
Recommend The Best Movies
With 4 Picture Illustrations!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Fukagawa Mai
Fukagawa will also recommend
The Castle of Cagliostro.
She is good at drawing.
This is clear!
- This is obvoiously going to be good.
- Very good.
Try showing yours Takayama...
Ugly!
At the top right corner there's an oval Doraemon.
He's here too!
That's true, there is.
Lupin, It's Lupin!
From this picture, the levels are clearly different.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Takayama's work
Fukagawa's work
The letter "N" in Lupin...
...has a bullet in it, yes.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
"Lupin III : The Castle of Cagliostro"
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Fukagawa Mai
Okay, we're starting. Ready...
...Start!!!
First, there's a fierce battle.
Their story to save
Clarisse begins.
They were in an action-packed car chase.
And Lupin managed to find
Clarisse being locked up.
With a magic trick, Lupin makes
a frightened Clarisse smile again.
However, a critical situation arises...
...Lupin was attacked and
was in a coma for 3 days.
Then, of course a major scene
happens at the end of this.
"On the contrary, he managed to steal
something you did not expect... your heart."
Yes, viewers please go see
The Castle of Cagliostro and enjoy the action of Lupin.
TIME'S UP!
Sugoi!
I did it!
Sugoi.
- Wait, isn't that great?
- Really?
- Extraordinary.
- Yay, success.
Takayama's is ugly!
Don't say it like that!
Like Heaven and Earth.
If we look at this...
That's true. Initially I thought
Takayama's was nice...
After you look at this, your stuff is REKT!
Attacks struck.
- Why?
- Plus, from the start...
Really! This...
This is really good!
- Very good, isn't it?
- Ah, I'm glad.
Probably better than
Monkey Punch*.
[Monkey Punch = author of the Lupin III manga.]
Better than the author?
Maybe the head part of the picture
would not be as good as the original.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
"Lupin III : The Castle of Cagliostro"
This section is also quite detailed...
This scene leaves the deepest impression.
And this!
The moment in which Lupin was attacked
was pretty severe, wasn't it?
Truly.
- And this, you drew this, yes?
- Yes.
Nice. Really good.
The way she tells the story,
her explanation is also good, it's like...
...the way kindergarten teachers explain something.
How she makes it easy for us
to understand, that's amazing.
Takayama, what do you think, do you see this?
Perfect!
Declaration of defeat.
Too perfect?
Recommend The Best Movies
With 4 Picture Illustrations!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Ikoma Rina
The next masterpiece film presenter,
is Ikoma, however...
Ikoma must be good because she likes manga.
First, I want you to know
how I'll show it.
I added "Ten-chan" into everything.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Ten-chan
Character for official products, designed by Ikoma
- Ten-chan?
- This...
Eh, in the scene?
That's Ikoma's character.
- Then, what movie do you recommend?
- I chose...
...Terminator 2.
This is the 2nd one, yes?
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
"Terminator 2" released in 1991
One day, there is an android who comes
from the future with a time machine.
Arnold Schwarzenegger plays T-800 and
is in charge of protecting the main character.
Then, there is another character, a
dangerous android made of liquid metal, T-1000.
The battle of these two Terminators,
coupled with special effects...
...makes this action film popular around the world.
And how will the awesome
final scene be presented?
Because I like Terminator...
...I often watch the 2nd one.
You can do that, yes.
Ready... Start!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
"Terminator 2"
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Ikoma Rina
De..de..den..de..den...
Kyaa... his body... his body...
Why is he naked!!
De..de..den..de..den...
First...
We don't know who this is?!
- ...Schwarzenegger has a nice body.
His face is the same.
Who?
De..de..den..de..den...
Inside the car
Car keys are usually
placed in the sun-visor!!
I understand...
De..de..den..de..den...
In the car, John Connor...
...amazes Schwarzenegger...
...because he shows him
where to store car keys.
De..de..den..de..den...
The machine T-1000...
...finally melts...
...the scene is frightening but
interesting and visibly powerful.
GOOD, TIME'S UP!
- Last...
- Ah, that's it!
His eyes closed.
Everything is Ten-chan, so it's confusing.
We are confused about everything there.
I know.
But this might be a new style, yes.
This is Schwarzenegger.
If you represent
Schwarzenegger with that picture...
- Long chin.
Because originally Schwarzenegger
did not wear anything,...
- He's naked, right?
- Right, so I just drew it up here.
Safe framing for recording.
So you don't show everything in the picture?
But, you can use Ten-chan there.
That's a great idea too!
Illustration
There is also such a way!
- There is such a way?
- Right.
- Because the time is 30 seconds, you didn't reach the end.
- Right, but here it is...
...Schwarzenegger raised his thumb,
If you watch it, you'll know.
Obviously you can't say,
"If you watch it, you'll know."
The part without explanation.
- You're too good to say that.
- We need an explanation.
But this is all... Ten-chan?
Ten-chan.
What do you think about this
original character made by Ikoma?
Perhaps, this character is already
famous among all of you...
...but my first time seeing it,
I totally do not understand.
"Ten-chan" is mysterious.
Ah, that's right, yes.
I also did not realize, I'm the
only one who knew about this!
- Right!
"Ah, she's drawing Ten-chan",
I know about this character, but...
...there are also people here who don't know.
A foreign word to him.
Right. I am also confused by this.
The whole studio, the mood here is like
everyone already knows what Ten-chan is...
...So I'm confused by myself here.
A strange place to him.
Then, as she shows her pictures...
...she gives sound effects.
It's very creative, using the
"Da..dan..da..da..dan."
There is a deep impression.
But because of that, she couldn't
reach the last picture.
Wrong timing.
That's right!
That part was interfering.
Recommend The Best Movies
With 4 Picture Illustrations!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
m 10 24 b 10 24 10 24 10 24 b 3 19 0 16 0 13 b 0 10 2 8 5 8 b 8 8 10 10 10 13 b 10 10 12 8 15 8 b 18 8 20 10 20 13 b 20 16 17 19 10 24
Presenter
Wakatsuki Yumi
Next, Wakatsuki will also
present Terminator 2.
Ah, there was news in the paper!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
m 10 24 b 10 24 10 24 10 24 b 3 19 0 16 0 13 b 0 10 2 8 5 8 b 8 8 10 10 10 13 b 10 10 12 8 15 8 b 18 8 20 10 20 13 b 20 16 17 19 10 24
Wakatsuki Yumi
Selected 2 years in a row for
Nika Art Exhibition "Design Category"
Right, a little news.
- She won in Nika, right?
- Right.  - And she's in there...
...it's like a great exhibition, right?
And she was elected to appear there.
That's great, right? How does it feel?
What? What happened to you?
- We'll start, yes. The movie you saw...
- Ah, I watched...
...the same as Ikoma, Terminator 2.
This part looks different, yes.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Ikoma's work
m 10 24 b 10 24 10 24 10 24 b 3 19 0 16 0 13 b 0 10 2 8 5 8 b 8 8 10 10 10 13 b 10 10 12 8 15 8 b 18 8 20 10 20 13 b 20 16 17 19 10 24
Wakatsuki's work
This is not Ten-chan, is it?
- It's Ten-chan.
- So it is Ten-chan?
Really, what is Ten-chan!
Ten-Stress.
- You don't know, Ten-chan, huh?
- Don't get angry...
All this talk in the studio about Ten-chan,
I really don't understand it!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
"Terminator 2"
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
m 10 24 b 10 24 10 24 10 24 b 3 19 0 16 0 13 b 0 10 2 8 5 8 b 8 8 10 10 10 13 b 10 10 12 8 15 8 b 18 8 20 10 20 13 b 20 16 17 19 10 24
Presenter
Wakatsuki Yumi
Wakatsuki, 30 seconds, yes. Ready...
...Start!
One day, Terminator T-800 came
to protect John Connor.
Because an enemy was after John, he
traveled back to a young John to warn him.
And here, the enemy, T-1000.
Very good.
His body made of a silver liquid, he
could disguise himself as a cop...
...or John's family.
What a powerful enemy!
Finally they begin fighting, T-800
is an older version of the android...
...He is severely damaged before he
can defeat T-1000 who is stronger.
Here is the major scene, when T-800 falls into the...
TIME'S UP!
- Great!
- The picture is good.
I couldn't get to the end.
But everything is good.
- I also have the same scene.
- Which one, show us?  - Here.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Ikoma's work
m 10 24 b 10 24 10 24 10 24 b 3 19 0 16 0 13 b 0 10 2 8 5 8 b 8 8 10 10 10 13 b 10 10 12 8 15 8 b 18 8 20 10 20 13 b 20 16 17 19 10 24
Wakatsuki's work
Stop~!!
Completely different.
You are watching the same movie, right?
This first motorcycling scene...
I didn't need much time to make it.
- This scene? Really?
- Right, it only takes 2 to 3 minutes.
It only takes 3 minutes?
Cocky! Cocky!
That's obviously showing off...
Nika Art Exhibition ability.
Because of that, there's no background.
After this, a devastating film presentation
appears and makes all sorts of disturbances!
Recommend The Best Movies
With 4 Picture Illustrations!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Hoshino Minami
The next masterpiece film presenter is Hoshino.
First, what movie have you watched?
This is it.
King Kong~
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
"King Kong" released in 1976
On an unknown island
lives a giant primate, King Kong.
Although Kong attacks the human
representatives who come...
...he protects the main character,
from other gigantic creatures.
And, slowly, he began
to relate with the human.
However, when Kong is caught alive...
...he must accept the fate of being
exhibited before the public city.
Finally, while thinking of
the person he loves...
...he loses his life.
Before we start,
you must not have watched it, right?
How did you know?
Seriously!!!
Ah, briefly...
...I caught a fever...
...so I didn't have time to watch it.
Even so, let's just listen to
Hoshino's explanation of this film!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
"King Kong"
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Hoshino Minami
Ready... Start!
Yes, King Kong... starts.
There's a gorilla.
A mess.
Then...there's a gorilla here.
His legs... his legs are long...
The gorilla and the woman became close to each other.
The gorilla is finally caught.
And the gorilla died.
This... next...
If you guys want to know how it happens
please watch it yourself.
GOOD, TIME'S OVER!
Great, she finished in exactly 30 seconds.
That's a good thing, yes.
The timing is super accurate.
It's great you got to the end.
It was really shocking.
Why do you always say gorilla?
The gorilla's the main character, right?
The main character?!
The topic is not clear.
There is a gorilla here, his name is King Kong, right?
The last picture is really disturbing
enough to make me shiver.
- What is this? Very disturbing.
- But this is it, right?!
HORROR.
What is that? What is that?
It's a turtle coming out of its shell.
It's not!!!
She lost, yes.
Recommend The Best Movies
With 4 Picture Illustrations!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Nishino Nanase
Next, Nishino. She will recommend
the same film, King Kong.
Nishino is good at drawing, isn't she?
She must be good.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
"King Kong"
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Nishino Nanase
Ready... Start!
King Kong.
Woah!!!
This is when the man asks the woman...
...to calm down because
they are stranded.
And Kong took the woman in his hand...
...he thought she fell into the river
and bathes her in the waterfall.
Then, there is a big snake that comes and attacks,
which angered Kong...
...and he kills it by tearing its mouth.
Lastly, Kong...
...is shot at and dies.
TIME'S UP!
Done.
Nice.
Hoshino, what do you think?
I think it's a gorilla too.
Hoshino keeps her stance.
At first, I thought this was a photo.
She drew each strand of hair,
the highlights too...
...it's really like the original.
The next one is very good.
- Great!
- The snake is also good.
Recommend The Best Movies
With 4 Picture Illustrations!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Sakurai Reika
The next masterpiece film presenter
is Sakurai.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
"Jaws" released in 1975
The film that Sakurai watched...
...Jaws, a work of Spielberg
when he was in his twenties.
On a beach, a large shark
attacks people one by one.
The battle of the police chief, the main character,
is combined with the drama of the film.
A masterpiece of Spielberg capable
of scaring people around the world.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
"Jaws"
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Sakurai Reika
Please get ready, 30 seconds...
...Start!
First...
...I want you guys to enjoy
the killer shark scenes.
At sea, there is a shark.
It's there, isn't it?
- Wah, this is great!
- Then, a woman...
...is attacked by the shark.
She became the first to be eaten, then...
Then there are 3 people here...
...they are old shark experts...
...who are also eaten by the shark.
He fell off the boat and was attacked.
Finally, the main character...
...from the boat, he attacked the shark
with a shotgun, "Bang, bang, bang!".
TIME'S UP!
- That's Nessie*...
- Nessie shows up there...
[Nessie = Loch Ness lake monster.]
So it's not Jaws but Nessie?
Let's look at the first...
- It's...
- I think Reika is good at drawing.
Are these bamboo shoots?
Man-eating bamboo shoots?
- Like that...
- It's the shark's body, right?
This is part of the shark, it's called...
-It looks like a bamboo shoot!
- ...What's it... the fin, right?
- The top fin, right?   - Yes.
The 4 people under it...
These are people who are relaxing on the beach.
Extreme levels of "messiness."
What's that box?
He's wearing shorts.
The person next to him is wearing a bikini?
New illustration style.
Right, like that.
The next picture is pretty good.
This is practically my best work...
The scene when the shark attacks
the first woman.
This is good, yes.
And from here, the problem arises.
This is somewhat...
Suddenly chaotic.
It's suddenly very bad, yes.
Jaws is quite difficult, isn't it?
The second one is pretty good, right?
It's like it's not her drawing.
It's mine, not someone else's.
This second image is the first
drawing I made.
Because I thought the 3rd and 4th
pictures would look similar...
...I changed my style of drawing
into this.
So you say, "Let's change the style"...
...with your drawing level
like that?
Direct protest.
Sugoi!
- She changed her style just like that, huh?
- Right.
Is Spielberg finally overtaken?
Unexpectedly, a new character appears!
Recommend The Best Movies
With 4 Picture Illustrations!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Ikuta Erika
Next, Ikuta
who seems to be a potential problem.
First, what movie did you watch?
E.T.
- E.T.?
- Yes.    - That is a great film, yes.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
"E.T." released in 1982
E.T., an alien left by his comrades...
...on Earth after departing
on an outer space flight.
Spielberg's masterpiece, a film that features
the purity of heart between the alien and Elliot.
How will she present
the main scene when E.T....
...uses his abilities to make a bike fly
in space when escaping from a bad scientist.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
"E.T."
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Ikuta Erika
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Ready... Start!
In a forest...
...E.T. is abandoned by the spacecraft.
Ghost appearance.
You obviously never watched this!
Then, Elliot took him home.
And E.T. finally...
Decaying?
...lost his energy.
And, because he lost his strength,
then came...
...zombie-like aliens to Elliot's house.
And E.T., it turns out, is dead.
Even so, he can live again...
...when he is brought back, that's the story.
TIME'S UP!
Do you understand?
It's different from the E.T. I know.
Wait, wait, this is really...
A new film?
Try showing the first picture.
- The first picture.
- It...
This is E.T.
That Gachapin* has had
a full-body hair cut, huh?
[Gachapin = famous cartoon character.]
After a haircut?
It's not! It's E.T.! Look, at this section...
Here are the wrinkles, right...
Spooky!!!
Ikoma-san keeps imitating his moves...
"Ah, I remember, oh!"
It's like a ghost from a long time ago, yes.
Ghost?!
That's like old man saying, "Wanna fight?"
No, not really.
He winked at him, so.
I think people who have watched it will say it's similar.
- I'm one of those who's watched it!
He always said that, yes.
Nothing like E.T.
His neck is smaller, right?
You didn't draw this scene?
Ah, that, in the movie...
- ...this finger scene does not exist.
- That scene?!  - Really!
The finger touching does not exist.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Although there was a similar scene on the poster
this part is not present in the film.
- I wanted to draw it, but...
- Really?!
- Really, watch it yourself.
- It isn't there, huh?
That's pretty famous, but it's just on the poster.
- Eh?!
- It's simply not there.
- Really?!
- So it isn't, huh?
Initially, many people thought so.
I thought it was there.
Because it's in the poster, everyone
remembers it, but...
- ...in the movie, the scene isn't there, huh?
- It isn't.
- I'm also surprised.
- How about the forehead?
- Is it to the fore...
- That scene is there, the touch to the forehead.
Even so, the image I chose
is right!
Oh, I see.
Recommend The Best Movies
With 4 Picture Illustrations!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Itou Marika
Next is Itou Marika.
How will she
recommend the film E.T.?
The same movie, E.T.
Wow!
Wait a minute.
What is this?
Ikuta, try showing your first picture.
Very simple.
- E~T~
- There are stars.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Ikuta's work
Itou Marika's work
Looking at this, it feels like
it's in outer space.
This is great!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
"E.T."
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Presenter
Itou Marika
30 seconds, starting from... now!
There is a mysterious spacecraft
that comes to Earth.
Then, the ship went back into space.
There is one...
There is one alien left behind.
His name is E.T.
Wow, great!
With these kids...
...he has various adventures
by riding a bicycle.
E.T. and this young boy
have a close friendship.
However, E.T. had to go back home.
"E.T. phone home... E.T. phone home..."
The spacecraft finally
took E.T. back.
Safely...
TIME'S UP!
- Safely, he can finally go home!
- Ah, amazing!
Sugoi!
The pictures are nice, but wait a minute.
Take a look at the third picture.
The obscure scene.
- This scene?
- Does the scene exist?
This part of the poster really
left an impression on my heart...
Eh? Have you seen it?
I did! I did! I already watched it!
It looks suspicious.
I have watched it, but...
So you inserted the scene
thinking we'd understand it better?
But your drawing is really good.
And that finger scene was...
- This is obviously E.T., yes?
- It's E.T.
Try showing E.T. your first one...
This is it.
You drew the same character?!
Disrespecting Spielberg.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Ikuta's work
Itou Marika's work
This, really!
The difference is worlds apart!
- Definitely very different!
- Unbelievable!
But I prefer the more cheerful E.T.
who resembles an old man.
The grandfather-like E.T.'s victory.
Why? I tried so hard too.
The most recent announcement
of Senbatsu members!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
Jaws
Akimoto Manatsu
And here, the pictures by members
that did not get displayed earlier.
[Best Kid = Karate Kid.]
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
Best Kid
Inoue Sayuri
Inoue, presenting the last scene
of the masterpiece, "Best Kid" with baby chicks.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
Best Kid
Hashimoto Nanami
Who's that pretty girl
with the blond hair?!
Here is her ex-boyfriend
who is good at karate
*Ex-lover
Hashimoto, using 4 manga illustrations.
She gives her recommendation
by writing out the story.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
Back to the Future
Matsumura Sayuri
Matsumura draws an unenthusiastic looking dog
for the film Back to the Future?
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
Back to the Future
Nakada Kana
Nakada concentrates too much on the title image,
the other 3 pictures are very messy.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
Back to the Future Part 2
Saitou Yuri
Saitou Yuri, showing her unique images
for the sequel of the same film.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Film Title
Back to the Future Part 3
Shiraishi Mai
Shiraishi who has watched through Part 3,
managed to explain well with 4 pictures.
In this case...
Best Work Announcement
Movie Presentation with 4 Illustrations
Shimada, who is the winner
of our episode this time?
Nishino Nanase-san!
Best Work
Nishino Nanase
Naa-chan!
As expected.
Lastly, Shimada will read your palm
Prize
Hands-on readings and luck predictions from Shimada Shohei
Now, Nishino close our show. Please!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
The closing of the members' excited presentations!
Is there a movie you want to watch?
Original Indonesian subtitle by Mastoppu.blogspot.co.id
English translation by weeabookstore
Yes, eh...
How should I do this? It's my first time closing.
- Ah, really?
- Yes.
Please watch next week's episode!
Autumn Art Inspiration!
See you soon!
See you again.
ByeBye.
Tickets for the Nogizaka Zenkoku Tour,
have sold out.
Viewers, thank you very much.
Then...
Senbatsu Announcement Episode!
Next week, finally the new
Senbatsu member announcement!
Everyone in the studio is surprised,
and what is the reason?
This time it's unbelievable, there's a big change!