Today's Nogidoko is a continuation of last week's segment of
A secret survey by the families, "My child is actually OOOO"
Tonight would reveal the remaining members private lives that have not been revealed yet!
And 2 months after the previous opening pitch, Shiraishi challenges throwing the opening pitch again!
Where will the ball go!?
Brought to you by IkomaSubs
www.Facebook.com/IkomaSubs
Translated by Jiaemi
Timed & Typeset by Michael Soares
QC by ramenrider
The segment starting last week, a secret survey done by their families, "My child is actually OOOO"
Episodes that only the families of the members would know were totally revealed!
Tonight the member's true selves that they don't want to be revealed will also be revealed!
Without further ado let's begin!
Here is the theme!
Only family members would know!
She is actually OOOO at home!
We don't want this! It's scary!
Okay
This segment unveils the self you don't want others to know about and have been keeping hidden all along
It would reveal you members this-and-that! The first person is this!
Hashimoto!
Oh! Her little brother!
Eh!? I didn't know about this, what is this about?
We've heard some things from Hashimoto's little brother
As to what it is, here it is!
She is actually a sadist!
No no no no!
Ahhh... yeah yeah
But everyone else went "Ahhh..."
But honestly speaking I somehow knew that Hashimoto is kind of sadistic
Already has a sadist character
Not at all, I'm totally normal
But when you both were baking snacks, you asked him to tell you when the oil was 80°C
But when he asked you how to know that the oil has reached 80°C
You replied to him "Stick your hand into the oil, if it's hot it's 80°C!"
Close to a hardcore sadist
*Please do not imitate this dangeous act
You're amazing!
She's super scary!
When your mother overheard this, she intervened
That's obvious!
He was about to get burnt
You know what would happen if you stick your hand into oil at 80°C right?
But he would be okay, he's a guy after all~
Because he's a guy, he would be okay?
Mysterious theory
What's with that declaration
Scary~
Nanami seems scary
Is there any of you that got into an accident instigated by her?
Everyone is too scared to say it out
But I, umm ..
Oh here's one!
When we went to Sapporo, we met her brother. Because it was at their hometown, he came to our live.
Your hometown?
Yes we did meet him
When we met him, he was a little shy so he was giggling a little
And then Nanamin said "What are ya looking at!" and slapped him
Uwahhh! Slapped him!
The sound from the slap had quite a sound!
You guys around were like "What happened?" right?
Yes, the sound was like BAM!
We were like "Ehhh?!"
When that happened what did her brother do?
But he was laughing like it was normal
He giggled
Masochistic brother?
No way!
She did it
She did it!
He was like "I got hit ❤"
Bliss
Your brother is admirable
My brother's friends watch this show too
Collateral damage
They have a good sibling relationship
Yes they have a good relationship
But there is sibling love between us
Because he is about to sit for his entrance exams
I would send him some recommended practice papers
And if he pass I would buy a watch for him
Oh amazing!
Admirable!
Kindness is also present
Oh so you do care for him
There is proper love between us
There is love eh?
And you would pull out all the needles on the watch right?
Ultimate goal is to bully him
Then the watch wouldn't move
This is not about that
Let's move on to the next person
Okay!
Next is this person!
Stop it for real!
Your older sister
Yes
What is it about?
To tell the truth, I'm the one who thought of her nickname
Ehhh?
What is this about?
You often call yourself Sayuringo right?
This nickname was actually thought of by your older sister
EHHH!?
Oh so you didn't thought of it yourself
I thought you were called that since a long time ago
You thought that you thought of your nickname yourself?
Because people around me called me that
But that is not true right sister?
Ah, yes
EHHHHHH!?
Sister?
Good day sister!
Sister stop it! That ain't good!
Matsumura's older sister
Ah, yes
Thanks for looking after us, we're Bananaman
Her nickname Sayuringo was thought of by you?
Yes that's true
No way!
She doesn't seem to remember that at all
I really can't recall it!
After watching Yamatomato's self introduction
I said it might seem good to put a word like Tomato behind her name for a nickname
And when we were talking about if Sayuri did that, her nickname would be Sayuringo
At that time, her reaction was like "Ehh~ it seems to connect"
It was a salty response
She didn't really like it
If it's Ringo (Apple) it should connect right? Or does it not?
Before I knew it, she used that nickname!
Yes
And she claimed that she was called Sayuringo since long ago
Actually likes the nickname ❤
Ehh!? You're kidding us!
So she's wrong about that?
She also wrote that our mother called her that since a long time ago
I didn't know anything about that!
But really, mother did call me that before!
Oh so your mother DID call you that before!
Nope, not at all.
Total denial
Sister!
Your sister said none of that sort happened
And that never happened at all
I've never heard mother call her that once before
"My child is actually OOOO"
The next informant is Nishino's mother
We've heard this from your mother
What is it about? Here!
She is actually a slob!
This doesn't fit the image you have, you seem to have a neat and proper image
That's right!
Here is an episode about your slobbiness
You will instantly take off your socks
You will throw them about 3m away once you've taken off your socks
But that's still cute!
This doesn't fit your image at all!
She sometimes just take things out from the fridge and leave them lying around
And I have to clean it up
What is this?
What did you do?
Why did you do this?
This happened quite a long time ago
I don't like wearing socks at home, that's why once I reach home I would take them off immediately
When you reach home?
And doing so made me feel like throwing my socks
You don't throw them into the washing machine?
I don't, it's nothing near that
Oh so you don't aim for a specific target to throw them?
I get the urge to throw them at random spots so I throw them
Why is that so?
Could you demonstrate?
With that said, Nishino reenacts the scene
Say you're home
I'm home~
Crude
Wait wait ..
That's far!
What are you doing!
What's that!
What the hell are you doing
What's with that unwillingness?
You want to feel released?
The feeling is like "I'm home!"
The socks might end up behind the fridge
It's no good that your mother is the one that picks them up, it might still be okay if you were the one that picked them up
Yes, that isn't good
I'll change my ways
Good
Let's move on, the next person is this!
Ikuta!
Ikuta you're up
What is she actually like? Here it is!
The truth is she actually has a weird habit!
When my daughter concentrates on something, the back of her leg gets abnormally hot
When that happens she has the habit of taking off her socks and throwing them at random places
YOU TOO!?
Habit of throwing socks
at random places
Why do you both have the same habits!
Overlap!
When I concentrate, this part of my leg becomes warm
I understand that feeling!
Each time I just feel like taking off my socks
And my mother picks them up for me
As expected it's your mother that does the tidying up
That's right
It's hard on your mother to tidy up after you, right?
Ah, hello~
EHHHHHHHHHHHH!?
Hi there!
Hi, thanks for always taking care of us
Same here!
Ehh!? Wow!
EHHHH!?
Mama~!
We were just talking about the matter about her throwing her socks all over the place
Yes
Do you tidy them up after her?
Yes I do
Under her study desk, or under the piano there's about 3 pairs of socks rolled up
So I pick them up
And I think to myself "She did it again" and put them into the washing machine
That's the usual pattern
Ahhhhhh
Oh so that's it
Yes
She doesn't tidy them up herself?
The socks land in hidden places which are usually overlooked
Oh I see
Yes
And furthermore, mother
Chancing upon this, you have a request right?
Yes that's right, umm...
My daughter doesn't really know how to pick and buy her own clothes
She doesn't have that kind of fashion sense
She always tells me to buy clothes for her because she doesn't have the time to go shopping
Oh, you buy clothes for her?
That's right!
Yes
Himura-san, there seems to be a segment where you bring the girls to buy clothes for them
It isn't a segment in this show!
That isn't a planned segment of this show!
We did that previously right?
Yes we did that some time back
If there is a next time to this segment...
By all means, please bring my daughter along too
Mother!
Yay!
Of course I would pay the cost of the clothes
This has turned into you just earnestly wanting her to go and buy her own clothes
Yes that's right
What am I to Ikuta?
Since her mother is coming up with the money, why not let's have this segment once again?
That's right
Okay I understand then
Yay!
Shall we go sometime then?
Successful negotiations
Thank you very much!
Oh I see
I get it, if there is a chance we will do that
Yes, by all means please do so~
Yes I get it
The next informant is Noujou's mother
What is the information from your mother? Here it is!
"She is actually troubled about something!"
Are you okay?
What is wrong?
She doesn't know how to excel at handshake events
You're troubled about that
Like for example, gestures or words that would make fans kyun
Such things .. just don't come to me
For the sake of Noujou, she would demonstrate her handshake skills on Himura
Let's begin
Okay
Okay and start!
Nice to meet you
Ah! Hello!
THAT'S TOO FAST!!
Usher from hell
That's fast!
That's too fast!!
You ushered me away too soon!
You're dangerous
Suspicious character
I'm not dangerous! You had me panicked just now!
Okay, now the normal version okay?
Okay, ready and start!
Nice to meet you
Ah! Hello!
Hello, I'm a fan of you
Nice to meet you
What's your name?
I'm Himura
Ah! Himura-san!
Pleased to meet you!
Hi, today it's very ..
Thank you very much!
Wait a moment!
Your 10 seconds have passed
10 seconds?
Tap his shoulders to usher him
From my point of view she isn't bad at all!
Good impression
She properly holds your hand and looks in your eyes
Isn't handshakes about that?
That's just the basics!
Ah is that so?
Mmmm ..
Who is good at handshakes?
Manatsu is!
Noujou doesn't have any areas of concern regarding her handshakes but ..
As per the member's recommendation, Manatsu-san would demonstrate
Do it as per usual, don't expect that much
Okay let's begin, start!
Nice to meet yo ..
Ah! Thank you!
Thank you!
Thank you very much
Did you come to see Manatsu?
Yes that's right
I'm happy!
Really?
I'm happy to see you too!
Uwahh!
Thank you!
Uwahhh!
Waaaaa!
Super excited
Wow you're amazing!
I'm jealous!
You're amazing!
Noujou you two are totally different!
Oshimen change
That isn't it
You're totally different
Could you give some pointers on how you do your handshakes?
For me, I fall in love with that person for that moment
You make them feel like they are in a relationship with you?
I see, but that should be the case, right?
And you winked too?
You winked at the end right?
You all didn't see?
At the last part where she was saying goodbye
She winked at me!
Fans would leave thinking "Was that a sign?"
What was that?
Amazing!
You're amazing!
That's all for Manatsu-san's lesson
Noujou challenges this handshake!
Say something like "It's a secret between us ❤" and wink
Something like that, you can do it right?
Yes
Good!
Okay ready and start!
Ah!
Did you come to see me?
Thank you!
What is your name?
I'm Himura
Forceful grip
Ah! Himura-san?
Do you like Ami?
Uh huh, I like you a lot
Really? I'm happy!
Thank you very much!
Finishing wink!
That's good
You were good
You were cute
But there was something different ..
Yeah but the way you closed up the distance between you two, wasn't that good?
The pressure she put on my wrist made it felt like she wanted to dislocate my wrist
Discomfort
What was your intention in doing that?
You were cute when you winked
Wouldn't you be happy if she came so close to you and winked?
I would be happy
You were many times better than your previous handshake
Her mimicry of Sakanoue-kun is good
Who is Sakanoue-kun!?
A talent of our child that definitely would become popular
Yes
We did that in the previous episode right?
Yes, this is the sequel to that
A talent that the members themselves don't think is so-so but family members think that it would become popular
Tonight, the members would have to fufill this unreasonable task!
The next informant is Wada's mother
What is her talent?
High kick!
Oh, the kick in karate?
This wouldn't become popular!
Ah? You learned karate?
I did learn, but this definitely wouldn't become popular
But your mother said that you might even be able to break a wooden plank
I have never even tried to break that before!
Try it?
She said you might be able to
She didn't say you would definitely be able to break it
She didn't say you can break it
Your mother said that you might .. be able to break them, so why don't you give it a try?
Try it!
Oh!
I have never tried that before!
But if you're able to break them, you might get offers from TV programs
This is good, you would be able to make use of this
Mmm...
With that said, without any prior experience, Wada will try to break a wooden plank
Hold it like this
Like this?
And then from here you do this
What's that?
Plate decoy
He got kicked!
You kicked me!
Now let's begin
The talent that your mother said might be able to break a wooden plank
Karate high kick, please go
Good luck!
It broke .. it broke!
She broke it!
Amazing!
She managed to break it
She broke it, and Himura you seemed to be in a dangerous position
I was in a precarious spot there
Barely safe
It was pretty dangerous, you should have bent away more
Next informant is Higuchi's mother
Higuchi (Laughs)
What is it about?
What is this? Your mother said you should do this on TV
Let's see what is it about
Wait a minute! Don't do that, for real!
What is that about~?
Umm, should we call this Sakanoue-kun?
Who?
Saka .. who is this?
You all don't know what is this about right?
It's really embarrassing for me!
I have totally no idea
Umm, for the talent that Higuchi's mother said she should show on TV is
She is good at the mimicry of Sakanoue-kun's mimicry of a dinosaur walking
Who is this person!?
Complicated setting
By the way, you all are curious as to who is Sakanoue-kun right?
It seems that he was Higuchi's classmate during elementary school
Insider joke
Higuchi please come up to the front
The first ever demonstration of a mimicry of Sakanoue-kun's, which reeks of suspicion
He was a transfer student
Sakanoue-kun right?
A transfer student apparently
Scaryyyy~
He was a very good boy
When he gets angry, he mimics a dinosaur
Seemingly a dinosaur maniac
Is this really going to be okay?
He mimics a dinosaur when he's angry?
I have never shown this to anyone other than my family!
Well, that's understandable
1st ever public unveiling
Yes
Let's begin then
Let's do it!
The mimicry of Sakanoue-kun's mimicry of a dinosaur walking, please demonstrate!
That's what he does
Sunken morale
It was good
This is amazing
Your mother said you should do this more often on TV
It honestly isn't fit for TV!
It's cute
You were cute
Mother you really shouldn't say something like that
The last segment of the family survey are interesting photos which were given discreetly for this show!
From all the photos, 10 were selected and will all be shown in one go!
Let's go!
We would see all the photos at one go, start!
Wada
Ehh!?
Higuchi
Oh amazing!
You're the monk Sanzou from journey to the west
Hashimoto
Cute!
Super cute
It's a photo of your brother
Your brother is cute
Sakurai
You're hilarious
It seems like you did that face on purpose
Cute!
Nagashima
You look constipated
Cute
Your family sent this!?
Kawago
Bone professor
Bone professor!?
Are you a bone professor!?
Itou
What the hell is this picture!?
EHHH!?
Itou you're amazing
My face... I'm sorry about that face!
Your body is soft
Yamato
Hey! That's not me!
Evil! What is this!?
Ikuta!
You're cute
CUTE!!
You're so cute
Saito Asuka
Oh?
You were fat!
You were so rounded!
To the family members, thank you all for your cooperation!!
Right after this, would the revenge pitch be successful or not!
For this episode there's another segment
Eh~?
There was a letter from someone
Oh? From a certain someone?
To Nogizaka46's Shiraishi Mai
Oh Maiyan!
On the 17th of September
For the match at Miyagi
Rakuten Golden Eagles vs Softbank Hawks
We would like you to challenge the opening pitch again
Oh! Revenge!
Good for you!
Just 2 months have passed since that major upset
Unexpectedly, Rakuten have once again made an offer to pitch the opening pitch!
Furthermore, the one who wrote the letter was Rakuten's President Mikitani
After watching Shiraishi crouching in despair, the president himself made the offer
With that said
But before the revenge pitch
There was someone they had to greet first
I'm really sorry about back then!
Start off apology
No no no, it's okay
But you were good during the practice
Yes
Even after you taught me so much, during the actual pitch I...
At the actual pitch...
Because I showed such a disgraceful self during the actual pitch
This time I really practiced before I came, compared to the previous time, I would definitely be better this time
Despite the pitching lessons from Tanaka
Shirashi failed big time during the actual throw
This time, to fulfill her revenge pitch
During her free time, she constantly practiced her pitching
And then... !
Your catchball has improved!
Praise
For real?
Its an encouraging praise
Perhaps thanks to her practicing, there was an improvement in her catchball
For Shiraishi, the famous Tanaka gives her advice on how to avoid a double bound
Aoyama also lent his support
While he was helping, Ikoma and Matsumura went up to the batter box and bat
And then ..
Good luck!
You have never seen him pitch before right?
Uwahhhh!!
Frozen
You're kidding us!
That's impossible to hit!
It would be 'delicious' for TV if you hit it
Matsumura that's dangerous!
Stop that!
Am I still in one piece?
No matter where the batter stands, whether the distance between the catcher and the batter is narrower or not
The zone for a strike doesn't change
Basically if you throw the ball above the baseline to the catcher, it would be considered as a strike
You don't really have to care where the batter stands
I understand
After taking the advice from Tanaka and Aoyama sportsmen to heart
The time for the revenge pitch creeps up!
The previous time, I was too impatient and nervous
And I threw the ball immediately
This time I would calm myself down first
I would confirm the other player's standing positions before throwing the pitch
And strengthen my will and resolve and all that's left is for the actual pitch
And the time for the revenge pitch comes ..
Today, Nogizaka46's Shiraishi Mai would throw the opening pitch
I'll be in your care!
Sorry, I'll be in your care
On 9 July, at the Tokyo Dome match, Shiraishi threw the opening pitch
Due to nervousness, she threw the pitch which bounced twice
I'm starting to feel nervous, what should I do!
Today, it's her chance for revenge!
With that said, Shiraishi please throw the opening pitch!
Ahh! I'm nervous!
With the members and audience looking over her
How would Shiraishi's pitch go?
Ah! I'm Sorry!
Amazing! Shiraishi Mai!
Shiraishi's pitch bounced once before being received by the catcher
It was an improvement over the last time
She barely misses her chance for revenge
And then...
2 bounces, 1 bounce, the next time would be a strike!
I'm really sorry about it!
Maiyan it's okay!
I was no good, I can't stand there anymore
It's going to be okay
I'm sorry...
Sorry..
It's okay
But I really did screw up
You don't have to apologize
I remembered the pressure I felt at Tokyo Dome
I didn't threw the ball as far as I thought I could be able to
But somehow
Things went better than the previous time but I still have some vexing feelings about this
I'll reflect on this
But it was fun!