zaka46sembungsub
Nationwide waterfall hit campaign, final part!
Ah, that is a good one.
Who would have thought of an enjoyable vacation?
Non-stop complaints against Okinawa Team.
That is unnecessary!
A hit prayer even on a bitter cold waterfall,
Why did everyone burst into laughter?
Credits to zaka46sembungsub for the original Indonesian subtitle and time setting
DON!
Ah, too short.
Nogizakatte Doko has started
we are your hosts, Bananaman.
yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
and they are... Nogizaka-chan~
Last week’s “Boron” made an appearance, huh?
The tradition of doing a single campaign
This time, all members went to a waterfall training.
Last time,
the members who went to Kanagawa and Gunma did various things
leading to a successful hit prayer!
And then, this time…
Starting from Okinawa’s waterfall.
DON!
Haisai~
Haisai – Okinawan dialect for hello.
Okinawa Prefecture, Nago City
21 Seiki no Mori Sunset Beach
We’ve come to Okinawa for Nogizaka46’s 7th single campaign!
High tension
What can you say about the sea?
It’s beautiful.
It’s so clear.
Emerald green
For a while, it bothers us a little,
it’s drizzling…
Ah, but the sea is so beautiful and clear.
It’s beautiful, I want to go in.
Eh? That’s not right.
Therefore…
You’re going in a waterfall!
Of course,
this must be done.
You’re in Okinawa, anyway.
It’s fun, really fun!
Members’ resort mood.
Kawaii ♥
This scene is unnecessary.
Let’s make some memories.
Something adventurous.
Where did these four go after that?
From this point, it’s meal time!
That’s very idol-like,
that’s great
They’re not done yet?!
Let’s go!
We’ll have a meal.
Ah, it’s raining.
This is a hundred year old establishment, Ufuya.
To compliment with this hundred year old Japanese architecture is…
You went for a meal?
Excuse me.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Looks delicious!
We have here a Soki soba set.
Soki soba – Okinawan-style stewed pork spare rib noodles
And here, we have sea grapes and vegetable salad.
I really like sea grapes.
Of course the customary bitter gourd chanpuru won’t be left out.
Chanpuru – Okinawan stir fry dish containing vegetables
including bitter gourd, tofu,meat or fish
Well then, everyone,
please deliver a proper food report!
So this is how it goes, huh?
Of course, because
they’re in Okinawa,
we have to see this.
How about this Soki soba?
Tastes like udon.
But this is noodles.
Harsh…
Hori will also attempt her first food report.
Thaks for the food.
What’s that?
Beef.
Uwah, Beef?
seems delicious.
It’s like, whenever I chew on it, the umami comes out.
It’s delicious.
Better than Nishino & Fukagawa?
Then, after the meal, of course there is…
Right here.
Dessert.
There’s even a dessert.
Oishi-sa-!
Combination of Oishii (delicious) and Shiisaa (Okinawan lion dog statues)
Oishiisaa, that’s great.
We needed that one.
After enjoying Okinawan dishes,
now, let’s head towards the waterfall!
Right there, it says Ta waterfall.
Sloppy sign.
The journey going to the waterfall is an environment suitable for adventure trekking.
Okinawa’s popular leisure spot.
Even though it’s November, the water temperature is around 20°C.
Adventure.
This is fun!
You’re not supposed to say “Yey”.
This is a waterfall training you know.
After 20 minutes of walking…
Ah! The waterfall!
Waterfall!
This is their destination, Ta waterfalls.
With the water falling from a height of 20 meters,
its force receive full marks.
Water temperature is 20°C while air temperature is 25°C.
Incidentally, this is a famous power spot in Okinawa.
Get that power right away, let’s start the hit prayer!
It’s nice in the jungle.
First to go, on her first campaign is Hori.
We’re starting off with Hori.
Ah, this is scary!
Do your best, Miona!
Isn’t the water quite strong?
Praying for the 7th single to be a hit!
Dance.
Miona, do your best!
Miona, be careful!
Dancing in a trance.
On her first campaign, we’ve seen Hori’s feat of being able to dance in the waterfall.
Next up is Fukagawa.
Will she be able to show the pride of a senpai?
Praying for the 7th single “Barrette” to be a big hit!
She didn’t dance.
She’s singing, right?
Fukagawa showed the pride of a senpai by being on
the waterfall for more than two minutes.
The youngest member, Saito Asuka, will she be able to continue?
Will she be alright?
Won’t she get washed away?
Praying for the 7th single to become a hit!
Ah, watch out!
There was a time back then where I almost drowned,
so the water is really frightening for me.
But, I think this was surprisingly okay.
It was fun!
Smile.
Saito’s smile gave support to their anchor, Nishino.
Can she add decoration to this crowning glory?
Nanase, do your best!
-Naachan, do your best!
Praying for the 7th single to be a hit!
Ah, look out! Look out!
Watch out.
I believe all of us did a proper prayer.
Smiling all the way until the end, Team “GI”
A successful hit prayer campaign!
That was really looking good, trekking on a paradise.
Was it hard?
Ah, but it was really fun, right?
The waterfall is really fun!
Do not say that it was fun!
Field trip?
But this one is a privilege for the Okinawa team, right?
You’ve had some of the local foods.
Was it delicious?
It was really delicious?
Does it tastes like udon?
Tastes like udon.
Oh, so it tastes just like udon.
What’s with you? What was that about?
You could have gone to more restaurants.
But we also had ice cream.
It’s not shown but you’ve had some ice cream?
Hidden away.
Do not even mention anything that seems fun!
An explosive laughter because of the extremely cold waterfall?!
You’ve seen the Okinawa team and it seems fun, right?
I got sad because of it.
They’re looking down on us!
Hey!!
Himetan had a sour look on her face for the whole time.
That wasn’t a situation where you can just laugh, right?
Difference between
heaven and hell?
We’ve come to Joudogahama, Miyako City, Iwate Prefecture!
Je Je Je!
From the TV drama Amachan aired in 2013.
Since we are in Iwate.
It’s so cold.
-Yeah, it’s cold.
Air temperature
The scenery is really beautiful though, right?
Please take a look at it.
It’s really beautiful, even the sea is stunning.
It really is beautiful but the excitement is not that obvious.
It’s the waterfall’s fault.
I have just found about this recently,
It’s near from where we are,
and it seems to be a spot that grant wishes.
-Blue?
-It is called the Blue Cave.
Before we take on the waterfall,
I thought that we should go there since we’re doing a hit prayer.
With that, they’ll go to the rumored place that grant wishes, the Blue Cave.
A cave?
I wonder if we’ll go inside?
It’s blue!
So pretty!
Due to the angle of sunlight reflected on the water,
it seems to transform into a magical color.
This is the Blue Cave.
And then, seeing the phenomenon of water gushing out
from a hole inside the cave will make your wish come true.
Without further ado…
First of all, we’re praying for the 7th single to become a hit.
onegaishimasu~
And then…
Praying for Himura to have a good health,
and together with Shitara-san, to be more active than ever!
That goes for us too.
onegaishimasu~
On their way back,
the Blue Cave’s luck immediately appeared to them.
While onboard the boat, the members are handing food over to the flock of black-tailed gulls,
then this happens…
Ahh! A bird poop just dropped.
Not good! No way!
A bird poop dropped on you.
What’s the matter?
Poop on the new uniform.
Seriously?!
Kawago only?
the Japanese believes that bird droppings are lucky since poop and luck are pronounced the same (un).
I’m really lucky.
Poop.
It seems like I’m really lucky.
After enjoying a brief moment of sightseeing,
the members are now headed to their original destination, the waterfall.
For that, they’re going into a steep mountain trail.
This journey is quite hard.
Completely different from the
Okinawa team.
The target waterfall is located
upstream of the river down the steep slope.
Because of a rain yesterday,
the water on the river is immense,
causing for some of the trails to disappear.
Submerged.
Falling down.
Finally, they have arrived at their destination.
That is the waterfall that everyone will take on today.
This is the waterfall that will pound the members this time.
The water temperature is extremely cold with 8°C,
and because of the rain, the water is quite strong.
A dangerous condition.
The water is
strong this day, huh?
Compared to the other waterfalls, this one’s not that high,
But the water volume and intense force is on a different level.
First one to go in this dangerous waterfall is Nakamoto.
Really Cold.
Uwah, that’s quite
close to the falls.
While trembling from the cold water,
Nakamoto approaches the waterfall basin.
The current is so strong it’s even hard to stand straight.
But, right here…
Praying for the 7th single to be a hit!
Himetan, ganbare~
With her body worn out, the first to accomplish this task is Nakamoto
You did great.
-Thank goodness.
Well, the three of them
still have to do it.
Next, Kawago will attempt to do the hit prayer!
Do your best!
In addition to the freezing cold temperature,
the fierce water is raining down on her body
that she couldn’t even bring herself to speak normally.
But, right here, she managed to show her fighting spirit.
Praying for the 7th to be a hit!
I want to appear more on TV!
That’s nice.
That’s a good one.
Right here, the monk sensed something wrong with Kawago and has to call it off.
Currently in a dazed state, Kawago efforts went through admirably,
and completely fulfilled her role.
Next is Eto Misa.
Do your best!
Misamisa, ganbare~
Praying for the 7th single, Barrette, to be a hit!
Continuously pounded by the waterfall,
Eto had a wish that she has to say.
that is…
I hope that I’ll be chosen on the next senbatsu announcement too!
Eto and the others have endured the pain
of not being selected for the senbatsu,
there’s no way she’ll give up in this campaign.
Eto won’t stop from trembling, but,
because of her will power, this hit prayer is a success!
Then, finally,  Akimoto’s attempt on the waterfall!
However, Akimoto, who had experienced
the waterfall before is going to a different spot.
Manatsu is going in that part of the waterfall.
With her clear approval, Akimoto is escorted towards the harsher part of the waterfall.
Praying for the 7th single, Barrette, to be a big hit.
onegaishimasu~
Do your best, Manatsu!
Praying to be a hit!
For Akimoto too, she also had a wish she wanted to say,
and that is…
I’m hoping to co-star with Degawa-san!
onegaishimasu~
Wish worth risking life for.
You did great!
A successful hit prayer for Team “ZA!”
That waterfall was impressive, right?
It’s on a different level compared to
the other waterfalls in terms of water volume.
It’s like taking a shower with ice water.
Because that was the coldest among all of the waterfalls, right?
And then there is Eto, for example, who added on her wish
that she’s hoping to be selected on the next senbatsu.
That’s a strong determination right there, huh?
On the other hand, Manatsu-san, what was that again?
I want to co-star with Degawa-san.
Her personal wishes are different from everyone else.
Her own route.
That’s what she wants, there’s nothing we can do about it.
That was great.
This one’s definitely gonna be a hit.
This time, there are those who were not able to get into the waterfall.
Who are they again?
Ikoma, Takayama and Ikuta
though she’s not here, there’s Ikuta too.
These three didn’t get into the waterfall.
Seeing everyone in Iwate,
I deeply apologize.
These three have to do something.
We’ll do anything.
-You’ll do anything?
We’ll think of something, just for the three of them.
The new single’s MV, waterfall version is complete?!
Using the VTR from this campaign,
the waterfall version of the MV is complete!
Barrette, it rests on your hair
like a large butterfly.
Barrette
raising its wings,
not wanting to be noticed, it sits still
like me.
By the window in the library,
female students whisper, conspiring,
While reading Hemmingway,
I glanced over them.
Tracing the movements of their lips in my mind
Can I get a hint?
By chance, our eyes met
As if you peeked into my heart
I already raised the white flag.
Barrette, in the wind,
You hold down your dancing hair.
Barrette, the sun,
Ah, it seems so bright,
I had to avert my eyes
It’s like you
Barrette, a lot like you,
with your mischievous eyes,
you smiled at me,
I wonder why?
Message from the graduating members, Kashiwa and Miyazawa
Ever since I entered Nogizaka46,
I’ve earned a lot of experiences and lessons.
I’m hoping to be able to work after graduation using those experiences.
I’ll never forget this feeling of gratitude towards everyone who had supported me.
I’ll do my best moving forward.
Thank you very much for your support.
I’m trully filled with gratitude towards everyone.
Please continue your support towards Nogizaka’s treasured members.
I also want to do my best from square one, please support me too!
Congratulations on your graduation!