Tonight, the big announcement of senbatsu members for the 8th single!
An announcement filled with tears and laughter,
a new era for Nogizaka46 opens up!
Nogizakatte, Doko?
DON!
Nogizakatte Doko has started, we're your hosts,
Bananaman, yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
and here's... Nogizaka-chan~
Full Force.
There are a lot of them.
There are a lot of them here today, we even have the 2nd gen.
They are here today.
By the way, it’s still not everyone.
Ichiki is not here because of schoolwork,
then Takayama is now headed here from another job.
-I see.
About what we’re going to do today, Himura-san,
Please go ahead and announce it.
Today…
We’ll announce the senbatsu members for the 8th single!
It has finally arrived.
This time, the 8th single will be on sale on the 2nd of April.
That has been decided already.
I see, so we’ll determine the members for that.
That’s right.
Along with the release of the 8th single,
tonight we’ll announce the senbatsu members.
We’ll start from the formation.
This is the formation for the 8th single.
Both first and second row has five members.
And in the third row, there are six members.
Yes, that's it.
-Oh, 5-5-6
And then, the five people in the first row will be the 5-Fukujin.
There has been another change.
-5-Fukujin.
The number of Fukujin is changing.
This time we have 5-Fukujin.
A new formation with 5-5-6 members,
We’ll start the announcement of the senbatsu members from the second row.
We'll start the announcement from the second row, numbers 6-10.
With that, please go ahead.
First up,
2nd row,
#10
The first member who will enter the senbatsu is…
Fukagawa Mai
hai, omedetou~
First is Fukagawa Mai,
a row forward from her position last time.
Last time, I was in third row,
this time, I’m in the second row,
I would like to do my best without forgetting my original resolve from the start.
Thank you very much.
omedetou gozaimasu~
#10
She's the first one who made it in the 8th single senbatsu.
Let's move on.
2nd row,
#9
The next member who will be called is...
Matsumura Sayuri
Matsumura was always a front member until now,
this time she’s in the second row.
From the start, I’ve always been…
-You were always a Fukujin.
7-Fukujin and 8-Fukujin, right?
-Yes!
It may be a different way of saying that I fell but,
since I was not chosen to be in the 5-Fukujin,
I’m wondering if I was depending too much on that position.
So that I would not depend on the position,
and to keep that whatever position I end up with,
I thought I have to work hard.
That's right.
I'll do my best.
hai, omedetou gozaimasu~
#9, huh?
Very well, I'll continue with the announcement.
2nd row,
#8
There are 14 remaining spots for the senbatsu,
The next member is...
Ikuta Erika
Ikuta, hai, omedetou~
She is out from being a Fukujin member,
Ikuta, entered the senbatsu for 8 consecutive times.
Even though I dropped from being a Fukujin,
I am in the middle of the second row.
Since this is the first time I’m assigned in this position…
once again, I want to give it my all and work hard.
Thank you very much.
-hai, omedetou~
I'll continue with the announcement.
2nd row,
#7
There are two remaining spots in the second row,
the next senbatsu member is...
Wakatsuki Yumi
For Wakatsuki as well, she is out of the Fukujin,
she is in the second row just like the last time.
I’ve always been in the third row, then last time, from the 3rd row,
I’ve got a chance to be in the 2nd row and be a 8-Fukujin,
This time, I’m in the second row again,
Being in the 8-Fukujin last time,
I was able to do various challenges for myself,
I’m thinking there’s still a long way to go.
I’m really grateful for being here in 2nd row,
this is something I won’t forget.
hai, omedetou~
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
Now, four of them have been decided.
-Yes.
All that's left in the second row is just one spot.
The last member selected for the second row is...
Sakurai Reika
Okay, it's Sakurai. Omedetou~
Captain Sakurai, entered in the same position as the last single.
I really appreciate being in the 2nd row this time as well,
then there’s that feeling of wanting to try harder.
My position never changes, it has always been the farthest on the right.
I’m happy… But won’t I be able to grow?
I don’t think that’s true.
It's like, because I'm the captain...
I’m told that I’ll always be in the Fukujin.
I'd like to do my best.
Because it seems things are all set for you.
It is annoying, when it is put that way.
Please do your best in this position and shine brightly.
Yes!
An announcement filled with tears and laughter,
the arrival of a new era!
Where do we go from here? The third row?
That’s right! Doing the front row first rather than the third…
although I’m thinking we’ll start from the third row.
Very well, from here, we’re going to announce the third row.
-We’re going with the third row.
First up in the 3rd row,
#16
The first one to be called for the 3rd row is...
Takayama Kazumi
Oh? Takayama
Moodmaker, Takayama, entered the senbatsu for 8 consecutive times.
Since Takayama is currently traveling from a different job,
she’ll be notified on the phone as soon as the call connects.
There are only 10 members remaining!
Among them, who are the 10 people that’ll make it?
Let’s get going.
Nerve-wracking senbatsu announcement,
The next member is...
Wada Maaya
hai, omedetou~
She has yet to enter the senbatsu until now, Wada Maaya,
finally made it in the 8th single!
This is your first senbatsu selection.
Yes.
Ever since I joined the group, I’ve always been an Under member,
so I’m surprised,
This is the first time I was chosen as a senbatsu member.
It’s okay, don’t rush.
So that I can show what I’ve done in under now that I’m in the senbatsu,
so that I won’t hold everyone back, I want to do my best.
That's great.
#15 right?
The other members are also happy for her.
It became their joy as well.
Now, Wada has been decided,
Do we have Takayama on the line now?
Takayama?
Yes?
Eh? Takayama, you sound like an old man right now.
Impersonation?
Takayama?
Takayama, are you on your way here?
Yes, that’s right. What happened?
Takayama, right now, we're doing the senbatsu announcement.
Eh?! Right now?
-Right now.
Are you under water right now?
While diving?
You’re talking like you’re under water.
I'm not under water.
Takayama?
-Yes?
We’re here to tell you…
Eh? Right now?
We’ll tell you.
Takayama-san, you’ve made it in the 8th single senbatsu.
Thank you very much!
hai, omedetou~
This time, the formation from the front is 5-5-6.
buhi~
Now a pig?
Buhi~
In the third row, on the...
The farthest one on the right!
Ah, how did you know?
Seer?
How did you know?
-That's right, you got that right!
I just thought there’s where I’d be.
Please tell us how you feel right now.
Sorry I didn’t make it in time.
I really don't know what mood the studio has right now...
The mood is completely different!
Endless difference.
That’s what I’m concerned about right now.
I’m sorry about that.
-See you later.
Until now, there has not been a senbatsu announcement with this kind of mood.
As expected from Takayama.
Takayama got in the #16 spot, then, right now, Wada got in the #15 spot.
There are 9 remaining. Let's move along.
Next, #14, the member who will be called is...
Akimoto Manatsu
Akimoto, omedetou~
Akimoto who started in the 4th single,
entered the senbatsu for 5 consecutive times.
First of all, thank you for choosing me for the senbatsu.
I'm really happy for being in the senbatsu this time as well,
but the place I was aiming for is a little higher than this.
It seems that I can’t reach it yet with the abilities I have right now.
I’m putting a lot of effort,
Even in this 14th spot, I’ll have my own way in order to shine.
I want to find that,
and I want to be an idol who will make everyone smile.
I'll do my best.
Please proceed to the #14 spot.
-omedetou gozaimasu~
Half of the spots for senbatsu are already occupied,
the next one who’ll be called is…
Higuchi Hina
Higuchi.
hai, omedetou~
Higuchi Hina kept waiting for her chance,
she finally entered the senbatsu in the 8th single.
Your first selection?
-Yes.
So this is your first?
Her first senbatsu selection.
I've always been an Under member,
But there are those who have always supported me,
The “Hinachima Family” who are in front of their TV…
Huh?
Why did you touch me?
Suspicious behavior.
Those were your fans, right? What family was it?
Hinachima Family.
-Hinachima?
Everyone in Hinachima Family will be glad about this.
omedetou gozaimasu~
-hai, omedetou~
#13, right?
-She made it in.
Hinachima Family is really pleased right now.
They are pleased about this.
There are 7 spots remaining,
the member who will be called next is...
Kitano Hinako
Oh, there she is, a 2nd gen member.
We got one from 2nd gen.
Come here.
Kitano Hinako, following Hori from the last single,
she is the second from the 2nd gen who made it in the senbatsu.
How are you feeling after your name was called?
All of my efforts were not enough,
It’s like…
I can’t meet the expectations of those around me,
I’m always frustrated by that.
I’m bad at dancing,
then, I really think that I don’t have any good points.
From now on, so that I could meet the expectations of other people,
I would work hard every day. I hope that I’d be able to shine.
Well, the group is divided into 1st gen and 2nd gen,
but you are all a part of Nogizaka46 already.
Since you were chosen, do your best.
So that Nogizaka46 will become better, please do your best.
Well then, please proceed to the #12 spot.
-Thank you very much.
omedetou~
Kitano made it in.
-Someone from the 2nd gen made it in.
3rd row, the last person who will be called is...
Kawamura Mahiro
Kawamura Mahiro, from the debut single,
it has been 7 singles since the last time she made it in the senbatsu.
What are your thoughts the moment your name was called?
Ehh... I just can't believe it.
Everytime I don’t get selected for the senbatsu,
even on handshake events,
the fans are always comforting me.
I was thinking that I want to repay them as soon as possible.
You were finally able to repay them.
Since I am chosen for the 8th single,
I'll do it with all I got.
Do your best, okay? Please proceed to your spot.
All that's left is the 1st row,
This time, we have the 5-Fukujin.
-Yes!
Only 5 people left.
After this, the front members are decided!
The first row will be announced in this order,
5→1→4→2→3
-Okay.
Very well, first up,
1st row,
#5
Finally, the front members will be announced,
the first one is…
Ikoma Rina
Okay, Ikoma!
Ikoma who has 5 singles worth of center experience.
impressively made it as a front member.
About the row... it’s been a while since I got in the 1st row,
-Is that so?
Oh, I see, so that’s how it goes.
Recently, in various variety shows or even live shows,
What I’m thinking of the most is the benefit for Nogizaka46, more than for myself.
But I’m also wondering if I’m getting noticed by other people.
But this time, I was given a spot where I could easily be seen.
I won’t waste this chance,
so that I can be noticed by other people as well,
I want to give it all I’ve got.
”For myself, for the group,” I think it’s good to have those kinds of worries.
I mean, this is not a group that has been around for a decade,
Aren’t those various activities you do each day what makes you grow?
I’ll do my best.
-Please do your best.
Please proceed to the #5 spot.
Then right here, Takayama arrived late because of another job.
What do you think about this?
Uhmm, eh?
I'm surprised with this formation.
Kitano, a 2nd gen, also made it in.
Ahh,
Hhmm,
Higuchi made it in.
That’s great. I’m happy for her.
Kawamura as well.
So there’s where Ikoma-chan is.
Ah~ I see.
What is your impression about this?
Wait a sec, you’re not an old woman so you don’t have to talk like that.
Gossip?
”Ah, so, there’s where she is.”
Well, it’s about the mood right? The atmosphere in this studio…
-I don’t have an idea about it.
I’m really happy I got in,
For the next single, moving a step closer…
Ah! So there’s where Maimai is.
New discovery after another!
What are you doing?
Just go to your spot.
Do your best, okay?
Certainly, coming in a senbatsu announcement with this kind of timing, you can’t really grasp what the atmosphere is.
It’s like, she’s surprised with the position the members have.
What are you discussing about over there?!
Murmuring is prohibited!
Very well, I'll continue with the announcement.
1st row,
#1
The next front member who will be selected is...
Hori Miona
In the last single, Hori is selected as the center.
For the 8th single, she is a front member.
I was first selected as a senbatsu member in the 7th single,
then I was the center.
At first, I was very anxious.
I was wondering if that was okay,
I was really scared, and then I had all sorts of thoughts,
but the surrounding senpais also supported me a lot.
It was a personality that I had never seen before.
It's like...
I was thinking that I wanted to do more things myself.
This time, I want to work hard in this position my own way.
Please proceed to the #1 spot.
-Thank you very much.
Now then, Himura-san.
-Yes?
The last center, Hori, is called in this spot.
It’s great, Hori even made it in the 5-Fukujin.
There are three spots remaining,
who will be called for the #4 spot?
Hashimoto Nanami
omedetou~~~~
A Fukujin member in all of the previous singles, Hashimoto,
she is in the front row this time as well.
Since I’ll be at the same position as before,
I guess for those people who will come to see me in live shows, they will be able to see me easily.
Beyond that,
I will do my best in order to become a person who will be noticed regardless of my position.
Although there are those who are familiar with you already.
But aim for the top. Do your best.
Thank you very much.
#4 spot right? omedetou gozaimasu~
hai, omedetou~
After this, with the announcement of the center comes a new era!
Very well, I'll continue with the announcement.
1st row,
#2
Next, 1st row, #2,
Whose name will be called?
Shiraishi Mai
hai, omedetou~
Shiraishi who served as the center for the 6th single,
following the last single, she made it in as a front member.
I’ve been chosen as a senbatsu from the beginning,
For every single, I have seen a lot of issues about myself that I have to address from within,
I find myself growing up little by little because of it.
I can see the members around me working hard,
I think that’s why Nogizaka was able to grow immensely to this point,
For the 8th single, I’m assigned at the same position as the last single,
So that I can support the members around me properly,
and so that I can bring my own color out, I’d like to keep working hard.
Please work hard in the 8th single, do it as Nogizaka’s face.
-I’ll do my best.
Please do your best.
-Thank you very much.
This is the birth to a new center no matter who gets chosen,
Whose hands will it be handed to?
Nishino Nanase
Nishino who entered the front row last time,
is appointed as Nogizaka46’s 4th center.
It’s like…
Even back then, because I was never a person who would be at a situation similar to being a center...
I do not feel anything right now.
I‘ve heard that the person who would become a center
is someone who can bring out the strengths of the surrounding members.
So that I could bring out the strengths of the surrounding members…
I’d like to learn a lot from this opportunity.
Please shine. Please proceed to the center spot.
It’s a really interesting one this time.
With the new center Nishino in the middle,
The new look of Nogizaka46 starts at the 8th single!