Nogizaka46 7th single campaign
Eh? You’re going here?
This time, all members are going to various waterfalls over the country to do a hit prayer.
And then, a shocking development for the members?!
You’re kidding, right?
Nogizakatte Doko
Sekkachi na Katatsumuri Fans sub
translator:hadie.azazel
timer:hadie.azazel
sub ini masih jauh dari kata sempurna
masih banyak kesalahan makna dan kata dan juga kalimat
harap di maklumin
↑Credits to Sekkachi na Katatsumuri Fans sub
for the original Indonesian sub and timing.↓
www.zaka46sembung.blogspot.com
and visit
www.nogizaka46art.tumblr.com
DON! Nogizakatte Doko has started, we’re your hosts, Bananaman.
-Yoroshiku Onegeshimasu
and they are...
Nogizaka-chan~
Finally, on the 27th of November,
the long awaited 7th single “Barette” is on sale!
That being said, this time…
During the time of release of a new single,
this show always do a campaign.
Established tradition
You’ve done a lot of things in the past, right?
In the past, the members have done various harsh campaigns
such as sky diving, waterfall and bungee jumping.
What are the details for this campaign?
This is what you’ll do this time…
Jan!
Waterfall
Again?
Is this a joke?
We’ve done that before!
Here’s the catch, this time...
All 17 members will be pounded by the waterfall.
All of them.
What is it? What is it?
What’s up with all of you?
Hori, is it alright with you?
She don’t know anything about it, right?
-About what?
She don’t know about the waterfall era…
Waterfall era?
That’s right, Nogizaka is significantly divided by it, right?
there’s time prior to the waterfall era and waterfall era up to the present.
Mysterious waterfall standard
Why are you dividing it with the waterfall?
Take a look at the four teams,
Each team will go to a waterfall singled out from all over the country.
Then, the four waterfalls that caught our attention are..
Gunma’s waterfall
Here’s the next one.
Kanagawa’s waterfall
Next,
Okinawa’s waterfall
Pleasant waterfall?
and last
Iwate’s waterfall
It’s cold.
Here are the details regarding the four waterfalls.
Average temperature
Average water temperature
Iwate has the harshest temperatures,
and of course, Okinawa has the warmest.
Who wants to go to Okinawa?
I do!
Natural outcome
Who wants to go to Iwate?
That’s odd.
To be fair, draw lots will determine which waterfall the teams will go to.
First up is “NO” team, which waterfall will they get?
Right here!
Gunma!
Okay, you’ll go to Gunma.
The end.
Next, “GI” team’s destination is?
Okinawa
Okinawa appeared!
It appeared, huh?
Please go to Okinawa.
Fresh team! No doubt.
The ones remaining are Kanagawa and Iwate falls,
Which one will the “ZA” team get?
Green team,
Iwate!
Magnificent!
With that, the waterfall assigned to “KA” team is determined.
Will they be able to do a safe hit prayer?
Today, we arrived at Daijouin, Odawara City, Kanagawa Prefecture.
We have a bit of a sad news…
One of our members, Ikuta Erika,
fractured her pinky toe a few days ago.
Because she can’t do the waterfall,
Serious Injury
she’s not here today.
Ikuta is out because of a fractured pinky toe,
a disappointing way to retire from the campaign.
What caused this frightening accident?
How did it happen?
Detergent!
Yes.
A brand new bottle of detergent fell on her toe, right?
While hurrying in the morning, the bottle detergent goes “BO!” then her pinky toe goes “KA!”
Hashimoto enjoys others’
misfortune, huh?
It was terrible right?
-I’m surprised by it.
Fracture because of bottled detergent?
Can that really happen?
Let’s all do our best together and fill in Ikuchan’s share!
And here to guide them is Daijouin’s head priest, En Junkou-san
and his deputy, En Komyou-san
This ritual is also called “Goma daki”
Before going to the waterfall, first they have to do the ritual of writing
their wish on a piece of wood and throw it into the fire and pray.
Everyone wished for the 7th single “Barrette” to be a big hit,
then they put the firewood containing their wish into the fire.
After the ritual, finally they’re headed to the waterfall.
What kind of waterfall will “KA” team face?
Today, the water volume is twice more than usual.
You are all going up there.
You’re going in there.
You’re going in this waterfall.
This is the Takigou waterfall.
With the water falling from a height of 12 meters,
it will echo even within the body’s core.
It will relentlessly drain the stamina of those who will try this.
Desperation, become serious, make an effort towards austerity.
Do you understand?
Yes!
Takigou falls that almost no one can go into,
going forward on a road without tracks,
climbing with the use of ladder.
This is quite impressive
According to the head priest, the waterfall have to be purified first.
The four members are overwhelmed by the force of the waterfall.
Before going to the waterfall, the deputy head priest
teach them the way of praying.
When you pray, you say your wishes and then say “BORON” (fulfillment)
Then face the waterfall,
and then say thank you.
Speak loudly.
Nanamin, do your best!
Start praying!
Do your best~
Praying for the 7th single, Barrette, to be a big hit!
Sing up!
By the window in the library, female students whisper, conspiring~
The prayer! The prayer!
Praying for the 7th single, Barrette, to be a big hit!
and for a stronger body!
Boron!!
Boron!
Thank you very much!
You did great.
Go right there.
Endure it, do your best!
Praying for the 7th single, Barrette, to be a big hit!
That’s nice,
When you see them like this,
It makes you want
to support them.
By chance, our eyes met as if you peeked into my heart.
I already raised the white flag.
Praying for the 7th single to be a big hit!
Boron~
Boron~!!!
Boron
Boron~!!
Thank you very much!
Go a little bit further.
Right here, right here.
Praying for Nogizaka46’s 7th single, Barrette, to become a big hit!
By the window in the library, female students whisper, conspiring~
Praying for “Barrette” to become a big hit!
and for everyone’s health and happiness!
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
Boron~!!!
-One more time!
-Boron~!!
Boron~!
Thank you very much!
-Thank you very much!
Please go ahead.
Praying for the 7th single, Barrette, to be a big hit!
Suddenly the water volume
seems to amped up.
While reading Hemmingway,
female students whisper, conspiring..
Eh? Aren’t the lyrics different?
-Reika’s lyrics are different!
In the midst of panic.
Boron~!
Thank you very much!
At the end, to wish for a hit, everyone sang “Barrette”
Hashimoto’s shaking.
It seems you want to
wrap it up quickly.
Big hit!
Thank you very much!
Okay, go here.
He went right in!
He went to the waterfalls.
Praying for the 7th single, Barrette, to become a big hit!
Boron~!!!!
Boron~!
Thank you very much!
Well done.
Boron~!!
Good for you.
Ikuta is not here today too.
Why?
What’s the matter?
Fracture…
-Pinky toe…
Hashimoto really likes others’ misfortune,
Can’t stop laughing
Hashimoto, how did it happened again?
A brand new bottle of detergent dropped on her toe, fracturing it.
She just keeps on laughing.
Her bone broke just because of that, huh?
It’s so brittle, right?
Seems wonderful…
After this, shocking development strikes to the members?!
There you have it, ”NO” team have come to Gunma!
We’ve arrived in Gunma!
Maiyan’s hometown.
Maiyan~
No, not Maiyan.
Today, it seems like we’re short of one person.
It seems so.
Kazumin’s not here!
Takayama absent
What happened?
What happened to Kazumin?
Kazumin is in a bad shape.
With Takayama out, “NO” team is reduced to three.
The three immediately faced the waterfall.
What on earth awaits them?
I could see it.
Wait, that one?
We are going there.
From this point, climbing up a trackless path takes 15 minutes.
The spray of water…
Eh? You’re kidding?
Pretty amazing.
The three will face a waterfall with a boasting height of 37 meters,
Tanashita Fudou falls.
One of the top 100 waterfalls in Japan,
this place is also used by monks for their training.
Among the waterfalls we have this time, this is the harshest.
This waterfall is perfectly suited for the hit prayer,
Will the three of them be able to do this?
First, the three prayed for their safety.
Eyes open!
Then, finally, the three are headed to the waterfall.
First, their bodies are purified with salt.
That was rough!
Isn’t this rough?
Emphasizes on the face
It hurts!
But this is a part
of the purification, right?
It’s an interesting prayer.
Something like this..
That hurts!
Interesting.
At this point, Ikoma is…
Shivers.
Is it cold?
It was cold that day, but…
So cold… So cold… So cold…
Is that salt sticking
on your face?
I suddenly felt really cold.
Let’s go!
-All right!
To get used to the cold, the three get in the water.
But right here, an accident regarding Ikoma.
Abiraunken!
Abiraunken~!
Abiraunken
Let’s go!
-All right!
Not good.
Seriously, this is not good.
It hurts!
I’m really sorry…
Ikoma panicked while in the water,
Ikoma unexpectedly retires here.
As expected, Hashimoto is laughing hard.
Finally, just the two of them entered the waterfall,
Will they be able to fill in Ikoma and Takayama’s share?
Do your best.
Abiraunken~! Abiraunken~! Abiraunken~!
Wakatsuki, taking turns with Matsumura.
The water is quite strong.
Abiraunken~! Abiraunken~! Abiraunken~!
Habiruanken ?
Abiraunken.
Abirau, right?
Abiraunken!
Both of them can’t withstand the cold and strong water pressure…
However, after that is…
Above the rock.
Eh? You’re going in there?
That’s so cool!
Then, Wakatsuki go towards the rocky area.
You’re really doing this?
This is really cool.
But it’s dangerous if you
can’t withstand the pressure.
That’s right.
Abiraunken! Abiraunken! Abiraunken!
That’s a good one,
Wakatsuki
7th single, yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
You forgot to mention
the title of the single.
Then, Matsumura also go for the second time on the waterfall.
Abiraunken! Abiraunken! Abiraunken!
Abiraunken!
7th single, yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
Abiraunken! Abiraunken! Abiraunken!
You’re cold.
That’s great.
Really cool.
It’s over with this, right?
Doing even Ikoma and Takayama’s share,
These two displayed their admirable will-power.
However, what was waiting for them is…
Unexpected third time.
Wakatsuki, Matsumura, on their sudden journey to the waterfall…
That’s cool.
It’s really cool!
The water is strong.
Abiraunken! Abiraunken! Abiraunken!
Intense, right?
Praying for the 7th single, to become a big hit! Yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
-Onegaishimasu!
Se~
No~
”Barrette, it rests on your hair”
"like a large butterfly"
"Barrette, raising its wings,"
"not wanting to be noticed, it sits still, like me.”
Barrette, yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
Team “NO,” a splendid hit prayer, a big success!
Team NO’s waterfall campaign was excellent, but…
Let’s start off with Takayama.
I’m really sorry.
Why? What happened?
From the previous recording, that one with the draw lots,
I have cough.
You were coughing, right?
Then it got worse…
that’s why…
You are considering your physical condition.
Disappointing stoppage from doctor
The doctor stopped you from participating.
Then, among the three who are able to do this,
suddenly on the last minute, Ikoma.
Trauma switch: ON
You got terrified?
I deeply apologize.
So with that, it became just the two of you.
-Yes
-These two are amazing.
Furthermore, they did it a lot of times.
When you thought it was over, the monk is right there like DADAN!
DADAN!
That was really funny.
I never thought that we’ll go there.
I’ve never heard that we’ll do it several times.
So you’ve never heard that you’ll do it three times
I thought it was over after my turn, then when I got out he is already on top!
Constantly going off on his own.
With that timing?
DADAN, please get on with this.
After this, the new song “Barrette”
will be performed in this program for the first time.
Please watch the studio performance of the new song “Barrette”
Barrette
Lyrics:Akimoto Yasushi
Music:Saito Yoshihiro
Barrette, it rests on your hair
like a large butterfly.
Barrette
raising its wings,
not wanting to be noticed, it sits still
like me.
By the window in the library,
female students whisper, conspiring,
While reading Hemmingway,
I glanced over them.
Tracing the movements of their lips in my mind
Can I get a hint?
By chance, our eyes met
As if you peeked into my heart
I already raised the white flag.
Barrette, in the wind,
You hold down your dancing hair.
Barrette, the sun,
Ah, it seems so bright,
I had to avert my eyes
It’s like you
Barrette, a lot like you,
with your mischievous eyes,
you smiled at me,
I wonder why?
www.zaka46sembung.blogspot.com
visit my tumblr
www.nogizaka46art.tumblr.com