m 0 0 l 155 0 l 155 35 l 0 35
m 0 0 m 6 5 l 10 5 b 8 12 8 17 11 22 b 12 23 14 17 15 15 l 18 17 b 17 21 14 26 12 26 b 8 26 5 20 5 17 b 5 13 5 8 6 5 m 19 6 l 22 5 b 27 9 28 17 28 22 l 24 23 b 25 18 23 10 19 6 m 34 4 l 51 4 l 52 7 b 50 8 47 10 44 11 l 42 9 b 43 9 45 8 45 7 b 43 7 38 7 34 8 m 36 14 l 38 16 b 32 23 40 22 43 22 b 46 22 50 22 53 21 l 53 25 b 46 26 33 27 32 21 b 32 20 33 14 36 14 m 68 2 l 72 2 l 72 5 l 81 5 l 81 8 l 72 8 l 72 11 l 80 11 l 80 14 l 72 14 l 72 18 b 75 18 79 21 81 22 l 78 26 b 76 23 74 23 72 22 b 72 25 69 27 65 27 b 61 27 58 24 58 22 b 59 17 63 15 68 17 l 68 14 l 59 14 l 59 11 l 68 11 l 68 8 l 58 8 l 58 5 l 68 5 l 68 2 m 62 21 b 62 22 64 23 65 23 b 66 23 69 23 68 20 b 66 19 64 19 62 21  SUBS
The 1st Event, Nogizaka46 Talent Showdown
Tonight, Nogizaka46 members will take on a talent showdown challenge
The members have been grouped into 8 groups and separated into team Red and White
The members will perform their act that they've practiced for 2 weeks
They will be scored on their performance and the team with the most points win!
With nervousness of doing a one-shot contest, they will explode their effort and will-power
The excitement and impression flowing in studio
Nogizakatte Doko in 2014, start!
Nogizakatte Doko?
Translated by Kanarin46, Jiaemi, Adel & Hayate, Timed by Michael Soares, QC by mahousentai
For more subs visit www.facebook.com/IkomaSubs | www.UKN48.com
Brought to you by IkomaSubs
This time,
It'll be serious.
All of you have done this in 2 weeks, right?
You've trained.
Yes
I see...
Actually, you're gonna do a live concert in Budoukan, right?
Actually this recording is just before the important concert last year
Frankly speaking, now is not the time to do this, right?
What do you think?
Although you are very busy now, but yet you all made it.
We'll do our best
That's great
This time, the winning team's MVP will get a present from Himura
Already usual thing
What kind of present?
Himura's present is...
A coat
Yeaaahh!!!
Himura's Present (Third Time)
What the hell is that?
Himura will be in charge as judge
They will be evaluated from techniques, arts, efforts, team play, and their smile, with a total score of 50.
First Round, first contestant from Red Team
What are you going to perform?
We will do a Magic Show
Magic Show?
You'll do that?
On the other side, what will Team White perform first?
Chinese Spinning Top
Wah, Chinese Spinning Top, huh
Is it something like this?
It looks difficult
Yes, it's really difficult
So, for first round, Magic Show from Red Team
Red Team's starter, include these four, who in the beginning couldn't even open the box of cards
With no member that is skillful, they have been training hard under the instructor
There's no room for mistakes
Let the magic begin.
Ready, go
It's Showtime
Okay...
First, here I have some unfolded trump card boxes
One, two, and three
I'll fold this box to its real shape
As you see, there's nothing inside hence it won't produce any sound
But, when I cast a spell on it
Huh?
From the inside, there is a Trump Card
Next, Ikoma-san, please
Okay...
So, I'm going to shuffle the cards that I received from Hori-chan
I'll do the shuffle normally
Try to imagine the usual me
Bad at Sports,
Clumsy
But, I'm...
You are very clumsy
I am, yes.
I'll do this
Wah, that's good
As I'm done shuffling, I will spread the cards
They have spread nicely
Eh, you're good
One more trick
If I spread it in a straight line, it will do as I say
Ha ha ha, wow, that's neat
But, the real magic starts now
So, what should I do?
She's is facing backwards
Ah, Himura-san.
Pick what you like from these cards
Point it with my finger?
Yes, any card will do
Which one did you choose?
Ah, I pick this
-This card?
-Yes
The card that you picked is this
Is that OK?
-Yes
Please show this to everyone
You don't see it?
I won't look at it
Show it to this camera
You've remembered it?
Please, put it back here
I'll close them
Himura-san please shuffle them
I'll do it
Yes, please
He will shuffle them randomly
Shuffle them randomly so I don't know where the card is
To avoid suspicion, any of the members can shuffle it too
Shiraishi's shuffling it too
It's okay this way?
I'm capable of performing magic.
It's absolutely shuffled
This time, I'll pass it to Manatsu
Manatsu will do it from now?
So, for Himura-san's card
You're kidding right?
Haven't we seen this before
This legendary saber will pick the card
What kind of legend?
This legendary saber is truly sharp
I'm scared
Eh, why?
Is there any magician like that?
Now, I will show what Himura-san's card is
For that, Ikoma-chan please
Okay, these card that you all shuffled will be put inside this hat
Now, I have cast the spell
Oh, legendary saber, please show us Himura-san's card
Wow, they're joking, right
Ah, it got stabbed
If that is the same card...
The card that you picked
Is no doubt an 8 Diamonds, right?
Eeeh, amazing!
Is this right?
Yes!
It is amazing
Why did she know it?
Next trick, I will put this card in here
I will put this card into this wooden box
The card is teared apart
I put it in
Then, zukkyun ♥
And, the card's gone like this
It's gone
And for the missing card,
Minami will show it
Here she is
What will Hoshino do?
As you can see, I'm wearing a black t-shirt now
Manatsu, give me the power
Zukkyun ♥
What was that?
From Manatsu's power
ta-dah!
Eh, why?
Eight of diamonds card is there
Last, we'll cast another spell
Go!
What will happen?
O,
Shi,
Mai. (The End)
Yeah!
Wow, that's amazing
Somehow, this is quite something
You've been training hard for this?
Yes we have
Is it necessary to train for this?
I've never succeeded in it before...
Really? You failed at this so many times before?
The first success
Yes, she did
But this can be considered good, right?
It's wonderful!
Well, next is the White Team
First round is Chinese Spinning Top
Be able to spin the top continuously is the basics of everything.
Members have been constantly practicing it.
Furthermore, while incorporating individual techniques,
they have been under heavy pressure when they practiced combination techniques as there is no room for mistakes.
These five members put in the most time practicing out of all the teams
Can they show it in a one shot game?
Start the Music!
Seira, go for it!
Here I go
Ah, I see...
Go for it!
Ready, Go!
Crap, it isn't spinning
It isn't spinning
Go for it~
I did it!
Here, ready, go!
Ready, go!
We did it!
At the last part, It touched the mic
Well, can't do anything about it
That's amazing and it looks very difficult but we don't know where's the difficulty
The difficult part is getting it to spin
I have never done this before
It's difficult to keep the balance
Because Wada can't do it
It won't spin
(Singing something)
It is difficult
To even incorporate with techniques, that is not something that can be easily done
Pass the top to me
Can't get away the song
Okay, you've all done it
So now, we want to know the scores
First, Red Team's Magic Show. How much will they get?
After this, the scores will be revealed
First contestant, Red Team's Magic Show, what will their score be?
Nine, ten, nine, ten, ten. And total is?
48 points
Now then,
White Team's Chinese Spinning Top Show's score is?
Let's have a look
Nine, nine, nine, ten,
Nine and total score is
46 points
Ah, it's 46!
Even when they lose...
46 has come out, eh?
Second round,
Red Team will show?
Ready... go, we'll show Tap Dance
Ah, tap dance you said.
And for the opponent, White Team's Nishino and Matsumura
Just the two of you?
- Yes, us two
What will you show?
Ventriloquist Manzai
Okay, let's see Red Team's Tap Dance
They have been given the choreography from the first day
They have been constantly practicing it to remember the rhythm
With Noujou who has experience as the center, a choreography with high level individual techniques is complete
Well then, It's show time!
Wow, It's amazing!
It is amazing
It's good...
Amazing!
You did it!
That's perfect
Noujou, You have some experience in this, don't you?
Yes, I did this for one year when I was in 3rd grade of elementary
It's only one year?
And, for the rest it's first time?
Yes, it is
This tap dance can't be done in a few weeks
How much tapping do you do?
This is two times, and this is one time, right?
Himura-san, can you do it?
Himura can do it
Wow, amazing!
But, it's still amazing
This is hard, for the first timer, you can't really understand it, can you?
The way to wear this heels is kinda...
But those are the usual heels
Those really are
Same with shoes
After this, Ventriloquist manzai will be shown
For second round, White Team will perform Ventriloquist Manzai
They have to practice to ensure the voice they use with the doll is the same at all times.
They must talk without moving their lips
And then, they had a problem with matching the words with dolls
But, the most difficult problem is the manzai
This is their problem which is more important than anything else
The results of their vigorous training... Ventriloquist Manzai!
Hello...
I'm Nishino
I'm Matsumura
I'm Akie
The three of us together we're...
Fourth Generation J Soul Brothers!
Well, with these three, we have to work hard
Hey, hey, hey! You forgot one person!
Ah, I kinda forgot you were there since you didn't have any presence!
In 2013, a lot of things happened~
Don't proceed on your own, I haven't introduced myself
So, please
I'm Hiroshi
Yes, yoroshiku. Okay
Eh? That's poor treatment!
What did you say after you said 'The three of us are'
Eh?
Fourth Generation J Soul Brothers, Mega Max
You extended the introduction! Did you ask for permission to do that?
I didn't. I can't do that?
Of course you can't
Change how you say it!
Well, how about this?
Ringo-hime who's come from Ringo's country, Nacchan, and Akie
You extended it further and didn't include me again!
Ah, you're so annoying
If it's so, let's just call you as a doll
Eh?
Am I not gonna get any nickname?
You're lack of affection!
Can I start first?
Yes, go ahead
Year 2014 is getting close
Err, but...
A lot of things happened in 2013, right Kie-chan?
Yes, there was
"Ain't I wild?"
That's in 2012
For events in 2013, there is that, Kie-chan?
Ah, 'that' is
Je! Je! Je! Je! Je!
It's not that!
But it can't be helped even if we keep clinging onto things from last year
Just like new year's day, let's decide this year's goal
Ah, it's true. But normally..
Because I haven't thought about this year's goal, how about making a syllable essay?
Well, Hiroshi..
Please say a word for the syllable essay
Well, how about 'Nogizaka' at first?
Nogizaka right? I will say Nogizaka's goal, okay..
Well, first is Nanase...
And then Sayuri
Me, and the next is Akie. How about that?
Okay, start from me
'No'
Have a big expectation
Oh, it's true
Then, 'Gi'
Aim to be first in the business world
That's quite good!
'Za'. Roughly to say...
'Ka'
Earn plenty of money!
It's too real!
Please say something more Idol-ish
Then, let's go to the next one
For next,
let's use Ta-ka-ya-ma (Kazumi), a suitable goal for Kazumin
Then, 'Ta'
To aim for higher personal goals
'Ka'
To make the goals come true for sure!
'Ya'
She seems like she can do it
'Ma'
Accumulate a lot of money!
Again?!
Then, let's use the word A-Ki-Mo-To (Manatsu), think of a suitable goal for Manatsu-san
This time, start from Hiroshi
Ah, me? Okay, then...
'A'
Full of energy and cheerful
'Ki'
Put some fighting spirit!
'Mo'
From a higher place...
Let her skydive from!
Oi!
Ah no, let's just leave it aside
Well, a syllable essay has been done perfectly
Let's close it with Hiroshi's special skill
It's so sudden, I don't know why I have to do that
Well, let's just do that. Ikkokudou's delayed to be heard voice
Ohh...
Ah, that is. Okay, I'll do it
Eh?
The voice...
Comes...
Late...
To be heard
That is what Sayurin said
That is something you shouldn't say!
That's all from us, Fourth Generation J Soul Brothers!
Please remember at least our names and performance act!
They won't be able to remember our entire performance!!
Thank you very much
Well, thank you
Thank you
Ah, I see
It's greater than I expected
Really?
Your teacher is the one who is wearing glasses, isn't it?
Yes, that woman
She's the person who laughed the most
Parental Love
My complex is that my lips doesn't move when I speak
Oh, you've said it before
I wondered if I can use it as my advantage
That's right. This is suited for you
It becomes your special skill
That's why she could do it immediately
Try to say 'Thank You'
Thank you
Oh, it doesn't move
What's your name?
I'm Akie
And you, what's your name?
Nishino
As a result, who is the winner?
Okay, first for Red Team's tap dance.
I'm curious, because Himura can do it for the first performance
That maybe so
The only regrettable factor
How will it be scored, right?
Well, their score is?
Nine, nine, ten, ten, nine.
Total is...
47 points
It's strict
From a technique perspective, I think they did great.
Within two weeks, they can do this much already, along with individual techniques. I think it's awesome.
It's just that, I can do it too.
So that's the minus points
Next, the opponent,
White Team's Ventriloquist Manzai
Their score is?
Ten, nine, ten, nine, ten.
Total is...
48 points
Yay, we did it.
You lose by one point
Frankly speaking, when I heard they will do Manzai, I think we'll win this
Underestimating
You all just lost to these two?
The first solo performance of Nogizaka in Budoukan a few days ago
Along with the passion from the fans,
A Birthday Live at Yokohama Arena has been announced.
You can order the ticket in our official site or mobile site after this show ends
Please check the official site or mobile site for more info
Next episode, there's even more talent and make everyone in the studio were deeply moved and teary