This is a fansubbed video, 100% accuracy isn't guaranteed.
This week's Nogidoko
Is a special episode before Valentine's Day
Chaos breaks out when chocolates are exchanged!?
Sweetness and bitterness mixed together
And now, a Bittersweet valentine!
Hello everyone, we're the hosts of Nogidoko, Bananaman
And here is Nogizaka
Oh, what are they holding
FOR YOU
Good good, you guys pulled that off with just a few seconds on air
What is everyone holding
That means all the members have presents
So, the topic of today's episode, Himura-san
Here
Say it with a voice as sweet as chocolate please
The show is starting
Which member will you give your gift to
Nogizaka's own Valentines
It's almost Valentine's Day eh
But Nogizaka has a love-ban rule
I see
But it's ok for the members to date one another isn't it
Secret rule?
So you can date other members
Is that true
Today's episode
Will allow Nogizaka members who have been looking forward to Valentines
To experience their own version of Valentines
However they can only give their presents to one member in Nogizaka
And not only chocolates
This time
There are also hand-picked presents for the target
Chocolates and gifts
You have it ready eh
Yes
The only thing left is to give it out
It's very interesting
-Ah
Like "Oh, so that person likes me"
Right
Or "Ah, that person didn't give it to me"
Many relationships will be exposed
I see
I will say this before we start, frankly
Of course there will be someone who won't get a present
such is life
That kind of feeling
Himura-san you're no stranger to it, right
Why me?
He represents avg. men
Wanting that person to know your true feelings
So
Let's go
The first person will be very important
Isn't that right
First is important
Let's start with Wakatsuki
Eh, what, why?
Wakatsuki-san, who are you giving your present to
From me?
So please
Step off to the front
There's a weird feeling of nervousness heh
There is
I didn't think my heart would beat like this
Because this is the real deal, giving gifts to another member
Yes
This time chocolates for love is more serious than chocolates for friendship
More serious than love
Yes, it's true it's more special than chocolates for someone you love
Of course it is
Now
Let's start
Who does Wakatsuki want to give her chocolate to?
The audience is more nervous of course
Sakurai Reika
Sakurai?
Really?
You look embarrassed
but happy at the same time
Obviously happy
Jumping up and down
I'm very happy
Happy huh
Sakurai please step out
What to do now?
What's this?
What's happening?
Why the nervousness?
This is good
Strangely flustered
Things like this also happen between girls huh
Right
This feeling
When you give the chocolate
Please say a few things
Say something, as if you're confessing
Please
Usually I've always called you partner this, partner that
But I never had a chance to show my gratitude
You're close to me
But I've never expressed it with the word 'love'
Real confession?
What's this?
This is good
This is me saying thank you and love! Thanks
EXCELLENT
Very good
This scene is good
Not bad at all
Aren't you happy to hear that
Super happy actually
Normally calling each other "partner", are you two close?
But can't say the word "love" huh
That's right, I can't really say it
Even "thank you"
Because I'm not the type to express my feelings so...
Really
Yes
You love her?
Love...
You love Sakurai huh?
Oh !
Yes, I do!
Good
Sakurai is very happy aren't you
Yes
Of course
Super happy
What to do now?
You two are pretty close right?
Yes, super close
Because we're always together
The present
Why don't you take a look at what's inside
What could it be
I don't know
Eh? You're not kidding me?
What is it?
Reika said before she wants whiter skin
So I bought a whitening pack and even something to put on the skin
Serious present
Oh
This is amazing, I'm happy
Happy huh?
Because she knows what you want, so she got you these
Eh~~~ Thank you
I will definitely use it
Thank you....ah I'm so embarrassed
This is such an amazing segment!
It is
Heartwarming
Really good
Anyway
And
This is only natural
Because everyone all brought a present today
We will see
If there's a case
Where the feeling is mutual...
or not...
So let's confirm Sakurai's feelings...
If she gives her chocolate to Wakatsuki
Then the feeling is mutual
Let's confirm. Do you want to return her feelings?
No...
No???
Not her!?
So it's someone else
The person that gave the gift first like me is super embarrassed
But they're [partners]...
Something just broke down
Wait, what is this
Wakatsuki, don't you feel embarrassed?
I am
Sakurai is hugging tightly but Wakatsuki isn't returning the embrace
I'm super embarassed
What a shock!
Better prepare yourselves
No, no
How sad
I'm very hurt
No
So Wakatsuki, please go back to your seat...
Wakatsuki-san
Wakatsuki Wakatsuki
Wakatsuki can't even look her in the eye
There moments are very cruel
So things like this can also happen
I love you, love you!
Love you the most!
Too late.
The most in the world huh
Love love love you
The next person to confess is Sakurai, who rejected Wakatsuki
Who does she want to give her chocolate to?
Naachan
Nishino
Wait!
Here comes new challengers!
This keep getting better
Ikoma, Higuchi
Don't you take my Naachan!
All of you want to give it to Nishino eh, amazing
Nishino is popular!
What's this feeling of nervousness
Now I understand what it's like for popular guys at school
The words "Wait a minute!" have appeared in Nogizaka's Valentines
Let's hear their confessions first
Sakurai goes first, please
You are the center for our 8th single
I figured you'd worry a lot
But we're friends of the same age and generation
So I will do my best to help you
Let's work together to create an amazing single!
Let us take care of each other
A new way to confess
I see
Seeing Captain being all serious like that
I feel a bit embarrassed
Please be my Oshimen forever!
I will always support you! Take care!
I see, so it's her oshimen
You're a fan?
Yes, fan!
Really
I believe no one beats me when it comes to being a Naachan oshi
I see
Top Wota Declaration
Ah, embarassing
Higuchi
It's Higuchi's turn
The smile, fashion or style of Naachan
I love them all! Please accept these presents!
What is this
Seems like a lot of gifts
Higuchi sure gave a lot
Presents from 3 people huh
Start with Sakurai's and go from there
It's big, I don't know what it might be
Woah it's huge
There's a box
Huh?
What's going on?
What's that
What is it Nishino
She's looking and still can't figure out what it is
Snail?
Sakurai, what did you give her?
Snail version of Human Anatomy
Weird gift
Why, why did you give that as a present
Because I like weird things
Naachan likes stuff like pigeons
I want her to know about my interests too
Also recently Naachan showed interest in snails so...
Is that true?
Probably not
Lately, you're interested in snails?
No...
"What kind of shape does a snail's mouth have eh?
I'm curious!"
Because she said things like that
So I thought "Ah, snails"
That's why you chose that gift
It's true that I talked about snails' mouths
I'm really happy because she still remembers that
Next is Ikoma's present
Looks small
I think she will like it
What is it?
Bookstore gift certificates
Bookstore gift certificates!
This is a gift for serious people
Because Naachan likes Manga
And we talk about it all the time
So I thought instead of buying gifts, I got her bookstore certificates
She can use it to buy books that she likes
Ah, letting her chooses the books for herself and not choosing it for her
Giving actual gifts is nice but
I want her to buy things she likes...
You're very considerate
Lastly, Higuchi's present
Because I heard Naachan is sensitive to the cold
I gave her a pair of warm socks
It says right there 'warm bath powder'
Everything has the word "tori" (bird) that Naachan likes
Ah because she likes pigeons
These presents are very well thought out
Amazing
Hie (cold) tori (bird) hie tori go well together
Hie tori = To get warm
The handkerchief is embroidered with a bird Naachan likes
Birds everywhere
And a cup with the design from Naachan's favorite manga
What manga
JOJO
Oh, JOJO!
My feeling is written on there
Higuchi's feeling
This is the sound of a kiss isn't it
Your message is like that?
The feeling of Zukkyun
Recently Nishino has taken a liking to snails though
But nevertheless you spent time on choosing the gifts
Amazing
Nishino is really popular
We're still alright so far
Yes, so far
We're still alright
Now is the time to check with her
3 people have confessed to Nishino
Is her target among them
Please
Now, Nishino
In these 3 girls, is there a person that you want to give chocolate to?
Yes!
Wakatsuki, did you hear that?
Rubbing salt in the wound
Wakatsuki don't mind it
It's not related, everyone here loves you
Are you 3 feeling tense now?
Yes, my heart is skipping.
Higuchi, how do you feel?
It's very complicated...
You want it to be you, isn't that true?
Yes
Definitely want it to be you right?
Definitely!
And Ikoma
Even though I want it, but with the mentality as a fan
I don't know how I should feel
Keeping the distance.
I see
A bit scary
Yes
What about Sakurai?
Sakurai is the complicated one here
Look at Nishino
Then look past her and you will see Wakatsuki
Wakatsuki right behind
That can't be
What's with this line of sight
This is bad
How complicated
Who will Nishino choose?
The one member that Nishino will choose is...
Ikoma-chan
Falls over
Ikoma
That means Higuchi and Sakurai
Please go back to your seats
This is not actually a break-up
It's alright
A sad scene.
I thought this should have been more cheerful
Higuchi's crying
Crying....
It's nothing, it's ok
It's not like that
Not in that way
What's the matter Higuchi, are you sad?
I feel like I just got rejected...
Unexpected rejection experience
It suddenly feels like a real Valentine's
But you can talk to Wakatsuki about this
Expert in rejection.
That means the feelings of these two are mutual
Now Nishino confesses to Ikoma
Um, you always tell me that I'm cute
Thank you
But you are cute
For Nogizaka to be even more popular from now on
Let's work hard together!
Thanks!
Ikoma must be happy
My cheeks are hurting from smiling so much
What's the present?
Nishino chose for Ikoma
How is it, try it on
Looks good
This is good
The feeling you get when you wear it is probably the same
Cute
- Isn't it
You can wear this at home or in the prep room
This is actually a pair
Yes, that's why there are two bags
What do you mean?
I wanted the gift to be something of a pair
With me?
A Wild Uncle Himura Appears
Where did this come from
So I'm wrong
Where did this monster come from!
Big mistake
Explain it then
I bought this as a pair with Ikoma-chan
-Nishino?
Same outfit
What do you mean Nishino?
I bought two jackets like that
Ah I see
Try it on
Did you buy an identical one
How awesome
It is awesome!
You look happy
What's this what's this
Spreading the joy
Good for you
Amazing
This is good
How cute!
Looks good doesn't it!
Cute!
It's definitely cute
Let me ask you again, how do you feel after receiving the gift?
Super happy!
Super happy!!
That's good
How do you say it, the show this time
Sweetness and bitterness are mixed together
The essence of Valentine's Day
But that's to be expected
Painful reminder
Nishino, why don't you also buy another one of these for these two
She cried a lot
Because when you wear it to the lockers room they are gonna stare at you
Higuchi please cheer up
Please go back to your seats
What a wonderful Valentine's
It is indeed
Nogizaka's Valentine was chaotic from the very beginning
This is the relationship chart so far
Nishino is the most popular
And Wakatsuki's love is still one-sided
Next is Kawamura
Kazumin
She chose Takayama!
What do you like about Kazumin?
I like her face
and she's also stylish
I want the entirety of Japan to know about her awesomeness
That's why I chose an outfit that fits her as a gift
Thank you
The present is a black outfit with a mature design
But the feeling was not mutual
And next, the person Takayama chooses is
Mayaa
You like Wada?
Maaya is always like a granddaughter to me
Granddaughter...
Still in middle school but came to Tokyo alone
When I was in middle school
My mother still had to peel my oranges for me
That's kind of over-protective
Because when I think about it and seeing you always trying your best
So from now on view me as your grandma and rely on me!
How weird
Please use it
Sister is ok, but why do you want to be her grandma?
Because she always calls me grandpa
Grandpa?
Even weirder
I do call her that
So out of the ordinary
Does she have facial hair?
Why do you call her grandpa
Now, please open your present
I definitely failed at this!
Fail?
She hasn't opened it yet
What is that
For real?
Stockings?!
A pair of stockings
Why stockings?
Maaya's feet are always bare
and always wore short pants
She still wears shorts in the winter
It's ok because she's still in junior high
But when she's in senior high she's going to feel cold
A grandpa's advice
I feel the same way
Because you're worried about her health huh
Everyone else bought such great presents
I'm sorry
Not being serious
That's what you meant by failing
It's ok
You didn't fail
A little bit
And now we will see how Maaya feels
The answer to grandpa Takayama is
Wada, are you giving your chocolate to Takayama
No
Blunt
Because I sit next to her so she told me her target already
Is it someone else
Yes, I already know it's going to be someone else
I see, you knew about it
How sad
After this, with the confession of Wada, spring came for a certain member
Next is Wada's confession, who will it be
Higuchi Hina-chan
That's great, Higuchi
Come up here
Higuchi, the person that got hurt huh
Spring came!
It really came!
Why don't you say a few things and give it to her
I feel a bit sad seeing you liking Naachan and cried because of that
Leave it out
But please accept this present
Thank you
What do you like about Higuchi
She is very sensitive, and nice
That's why I really like her
I was considering
if I should choose Naachan or Maaya
Really?
-Yes
If chocolates for friendship then Maaya
If chocolates for love then Naachan
Don't say it right here...
Right in front of her
She's standing right here
What's this
This show is hurting people's feelings
I'm really happy
Let's see Maayas present
What is it?
Styrofoam
Styrofoam?
I didn't think everyone chose their gifts seriously
Cute
Put it in front of the camera
A ticket for shoulder massage huh
Because she studies a lot during breaks
So I figured she must be tired
I made this ticket for a free shoulder massage
Thank you
How happy
I will use it a lot
Use a lot?
Come here! Wada, Wada!
Massage hell
Isn't it for only one time?
I intended it for only one time...
But you can use it whenever you want
The relationship chart is as follows
Only Nishino and Ikoma have mutual feelings toward each other
Up until now, unrequited love is prominent
After this, shocking events!
Credits: Maiyan46 (translation )& HAN48 (timing)