Tonight will reveal the special secrets
of 8th single center Nishino Nanase.
❤Sayringo gundan❤
乃木坂46
weeabookstore
m 0 0 l 0 14 l 3 14 l 3 0 m 4 2 l 4 16 l 7 16 l 7 2 m 8 0 l 8 10 l 11 10 l 11 0 m 8 11 l 8 14 l 11 14 l 11 11
Everything unknown about Nishino will be revealed.
Nogizakatte, Doko?
Don.
The Nogizakatte Doko show has begun,
and we are the MC, Bananaman.
And this is Nogizaka-chan.
www.IkuchanCheeks.blogspot.com
www.weeabookstore.tumblr.com
This sub is far from perfect.
Always support Nogizaka46.
Translator: Hadie yantoo
Timing: Hadie yantoo
QC: Ayok Benington
Indo To Eng: weeabookstore
Please, announce tonight's program.
Present in a tone like you're chasing love.
Get to know more about the new center, Nishino Nanase.
Well, the center for the 8th single is Nishino Nanase
About her whole image, this show has been running
for two years and all we know is that her image is quiet.
But when you were in Macau,
you cried a lot, didn't you?
Bungee jumping terror.
It was so sudden.
You didn't think it would happen like that, right?
I've never screamed like that before.
Her screaming ability is amazing.
- You could say that maybe Nishino has changed a lot.
But even so, I still don't know much about Nishino.
Perhaps with this,
we can find something about her that isn't yet known.
Whenever she's like this, she has a quiet impression.
Nishino, who is the member who is most familiar with you?
Who?
No one is close among all the members.
Doesn't have close friends?
This is a problem if it's really like that.
Actually, she has a good relationship with all members.
- Ah, is that so?
If she chooses just one person, we'll all be very jealous.
Very jealous.
It's about the chocolate, isn't it?
Then, who did give it to her that time?
Higuchi.
But she got rejected.
After that, did you get something from her?
After the Valentine's show,
I received a present from Naachan.
So you really did give her something?
I felt bad inside.
It should be like that because you made Higuchi cry.
When she says, "I feel bad inside,"
she's actually like another version of Nakamori Akina.
Nakamori Akina is a famous Japanese artist
with a small voice
Whispering voice.
She's an idol whose personality is having a small voice.
Maybe with this opportunity,
we can dispel some of the mystery.
Let's watch this video.
Nishino Nanase.
Senbatsu announcement.
It's her first time selected as center.
Although what we know about her isn't much,
Nishino received the new position.
Before showing the full video
for the new single to the public for the first time,
we'll begin at the announcement of the new 8th single
at the last rehearsal for the concert in Yokohama.
Nishino remembers her first feelings after
the dramatic moment of the new single announcement.
In comparison to happy, I felt feelings
of anxiety, worry, and negative thinking.
Like if it doesn't sell very well, it's Nanase's fault.
This is a very important position
for the future of Nogizaka46's activities.
It's the responsibility.
You ask yourself,
if I received a position like this, can I do well?
In Nishino's previous appearances...
It's okay.
I really like fat pigeons.
Such is the personality of Nishino.
How do other members feel about her?
She's often crying on TV shows.
She's quiet and soft, but underneath that,
when doing something
she will do it seriously. She really is like that.
In the activities that were done with her before,
it felt like she was becoming stronger than she was.
Her personality is like someone
who focuses when doing something.
Hates to be defeated, that's like Nanase.
She is a member who fights hard.
She has the personality of someone
that does things perfectly.
Sometimes, she'll say some negative words,
but then she becomes more active, and she looks forward,
and she fights toward that direction.
Although we don't say it on TV,
Naachan is really weird you know.
At first, Naachan had habits that she did often.
Naachan pulled out her eyebrows
and put them in a notebook.
She was using her notebooks
to collect the eyebrows she pulled.
Ah, I remember.
Naachan cuts her nails very short.
She does.
As the members said,
she has a hidden power in herself.
In this case, we are able to see some of this
in the following video footage.
The event is held at Yokohama Arena.
As many as 42 songs will be sung
with the concert lasting more than four hours.
Let's watch Nishino's rehearsal process
behind the stage.
She rehearses with a very serious attitude
and also practices for the unit song
that she is included in.
She also participates in interview.
I like to sing, but that doesn't mean I'm good at it.
So...
I really feel like I can't remember anything.
Behind her negative statements,
her own heart is hidden underneath.
The day before the live concert,
she visits the stage for the first time.
On the day of the show,
you won't have very much time to practice on stage.
Because the show is tomorrow, you will perform
here today as if it were the real show.
Then rehearsal begins immediately.
To get rid of the nervousness before the live show,
she begins rehearsal on the stage.
As the rehearsal proceeds, we also continue
to monitor the performance backstage.
Now that rehearsal is over, I have to start makeup.
Are you nervous?
- Very nervous
and also worried. I'm going ahead~
46!
And finally...
There were a few minor mistakes.
Maybe they won't realize it.
Although sometimes,
facial expressions are difficult to see.
And at the end of the concert...
I, Nishino Nanase, was chosen to be the 8th single center.
Nishino takes a bow.
Arigatou gozamashita!
The concert attended by 13,000 spectators ended.
How are you feeling?
- Very pleased and also touched.
After the concert ended,
There were also a number of statements from...
I am the father of Nishino Nanase.
Today during the concert,
Nanase gave her best in an amazing performance.
Since Nanase was chosen to be the 8th single center,
although she isn't good standing in front of crowds,
I hope to see more of her color.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
The next day after the concert,
she proceeds with shooting a scene for the single's MV.
Hungry~
Udon.
Kitsune Udon is oishi~
During my time in Tokyo,
I've never had the opportunity to eat udon.
I love it.
I honestly believe I love udon more than Ikuchan does.
Although from the beginning, Ikuchan always said it.
But after saying she likes udon,
I don't think I often see Ikuchan eating it.
On her own,
Nishino shows a sense of not wanting to lose to her.
February 24,
she works on a bonus scene for the single.
But after taking photos today,
There are two announcements.
The 6th single handshake event
Ikoma Rina receives kennin status at AKB48
I've thought carefully about the decision I've made.
With the shocking news for Nogizaka members,
the reveal of the new song remains decided.
I can't believe it.
The recording isn't finished yet.
What feeling does all this convey?
Because it's my first public appearance,
I have to do very well,
and that there isn't enough time worries me.
Suddenly, she reveals what she's feeling.
In the early morning of February 25,
she does a photo shoot for a magazine.
It is also the last day of recording.
Of course, Nishino's solo part...
[Lyrics from Silenka@Stage48]
I kept wondering where you were.
(It's useless.)
I want to hear your voice on the phone.
How is it? Does it all sound okay?
Let's do it once again.
- Hai.
For now, we'll stop here.
She doesn't seem quite satisfied,
but she continues recording for the next songs.
It's over. Thank you for your cooperation.
- Thanks for your hard work.
But first, let's retake Nishino's solo part.
- Uh, hai.
Let's do it one more time.
Nishino's feelings change as she records once more.
...to spend them all by myself.
(It's no good.) I kept wondering where you were.
Good enough, isn't it?
So far, I think this is the best take.
Hai, thank you for your cooperation.
Ah, it's over.
Staff patience has an impact and influence
when recording for a song.
When they said, "Please, record once more,"
it made me question.
Because that was a very important part.
I hope people will be able to hear it clearly.
Because you have tomorrow as good as off,
is there somewhere you'd like to go?
I don't want to.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I can't go because train fare is expensive.
Even if I don't leave the house for a day,
I don't think it matters.
Even two days is no problem.
I've never spent three days without leaving home.
If I ever get three days off,
I'll use all three of those days to stay home
without stepping a foot out of the house.
I'm that type of human.
So you're a human like that?
- Yes, I am a human like that.
The following day,
there is a magazine photo shoot with five popular members.
Afterward, there is training
emphasizing dance moves for the new songs.
I really like this choreography.
I hope it continues to go well in the end.
During this time, the members will practice
the same song for two hours to master the dance.
However, in the latter part of the training session,
Nishino's steps are misguided.
We can clearly see her mistaken movements.
Being positioned in the front row
requires her not to make mistakes.
Before the official release,
she must completely learn the dance moves.
One day before release,
she is practicing choreography
for the coupling songs.
Yesterday, after training ended,
I immediately returned to Shibuya.
I thought about all the individual steps
of how to get home as soon as possible.
It's been a long time.
This is the first time this year that I went to Shibuya.
Yesterday, she could breathe a little.
The following day is the release of the 8th single.
There are small changes in the final steps of the dance.
To say we'll sing in a truck,
I don't know if I can do it at 100 percent.
But surely, ganbarimasu.
Release day,
a handshake event begins in the morning.
After the event ends, they once again practice
the dance to ensure they know the moves.
Well, let's get started.
Ganbarimasu~
At the venue immediately crowded by fans,
they continue practicing in the truck.
There will be small changes in the steps.
Her next performance will be
Nishino's first as the center.
Nishino's debut as center will soon begin.
Konbanwa~
Right away, we'll present our new center, Naachan.
- Hai.
Arigatou gozaimasu.
Today is my first public performance,
I am really nervous.
In reality, it's not because of standing on stage
but in this truck which makes me a little nervous.
Please, everyone enjoy, and thank you
for your warm welcome. Yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
And please listen to the following,
"Kidzuitara Katamoi."
[Lyrics from Silenka@Stage48]
When I realized, it was unrequited love.
I fell in love with you before I knew it.
Every time I think about you,
it feels somehow painful.
How many times in their life does a person meet someone,
and always think, "This time, it's definitely fate"?
Nishino is the kind of person
who does not like to stand at the front.
She doesn't think she's very good at singing or dancing,
but she shines with her own style.
Putting aside memories of the past,
Nishino has her own charm.
We can see the real Nishino in the following footage.
When I realized...
When I realized, It was unrequited love.
I fell in love with you before I knew it.
About you...
Nishino, unaware of what makes her own charm,
now occupies the center.
Arigatou gozaimasu~
Her first appearance has ended.
At the time, I was very worried.
I don't usually wear these kind of shoes.
Also doing the show in the truck,
all of that made me anxious and very tense.
I don't think there were no mistakes,
but I think the first performance went well.
Slowly, Nishino reflects on the prior performance.
But today,
there are some things that won't be remembered fondly.
I don't want to do it in a truck anymore.
I want to show a good performance.
For us, it was very difficult to do.
Of course because this is the first show,
there will be a lot of attention fixed on us.
Disappointment.
Because this is her first live show as center,
Her feelings should be stronger than anyone's.
This is the first time she's seemed so serious.
A few days later, Nishino returned to say something.
After disclosing my disappointment,
I felt very negative.
I went home and thought about this seriously.
There seemed to be some not-so-good parts at the end,
but it seems like it's only me
who's uncomfortable with it,
with that tone of voice.
It my be more difficult to make the VTR this time.
I really feel bad about saying those things.
This is also the real Nishino.
Nishino's true challenge has just begun.
After this change,
a new wind will blow toward Nogizaka46.
You don't want to do a show inside a truck?
What should I say about the truck?
Really, it'd be better if we sang the new song in Yokohama.
- Ah, if you did it there?
But we couldn't do it.
So the truck...
Hates the truck.
But if the truck shows up next time, you'll do it right?
- Hai.
It's because she doesn't want to lose.
Like you enjoy udon more than Ikuta?
- Hai.
No!
I like udon!
The stubborn one.
I love udon.
- Is that so?
They rarely see you eat it.
Ikuchan will eat whatever.
On her basis, I love all food.
All she can eat, she will eat.
This section is about what isn't displayed in the VTR.
The unknown things about Nishino
that make her so amazing.
The clothes she was wears still have the price tag
clearly visible.
Why not throw it away?
Because it's troublesome.
So you think that's a troublesome thing?
On the contrary, I have no problem with such a thing.
But people will say, "There's a price tag on your clothes,"
or something like that.
That's a problem. I hide them so that they aren't seen
because it's something embarassing if people see it.
But why don't you just cut it?
What about cutting it?
It's like...
- No, don't cut it right now.
Expecting "now"?
Why would we do it right now?
Somehow, you're bearing all the burdens
focused on you.
But it's really very unique.
Nishino is quite unique.
From Nishino's point of view,
who among the others feels weird?
Pretty much,
Reika's strange, Ikuta's strange, Hori-chan is strange.
Maiyan is quite serious.
Nanamin is also strange. They're both also weird.
Except for Shiraishi,
all of the front row is the strange group.
Strange idols.
Hashimoto was unique.
It looked once like she changed when she was in Macau.
What about me changed?
It's because when everyone was gathered,
you were the only one outside the crowd,
standing frozen elsewhere.
When you were asked to speak,
It's like you didn't want to do it together.
This part isn't really relevant.
The original subber just left some blank lines here.
But I didn't feel like deleting them~ :P
"Romance no Start"
Lyrics/Akimoto Yasushi
Music/Oshida Makoto
Arrangement/Sasaki Sosaku, Oshida Makoto
Translation/Silenka@Stage48
I chased the bus on my bike,
the one that was separating us.
From the window, you looked at me
with a puzzled expression.
Even if I catch up at a red light,
I just can't do anything about it.
This morning, why have I been
pedaling so desperately?
I woke up to it suddenly
like an electrical current ran through me.
For the first time,
I fell in love with you.
I woke up to it unconsciously.
This is different than before.
My wondrous encounter with you is
the start of romance.
I woke up to it suddenly
like an electrical current ran through me.
For the first time,
I fell in love with you.
I woke up to it unconsciously.
This is different than before.
My wondrous encounter with you is...
romance no...
Romance no...
Romance no Start~
I am amused by the image of Aki-P trying to access
his inner girly innocence when writing songs like this.