*MARSub*
8th single campaign Macau tour: Final part
At a height of 233m, the member's fear will grow
Finally, the Guinness 'bungee hit' campaign takes place
So who jumped?
NOGIZAKATTE, DOKO?
TL : Noily
QC : Senjuri
For the 8th single campaign, the members go to Macau
In this campaign, one member will perform a bungee jump
Last week...
Three people from bungee senbatsu...
In the previous 7th single campaign, Ikoma, Takayama, and Ikuta couldn't participate
And Himura will also participate
They will participate in a frightening walk from a height of 233m outside the tower
They will be doing the skywalk challenge
From here on, you'll do the skywalk
Okay, here we go
- We will see you from inside, and tell you various things to do
See us from inside?
- Yes
Evil commander appeared
Of course we will do it
Here we go...
233 meters high
Cars are tiny
Now, finally, skywalk will begin
Go for it...
Here we go, everyone...
They are going
They're supported just by that rail
Wooow~ scary~
Can't look down
Fearful scenery
I can't face this side
Wow, this is terrifying!
You alright?
Macau scenery
Scary!
This is frightening...
They look awesome
Looking down is scary!
- Face that way!
Here, devilish orders start to rise up
I'll give them orders
They must sit down there with their legs hanging off
Try to sit down there with your legs hanging down!
Impossible!
Can we sit down here?
Prolonged!
The staff commencing preparation
It is serious, we'll do it
Here?
Wow, very scary! Try looking down!
Here I go!
Verge of death
Dangle your legs!
SCARY...
Let go of your hand!
Ikoma! Ikoma!
As for us, there is glass, but it's still frightening
Prank at 233m high
I think that person became strange
Slowly... slowly...
Great!
- Ikoma can you let go with your hand?
Take a photo
Ikoma... Ikoma... scary?
Voice doesn't come out
Come sit down everyone
What's with that attitude!?
Heaven and Hell
What are you guys doing?
Well this is scary
Are you alright?
Please stop that. What's with this guy
Playful employee
How annoying
They're doing something
All body weight on the rope
What is he doing?
I can't do that
We have a bungee jump after this, so please be quick
Winding
Easy for you to say
First Himura will challenge this fearful act
No, no, no
How pitiful
Let go of your grip
Floating high in the air
Next, Ikoma
This is very scary
She can't let go with her hand
Go for it, Ikoma-chan
Definitely, she will hate that person
You can do it
Freezing face
Everyone is awesome, right?
This all is for the 8th single
And then Ikuta also take challenge
Look down! Go look down!
Takayama's face became dark
Hates high places
Takayama, go for it
Last is Takayama
But she can't let go of the rope at all
Takayama
Scary, scary
Do your Amejing!
One... two... Amej...
Nose dripping
Her nose is dripping!
Dripping nose? Takayama...
20 Macau points
Reaction +20 MACAU
Takayama, when doing Amejing, her nose was dripping
I give you 20 Macau for that
They took her photo when her nose dripping
How pitiful
How was it?
What's the most frightening?
That
That was very frightening. We felt it too
Ikuta, you were scared?
Walking is scary enough
but jumping from there is really impossible...
I see
Bungee jumping from here is more frightening
This is truly frightening
If someone says it's not scary, their head must be broken
But, thanks for your hard work
From here, there's nothing left but to bungee
Time for the last lucky card draw!
If you get 7 it will be a big help
7 is high
0 is in a pinch
I also think so
Takayama got 20 points for her dripping nose
Dripping nose points
That was good
The last card drawing
How will it affect the final result?
Se no
Nishino      Wada   Matsumura  Hashimoto  Ikoma       Ikuta      Takayama
Yatta
Wada 7, Nishino 6
This side is...
Even they participate
With the last card drawn, final results will be announced
I'll announce from first place
First is...
Hashimoto
1st      Hashimoto Nanami 22 Macau pt
Great!
She's safe. Come here
Last night she was fast
Second...
Wada
2nd      Wada Maya 12 Macau pt
She worked hard until this day
Third...
Ikoma
3rd       Ikoma Rina 9 Macau pt
She's safe
So then, 4 people left
Fourth...
Matsumura
4th      Matsumura Sayuri 8 Macau pt
Matsumura did it!
Fifth...
Takayama
5th     Takayama Kazumi 7 Macau pt
Two people left
Impossible
Ikuta and Nishino left, who will jump from 223m?
Really impossible
Sixth...
Will it be Ikuta or Nishino?
Who will do the Bungee hit campaign?
Ikuta!
6th     Ikuta Erika -20 Macau pt
Therefore, Nishino will do the bungee
Minus 21 Macau pt
One point difference
Ikuta                                                        Nishino
Maybe because of last night
Your score was reduced quite a lot, minus 30 points
Ikuta lost a lot of points too
If you had done that Inagawa impersonation once more, your score would be equal
So the one who will bungee is the new center Nishino
Soon the preparations for bungee started
As for sixth place, Ikuta will be the backup
Other members wait for Nishino on the ground
Preparation is completed
How is it?
Very scary when I realize it'll be soon
I'm shivering so much
Shivering
Right
I can see you shivering
I don't know how, but you are the new center
This is great!
Right, such a coincident
You'll jump and pray for the single to become a hit
Right!
If something happens, Ikuta will jump
I'll give support from beside her
Finally, Nishino will do the hit campaign prayer
The Guinness world's highest bungee from 233 meters
This is not likely to be a joke anymore
I can't imagine jumping from this height
Nishino's face... looks like she's scared
Are you starting to panic?
Even though Nishino really hates this...
Oh, you're crying?
Panic of flying
It's alright to let out your tears
We're counting on you
For the 8th single, jump
Nishino, scary
Scary~
Nishino...
10 macau
There is no meaning to getting the points now
Well, if only she got these 10 points earlier
Too late 10 macau
Right
Naa-chan
Naa-chan, it's alright. I'll be here
Go for it!
Various things being put on her. How's your feeling now?
Scared
- Fearful
But...
I want to jump, but still
Scary
Then, standby preparation is completed
Nishino, if you can, please say it loudly for the 8th single to become a hit
It'll be great
I'm counting on you, Nishino. Let's pray for the 8th single
Nishino Nanase
Choosen as center in the 8th single
As center I'll take part in a campaign, and work hard
Whatever campaign it will be, she's ready to do it
But this time, coincidentally she is chosen to jump
It's inevitable, and something for her to accept
For this campaign to succeed, she must overcome her weak self
She must raise her confidence as a center
With that in her heart, she'll do the bungee with a smile
So they will do it from that
Go for it, Nishino!
Waa~ scary!
Nishino, don't look down, just look straight
Don't look down, Nishino
Is it ready?
It'll definitely make you cry
Go for it, Nishino
- Naa-chan go for it
Frightening? Dangerous?
Ikuta, maybe you must prepare to put on the belt
Not prepared for this
Not yet?
What is it? Nishino, is it dangerous?
Naa-chan's crying
Panic
What's the matter, Nishino? Is it that dangerous?
Nishino is crying like crazy
Nishino has never cried like that
Nishino, calm down
Relax.
- Look straight into the distance
Nishino, try looking at the sky, don't look below
Nishino is vigorously sucked into the fear
Can she jump?
She's crying out loud. Nishino, is it that scary?
Emotion is unsteady
This must be scary
- Nishino. Calm down
Relax.
- Look straight
Nishino, try looking at the sky. Don't look below
Naa-chan!
- Nishino. Nishino, look straight, don't look below
Oh, is she gonna go?
Well, that must be impossible
Nishino
Take a deep breath
This is scary
After hearing Bananaman and Ikuta, she begins to calm down
In the debut campaign, Nishino cried while distributing tissue that time
She also cried easily on the program, she hates her weak self
But, from that fateful moment, she decided to change
In order to change from her weak self, to be accepted as the new center
Furthermore, these are her words in the PV
I...
have been chosen so I'll do my very best
To show her determination
...and to change herself
...now she must step onward
8th single, let it be a hit!
Is she going?
Even so frightened like that
- And she said it
Great!
- She's cool!
Nishino takes the step forward
She is not the type of person that lets out a big voice
But, she had confidence like no one else, and won't lose to anyone with this strong feeling for the 8th single
For her beloved Nogizaka, and to surpass her weak self
Now she jumps from the Macau sky with full courage
Well, next, Ikuta, you go
Go to the ground
Nanase!
Come here
You're great
Is it scary?
You're really great!
It's okay now. You did your best
Naa-chan, you're great
You tried your best
Nishino, you did it
- That's great!
Very good
- Wonderful
You scared?
- Very much
But you screamed out loud
Still trembling?
I was all alone, and it was scary
That was great, I'm deeply moved
You are wonderful
Well done
I see. Well, for your great hard work
1 macau
Macau points is no longer have any meaning
That's not right
No matter how much you get is meaningless now
Let's pray for the big success of the 8th single
Success. We're counting on you
This is the 8th single Nishino campaigned for, released on the 2nd of February,
First appearance from the studio, Kizuitara Kataomoi
Kizuitara kataomoi
Itsunomani ka suki datta
Anata wo omou sono tabi
Nandaka setsunakute
Kizuitara Kataomoi
Hito wa umarete nankai no deai ga aru no?
Kondo koso unmei da nante itsumo shinjite
Soredemo naze ka tsurechigatte kizutsuite
Zettai koi nanka tsurumonka to arekara kimeteita no ni
Shokai sareta toki ni kyou minai furi wo shite
Buaisou datta no wa jibun wo mamoru tamedatta
Tanjoubi mo kurisumasu mo barentain dei mo
Hitori de mo tsugoseru tsuyosa wo
Youyaku minitsuketa hazu
(Dame yo)
Anata ga doko ni iru ka ki ni narushi
(Muri yo)
Denwa kakete koe wo kikitai
(Iya yo)
Anna ni kurushikute tsurai hibi
Namida datte mou kareta ima no watashi yo
Kizuitara kataomoi
Itsu no manika suki datta
Anata wo omou sono tabi
Nandaka setsunakute
Kanjou wo saetemo
Iki ga kurushikunaru
Konna ni suki na no ni
Kotoba ni shitara kiesoude
Kizuitara
Kizuitara kataomoi
Mitometaku wa nai kedo
Kouchou ni natte irubun
Kokoro wa moroi kamo
Ukeireru shikanaine
Kizuitara Kataomoi Tokuten Eizo
Type-C has a documentary from 4 members
Type-A and Type-B have separated Creator's Etude
Please enjoy these Tokuten Eizo too
Shopping with uncle Himura
Next week, Himura's prize is summed up
Without hesitation, Himura goes shopping with Nogizaka
Furthermore, why is it always a hindrance
Why do you all come along?
TL : Noily
QC : Senjuri
Visit : marsubber.blogspot.com
Uncle Himura, thank you very much
You're welcome, my dear little sisters