This week's Nogidoko is the second half of the Valentine's Day Special!
Members are anxious to see who will get the chocolates!
Wait, is this some sort of triangle relationship here?
Valentine's Day is not over yet for Nogizaka!
Each member can only choose one person...
I AM SHOCKED!
Hey Higuchi is crying!
It's like heaven and hell for the ones that were rejected...
...and the ones where the feeling was mutual.
This is the Valentine's Day chart so far...
What will we see in the second half?
Let's start with Fukagawa
Who is she going to call?
Nanamin!
It's Hashimoto!
You're quite popular, huh?
We always eat together...
I really enjoy hanging out with you because it's so comfortable
Thank you for everything!
Oh my god thank you!
Cute!
And here's the gift...
-Thank you so much~
What did you get...what's that ringing?
Sleepyhead
Oh it's an alarm clock
She has trouble waking up, so I got her that...
and there's something else...
She is kind of weak, so I got her herbal tea supplement
"For when you want to recharge yourself"
Right, that's a great gift
She bought this because she knows you very well
It's very practical
This looks like something that can really wake you up
I picked a really loud one...
Oh is that so?
scary scary scary...
...Oh
Not loud enough?
Can you stop looking like this is not loud enough?
The look on your face says you think this won't wake you.
Now let's see if the feeling is mutual
It would be mutual if she chooses Fukagawa
So Hashimoto, please tell us if it is Fukagawa
Umm...actually...
Eh?
Well, you see...
If I were serious, then it would be Maimai
Stop it please!
No excuses!
I think everyone here is serious about this
I am for real!
If it's for real, then absolutely it would be Maimai
How about just "Yes" or "No"?
Is it Fukagawa?
Nope...
What is this mess?!
It's too embarrassing if I take this seriously and give it to Maimai, I am not sure if I can handle it emotionally
But Fukagawa seemed serious, what do you make of that?
ME TOO!  That's why I couldn't choose Wakatsuki...
You of all people shouldn't be talking!
Your case is closed!
You were totally serious, right?  - Yes we were
So...please go back to your seat, Fukagawa...
A sad ending
Now that Hashimoto rejected Fukagawa...
Who will she choose?
Akimoto Manatsu!
Wait!
Here comes a new challenger!
Then please come up and get in line
Heh, really, for real?
With Hori joining,the battle is between Hori and Hashimoto for Akimoto
First is Hashimoto's confession
Recently, I actually got fished by Manattan
I think Manattan is the second person who makes me feel comfortable just after Maimai
After Maimai?
Sounds like some kind of careful wording
Gleaming
Only after Maimai
Today I brought something for Manattan, Chocolates
Please eat it
Thank you so much
Next is Hori
Suddenly, the alarm clock...
Horror?
Fukagawa's curse
As if it's saying "time's up" ...
A Warning?
Fukagawa's curse appeared
She's telling you to "open your eyes"!
What perfect timing!
And now we're back to Hori's confession to Akimoto
Manatsu-san is known for fishing people at handshake events
Because a lot of fans will go to her line
So I'm afraid she will be tired
That's why I chose something fitting
Please take it
Ahh thank you
Yay!
What do you like about her?
Manatsu-san is very kind
I feel like she never gets mad at anything
Sadistic perspective?
You sound like a sadist
No, she's like a mother
Now let's take a look at their presents
First is Hashimoto's present
What's this?
It's a piece of fabric...
Fabric?
Fabric? Why fabric?
Manatsu isn't very healthy
But she always wears shirts that reveal her shoulder
So I gave her something to cover it up
Using fabric?
It seems like I'm gonna have to cut it
Is it normal fabric?
It's actually only a piece of fabric
Just a piece of fabric
Wait, it actually looks kinda cute
Don't say it's only a piece
That means you bought a roll?
The girl who gifted fabric
Amazing
But it will look cute when you put it on
I will see it as a scarf
Ah, thank you
It's good to use it like that
But then again it's only a piece of fabric
And Hori's present
What's this?
Only a notebook
Notebook, a notebook
It's a notebook for easy writing
Because she's good at fishing
"If a person approaches me like this,
then I will respond like that"
So I hope she can write it down casually
Silly
Writing casually
I see
Write down things casually...
in a notebook made for easy-writing
So she won't confuse herself
Now the answer
Who will she choose?
Is the person you want to give your gift to among these two?
No
It's not?
Looks like your feelings won't be returned
Please go back to your seats
Here is the updated relationship chart
Seems like it's hard to be mutual
Akimoto, who rejected both Hashimoto and Hori, who will she choose?
Matsumura Sayuri!
Matsumura, come up here
Really?!
Are you surprised?
Wait a minute
Ah, Ikuta just said "wait"
Matsumura is amazing huh
This is surprising
Please give a speech and then give her your gifts
Ever since the audition, I have always admired your face, especially your mouth
Please receive this gift
Thank you!
You like her mouth huh
Yes, really
I see, is that so
Now, Ikuta
I feel comfortable every time I look at Sayurin
I made some food for someone that loves eating like Sayurin
It's homemade?
Yes, I made it myself so please eat it
Thank you
And after thinking about her health, I give you this
What is it?
Konnyaku
A whole piece of konnyaku
Konnyaku: thạch làm từ konjac
This is like looking down on her!
Telling her to slim down?
Let's open Akimoto's present
I also made chocolates
By yourself?
These are both homemade huh?
Great
This is chocolates eh
Yes, the small box
Looks like Akimoto is good at making sweets
Amazingly good
Eh? You really made this?
(Ikoma)Give me a piece!
You can make it this well!?
Amazing
I'm so happy
Take a bite then!
I will choose my favorite color,pink
What flavor is this? - Strawberry
You really made this?
I'm gonna eat it
Don't cover your mouth that she loves so much
Super delicious!
So delicious she feels moved
Delicious?
Thank you
What about the other gift?
What is it?
A whole cake!
Amazing! It looks great!
I really like it when Sayurin eats
So I want her to eat this
I made a tart
Homemade?
Great
Truth is, for a long time now
I've always dreamt of eating a whole tart by myself
I always tell Manattan "make a strawberry tart!"
You said so?
This is...not good...my dream came true!
Take a bite
Good stuff
What does it say?
Right here
You made the whole thing yourself?
Sayuringo
I'm eating now
Delicious! Unbelievable!
Did you also make the crust?
Yes
Professional level!
Only for Matsumura
How long did it take?
About 2 and a half hours
The chocolates?
About 1 hour
How talented
Ikuta's is also handmade?
Yes
A bad feeling about this
Ikuta can't cook very well
This time I tried for Sayurin
Really?
-Yes
Wait
What, what?
Forced smile
Let's see it
Everyone wants to see it
What is that
Mysterious object
The heck is that
Honestly, I feel terrified
Weird present
How can you say it's terrifying
Looking at it, I can't understand why chocolate sauce is on top of konnyaku
That isn't chocolate sauce, it's miso paste
Dengaku! Miso Dengaku!
About the chocolates
I thought Sayurin already had too much to eat
So I made it using konnyaku
I made the normal kind and the kind with miso
And white Konnyaku?
Yes, I put miso over white konnyaku
I have never heard someone say white konnyaku
First time
What does it taste like?
Miso isn't it?
If it's bad then it's ok to not say anything
Not good?
Delicious...
Because it was made with love for Matsumura?
Yes, even though the appearance can't be compared
But the feelings are the same as the tart
Same level of love
The love is about the same as the tart heh
Will the feelings be mutual for any of them?
Matsumura got confessed to by Akimoto and Ikuta
And her answer is
Who will you choose between these two?
Neither
Neither?
Well...then please return to your seats
This is not really turning out as expected
Matsumura who rejected them both, who will she call?
Shiraishi Mai-chan
Honestly, I have liked you for a long time!
Direct confession
What's this, an actual confession
So embarrassed
From now on always be with me!
Please!
Thank you!
As if this is a real confession!
Aren't you happy
What do you like in Shiraishi?
I love everything!
As a fellow member, as a friend
Or as a girl
She is perfect
She's also gentle
Really, she also praises someone like me
Spoiling her
Is that so
- She's super gentle
Do you want to date her?
Yes
Hey hey
You made the chocolates yourself?
-Yes
Ah so it's homemade
Surely it should not have anything weird in it
I put a lot of effort in this
They say the way to the heart is through the stomach...
It's true that's important when you get married
So I made it seriously to know the way to her stomach
What is it? Shiraishi-san?
Amazing
Mysterious object part 2
Eh what's this
Why is the banana black
What is this thing?
Fruit flavored bread pudding
Great
-Bread pudding with fruits?
Did bake it?
-Yes
I see
You can make stuff like this
-Yes
Because the chocolates you made last year looked like charcoal
You made it using a stove
-Yes
Then I put it in the oven so the fruits are a bit crumpled
But you improved a lot
Ah, thank you!
And now is the tasting
How is it?
Um...there's no flavor...
Even with that appearance
For real...it can't look like that and not have any flavor
Even so, it should have the flavor of fruits
Or you haven't eaten the pudding yet
Eat the pudding part!
The bottom part huh
Pudding is mainly that part
This is like grilled pudding
Eat it, there should be some kind of taste
Delicious
Flavor?
Nothing...
Pudding with no flavor
For real
Matsumura, try it
See if there's any flavor as you made it?
How is it?
How's the taste?
Nothing...
There's indeed no flavor
What do you mean by it doesn't taste like anything
Making pudding and putting a whole lot of fruits on it
And you managed to make the flavor disappear
A magic cook
But it's fun to eat
But it's the thought that counts
Because you made it for her
Look at the present
Ah, cute
What's that?
Teddy bears
Actually the blue one is for Maiyan
And this one is mine
Ah, a pair huh
Silly couple
Thank you
Ah, they're holding hands
Eh, what do you mean?
It's magnetic?
-Yes
Cute
Yay!
This is great, they're holding hands
Thank you so much
Sorry but I can't watch this anymore
Seems like consensus
But it's a great gift
Matsumura is in love with Shiraishi, her answer is?
Shiraishi, do you choose Matsumura?
Sorry, no...
Shiraishi-san, it's not her?
I was reluctant, because I also like Sayurin
But this time, I want to give my present to someone else...
You were reluctant?
Yes. Sorry!
Heartbreaking
It can't be helped
After this, sticky situation?
Next is Shiraishi, who rejected Matsumura
Who will she call
Iku-chan
But you were already rejected
Ah, I see. So this is a love triangle
Sticky situation
What is this
Ikuta come up here
Ikuta who Matsumura... is that so...
When I was sitting there I realized it's not me
How complicated
But Matsumura
So I had some second thoughts
It's not like that! Listen to me!
How can I give Konnyaku to Maiyan huh
It's true that you look down on Matsumura then
What is this!?
Cold voice
Your "what is this!?" is so straightforward
Shiraishi's feelings can't be mutual, but let's listen to her confession
Even though it's late, but Ikuchan, happy birthday
Because you don't really have a good eye for fashion
So the present is something that I want you to wear
I bought it so wear it often!
Thank you
Good good, chocolate and gift...clothes?
So cute
Amazing
Oh~!
Shirt?
-Ah, it's a full set
That's a skirt
Cute
There's more
Ah
Good stuff
So Ikuta, why don't you change right here
Advertising on the spot?
And last is Kitano, who will she give her present to?
Miona
Hori?
Too bad their feelings can't be mutual
But let's listen to what Kitano's got to say
You're always with me
I really enjoy your company
I want to be with you from now on
So let's work hard together
Ah, both of you are second gen huh
So you guys are close
I intend to give a present to Hinako on the actual Valentine's Day
I'm happy
Good excuse!
Nice excuse
If it's not an excuse then all the better
What about the choco? It's homemade?
You pulled it super hard huh
Unexpectedly violent
What's this
And now she will eat a piece of homemade brownie
Um, delicous!
Relieved
You made this for Hori huh
And the gift is
What's this?
Pays no attention
You pulled it hard again
Oh it's the same...
Both are alarm clocks
Alarm clock
-That's fine
Why an alarm clock?
One time me, Miona and Junna stayed together
We all woke up late and got scolded for that
And normally she is tired
So it's hard to wake up right away once she's sleeping
So you know that
Listen to it?
Wait, Hashimoto
Please do not disturb
Hashimoto, now is Hori and Kitano's time
Why are you trying to get in the middle heh
Suddenly it rings really loudly
What is this
The full relationship chart of Nogizaka is as following
There are those who got presents, and those who didn't
But from now on let's work hard together and be closer
The plans for campaigning 8th single will be announced!