Nogizaka46's 8th single campaign in Macau
The best part of this trip will be a bungee jump!
Here we will also discover things about the member's human nature
And finally, we go to Macau Tower
The campaign for the 8th single,
Kidzuitara Kataomoi, will take place in Macau
In this campaign, the member with the worst luck will jump so that the single becomes a hit
Continuing from last time, the member with the lowest score is Ikuta
Then, the next place to go to is...
Everyone, you said you're hungry, right?
Let's get some food
Here's a Portugal restaurant called "Busshourou"
This is a restaurant specialized in Portuguese food in Macau
But of course even here..
Here we go, lucky card draw time
The members ranked first to fourth will get to eat delicious food
Four of them get to eat the delicious food
That's pretty lucky
And for the rest, you get something else
Scary
Who will get to eat the delicious Portuguese food? The result is...
Ikoma has 7, first place. Takayama has 6, second place
The three that don't get the delicious food are Nishino, Matsumura, and Wada
What will they get?
From now on, there will be food coming out. For the three of you, the person with the highest rank will have to choose whether to eat the meal or pass it on.
Now Macau meals will be served one by one in front of them
And starting from the highest rank they must choose to eat or not to eat that meal
Takayama, there's something behind your head, is it okay?
Kazumin's head bumped into it
You bumped into it, right? Minus 5 Macau.
Well, here's the first dish
Here it comes
This is...
We don't know yet
- We'll tell you later
But it looks delicious
- We can see the shape
You're right
Well, I'll eat it
As expected from the new center
Which part will you eat?
- Maybe this part
Delicious piece
Go for this part
It hurts
Himura's other self?
Get ready
You get it, right?
It becomes like that
Go ahead
That was shocking!
I'm surprised, wow scary
So funny, please watch it one more time
Hilarious!
I thought it was a ghost
We're sorry. Please eat it
Ah, but... it tastes like regular meat
Well, it is edible after all
Now that Nishino has finished eating, what are these exactly?
Well, these are whole heads of a roasted pig and duck
Pig and duck
Hello I'm pig
- I'm duck
Together we're pig and duck
Next, the meal for Matsumura
Impossible
- Nanamin will like this
It's noodles
- No, no, impossible
Why? It's ramen
It's okay. You can pass it on, but you'd have to eat the last meal
What should I do? Impossible
But this is ramen
Can I pass this?
It's alright
Then, I pass
- No, no
Wada doesn't have any choice but to receive it
No Choice
Yes, she doesn't have choice
Wada has to eat this
It looks like real food
Looks delicious
How is it?
Really delicious!
Huge Grin
Why did you turn it down, Matsumura?
Because of the toppings
The toppings for the noodles
Try it
Wow you ate it all in one bite
You are the one bite type when eating ramen, right?
Really delicious
Super delicious?
Like a liver taste
It's great! It's like you got it right
So, what is it?
- This is pig's brain ramen
Eeh~!?
Why are you looking at this?
Owner of the brain?
Maybe it was his brain
Then, what will Matsumura have to eat?
Please be normal, please be normal
Matsumura, please look at it
What is that?
You can't pass anymore. Matsumura, this is your dinner
I think I know what this is
So that's it
Good, good
Same as this
Bite it
Ouch, ouch
How's the taste?
No taste
No way
I ate it
This is... well, what do you think?
What is it?
Human?
Ah, chicken. A chicken's feet
Is this real!?
Wada, that was a good comment
Is this real?
Is this frozen?
Similar with "Take me skiing"
So plus 5 points for you
5 Macau
Next, time for these four to eat
These are grilled prawns
Then, African chicken
And Curry lobster. Enjoy
Ikuta, how's the shrimp?
The taste is really strong
It has a great flavor, really tasty
Looks tasty
Curry lobster
This is very delicious, also the spiciness is perfect
Really good
Really delicious
Is the African chicken good?
What kind of taste?
What is this?
-1 Macau
Maybe this chicken has been simmered, the taste has been absorbed into it
And it's soft
So what kind of taste? -1 Macau
We asked for the taste
Ikuta, can you describe what African chicken tastes like?
When it first came in my mouth, it tasted like something from a foreign country
Of course it did
But the more I chew it, it becomes more and more like my own home country
Tastes like home?
Really? Even though it's African?
German
Nonsense
What is up with that?
Now that dinner has ended, the first day of recording the Macau tour is done
We moved using different buses than the members
At that time, only Wada waved her hands at us
Well, for Wada, +5 Macau
We did it too
But, before that, our bus was side by side, some of you maybe waved to us
But, Takayama was sat at the back
She waved her hand but suddenly bird shit landed there nicely
Senseless woman
Even if there was a window, Takayama -3 Macau
Just now in front of her there was some dirty looking rubbish
Hashimoto and Ikuta gave no reaction
-10 Macau
No way
If you don't act more lively...
We should make this more exciting
Right, Nishino?
YES!
Full of spirit!
We've never heard Nishino answer loudly like that before
This is the first time
- Right, Nishino?
YES!
Abrupt power
Really cute
Right, Hashimoto?
- YES!
Ventriloquist
Good, good
Next, the member's true nature is revealed
The recording has ended. The members are resting in the hotel to prepare for tomorrow
There...
Nogizaka's true nature check
We've arrived at the hotel
Staff will call them in from each of their rooms for to prepare for tomorrow's recording
The truth is they will come to this room.
We will check who is the fastest one to come
They will get points according to their order of arrival
Is it alright if they come with no make up?
They will hate it
Make up is not for men?
No, they are girls
That's why I've prepared this
Ikoma
If they don't want to show their face, they can use it like this
The members have been called. Who will be the first member to arrive?
How about this?
The others are two girls in one room
Is there a possibility of someone not coming?
No
Everyone must come, we told them we're having a meeting
While they are talking...
They've arrived
Thank you
Stop it! Wait... No
Panic
Is it Ikoma?
Come here!
Hurry!
- You're first. 7 points
Come here, they're arriving
Blank
Oh, you're here. Hashimoto, you're second, so 6 points.
Hashimoto is unexpectedly quick
Please gather here
Therefore, Ikoma is first and Hashimoto is second
They came right after being called, what a wonderful attitude
Naa-chan was taking a bath!
Really? So that is her fate
You got a room alone
Yes, right
Selfish
You're like an actress
No
That's what actresses get, right?
Seems like I'm the only one who is okay to stay alone
What excellent members of Nogizaka, but...
It's pretty late
What a shock. We starting to doubting their personality
Five minutes past
What is this?
What do you mean?
Like how serious they do their job
Like to come as soon as they're told
We also like to take a bubble bath
Normal bath is alright
Example of professional
I'm tired
Murmuring is prohibited
Minus 5 macau
What are you doing?
Everyone was called at the same time?
- Yes
Isn't this late?
- It's late.
We've waited long enough, staff will call all of them once again
Thanks for your hard work. Excuse me for calling you again. But, can you come here right now?
Thank you, we're counting on you
This is... I looked at these faces one by one
Members
It's not important!
How about the call?
How was it?
She asked if there was a photo session
She asked that?
That's right~
Photo session!
And then...
Someone's coming
Whaat~?
You're third
Sudden rank announcement
You're late!
It's not like that, a lot of things happened
Matsumura is third, but it's past 13 minutes after the first call was made
Iku-chan is taking a bath
She knows about the call?
I've told her
She was with me when I picked up
And because I got the second call... I left her
- They're late
- What happening over here in room 406?
They're late...
This is strange
From the first call... I think maybe we should change their point with this situation
Yes
Thanks for your hard work
Thank you... Eh! Wait!
No Make-up
No way~ it's a joke, right?
No makeup, no makeup
Alright, Takayama and Maaya
Fourth are Takayama and Wada who arrived at the same time
They've arrived 18 minutes after the first call
You're late
I'm sorry
When I got the call, I was bare naked
Well...
Plus 5 Macau
Why!? What are those points for?
Why do you give 5 points for being naked
Maaya..
I can't open my eyes
Were you sleeping?
- Yes
Bathrobe is good
I'm not wearing anything under this
Eh!?
I'm not even wearing a bra
You're not wearing a T-shirt?
Plus 5 Macau
Takayama-san, you could be number one with this
No, no.
Hiding
Okay, Ikuchan, come over here please
What is this?
We're in the middle of a true nature check
Ikutadon, right?
Pajama
Go ahead
What is this?
Ikuchan sleeps covered with music
No way, no way
Eh, what is this? This is bad.
Sixth is Ikuta who shows up wearing pajamas
She's twenty minutes late
Ikuta, what's up with that pajama?
This is a pajama, right?
I always wear this pajama in every sleepover to feel comfortable
Full of instruments
Those are guitars
Very cute
With this pajama...
Ikuta gets plus 5 Macau
Yes! Great
It's like coming late is good too
No, no. The first one is the winner
All that's left is Nishino
But she's not coming as they wait, without saying anything, Ikoma will go pick her up
Just finished taking a bath
What?
Okay, Nishino-san...
We ran into each other in the hallway
Nishino-san, if you don't want to show your face, this is a no make-up guard
Everyone is here
Nishino-san... you're last
Nishino-san, you're the very last
Wrapping up, that was the true nature check. In last position is Nishino
She's 30 minutes late
Suddenly I started to think there was a ghost
Because you heard the phone ringing?
I thought it was the receptionist
Because it was so persistent
I became afraid
It's scary~
You hate it
Somehow I hate it, scary~
Inagawa Junji impersonation
Why are you impersonating Inagawa
Doing an impersonation of Inagawa-san, +1 Macau
You got one point
Now Shitara has a proposal about their points
Having these two arrive very quickly after all
Start from the third position...
Their points will be deducted by how many minutes you were late
What does that mean?
- Wait a minute!
Therefore, third position and below get minus points according by how minutes they came late
Here is the ranking of their points
Are you scared, Nishino?
You were like, it's scary~
Right, after I got out of bathroom, I heard sounds
It's scary~
You hate it
I hate it~
You get 1 Macau
Doing Inagawa's impersonation just gave you one point
After this, they finally arrive at Macau Tower!
Everyone, please look at this!
This is Macau Tower
Looking at it from here...
Everyone is prepared, right?
You're ready
No? Takayama
-10 Macau
No, no, no
If you get too many minus points here, it'll be the end of you
Nishino is not talking at all, -10 Macau
Last night you were last
I'm prepared
I don't want to lose 10 Macau points
Questioning the points, you get -5 Macau
Your points are getting deducted quite often
Here is the MV of the 8th single, Kidzuitara Kataomoi. Please watch it!
Finally, who will jump from the tower?
We must get one of you to jump
But on top of the tower we can walk around...
I know it
- You know?
It's called skywalk
You said it first, -10 Macau
Why!?
This is not good, information thief
We talked about it earlier, didn't we?
Skywalk is a popular extreme attraction where you can walk outside the tower
The three people from the bungee senbatsu
You didn't participate in the previous waterfall campaign, so you will do the Skywalk
Don't you think you should do something
I thought so
Please let us do this
Therefore, Skywalk, Skywalk, Skywalk...
Skywalk
- Stupid!
I saw that coming
Who will be the one to jump?