Tonight, we’ll announce the senbatsu members for Nogizaka46’s 9th single.
What will happen? And what will the changes be?
Nogizaka46 takes a new step towards great leap!
Nogizakatte, Doko?
DON!
Nogizakatte Doko has started, we're your hosts,
Bananaman, yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
and they are... Nogizaka-chan~
There's a lot of them.
What do we have for today?
Himura-san, please go ahead.
Big announcement of the senbatsu members for the 9th single!
It felt like the 8th single is not a long ago,
but we’re already at the 9th single.
I mean, it’s simply amazing that we’re already at the 9th single.
It’s so fast.
So, how will this turn out?
There has been various changes even in Nogizaka, right?
Well, Matsui Rena…
-That's right.
It has been announced that she’ll be concurrently with SKE,
so there’s a possibility that she can get in the senbatsu, right?
-That’s right.
Ikuta who has announced a hiatus for the 9th single,
along with Inoue, whose performance in a stage play overlaps with this recording,
the two of them are absent today.
Well then, first, we’ll announce the formation for this single!
This is the formation for the 9th single.
Front has five members,
Second row also has five members,
And the last row has seven?
Yes, that is right.
And then, the 10 members from the 1st and 2nd row are…
the 10-Fukujin.
10-Fukujin?
Apparently, we have 10-Fukujin everyone.
So this time, 10 people will make for the 10-Fukujin?
There are even a few laughs going on.
10-Fukujin~
That’s what it seems this time.
Now everyone, finally, we’ll do the announcement.
Okay, lezz go.
You said lezz go though.
Let's go!
Well then, shall we begin?
First is…
3rd row,
#17
The first member to enter the senbatsu is…
Takayama Kazumi
With her numerous incomprehensible behaviors,
Takayama has become an indispensable presence in the show,
she made it in the senbatsu this time as well.
You’ve been in this spot for quite a lot of times, right?
Yes, that’s right. After entering Nogizaka...
I’m thankful for always being in that rightmost spot,
I’m always in that position so I’m sure there’s a meaning to it.
Performing the role of that position,
To feel that my existence over there has a meaning,
I’d like to do my best.
Do your best to have a lot of savings too.
Shitara only knows.
It’s on the internet, you know.
Shitara is shocked by Takayama’s savings.
It appeared right there.
I'll work hard.
I’ll do my best!
Please proceed to the #17 spot.
hai, omedetou gozaimasu~
That's the first one, there are 16 remaining.
The next member to enter the senbatsu is…
Eto Misa
Eto?
hai, omedetou~
As the oneesan character of Nogizaka,
Eto has showed her charm even in the show,
it has been 2 singles since she last made it in the senbatsu
I’m a little surprised,
because I was called too soon.
But being in the #11 spot means that…
together with Kazumin, we have oneesan at both ends,
I’m also thinking that there’s probably a meaning in this position,
This time, from this position, I’ll get to see a brand new scenery,
so I’d like to do my best as a senbatsu member.
Do your best.
-Yes.
omedetou~
The two of them have been decided, 15 members left.
3rd row,
the next member to enter the senbatsu is…
Hori Miona
hai, douzo~
She appeared like a comet from the 2nd gen,
recently, Hori began to show her mysterious charm even in the show,
this time she’s in the 3rd row position.
How are you feeling about this?
Well...
In the 7th single…
In the 7th and 8th single,
I was chosen as a senbatsu member,
I was even allowed to go up front, however,
I wasn’t able to leave any big results.
But since the members and the fans have given me so much support,
I’ve been thinking a lot that “thank goodness I entered Nogizaka.”
For this single,
I’m next to Takayama-san,
she is very cheerful and funny.
Me all of the sudden?
I’d like to do my best again in this new position.
Thank you very much.
Hori is the center in the 7th single,
then this time, you’re in the 3rd row so you don’t have to be sad.
if you were to take it positively…
A group having someone with a center experience in the 3rd row is amazing,
someone like that being assigned right here.
Well, Takayama could also teach you a lot of things,
Do your best on a positive note.
-I will.
Thank you very much.
It's amazing.
Three have been decided.
Then, I'll continue with the announcement,
#12
The next member to enter the senbatsu is…
Inoue Sayuri
Oh, Inoue, she's not here today, right?
hai, omedetou~
Inoue is performing in a play right now right?
She’s on stage right now but aren’t we gonna give her a call?
Phone call during the play?
Inoue, whose tears were impressive in the show,
her participation in stage plays widens her place of activity.
this time, she made her way back to the senbatsu.
Let’s move on.
3rd row, the next senbatsu member is?
Yamato Rina
There she is!
hai, douzo~
While being an under for all 8 previous singles,
Yamato lured everyone to smile using her cheerful character in the show,
her long-awaited first selection for the senbatsu.
You did it!
-You were finally called.
It’s been a long time since I’ve had my last conversation with you.
Long time no see.
What do I do?
You were always an under member until now,
this is your first senbatsu selection.
-This is your first.
Yes.
Thank you very much. I’m so happy.
-You made it! Omedetou~
What do I do?
But…
I’ve always been an under member, it’s like… I thought I’ve been forgotten.
I also think that way.
Still, there are fans who have been supporting me for a long time,
they have supported me and never abandoned me.
I, myself, this time…
At the moment I thought I need to work harder,
I got this senbatsu announcement.
That’s why…
I’ll put everything into Nogizaka and do my best.
Since this is also a long-awaited selection,
I’m so happy.
-You never made it in until now,
So, drop all those thoughts of “why didn’t I enter the senbatsu?”
I'll do my best.
hai, omedetou~
Good for you, please go ahead.
-Thank you very much.
This is… her first senbatsu.
That was cute.
-That’s true.
She made it in her first senbatsu selection.
However, all that’s left are 12 spots.
3rd row,
The next one who will enter the senbatsu is…
Saito Yuuri
Saito Yuuri, omedetou~
Saito Yuuri who has always showed her cheerful self in the show,
it has been 3 singles since the last time she made it in the senbatsu.
Eh? What should I do?
Simply put… no, not that. Honestly, I’m really happy.
I have been working with various under members
it’s like.. because I had learned a lot…
it would be great if I could show them here.
Eh? Now what? It's been a while.
Good for you! You’re happy, right?
I'll do my best.
omedetou!
-Thank you very much!
Yay!
Now, one spot remains for the 3rd row.
-That’s right.
3rd row,
the last senbatsu member is…
Hoshino Minami
With her carefree appearance,
a character loved by the members, Hoshino
She's in the senbatsu three singles back,
will she be able to show her growth since then?
It’s been a while.
-It’s been a while.
What are you feeling right now?
Until now,
I’ve been given a great chance at the beginning,
with being a 7-Fukujin and such.
But, what’s that? there’s that half-hearted feeling...
So the chance slipped out.
Because I got chosen this time, I’d like to give it all I’ve got.
Ah, I see...
Fill up the questionnaire provided by the show, okay?
We’re counting on you.
-I’ll fill them all out.
Declaration of filling everything out.
You said it, we’re counting on that.
Well then, please do your best.
-hai, omedetou~
After this, the announcements for the 10-Fukujin!
10-Fukujin right?
Yes, from this point onwards, it will be the 10-Fukujin.
10-Fukujin,
the first one who will be selected is?
Wakatsuki Yumi
omedetou~
Wakatsuki who has an impressive motor nerve
and has an all-out effort image all the time,
as a 10-Fukujin this time, what kind of image will she show?
I'll be turning 20 this June.
Before that, I was allowed to be in the #6 spot this time.
I’m very thankful for that.
I’m filled with feelings of “I have to really do my best.”
The goal is only thing that is high,
so that I could be more satisfied with myself, I’ll do my best.
You’re turning 20 already.
-Yes.
Then, we’ll look forward to your growth.
Yes.
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
-omedetou gozaimasu~
10-Fukujin, one spot has been decided.
There are 9 remaining.
-Yes.
The next one to be selected in the 10-Fukujin is…
Ikoma Rina
She’s leading Nogizaka with her angelic character, Ikoma,
the experience she gained from her concurrency with AKB,
can she demonstrate that in Nogizaka this time?
This time, you’re in the 10-Fukujin.
My goal this year is to acquire a craft or special skill,
I’m thinking of acquiring skills as my own weapon.
The concurrency as well.
In Nogizaka46 alone, I think there are a lot of things where I could grow, but,
by adding some uneasiness like, “I wonder if I can do this on my own?”
I’ll set myself in motion.
In this one year as a kennin, with the thinking of wanting to develop immediately,
I'd like to give it my best.
We were surprised by your concurrent position in AKB, then you’re even participating in the general election.
Yes.
But this is all for Nogizaka's sake, right?
-That's true.
Well, I’m the one responsible for it,
but I want to elevate Nogizaka46.
I really wanted to extend the fun and happy things to these members,
and I want to know more about them.
Do your best.
-I'll do my best.
omedetou~
Three spots remaining for the 2nd row.
Eight spots remaining, the next 10-Fukujin is…
Akimoto Manatsu
hai, Akimoto~
Akimoto’s presence in the show gets bigger after she started her reaction skills,
with her black-hearted character, can she amass new wisdom and courage?
I came back during the 4th single,
I was allowed to be in the 8-Fukujin for two singles, but…
after that, I dropped in the 3rd row.
From here, in order to go up front, I have to exert effort.
I’ve always wanted to be up front.
I was given this position but…
I won’t lack any effort, I’ll thank the fans and I will work hard.
That’s how you honestly feels right?
You have those feelings of wanting to go up front.
The time I get in front,
I will still keep on showing my thighs and shoulders.
With that, I’ll do my best.
It’s alright. You could go to another trial.
Oath of exposure.
Do your best.
-Yes, I will.
hai, omedetou gozaimasu~
-Thank you very much
Now, two spots left for the 2nd row.
The next one to be selected as a 10-Fukujin is…
Fukagawa Mai
hai, Fukagawa, omedetou~
As Nogizaka’s healing oneesan,
Fukagawa gives tranquility to the members,
with her dearest wish of getting in the 10-Fukujin, a new start has come!
The number of people has changed again this time.
This is my first time being selected in that area of the Fukujin.
The fans are like… coming from those fans from the very beginning…
”Do your best so that you’ll be selected someday.”
I’m very happy that I can finally repay them a little.
This position in the 9th single,
is this a chance for something great?
I'll do my best.
-Do your best.
Thank you very much.
omedetou~
Fukagawa made it in, all that remains is the one at the middle.
The last 10-Fukujin in the 2nd row is…
Sakurai Reika
hai, omedetou~
As Nogizaka’s immovable captain, Sakurai has been pushing forward while bearing that heavy pressure,
by being a 10-Fukujin this time, can she make further progress?
This position is not…
-This is my first time here.
I've always been in the #6 spot.
-Is that so?
That's right.
Last time, during the announcement,
I've said something negative.
However, at handshake events, the fans who saw it...
they said something like “That’s not true!”
and that made me really happy.
Without saying anything negative like that, I have to try harder.
It would be great if I could return the favor with this single.
hai, omedetou gazaimasu~
We’re already at the front, five spots remaining.
Now, let's get to the first row.
Finally, the 1st row, who will be called first?
Matsumura Sayuri
Matsumura, a well-known gluttonous character in the show,
this time she made her way back to the 1st row, we expect her to bring out even more charm.
I'm really happy but... really, it's like...
It’s like, I’m happy that I got in, but…
of course there’s a lot of frustrations.
-I get it.
This will be a long story so I won’t say it, but,
Himura-san, do you like me?
What's gotten into you?
What do you mean by that?
I do, I like all of you.
-Right?
-Do you like me back?
Shitara-san, do you like Nogizaka46?
I do.
Then I will work hard with everyone in Nogizaka!
Well then, please go ahead.
-Do your best.
There are four spots remaining. onegaishimasu~
The next member who'll make it into the first row is...
Matsui Rena
Matsui Rena-san
Concurrently with SKE48, Matsui Rena,
this time, she suddenly entered the senbatsu as a 10-Fukujin.
What kind of fusion will she show with Nogizaka?
So Matsui Rena-san goes right here?
-Yes.
Now, we’re down to three.
The next name that will be called is…
Hashimoto Nanami
Hashimoto made an appearance in a golden hour drama,
playing an active part in various genre,
we’re looking forward to the further progress of that sadistic character?
I cut my hair…
That’s right.
You cut your hair. It became shorter.
Ordinary report?
It became shorter.
I entered Nogizaka when I was 18,
It has been three years…
it is said that the 3rd year is a turning point.
I think maybe this 9th single is also going to be a turning point for me…
in various ways.
It would be nice if we could make a good one.
For the 9th single, what kind of a new Hashimoto will emerge?
Please do your best, okay?
Thank you very much.
After this, finally, the center will be determined!
Just two remaining?
-We’re down to two.
The next one will be the #2 position.
-We’ve come to this.
Two spots remaining, the first one who will be called is?
Shiraishi Mai
So far, Shiraishi had shown various expressions in the show,
including her new character called Kuroishi-san, we expect to see even greater activity.
Rena-san joined us this time.
With this brand new look…
I’m wondering how it will turn out but…
In order to make a better single than what we have so far, together…
I think it would be nice if we could put our strengths together and do our best.
That goes for everyone, wondering how this will turn out,
then there are also a lot of worries, right?
You have to deliver something good if you’re going to do it.
Please do your best.
I'll do my best.
omedetou gozaimasu~
All that’s left is just one spot, the center.
Nogizaka46 9th single’s center is…
Nishino Nanase
Despite being mild-mannered in character,
With the strength hidden within herself, Nishino has gone beyond many walls,
Center for two consecutive singles.
It’s like… uhmm…
I never really thought that I’d be center for the second time.
The activities in the 8th single…
(Being the center) I thought it was just a one-shot.
When I feel really anxious,
The members around me, my family and the fans supported me.
I managed to get through it somehow.
Personally, I was able to do all of the 8th single activities without any regrets.
Being the center for the next single too…
that was the most frightening.
When one became a center for the second time,
the way the fans observe, won’t it be strict?
I’m really scared.
Everytime, right here, Nishino’s words are always pessimistic..
You are scared.
but those around you will support you again. You’re not doing this on your own.
In the 8th single, you did a lot.
Since you were chosen as center, the attention you received increased too. You also did the bungee.
With confidence, do your best in the 9th single as well.
I will.
I’m nervous…
I’m nervous~
9th single senbatsu members are determined!
Inoue who was absent from the recording today,
in order to inform her about making it in the senbatsu,
we go straight to the dressing room after her performance.
Eh?!
Wait a minute… right now…
I was going to take off my costume. I took it off partway.
I got surprised. What’s this?
I hate it. If this is a prank, no way…
What is it?
You made it in the senbatsu.
-Thank goodness!
I made it! Thank goodness!
Since there are a lot of things I learned in Under,
so that I could make the best out of it, I’ll give it my all.
And then, Matsui Rena also expressed her feelings about making it in the senbatsu.
Because I was able to get in as a senbatsu member,
that part, of course… as a Nogizaka member,
I want to do my best.
In NogiDoko, they always do a project that seems to be a hit prayer right?
Getting pounded by a waterfall, then recently, doing a bungee jump.
I think everyone seems to be having fun.
I thought I wanted to do that.
Because I became a Nogizaka, even if I have to work hard to the bone, I hope I could participate in it.
yoroshiku onegaishimasu~