Nogizakatte, Doko?
DON!
-Ouch!
Nogizakatte Doko has started, we're your hosts, Bananaman.
I'm sorry.
and here's... Nogizaka-chan~
There are a lot of them.
There are a lot of them here, what are we gonna do?
You know it, don’t you?
I don’t know, I don’t know anything.
-We don’t have an idea.
You knew about it beforehand, didn’t you?
-What could it be?
I don’t know…
Now then, Himura-san, what do we have for today?
Big annoucement of the senbatsu members for the 10th single!
So fast, huh?
We’re at the 10th single already, and again, this is kinda awesome,
This is like a marker…
A milestone, right?
-That’s right.
In this milestone, Ikuta who was in hiatus due to school work has returned..
Until recently, my hair grew long and I looked mature.
But for this recording, I cut again back to the way it was.
To the way it was.
Were you out for a long time?!
-Yes.
For your hair to grow that much…
Yes, that’s how it goes.
Growth period?
She’s young so her hair grows rapidly, right?
-Really?
But, from here on out, let’s work hard.
yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
And then, there's a new kenkyuusei
Where is she?
Who is it?
Can you please introduce yourself?
Raised in Saitama,
in my 2nd year of high school, 16 years old, I’m Sagara Iori.
yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
Sagara-san?
I am often called as Sagara-san by mistake.
Shitara is almost same as Sagara
Not as Shitara, right? Since it is also read as Sagara.
Sagara, it is “au” followed by “tanoshi” right?
Ah, yes. Ah…
Same as Sagara Haruko-san?
-“ai” in aite followed by “tanoshi”
“Ai,” right?
Uhmm, I’m in a panic, what to do?
Isn’t getting through.
It’s nothing to panic about.
”Au” followed by “tanoshi” right?
That’s what I said.
-You did?
Oi! That’s what he said!
Baptism of Banana.
We’re just kidding.
-I’m sorry.
Again, this time, Matsui Rena and Saito Yuuri are absent due to work.
Well then, the 10th single senbatsu announcement,
the formation is…
Here is the formation for the 10th single.
As you can see,
1st row has five members,
2nd row has five members as well,
3rd row has six members.
There’ll be 16 senbatsu members.
And then, the 10 members from the 1st and 2nd row will be the 10-Fukujin.
There were 17 members for the 9th single,
so it is one person less this time.
But the 10-Fukujin stays the same, right?
5-5-6, right?
Very well, shall we begin?
yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
Very well,
3rd row,
#11
The first member who’ll enter the senbatsu is…
Eto Misa
hai, Eto, douzo~
Eto who has her first consecutive selection in the senbatsu,
we look forward to more of her activities as Nogizaka’s oneesan.
I made it in the senbatsu for the 9th single,
but for me personally, I have some regrets.
Oh, really?
I’ll go back to the basics once again.
Regardless of being a senbatsu or an under,
knowing what my dream is,
thinking of the team more often,
I’d like to do these properly.
Because the chance was given to me this time,
I’d like to do my best in this position.
And I’d like to convey my gratitude to the fans.
Thank you very much.
Do your best, okay?
-omedetou~ ganbatte~
Proceed to the #11 spot.
One member has been decided, there are 15 remaining.
The next member who’ll enter the senbatsu is…
Saito Chiharu
Oh?
hai, omedetou~
She’ll have her most desired first senbatsu in the 10th single,
Please show off that character loved by the members as much as you like.
It took you a long time.
It took me a long time.
You made it in.
Good for you.
What do you think about this?
I've always been an Under,
As I’ve thought, it’s like…
More than anyone, I can’t get anything done and I was really frustrated of it.
So I knew I won’t be chosen.
but…
Thank goodness right?
-It's alright, it's alright.
But you know this day will come, right?
You were working hard while thinking of it.
I want to change for the better with this opportunity.
I want to be a someone who is acknowledged by everyone.
Then, do your best.
Please proceed to that spot.
-Please proceed.
hai omedetou~
Amazing, right?
-Good for her.
There are 14 spots remaining.
3rd row
the member who’ll enter in the #12 spot is…
Wakatsuki Yumi
hai, douzo~
Wakatsuki who always give her 100% in Nogizaka,
that handsome guy personality of hers is essential to the group.
Okay, Wakatsuki.
It’s okay.
I’m sorry.
-No problem.
Recently, there have been a lot of things that I’m worried about.
Oh really?
Why is that?
Well, you see… I’ve been wondering if I’m making any progress.
Really?
And then, this time, my position dropped.
What should I say?
Were my efforts not enough?
That’s why your emotions are mixed up.
I think you’re thinking too much.
Although, I think everyone has their own worries.
I’m not the only one who has worries,
I’m not the only one who is giving it their best.
Everyone is working hard, I have to catch up with them.
This time, I’m reminded of that.
I'll do my best.
Do your best, okay?
I can’t say anything but do your best.
Everything will be alright.
-Do your best!
Thank you very much.
omedetou~
Wakatsuki got in.
Next, 3rd row, who’ll get in the #15 spot?
Takayama Kazumi
hai, Takayama.
Nogizaka's moodmaker, Takayama
recently, she’s in charge of variety, even appearing in other programs often.
We expect more of her progress!
The moment I wasn’t called for the #16 spot...
Saito Chiharu’s spot is Takayama’s usual spot, right?
I thought I won’t make it...
It really hurts...
The fans have seen me from the start until now,
I’m wondering if they’re getting tired of me already.
What’s wrong with everyone? Have you all lost your confidence?!
We’re already at the 10th single!
Are you okay?
You’ll be fine!
You’ll be!
Positive positive...
-That's right.
I haven’t heard that for quite some time now.
-That’s true!
My ribs…
What about it?
My ribs hurt.
With this kind of timing?
Are you okay?
-I’m fine, thank you.
You are rubbing it too much.
Your ribs hurt? Are you okay?
I’ll do my best to be positive in the 10th single.
Thank you very much.
Please do you best.
#15 position.
Everyone who have come up here, they’re like…
Well, I think they have different kinds of emotions, right?
It can’t be helped, so even if they differ from each other,
it’s better to let it out, don’t hide it.
Next,
3rd row,
#13
Will their various emotions be restrained? The member who’ll be called is?
Hori Miona
hai, it’s Hori~
Recently, Hori showed her monomane and weird tastes,
that personality of hers shines more and more.
In the future, pay attention to the personality that she has yet to show.
Uhhmm, the first time I’ve been in the 3rd row,
I’ve learned about a lot of things.
Oh, really?
I want to bring myself out more.
Watching the backs of the senpais,
I’d like to do my best in order to ensure growth.
That’s nice.
These past few singles, it’s kinda….
It’s interesting to have Hori, right?
That’s why bring yourself out more and more.
Please do your best.
Thank you very much.
hai, omedetou~
One spot remaining for the 3rd row.
The last member who’ll be called for the 3rd row is…
Hoshino Minami
Hoshino, omedetou~
A natural-born idol who is loved by everyone, Hoshino.
Will everyone be lured into Hoshino world again this time?
It's like...
Because of the staffs…
Huh?
Because of the staffs… Uhhmm...
Why?
What's the matter?
Because of the staffs, it’s like…
Stop reacting to her response.
Because the story won’t progress.
Did the staffs tell you something?
”Smile = to become Minami”
I was told to smile, and then,
I said okay.
Certainly, you have this smiling image a lot recently.
-I think so too.
That’s true, I think it’s better if you smile.
Therefore,
I thought that I would smile and I won’t cry today!
-Nice one!
There are various things you must change within yourself in order to for you grow.
I'll do my best.
Do your best.
She even did a salute.
That’s nice. Cute, right?
-Keep on smiling.
Salute with a smile.
Please do your best.
-I will.
After this, we’ll start the announcement for the 10-Fukujin!
All that’s left are 10 spots.
From this point, it’ll be the 10-Fukujin.
-That’s right.
The first member who’ll enter the 10-Fukujin is…
Fukagawa Mai
hai, Fukagawa.
Following the last time, she made it in the 10-Fukujin.
With her generosity, we expect her watch over the members and be in the position to lead them at the same time.
This 10th single is referred as a milestone,
I’m also very happy to be selected as a senbatsu member.
I’d like to make a great single with everyone.
For the 9th single, you’ve been in Daibutsu-san right?
See nogidoko ep141
You went to the top of Ushiku Daibutsu to clean it up, huh?
Yes.
Do your best on the next campaign.
Right, there may be another campaign this time.
I'll do my best.
-Please do.
Thank you very much.
-omedetou gozaimasu~
Now then, there are 9 spots remaining.
The next member who’ll enter the 10-Fukujin is…
Matsumura Sayuri
Matsumura, omedetou~
Unlike her image, Matsumura is actually smart and has a strong character.
this time, will we see another side of her?
I don’t know what kind of song this is gonna be...
Since Takayama-san doesn’t say “positive” that much anymore,
What if I will copy that positive chara here in the 10th single?
I see.
-That would be nice.
Positive! Positive!
Don’t do it!
At a handshake event, a 5 year old kid told me…
”I want to see Kazumin’s ‘positive’ on TV.”
Low tone.
You better say it so it won’t get stolen!
Let’s give it a go. Ready, set~
Everyone, starting from tomorrow, be positive!
Face is negative.
Your face is kinda gloomy.
That was probably the maximum “positive” that Takayama can do right now.
Limit for positive.
She was too stiff.
-Everyone, positive!
It’s like a normal fighting pose.
Saying “positive positive!” to everyone,
so that the fans can also be positive.
I’d like to be positive and do my best.
Do your best, okay?
Thank you very much.
Please proceed to the #6 spot.
There are 8 spots remaining.
Let's get going.
I'll continue with the announcement.
2nd row,
#9
The third Fukujin member is...
Sakurai Reika
hai, Sakurai, omedetou~
As the captain, Sakurai brings the group together,
with her leadership skills, will she be able to overcome the tasks at hand?
The next one will be the 10th single, so…
it will be an important milestone.
So that Nogizaka can accelerate further and move in a good direction,
In this single, I’d like to do my best once again.
At the end, we’ll be hearing from you again, so…
Oh no! I’ve said it all already!
Say something different.
We’ll have another take!
omedetou gozaimasu~
Two spots left in the 2nd row, #7 and #8.
Next, 2nd row, the member who’ll get in the #7 spot is…
Akimoto Manatsu
hai, Akimoto~
Following the last time, she made it in the 10-Fukujin.
She has also developed a black hearted character,
it seems like the teasing from the members will increase this time?!
Nogizaka’s 10th single.
We were allowed to do different kinds of things,
and because we have grown...
we have to brace ourselves and unite again.
That’s right, you must be united as a group.
Because I really love Nogizaka,
I want to grow more and work harder so that I could be someone who can lead others.
That’s nice.
Do your best, okay?
Thank you very much.
omedetou~
- #7 spot, right?
One spot left in the 2nd row.
-Ah, you’re right.
The last  member who’ll make it in the 2nd row is…
Ikoma Rina
hai, douzo, Ikoma~
Ikoma became active as senbatsu member for both Nogizaka and AKB,
What lies along that path?
I’m happy to have a lot of work and opportunities.
To be honest,
I also have worries that I won’t be able to finish the things that I have to get done.
There are a lot of things you have to memorize right? Twice than what you have?
Or maybe more than that? You have to memorize everything from the start.
You have to work hard to squeeze it in and remember it all.
But this is the path that you chose.
I think you are growing bigger and bigger.
Do your best, so that you can lead again.
Please don’t give up!
-Please!
I'll do my best!
Then, proceed to your spot.
Only five remaining, who will be chosen as the center?
We’re at the 1st row.
Let's move on, onegaishimasu~
1st row,
#5
The first front member is…
Hashimoto Nanami
hai, Hashimoto~
She's always composed, Nogizaka’s cool beauty, Hashimoto,
She has acquired the Nanamin-beam recently, along with a new side of her.
To be honest, I thought I’ll be replaced.
I thought I’ll be in the 2nd row…
I was wondering if I’ll be called right there.
Why do you think you’ll be replaced?
How do I put this? It’s like…
I have felt that I am stagnant.
I have brought it on myself…
Hashimoto is like that, you often think low of yourself.
I think that you’re making progress.
This group is already growing rapidly at such tremendous speed.
When you’re in that group...
you may not see your surroundings well at times.
You can't see it because there are times where you think too much.
That’s what I think.
I think so too.
-Yes.
It would be nice if this could be a chance for me to become positive.
Do your best, since you’re someone who leads the group.
onegaishimasu~
hai, omedetou~
Four spots remaining.
Yes, four spots.
1st row, who’ll get into the #1 spot?
Matsui Rena
Matsui, right?
She’s not here, though.
She likes talking about her favorite bread and anime,
Matsui gradually began to show her color.
We’ll take more notice of her from now on!
Now then, just three spots left.
Next, 1st row,
The member who will be called for the #4 spot is...
Nishino Nanase
hai, Nishino~
Nishino who served as the center for two consecutive singles is growing rapidly.
We expect her to take on the role of leading the members in this single.
I was allowed to be the center twice.
What was it?
I remember the challenges.
No matter what it was, I never ran away.
It’s like… I am able to change just so that I could challenge those things.
Because it gave me a really valuable experience,
I’d like to do my best in the 10th single so that I can grow more.
She has already grown, right?
It’s because, I was thinking of the past, you can even announce your feelings publicly like that.
What was it?
I don’t really like how I look…
I’m not cute at all.
That’s not true.
Everyone was like “ehh?”
Himura-san has to kill himself if that’s the case.
-That’s true.
I have never thought, not even once, that Himura-san’s face is disgusting.
Nobody has mentioned anything about it!
Don’t go that far.
We didn’t mention anything about his face being disgusting!
You can’t go that far!
After this, the center will finally be decided!
Who will be the remaining two?
We’ll start with the announcement of #2, right?
Last two, the first one who’ll get called is…
Shiraishi Mai
She’s always standing at the front, Shiraishi is pulling the group.
We expect Kuroishi-san’s activation in the future.
This will be the 10th single.
Nogizaka is also in its third year.
I can really feel that this is an important period.
That’s my impression of it personally.
I think it would be nice if our scope can expand.
I thought Shiraishi will be called as the center,
for this 10th single.
No, no.
I’m the same with Hashimoto, I thought I’ll be replaced.
Really?
We never had the impression that you felt that way.
That’s why I thought, “She’ll be called right here!”
Please do your best.
Yes. Thank you very much.
-omedetou gozaimasu~
All that’s left is the center.
Whoever it is, this is gonna be her first?
Someone who has no center experience until now.
Nogizaka46, the 10th single which is worthy of being commemorated,
the center is...
Ikuta Erika
hai, Ikuta~
Ikuta is selected for her first center immediately after her hiatus.
With that innocence, will she be able to build a new image for the center?
We’ve arrived at the 10th single.
Wait, are you okay?
Right now, you’re kinda…
Her face is… she’s completely stunned.
Ikuta, you were called.
I never predicted this would happen.
You’re the center.
I was away for a while,
furthermore, I can’t really feel it.
I got that kind of feeling but, you were called as the center.
Ikuta-san will be singing as the center for the 10th single.
No, no.
She even tilted her head like that.
That’s true, but stil…
It’s like… I just came back, then suddenly, I’m the center…
Personally, I have mixed feelings about it,
I'm pretty sure that it is impudent of me to be here.
Hmmm, it’s like…
Hhmm, but...
My own power… it would be nice if I could show a lot of it.
But…
-There’s nothing you can do but to do your best, right?
Do your best.
You’re going to do it anyway, so you’ll do it, right?
-Let’s do this! Do your best!
I will!
Please go to the center spot.
yoroshiku onegaishimasu~
Please go ahead.
There we have it, worthy of being commemorated,
the senbatsu members for Nogizaka46’s 10th single are decided.
Finally, here’s the comment from Matsui who made it in the senbatsu.
I’m really happy to be able to participate in the single as Nogizaka’s senbatsu once again.
Since Iku-chan was taking a break during the last single,
This will be the first time I’ll be able to work with her along with the senbatsu members.
I’m really looking forward to working with Nogizaka.
For the 10th single, with the feeling of putting everything on the line,
I want to make a great single with everyone.
For the fans, please look forward to its completion. We’d be glad if you will wait for it.