DON! Nogizakatte Doko? has started, we're your hosts Bananaman
And, and these are the Nogizaka-chans
1, 2... Do you like ski?
[Pun with "ski" and "suki"]
So, Himura, tell us what we're doing today
- Eh, say it coldly
- Coldly?
Nogizaka Ski Camp!
These two have said in the show...
- I'm really strong in the snow
- It's true, it's true
Weren't you two bad at sports?
No, we're really strong in the snow
You can ski?
We can!
With that said...
Akimoto & Ikoma Presents: Nogizaka Ski Camp!
The snow!
This time it's us, the bottom two athletes in Nogizaka, but
when we said we were good in the snow, everyone came along! Yay!
We can only ski!
Yes, only skiing
This time we're at the Maiko Snow Resort, Niigata prefecture
with collaboration of Maiko Hotels
The members, divided into team Akimoto and team Ikoma, are having a ski classroom
Ultimately, to evaluate each team's progression, we're having them compete in a race
First it's team Akimoto
To be honest, I haven't had a single ski experience
- She hadn't? That's bad
I used to go skiing with my family in Hokkaido, but
I got scared once and haven't done it since
I'm inexperienced along with Maimai! I'll do my best!
I'm Iori Sagara. I've already skiied twice. I'll do my best
For me it's the 9th time
Wow! Cool
- It's cool so please call me for help today
- It's unexpected!
And for team Ikoma's members...
I went skiing only once
but I fell and got scared
so I changed to the sleigh immediately
I went skiing in a school trip
only once, but
How many years ago?
- Uh...
- Eh, even if you ask me...
I don't have any ski experience! I'll do my best
I don't have any ski experience as well! I'll be in your care
This ski camp is almost full of inexperienced girls
First, we'll show each team's teacher's skills
What kind of sliding will these two bad athletes show?
You wouldn't think those two would be good at skiing!
Teacher Akimoto, good luck!
I'm going!
Manattan, where is your zukkyun?
To everyone's hearts, zukkyun!
Yes, I can slide
Teacher Ikoma, good luck!
I can only ski
Then, let's start the ski class
I'd like to start by putting the ski boards
Do you know how to do it?
I don't know
- They're heavier than they look
- Heavy!
If you aren't careful, you can cut your finger in this part
Where?
Is there a left and right board?
There isn't left and right
I think there's some snow left
Hit it with the stock
- Is this called stock?
- Yes, it is
If you start by your toes it's easier to put it on
Did everyone manage to separate the boards?
I can't
- Huh, it's hard to pull off
- Teacher!
Even though you have been doing it for 9 years
We need a real teacher...
They realized I'm not a real teacher
If you slide this up, you'll be able to separate them
You slide them up
I've been doing it backwards until now
Thank you
Now, with advice of a real teacher,
they're learning the very basics: how to fall and stop
by practicing in small slopes
Noujo, yabai! Once more, once more
Am I going fine?
1, 2... Yes, slide
Break!
My legs are supposed to open this much?
Stop, I'm scared
Well, if it was with Nogizaka, I'd like to go skiing
Why?
But now, until they get the hang of it, they've got to practice by repeating it
Let's start going by lift to the main course
In team Akimoto, where everyone is advancing at the same pace...
Miona is a bit...
Hori of the Ikoma team is facing her own struggle
My legs are dying...
My body is really stiff...
But the rest of the Spartan team Ikoma is already advancing in a fast pace
When...
Miona, why are you by yourself?
Um, I got left behind because of my speed...
Only now I've been able to stand on top of the snow
Aren't you already pretty late?
The upper half of your body is falling
Everyone's telling me that
Overcoming the humiliation of being made fun of by Akimoto...
Will Hori be able to improve?
After this, members of both teams are somehow acquiring the basics
Will team Akimoto win with its teamwork
or will it be team Ikoma and its Spartan practice?
The pride of the two bad athletes is at bet in this showdown!
Continues in the next half!
But really, you two are really good!
Yes, we are
On top of the snow, my blood starts boiling
It really is easier when you have something stuck to your legs
But it's difficult! I wonder how you can do it so much better than the other sports
Because we like it
Here it is! "Suki" and "ski"
[A cheap pun.]
Among other members, there were many inexperienced people
Noujo... Did you choose your own clothes?
I did
Eh... Funassyi
It's true, it does look a bit like Funassyi
Nogizaka karaoke competition!
Some old guys showed up!
From now on, we're having both teams compete in various things
and this will add to the ski challenge to decide the winner
By the way, it's Biking who will host the challenges
Representatives of both teams will face each other at karaoke
The team with the highest score wins!
It's not like you guys are singers, you are idols
That is your main work
This will measure your improvement
Do you usually go to karaoke?
Why are you singing!?
I don't want you to sing!
The first battle is Noujo of team Ikoma versus Wada of team Akimoto
I frequently go to karaoke with other members
I like old songs
I only sing Showa era songs
First is Noujo from team Ikoma
What in the world is she going to sing?
"Omatsuri Mambo" (1952) Hibari Misora
The old man next to me
Watashi no tonari no oji-san wa
Was born in Kanda and is an efficient Edo man
Kanda no umare de chakichaki edokko
He enjoys the noise of the festivals
Omatsuri sawagi ga daisuki de
With a towel in his head and a matching yukata
Nejiri hachimaki soroi no yukata
Rain may fall, jeers may fall
Ame ga furou ga yari ga furou ga
From dawn to night, he carries a portable shrine on shoulders
Asa kara ban made omikoshi katsui de
Hooray hooray
Wasshoi wasshoi
Lift your spirits up, sprinkle some salt
Keiki wo tsukero shio maite okure
Hooray hooray hooray hooray
Wasshoi wasshoi wasshoi wasshoi
That's it, that's it, that's it, a festival
So~re sore sore omatsuri da
The song chosen by the opponent, Wada from team Akimoto, is...?
You'll see I suck at this
[Tulip]
Saita saita tulip no hana ga
They bloomed, they bloomed, the tulip flowers
- It's bad right from the beginning!
All lined up, all lined up, red, white and golden
Naranda naranda aka shiro kiiro
- She looks like a dumb girl
Wherever you look, all the flowers look beautiful
Dono hana mitemo kirei da na
They bloomed, they bloomed, the tulip flowers
Saita saita tulip no hana ga
All lined up, all lined up, red, white and golden
Naranda naranda aka shiro kiiro
- The "kiiro" part is really bad
Wherever you look, all the flowers look beautiful
Dono hana mitemo kirei da na
The score is like this, but the next challenge will have more people singing
The song chosen by the 3 members of the losing team Ikoma is...
"Hanamizuki" (2004) Hitoto Yo
Reaching for the sky
Sora wo oshiagete
You spread your hand in the month of May
Te wo nobasu kimi gogatsu no koto
Please, I want you to come
Douka kite hoshii
I want you to come to the water's edge
Mizugiwa made kite hoshii
I'll give you a bud
Tsubomi wo ageyou
A dogwood flower from my garden
Niwa no hanamizuki
You look cute when you turn pink
Usubeni iro no kawaii kimi no ne
I hope the neverending dream will properly end
Hatenai yume ga chanto owarimasu you ni
I hope for you and your loved one to stay together for 100 years
Kimi to suki na hito ga hyakunen tsuzukimasu you ni
Nice, nice.
The song chosen by the 3 members of the opposite team Akimoto is...
"Kimagure Romantic" (2008) Ikimonogakari
Romantic, my love antennas
Romantic koi no antena wa
Flew away with a storm
Arashi de dokoka e tonde itta
You treated me so coldly, it must be a joke
Uso deshou tsumetaku ashiratta
My heart wavers a little from looking at your cheeky dimples
Koshaku na ekubo ni chotto kokoro ga yureteru
I may bother you with my unpredictable tension
Kimagure na tenshon de furimawasu kedo
But don't you let go of my hand
Kono te wa kanarazu hanasanaide ne
Darling, darling, break down the door to my heart
Daarin daarin kokoro no tobira wo kowashite yo
Look into my eyes when telling me important things
Taisetsu na koto wa me wo mite itte
If I'm with you, we can run away from this city
Anata to naraba kono machi wo nukedaseru
Take me away right now, My Sweet Sweet Darling
Ima sugu tsuredashite My Sweet Sweet Darling
What are this kind of videos?
It's a 3 point difference from "Hanamizuki"
After the 2nd round, the team Ikoma is leading. Will there be a turnaround?
The next game is Russian takoyaki!
You get what it is, right?
Out of 10 takoyaki, 3 are very spicy
In turns, each team's members will eat one
The team who catches the spicy ones will lose 10 points
Will team Akimoto be able to reduce the score difference?
There's a chance it could suddenly be spicy
Itadakimasu!
With the sudden spice hit of captain Ikoma, the team loses 10 points
It's amazing she got it at the first shot
She doesn't seem like she's coming back so let's start
It's good!
Safe!
Next, team Ikoma's Noujo
and team Akimoto's Wada are safe
Then...
Eto from team Ikoma
It's like there was another ball inside of the takoyaki
and it burst when I bited it
Something like a small bag
That kind of thing doesn't even exist in variety. Never heard of that
Thanks to team Ikoma's spicy combo, the difference has been reduced
There's only 1 spicy takoyaki left
The next challengers are team Akimoto's Sagara
and team Ikoma's Matsui. Both safe
Then, Fukagawa also...
It's good!
There are 2 left and 1 of them is spicy
They will be eaten at the same time
Let's eat it!
- What's this?
- It isn't spicy?
In a sudden change of events, neither is spicy
But now, there is a shocking revelation
It isn't spicy
It isn't?
It could have been me
Really?
What about that lag?
What made you think that?
I'm absolutely fine with spicy food
When I ate it, I felt some crunchiness
Wait, you can't eat this without reacting
I can't feel spiciness
Then you are a disgrace to this game!
After Matsui's special power revelation, with 3 spicy takoyakis, team Akimoto has turned the tables
Finally, the 2 captains face a showdown
How are their karaoke skills?
I'm great at skiing but terrible at singing
That's not true
When I hear myself singing in the TV, I hate my voice so much I cover my ears
Stop doing that!
Recently, I've not been able to go to karaoke but I've been humming nicely at home
In the shower, my level has been increasing
Your humming level has increased?
It's quite up
and I think I'm pretty prepared
The song chosen by leader Ikoma is...
[Youkai Taisou Daiichi]
I'm nervous, though...
Monster exercise number 1! Uissuu!
Youkai taisou daiichi! Uissuu!
Hey show up (x4)
Yoo deru yoo deru yoo deru yoo deru
Is a monster showing up or not?
Youkai deru ken deraren ken
Hey show up (x4)
Yoo deru yoo deru yoo deru yoo deru
Is a monster showing up or not?
Youkai deru ken deraren ken
Rooire rooire rooire to your mates, friends are important!
Rooire rooire nakama ni rooire tomodachi daiji!
Youkai youkai youkai watch-ch!!
Youkai youkai youkai uocchicchi!!
Kai kai kii kii kui kui kei kei
Come, come, youkai watch-ch!!
Koi koi youkai uocchicchi!!
After this, Akimoto's song will be shocking...
Lastly is Akimoto. To win, she needs more than 80 points, but...
A while ago on Nogidoko we had a singing corner
and she was quite bad
But my level has increased since that time
You're going to show us that improvement
Yes
It's been 2 years since that shocking singing. What kind of improvement has she got?
It's the same song as before!
"Nantettatte Idol" (1985) Kyouko Koizumi
I heard she sucked at singing this song!
Today is my revenge!
Somehow, an idol
Nantettatte aidoru
Do it seriously!
I pop out from a red convertible without opening the door
Akai konbaachiburu kara doa wo akezu ni tobiorite
Catching the boys' stares while wiggling a miniskirt
Mini no sukaato hirari de otoko no ko-tachi no shisen wo kugizuke
After this, she continued to sing joyfully, but we can't let you hear any more...
I was so nervous...
This wasn't nervousism's fault
The score is...
More than "Tulip"?
I'm definitely improving
Akimoto's high score left some doubts but
team Ikoma has won the karaoke competition
Wow, Akimoto...
And Wada...
Is this an experiment?
While I was singing, I thought it was good, but after it, they called my manager
For not being able to broadcast it?
Yes, that was when I noticed
It was awful, you really suck
Really...
It could be that your ears are too good, it's what they say
Ah, so that's it
That's not it!
[Probably at school]
What did you write as your dream work?
Singer
That's nice
Well, it's not like you really have to be good at singing
As long as your heart speaks
[Because singing is about heart (LOL)]
Aren't you laughing?
Wada was terrible as well
The "kiiro" part
I didn't really think I was a bad singer before entering Nogizaka
but after everyone started telling me that
I started thinking "am I a bad singer...?"
But...
- Wada, are you on drugs?
- Shut up, she's not
You sang "aka, shiro..."
"Aka, shiro, kiiro"
It's not like that
Is this right?
Do it from "aka"
"Aka" is already wrong
Wrong!
[Can't do it.]
But there was a unit of Onyanko Club called Nyangilas
They took Oricon 1st place being bad singers
If it's Mr. Akimoto, he can pull off a song with only bad singers
Let's do a karaoke competition again sometime
No, that's hell
You guys get really nervous about karaoke
We do
I wanna go to karaoke
"I wanna go to karaoke", "if it's with Nogizaka I'll go"...
What are you saying?
You sound like an old man watching late TV
The 11th single individual handshakes are as shown
For more details, go to the event organiser forTUNE music website
Tickets for Nogizaka46 3RD YEAR BIRTHDAY LIVE are up
Let's celebrate Nogizaka46's birthday at February 22
For more details, go to the official site