m 0 0 l 0 27 l 2 27 l 2 0 l 0 0 m 2 0 l -4 0 l -4 6 l 16 6 l 16 4 l -2 4 l -2 2 l 0 2 m 2 2 m 16 0 l 16 27 l 18 27 l 18 -1 l 16 -1 m 22 0 l 22 0 l 24 0 l 24 11 l 19 11 l 19 9 l 22 9 l 22 2 l 15 2 l 15 0 m 6 18 l 6 12 l 12 12 l 12 14 l 8 14 l 8 18 l 6 18 m 12 18 l 12 20 l 6 20 l 6 18 l 10 18 l 10 14 l 12 14 l 12 18 m 5 7 l 8 9 l 7 10 l 4 8 l 5 7 m 10 9 l 10 9 l 13 7 l 14 8 l 11 10 l 10 9 m 3 24 b 3 24 3 23 3 23 b 7 21 11 21 15 23 b 15 23 15 25 15 25 b 11 23 7 23 3 25
MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
weeabookstore.tumblr.com
Nogizakatte, Doko?
Original Indonesian subtitle by MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
English translation by weeabookstore
Because this is sudden, I feel lonely...
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
The 3.5 year journey of Nogizakatte, Doko? Was over
The members cried hysterically, because of Bananaman's last words
Events where I can learn a lot...
After I said, "Let's go eat
with Bananaman-san"...
...and, because you said "Let's go!"...
Thank you for all this time.
Thank you very much.
Shocking announcement at the end of the previous episode!
Previously, Bananaman announced
a surprise about the show.
Fighting spirit!
We started this show in October 2011,
and Nogizakatte, Doko...
...is over today!
Lie!
After this recording...
...the show will probably run...
...about 2 weeks.
But, today is the last recording of
NogiDoko in the studio.
We're done.
- Suddenly?
- Right, suddenly.
You weren't aware of this, and we also...
...just found out not long ago.
The show is over.
It's too bad, but it's real.
They didn't just change the air time?
No. Nogizakatte, Doko is no more.
- Eh, but the prediction...
m 30 0 b 30 0 30 0 30 0 b 12 0 10 12 10 30 b 10 48 12 60 30 60 b 90 60 150 60 210 60 b 228 60 230 48 230 30 b 230 12 228 0 210 0
Previous prediction results
There will be a change in your program
- She did say that, right?
- We are also surprised about that.
Nowadays, variety shows like this...
- ...rarely last long.
- So true!
Since we were involved at the beginning of this show...
...we have been happy that we were able to do it.
Well then, one by one you guys...
- How?
- Eh, you're lying! Really?!
- It's real!
- Seriously!
We're the MC, Bananaman!
Started in October 2011
Nogizakatte, Doko? Ends
It's been 3.5 years since 2011 when this show began.
Today, Nogizakatte Doko is over.
Nogizakatte, Doko? Parting Episode
For now, let's hear
what the members have to say...
...about this farewell episode for NogiDoko.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in April 2012
Special lessons on being female newscasters
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Nishino Nanase
First, Nishino who was usually quiet
and has been involved since the beginning of the show.
Aired in June 2014
"I want to talk about this!" competition
She has managed to change for the better...
...and was chosen to be the 8th single center...
Aired in March 2014
8th single campaign, Macau Tower Bungee Jumping
She herself was willing to
bungee jump from Macau Tower...
...and managed to leave a deep impression.
It really feels like...
...if we won't be able to meet
Bananaman-san often, it'll be really...
...lonely.
Here really...
...feels like a place where I can grow.
And also...
I'm really grateful
for this Nogizakatte Doko show.
Thank you very much.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in May 2013
Nogizaka46 Detailed Blog Analysis
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Takayama Kazumi
Furthermore, the moodmaker of Nogizaka...
...who until now, always performed excellently
on this show, Takayama!
Aired in April 2012
First time Dokkiri on others
Aired in December 2013
Selection of the lousiest sports member
Her silly nature and unique reactions...
Aired in December 2013
Christmas Mousou
...is the source of much laughter.
...it's unnecessary, huh?
What...
...is this, huh..?
Really, all this time...
...because we don't have a theater..
Nogizakatte Doko...
...was like a theater for us.
Since the beginning...
...we've done this together.
This makes me feel lonely,
and I'm surprised...
Also, there are many
things we can do thanks to NogiDoko...
...so we will feel lonely.
This is really...
Eh... if it's really over...
...then it's sad. So...
...this...
I feel lonely.
So...
Thank you very much.
Thank you again.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in December 2011
The first cooking ability check
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Ikuta Erika
Furthermore, she is the most bizarre
among the members...
...but also the most blunt, Ikuta!
Aired in April 2012
Challenging sketch comedy for the first time
That means there's a new plan.
Aired in March 2014
The Macau Tour single campaign part 1
After getting the position as the 10th single center...
Aired in October 2014
10th single campaign, climbing Mount Fuji part 2
...she volunteered to climb Mount Fuji,
and made it to the top!
Because I'm told this so suddenly...
... I really don't know how to feel...
Really...
It really surprised me...
...that this is the last one.
I also...
...managed to develop myself through NogiDoko.
For example, if this show never existed...
...I think, there would be a lot of things
that feel like they're missing.
I will feel lonely...
...when this show no longer exists after this.
But, really...
...to Bananaman-san who were willing
to guide us...
...and to the staff who were willing
to think of many segments for this show...
...I'm really grateful.
To the audience watching this show...
...thank you very much.
Good.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in February 2013
Celebration of Member Birthdays in February
Everyone...ev...every...one...
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Saitou Chiharu
Next...
...she who often feels insecure...
...but with her quite popular Saitou
family song, managed to make this show lively...
Aired in November 2014
The finale of the Nogizaka Observation Competition
...a few words from Saitou Chiharu.
Every time, I really look forward
to being able to meet with Bananaman-san.
Now, as I think about...
...how I won't meet the staff as well...
...of course, I will feel very lonely.
Thank you very much.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in November 2013
The 7th Single Waterfall Campaign Finale
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Nakamoto Himeka
Next...
...she who really wants to continue
to be an idol more than anyone...
...Nakamoto Himeka.
Aired in December 2013
Christmas Mousou
No matter the conditions,
with her Himetan Beam...
Aired in November 2014
The finale of the Nogizaka Observation Competition
...she can cool down any situation in the studio.
Well, thank you very much.
I'm really happy when Bananaman-san
calls me Himetan.
And the staff are also good...
That's what makes me so happy...
...every time I attend a recording.
I'll be lonely later.
Thank you very much.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in March 2013
5th Single Skydiving Campaign
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Akimoto Manatsu
Furthermore, she who likes
risking herself...
...a playful character...
Aired in December 2013
Selection of the lousiest sports member
...she who feels herself the most beautiful...
...she who always thinks of how
to become the center of attention on this show...
Aired in April 2014
Semi Real Neoki Dokkiri
Court for the Cunning of Akimoto
...Akimoto!
Because...
...this is sudden, I feel like I...
...still can't accept this well.
In NogiDoko... during the...
...Senbatsu announcement, when
I just came back to Nogizaka.
Since then, I'm now better known to many people...
You could say Akimoto Manatsu is known...
...because of NogiDoko.
Because this is where it all started.
I really will feel lonely.
I'm very grateful for everyone...
...who always watch this show
every night when it airs.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in December 2011
The first Member Reaction Check
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Ikoma Rina
Furthermore, the center when Nogizaka formed...
Aired in June 2012
Himura's paying, let's buy Ikoma clothes!
...even today, on such an occasion, she always gives off an adult aura, Ikoma!
Aired in March 2013
Debate! Who will go Skydiving
Never forgetting her origins...
...as the face of Nogizaka46, she
also tried hard in other activities.
Aired in December 2013
Selection of the lousiest sports member
To be able to appear alone on a variety show...
...of course, on NogiDoko...
...there are many things I can learn...
...that I can't learn outside,
except on NogiDoko...
...while thinking about things to talk about...
...during recordings here.
Of course, since this is...
...only Nogizaka's variety show...
...this is where we can make an effort.
This has become a show where we...
...can grow.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in February 2013
A bloody contest over Yakiniku
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Shiraishi Mai
Furthermore, she is out of the
idol comfort zone...
...as a recognized model, Shiraishi.
Aired in November 2013
The 7th Single Waterfall Campaign Part 1
She also showed a lot of
talents in this show...
Aired in April 2014
Court for the Cunning of Akimoto
...and managed to pull out the
charm of other members.
Shiraishi-san, laugh!
Honestly, I really...
...didn't expect this,...
...obviously this surprised me.
This show began...
...when this group...
...just formed.
And, we've also received a lot of
assitance from Bananaman-san together.
Nogizaka also...
...became bigger because of it.
Also because of NogiDoko...
...all of us, the members and I...
...each one of us were able to...
...develop our characters.
This show is also the place where we,
as a group, can continue to grow.
When there's another chance, I think...
...it would be good if we...
...can perform at events like this together again.
Thank you very much.
So, the bones have broken?
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in November 2013
The 7th Single Waterfall Campaign Part 1
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Hashimoto Nanami
Next...
...Hashimoto, with her unique sense of humor,
succeeded in bringing laughter to this show.
Aired in February 2013
Celebration of Member Birthdays in February
Behind her calm appearance
she also has a funny side...
Aired in March 2014
The Macau Tour single campagin part 1
...that encourages other members to follow along.
As soon as Hashimoto eats...
...only the stem part of the spoon breaks.
The staff from...
...Nogizakatte Doko, and also...
...Bananaman-san...
Indeed we don't meet
with them every day...
...but, of course, the place where
we can get to know Nogizaka is...
...Nogizakatte Doko.
This is the most important place for us.
Because from the beginning...
...we have worked with many people here...
...who are concerned about us.
Of course...
...Only here can we
show ourselves as we are...
...both the good and bad things.
The staff here...
...and also Bananaman-san...
...to end things like this now...
...slowly it will become more difficult
to get together again, it feels...
...sad...
...and there's also an increasing
sense of loneliness now.
However...
...certainly...
...if Nogizaka becomes even greater...
...I believe that we can all
work together again some day.
With that belief, we will try harder.
Thank you very much.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in December 2011
The first cooking ability check
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Matsumura Sayuri
Why did she put water in?!
Furthermore, with a strong Kansai aura
and cheerfulness as she eats...
Aired in September 2013
Who's the most daring? Selection of Gang Leader
...a really unique original character...
...she who shows a lot of exciting
things, for this show...
Aired in November 2013
The 7th Single Waterfall Campaign Part 1
...Matsumura!
Hm...
Participating in Nogizakatte Doko...
...really, this show...
...truly...
...has become like home to all of us.
We got...
...lot of help here.
I really...
...am grateful. Thank you very much.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in August 2014
Selection of the 10th single Senbatsu
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Sagara Iori
Joining the show during the 10th single...
...as a 10th single Senbatsu member...
...Sagara Iori.
Aired in February 2015
Snow Sports Match Part 1
Although not used to appearing on TV shows,
she tried hard to find her true identity.
Because it was just a while ago
that I was allowed to appear here...
...I don't know yet...
...how I should feel now that it's ending.
So I want to...
...make more effort in the future.
Thank you very much.
After I said, "Let's go eat
with Bananaman-san"...
Tears...
and more tears
Given the 3.5 year memories of NogiDoko,
the members are crying!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in December 2013
Selecting the Eating Queen! Great Eating Contest!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Saitou Asuka
Next is Saitou Asuka.
Her unique commentary is the hallmark of this show.
Recently starting as a model,
she is someone with a lot of talent.
Aired in November 2013
The 7th Single Waterfall Campaign Finale
As others have said,
the staff here...
...and also Bananaman-san...
...as I think about...
...not being able to meet them in a place like this...
...I will feel lonely,
and I don't like that.
If this show had never existed...
...we would not have developed
into who we are today.
I also...
...would not have been able to thrive.
I'm really grateful for this show.
Thank you very much.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in September 2013
Who's the most daring? Selection of Gang Leader
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Itou Marika
The next member, Itou Marika.
Aired in February 2013
Celebration of Member Birthdays in February
So your face is big and round?
Eh, why?
Aired in November 2013
The 7th Single Waterfall Campaign Part 1
With a soul derivative of...
...her parents' own art, she often shows her
artistic soul on this show.
A year has gone by
since I entered Senbatsu...
...looking forward..
...I think I want...
...to be able to perform better.
But, really, because this show is over,...
...at a time like this, it'll be really lonely.
But, though I feel lonely,
if there's a chance...
...I want to do this again.
Thank you very much.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in October 2013
Selection of the 7th single Senbatsu
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Hori Miona
Furthermore, she who was surprisingly
chosen to be the 7th single center...
...Hori Miona.
Aired in December 2013
Christmas Mousou
With quick improvisation...
...she showed her talents
in a captivating performance!
Aired in October 2014
10th single campaign, climbing Mount Fuji part 2
This show was practically a showcase for
the Nogizaka members with Bananaman-san.
I always looked forward
to watching this show each week.
Then when I joined the show...
...and I participated in my first recording...
...I was really...
...full of pleasure.
That's because I received
a lot of experience here.
There are a lot of things that I
did for the first time on NogiDoko.
There are also many things I learned...
...through NogiDoko.
Those are the things I'm using now...
...and I will try very hard...
...to make Nogizaka even greater.
Thank you very much.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in March 2013
The 5th Single Skydiving Campaign
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Hoshino Minami
Next, her character
doesn't like trying things...
...but there are also times when
she shows us amazing things, Hoshino!
Aired in September 2013
Who's the most daring? Selection of Gang Leader
Once she decides on something,
she will definitely follow through...
Aired in June 2014
"I want to talk about this!" competition
...and often stun everyone.
At first, I wasn't good at speaking...
Ehmm...
But, because of this show...
...I'm getting better at talking.
Some time ago, because I
I didn't receive the Himura Prize...
...and another time, Bananaman...
...didn't buy me clothes...
...Afterward I said, "Let's go eat
with Bananaman-san"...
...and, because you said "Let's go!"...
...I was really looking forward to it...
But, because it was said
that this show will end...
...we definitely won't be able to go...
In the future, we all want...
...to chat casually with Bananaman-san.
Ehm...
I'm sure I'll feel lonely...
Thank you very much.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in December 2011
The first cooking ability check
The oil!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Etou Misa
Next, Etou, the girl full of spirit,
with her distinctive Oita accent.
Aired in January 2013
Congratulations! First tour as an adult woman
As a senior member...
...she is often embarrassed on this show.
Aired in September 2013
Who's the most daring? Selection of Gang Leader
Do not underestimate the girl from Oita!
Okay, let's go!!!
During the Senbatsu announcements, of course...
...everyone feels like
that is where they should stand.
As an Under member, I'm really...
...under a great amount of pressure.
However, Bananaman-san...
...are always delivering comments
that are full of love.
That...
Things like that...
...only Bananaman-san alone is willing
to say such things, and it really has...
...helped me a lot when
I remember those things.
The only thing I'm feeling right now is
a thousand feelings of gratitude.
Remembering events over the past 3.5 years
The 3.5 year trip has finally ended.
the members cry
Goodbye NogiDoko!
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in September 2013
Who's the most daring? Selection of Gang Leader
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
m 10 24 b 10 24 10 24 10 24 b 3 19 0 16 0 13 b 0 10 2 8 5 8 b 8 8 10 10 10 13 b 10 10 12 8 15 8 b 18 8 20 10 20 13 b 20 16 17 19 10 24
Wakatsuki Yumi
Easy!
Next, she is always carefully
paying attention to the group...
Aired in June 2014
"I want to talk about this!" competition
...she is always concerned about
the problems of other members...
...Wakatsuki.
Aired in June 2014
Ikoma Rina, en route to Sousenkyo
Ikoma Rina, you'll be fine.
We all support you. Good luck!
This means that won't be any more times...
...we...
...can come back here every week...
Everything about Nogizaka...
...I think comes from NogiDoko.
Everything about Nogizaka, was made here...
Of course, we want to convey...
...how grateful we are for this show.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in May 2013
Nogizaka46 Detailed Blog Analysis
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Fukagawa Mai
Fukagawa, the most senior member of the group.
Aired in April 2014
April Fools Competition
She get's called Holy Mother...
...her gentle sincerity need not be doubted.
She puts on a good face, even as
she sheds tears for her friends.
Aired in December 2013
Christmas Mousou
Fu...Fukagawa!
We've been doing this together for about 3 years...
...It's really like everyone is here.
Only on this show, we all...
...were able...
...to learn a lot from here freely.
That only happens on NogiDoko, I think.
The fans also tell me that they
look forward to NogiDoko every week.
So, this show for us...
...is a very important thing.
I still can't imagine,
that this show will not exist from now on.
But really, I'm so happy...
...to be working together with Bananaman-san.
From now on, we'll all strive
to one day be together again.
Thank you very much.
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Aired in December 2011
The first Member Reaction Check
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Sakurai Reika
The last heartfelt expression,
comes from the captain, Sakurai.
Since the beginning of the group...
Aired in April 2012
Special lessons on being female newscasters
...she's always been there
and grew up alongside this show.
What are Sakurai's current thoughts?
Aired in May 2013
Nogizaka46 Detailed Blog Analysis
Welcome!
I do not want this...
...to end.
However, it is better that we are
notified beforehand.
That's what I think...
When our group was newly formed...
...when we still did not have a song...
...the first thing we were given...
...was NogiDoko.
Through joy and sorrow...
...everything we have we get from NogiDoko.
Although there are still so many...
...who watched this show from the beginning...
...that NogiDoko will not be
there anymore is really...
...frustrating.
If later NogiDoko...
...is rebooted...
Hopefully...
...we can work again with the same team.
Of course with this...
In a way, we were also involved from the beginning...
...and now we have reached the 10th single..
...of course we don't want to stop
after just the 10th single.
They are also growing quickly, aren't they?
With this sudden thing, maybe
we've rarely said this before.
Other shows may also be like this, we
requested to stay on the show until the end.
But, in my personal opinion...
...by looking at their development...
When compared to other shows...
...NogiDoko, in our opinion, is different.
We also feel good when we come here.
With the more and more activities we do...
...we also enjoy just talking with you for example,
"What are we going to do next?"...
I think maybe after this we
might not be that way again.
I thank you deeply.
Anything you want to add?
I think basically the same, yes.
Of course, with any show, when there's a beginning
there is also a time when the show will end.
And Nogizakatte Doko has
already run 3 or 4 years...
...It can be said that...
...the progress you've made from
when we first met...
...cannot be compared to anything, right?
You are also able to
fill the Seibu Dome now.
From this point...
...the show is indeed over, right?
We can all behave
as usual after this.
We'll still be here.
I think there's still a chance that we
will be able to meet again.
Whether this announcement becomes the last
or something new appears...
...there may be a lot that can change.
Today is the last studio recording for NogiDoko.
Thank you for all this time.
Thank you very much.
Because of Bananaman's last words
The members cry hysterically
After this, the last words of Bananaman...
...make members cry!
Thank you for all this time.
Thank you very much.
Then, Nogizakatte Doko is over,
but there is a new show that will start.
The MC are Bananaman...
...all of you will also participate.
We will renew this show.
Heeee~
Crying disappears.
- Shitara-san... this...
- Really, their development is visible.
There were too many speeches to get to this point.
A ridiculous 25 minute charade.
They even cried...
We asked them to say something,
and they said a lot.
- Very long!
- Because I thought this was the last...
Because this is the last Nogizakatte Doko...
- Long...
- We'll keep showing new NogiDoko...
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
19 April (Monday) 00:00 - 00:30
New show begins
MC: BANANAMAN    Performers: Nogizaka46
- So we will renew this.
- Yes, that's right.
Still at the same hour, so all the audience
please continue to support us from now on.
Then are any of the staff replaced at all?
- Still the same!
Ah, come on!
Seriously...
Unexpectedly, you are all grateful
for Bananaman, yes.
That's clear!
Ah, you guys... you even cry for us.
Tears from the heart.
Of course we'd cry.
Look at Sakurai, her face is scary!
That is true.
Are you mad?
Worst! You're the worst!
After this you have to sing
and dance, your tears...
Of course we're crying...
I have no idea how we're going to feel
when we perform.
Because we also do not know when this show will end,
so you need to prepare yourselves, yes.
Hoshino was great, she...
...spoke loudly for the first time.
This is the best moment in Hoshino's history.
"I want to eat together!"
This is great. You can
express all those feelings.
That's great.
Hashimoto was crying a bit...
Of course, when I think I will not be able
to meet Bananaman-san again, it's really...
Because I really like Bananaman-san.
From now on express your appreciation.
- We're happy!
- Right, we are happy.
Forgive me.
After this, yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
Onegaishimasu.
And, all of you...
Thank you for watching
Nogizakatte Doko.
Please join us for our next show.
All right, everyone, see you again.
- See you again!
- Goodbye.
Thank you for 3.5 years
We ask you to support the new show.
The battle of the audition for the stage play
Nogizaka46, "Joshiroku" has finished.
Among the 26 members who participated...
...these are the 15 who have been elected
to play in the stage performance.
Look forward to the show, starting in June.
Original Indonesian subtitle by MasToppu.blogspot.co.id
English translation by weeabookstore
m 167 42 l 0 42 l 0 0 l 167 0
Furthermore, why are these two people featured in the last episode of "NogiDoko?"
Exciting chats and silly Kawago and Noujou scenes show up!
Once again, we want to see...
...the scene.
- Ah, were you still 13 years old?
- Yes, that's right.
Bad!
Although I tried hard at that moment...
- The day before yesterday, they just appeared?
- Wait, wait a minute!
Tragedy strikes Kawago & Noujou!
And, tragedy came to Kawago and Noujou!