Suicide?
Oh no
Excuse me, could I borrow a rag?
A rag right?
- What's the matter?
Looking for a rag
Why don't I wipe it for you?
- No it's fine
Sorry about that
I was surprised
For Samu to have commited suicide
Please hand me some tissue as well
Kimu no Koto
What did the driver say?
My sister was staggering towards the truck
Even though he honked the car horn and stepped on the brakes as quickly as he could,
she didn't stop, he said.
She was out to buy something right?
- Yes
What did she buy?
Chocolate
Chocolate?
- Yeah
Was it Apollo?
It was Takenoko no Sato right?
No, it was Kinoko no Yama right?
Choco Baby
It was milk chocolate
It couldn't be..
So it was milk chocolate after all...
Not that
I was talking about it being a suicide
Here
- Thank you
Is it because you're driving?
She just doesn't drink alcohol
Please come in
If you'd excuse me for a bit
For it to have been a suicide...
It hasn't been confirmed
Maybe she bought chocolate for comfort..?
That's what happens to people with dependence
Although I don't know on Samu's case but,
knowing that you must quit something but you can't.
I understand that feeling
I had an addiction to drinking alcohol after all
2 years ago
There's only 10 minutes left, please get ready on standby
- Okay
Kimu? Something wrong?
Sorry, I'll be going now
I've always been easily nervous
Without knowing it, I couldn't stand on stage while sober
To make it worse,
having this piling anxiety of not being able to sell well
I go straight to the bar after work
I can forget everything if I drink after all
Excuse me!
Refill please
This will be the last orders for drinks
Then another 3 of the one I had
3 High balls!
As the number of alcohol increased,
so did the number of things I did.
There was a time I found the button for calling the clerk at the bar in my bag.
There has also been a time I was sleeping with a red cone from a construction site.
There is a missing part spotted on the bronze statue of a girl smelling a flower.
The concerned locals have began to search.
Here is a report from the area.
I am here at the place where the statue is found, Tsujigaoka Danchi shopping district.
As pointed out by my right hand,
this is the shopping district's symbol that has grown to be loved by the community, the bronze statue of a girl holding a flower.
Like this, the flower that the girl is supposed to be holding
has been broken off and stolen by a cold-hearted person.
As stated by the woman in charge of cleaning the area,
"When I was cleaning the statue, I noticed the flower was gone,"
"I couldn't find the broken flower anywhere either while cleaning nearby."
So right here, we have the Shopping District's Promotional Association's head, Karasawa-san, to talk about it.
First of all, please let us hear your feelings about this.
It is the shopping district's symbol after all,
it is important and cherished by us.
Like this,
the people of the shopping district and its locals
are furious at this cold-hearted person's prank.
The next station is Higashino
The exit is at your left
Please be careful of leaving things behind
This should be fine
That flower will go around and be seen by many people
and it will be back to where it belongs.
Kimu!
It really is you!
You forgot this!
Thanks
What's that?
I don't know. I just got it from a fan awhile ago.
Eh~ I want to see what's inside
Sorry, I was told to take a look at it once I'm home
It's fine, just a little bit
I said you can't
Why~ Just show me
- I said no
Every morning that I go here, I always look at it thinking it was cute
It was a source of encouragement for me
For this to suddenly happen
It's so unfortunate, and looking at it now, it's pitiful.
That's why I hope it is returned soon
Good morning
- Morning
I really can't forgive people like this
What's that?
Someone took the bronze statue's flower
Isn't that horrible?
It is
The statue itself has no damage besides the missing flower
This is the first time this has happened
The town is currently discussing strengthening security via installing security cameras.
Great job
- Great job
Samu?
I told you not to look!
Isn't this the thing in the tv?
Come with me
I'm tired
There wasn't much people today either
Well it can't be helped.
It was a lie, that it was given by a fan
Are you the culprit?
Probably...I drank too much so I don't recall doing it though
You drank that much huh...
Yeah
It's embarassing, so don't tell the others okay?
Then let's go put it back
If we put it back to where it was, there will be no problems right?
We'll be found out if we do that!
Everyone will be shocked if it suddenly returns!
I told you we can't!
- It'll be fine. Let's go?
Samu! Wait a minute!
-It'll be fine I'm telling you
Samu was really a troublesome person
Not minding the atmosphere
She didn't mind other people's situation and feelings
In the case she didn't get to answer her phone,
she's the type to keep on calling back until you answer.
Welcome
That's it!
It'll be fine
We're just looking at this famous statue after all
Want some?
As if I would right now
Now's our best chance
Get the flower
Make it quick
Well? Did it stick?
Yeah, looks like it.
Let's get out of here
Wait
Wa-What are you doing?
Come on, to commemorate this
Look
We look so ugly
Come on already let's go
Oh no
The flower sticked somehow
The incident ended with no problems
We have come to the place where the damaged bronze statue is, Tsujigaoka Danchi shopping district.
It originally is a statue of a girl smelling a flower but the once missing flower has now been returned.
Then again, please take a look.
The flower is faced differently.
Here is how it looked before being damaged
Its original position had the flower facing the girl's face like so, however,
right now, as you can see, it is facing the other way around.
The girl is now not smelling the flower,
it has become the girl that is throwing away a flower.
Was it planned to be this kind of prank all along?
It's finally over
The head of the shopping district's Promotional Association, Karasawa-san, was invited over today
I like it better like this though
Good day. So Karasawa-san, so now the girl is-
I'd like to thank all of you for making your way here for Chika
Even so, that news had a follow-up.
"Why is it that the bronze statue,"
"the girl who is not smelling the flower", became a buzz.
People came to see the statue
The shopping district which was close to closing came back to life
The people were able to quickly turn things around,
and the situation calmed down.
What were you all called again?
It was that name that sounded like a baseball team
It was "Udagawa White Bears"
Right, right, it was "Bears"
What did you guys do again?
What work could it have been?
We sang songs
You sang? What was the chorus?
We were idols
Idols huh?
- We've already disbanded though
I didn't know at all! Were you guys popular?
Not really...
I see... I mean I've never seen you after all
I don't know much about the entertainment world but...
It's a pretty cruel world to those without talent
You see, when I was young, I drove a taxi.
But you see, I couldn't read maps!
I quit after half a year!
I often had fights with customers, but it's fun to look back on those memories!
Here you go
I'm sorry, I don't drink alcohol.
You should be fine with a little
I'm fine
You guys are really well-mannered huh~
because of that you guys think I won't suspect you?
Old man, you've drank too much
Let's get you to sober up outside, come on I'll help you stand.
See you again~
Speaking of idol groups,
you might think that there is a strong relationship within the members.
But at that time,
even though we had to align ourselves everyday,
but rather than a friend,
and not just someone you want to beat either,
with a plastic like superficiality,
it was an unreliable relationship like a sponge.
With no big problems between members,
nor any touching moments,
without really meddling on each others lives
within ourselves.
Only Samu was the troublesome one.
You think Komiyama-san will come?
He's our ex-manager so he'll probably come right?
But the ones he's handling now is busy
Are they selling well?
- Yeah
They're pretty popular
Their next live is in Budoukan
Budoukan huh...
That's great for them
That's true
- Yeah
If Samu were alive, she would've probably felt the same
Samu really died already...
Sorry for the trouble I caused you
Not at all
He's usually very kind but when the alcohol hits, he can be very hard to handle.
We kind of figured
Is it fine if I join in the conversation?
Yes, of course
How was Chika around the family?
My sister was...a naive person.
Naive?
- Yes
She's so spoiled at home
She used to follow me wherever I go when she was young
When I go out to play with friends, she makes sure to come along
That's why I always left the house quietly so that I won't get caught by her,
but somehow she senses it and still catches me.
I was already of age at that time so I'd play tricks on her
she'd follow me even if I teased her.
My bicycle was already small and slow even when I'm alone,
but she'd still pedal with all her strength.
That's cute of her
Since I know I can't top her stamina,
I tried thinking of a different way.
And then actually she often lied
Really?
It was stupid lies though.
Like "my foot got dislocated, or "my heart stopped".
Or "I'll be taken away by a big bird"
It was quite easy to find out though
Was it only lies for deception?
Eh what's with that?
Like "stopping global warming"
Global warming?
Yeah, she says it and just stopped one day
Nope, I've never heard that one before
I see
- I thought that would be the case
But somehow it's just like Samu
Samu?
Yes, we referred to Chika-san as "Samu"
Well, she was the one who told us to call her that
I see....
Is that so....
So she went by as "Samu"...
I see
"Samu"...was Chika-san not called "Samu" since before?
Samu is my nickname
I was called "Samu" before
"Samu" from Osamu
Why would she say that?
Samu no Koto
Then who is this? A different Samu?
The feeling of "My sister's happiness is also my own"
I'll quit from being an idol after all
Since when did you find out?
We're already here so why don't we take a look?