I will call you back later
Once the festival schedule is out
So "Samu" isn't really her nickname?
I believe so
I've always thought it was weird
Samu had the looks after all
She's a woman in the first place
Momo no Koto
Here
Thank you
Everyone please help yourselves as well
Thank you very much
But why would she use your nickname?
Did she look up to you or anything of the like?
I wonder
I don't think so
Then is this another "Samu"?
Samu...
Samu
Samgyupsal?
Ah right
While I have the chance,
could I ask for your signatures?
Yes, of course
That's our debut single
I'm aware, the one that has the "a" and "r" in "Bears" swapped right?
Yes
No one, not even the recording studio noticed
No one would want to listen to it after all
That's not true
I sing the songs often at the karaoke
Do you girls not sing your own songs? At karaoke and the like
Not at all recently
You guys?
It's been a year since I sang
You used to sing that one song a lot
We used to sing a lot in our free time
I see
That's a pity
Here
Thank you very much
TN: Mercari is an online market
I'll quickly put it up for sale in Mercari
Just kidding
I'll treasure it
Please take it easy
- Yes
If you'd all excuse me
Thank you very much
He's not just looks, he's also interesting
Having a sibling must be nice, I'm an only child after all
I mean an older brother having an idol sister, he would be proud about that
Momo you did say you were proud of Kirara-chan too right?
- Yeah
You never felt bad because of her?
Nope
It's like my sister's happiness makes me happy as well
Sounds like you
I'll just take a call
Sure
Not wanting to talk further, I just stood up
I don't think all sibling relationships are good
Contrary to that,
I think being connected by blood makes things more unforgivable.
2 years ago
Good morning
- Morning
You just woke up?
Kirara help out too
- Hassle
Just get your own soup okay?
What coat should I wear for the new year's shrine visit?
Don't you have a lot?
I'm tired of them all
Wanna borrow my Chloé coat?
Is it alright?
- Yeah
The Chloé one? Didn't you buy that just the other day?
Yeah I haven't used it much so it still looks new
It would probably look good on you
- Alright!
Come on Kirara!
My sister Kirara
She's a popular idol, different from me
She's only 15 and still small
- It's amazing right?
You also appeared in the morning show right?
Everyone in the neighborhood saw it!
Grandma is so proud because of Kirara!
What kind of person was the host? Same as how he is in tv?
The difference is a little big
Eh is that so?
And here I thought he was a good person
As an idol, Kirara received more attention
Because products of cosmetic brands began to rise,
it became something sought after by junior high students.
Momo-chan what have you been doing these days?
You used to sing in a group right?
It was that, the one with the boys baseball team like name
It's Udagawa White Bears, I still sing there
You still do that?
More or less
I saw you guys the other day
You were planted in mud by Kojima in that late night show!
That really made me laugh!
It was really hard after that!
Mud even went into my nose
There were crayfish inside the mud
Did you not get pinched?
I did and it hurt!
I didn't know idols had those kind of work too
It's really hard
Why don't all of us relatives go to Kirara-chan's concert next time?
T/N: In case some don't know, uchiwas are the fans that have their faces
That sounds great, with us all holding her uchiwa
When grandma stands up, I wonder if she'll stand out from the big crowd?
That doesn't matter, I mean we're just watching!
I'll quit being an idol after all
What's wrong..?
Kirara!
Did I say something..?
It's nothing
Fatty even in 5th grade
#Kirara
Isn't the management forcing it?
# Kirara
Seems like she goes to night clubs
#Kirara
Kirara is already washed up!!
# Kirara
Kirara what's wrong?
Is something bothering you?
My sister became a shut-in from that day onwards
Kirara? What's wrong?
After becoming big,
haters started to appear and say things.
I'm kinda getting tired of her now after seeing her too much lol
#Kirara
I never thought that she was cute!
I don't think she can handle variety shows
# Kirara #Kirara #Bang✰binaKirara
The clothes she wear are crazy right
#Bang✰binaKirara
[Leak] I think she uses eyelid glue
#Kirara #Bang✰bina
Kirara, come out
Don't mind the rumors
Let's eat breakfast
I'll be going now
Kirara, your manager is waiting you know?
There were no fake rumors
I mean, the one who started the negative campaign
was me posting from fake accounts after all.
What kind of person was the host?
Same as how he is in tv?
The difference is a little big
Eh, is that so?
And here I thought he was a good person
Of course there's gonna be a difference
There's the popularity to maintain
But he's not a bad person! He comments when needed, and he isn't perverted.
That's Kirara-chan for you! He even follows up for you
Momo-chan what have you been doing these days?
At that time I was harassed by negative comments,
and it just suddenly stopped.
A performance that is just spoiled by the crowd
#WhiteBears #Momo
She's the only one that messes up the choreography
#WhiteBearsMomo
She just sucks up to the management
#Momo
Eyes were definitely fixed
No good qualities! Bad upbringing
#Momo
She runs weird
Really bad physical abilities too
#Momo #WhiteBearsMomo
As I envied my sister's success,
I thought of giving her the same suffering I get
So?
I'm worrying if this move will be seen properly
Excuse me, here are your drinks
Thank you very much
You guys really like to sing
Thank you for always coming here
We're sorry if we stay too long sometimes
We're free after all
Not at all
I always think it's nice seeing how close you all look
Thank you
Back then, we used to go for karaoke often
Without troubling anyone, it was our own little place
Thank you for your patronage. If you'll excuse me
I wonder if she thinks we're just that group of friends that likes to karaoke
I wouldn't be surprised if she did, I mean we've always gone here
It's like our second home
Looks like Komiyama-san won't come
I told him to show his face
He really doesn't come when you want him to
Anyways, let's put on a song
I don't really remember much
I kinda remember the lyrics though
How did it go?
Something like "Meeting you, it felt like there will be a new tomorrow"?
#Kirara has stinky feet
Those are pretty common lyrics
I can't tell from that
Do you remember anything else?
Samu
Go outside
It's the one where you think it's already the chorus, but it actually comes after that
A song with typical lyrics and grand music?
Is it that?
You understand?
- Hand it to me for a bit
What is it?
I know of that. It's the stolen picture of my sister's face right?
The culprit that can be seen from the side mirror
is without a doubt, me.
When did you find out?
Just awhile ago
You must be disgusted
You're probably wondering what am I doing
to my own sister no less.
I'm really the worst
Rather than the worst, more like scum at the very least
But having a successful sister like that, even I would probably pretend to be a hater.
I mean someone can be jealous of you too, then it would be just the same.
No one would be jealous of me
Have you not seen the things they say about you?
I don't look at those
A performance that is just spoiled by the crowd
Can't follow the choreography at times
Just sucking up to the management
Well, there's stuff like that
Really, they should come up with something new
Probably got her eyes under surgery
As if, if I did that I would do it to fix my nose
She's unrefined, looks like a result of bad upbringing
How I was raised was fine
True, your parents are fine
Then there's the weird way you run
Also horrible at physical abilities
That sounds about right
How do you know all of those?
Because the one negatively campaigning you was me.
No way
Maybe?
What? Are you just playing me?
I'm sorry I wasn't able to take your call
We'll push through with it
Shinagawa Stadium at 5 in the morning
I understand. I will confirm it quickly.
Thank you for calling
I am currently working as an idol manager
It's not as glamorous a job as before,
but the feeling of jealousy is gone.
It is surprisingly fun to do
In the end I don't know if Samu saved me or she was just after me
Which was it I wonder
Keep it a secret from the others okay?
Where did you guys go? It's almost time
Samu wanna sing?
A song to get us pumped would be good
- Yeah!
Samu always gets things out of people
Forcing herself inside the hearts of others
Love is over
Kaoru Ito
But we never listened to Samu
I wonder why "Samu"
What kind of love did you experience?
This is supposed to hype us?
You were here
Why?
We were talking about leaving soon
It would be bad if we miss the last train
-That's true
Let's tell them before leaving
What's up?
We're already here, so why don't we take a look?
It feels like her undying spirit will appear
I bet it will be an amazing room
Pitch dark, with a skeleton and the like?
Like Torii Miyuki's home?
Or it's really dirty, like a garbage house?
You guys should stop that
Here it is
Then, I'll wait downstairs
Thank you very much
This was Samu's room?
It's typical
It really is
This is too normal
Or is it strangely just like her for it to be like this?
There's none of our idol stuff
Shouldn't there be at least a little trace of it?
Like a past she wanted to erase?
That's cold
I don't know why she suddenly left
Maybe Samu didn't really care what happened to Udagawa White Bears
That kinda gets me mad
It means she already got rid of us right?
You wouldn't know that, unless you ask the person herself
But somehow, doesn't it make it seem like it's not real?
That in reality she's alive, hiding somewhere
Like a grand prank
With a hidden camera, watching us be deceived while laughing
Through a monitor?
Sooner or later she'd come in holding a sign
For real?
Sorry, could you guys sign this t-shirt as well?
Thank you very much
I'll quickly post it in Yahoo! Auctions
I'm kidding, I'll treasure it
I'm sorry but I still can't laugh at that
Even after the second time?
Sorry, even I wanna kill him
Let's go home?
What the hell is this?
Look at your phones
Samu?
Samu
New Message
Samu no Koto
How do you know?
I can see it
Pay up already!