A new message from a supposedly dead Samu...
None of us has opened it yet
Sumi no Koto
I'm sure we'll die if we look at it
As if that would happen
But isn't it a little scary?
I don't believe those kind of stuff
Then you take a look
Fine by me
I don't believe in ghosts and the occult
Unlike before
2 years ago
Sorry, I think I got that last part wrong
It's fine, I made a mistake too
I'm not sure but I think I got it wrong too
You forgot it too, right Samu?
Nope, I'm sure I did well
Well what nothing we can do now
Let's just do our best next time
- Yeah
Everyone makes mistakes
So no one blames anyone for it
Then again, I've always thought about it
The fact that we can laugh like this over such things
maybe its the reason why we're not selling well.
They're not looking anyway
- Yeah, no one would notice
I never had an interest in fortune telling up 'till that point, but...
I had an uneasy feeling at that time so...
Your ambitions are quite strong
However, there seems to be a "wall" obstructing your job that you need to bust through
You feel that your friends are still immature
and it kind of gets on your nerves.
How do you know this?
I can see it
I was surprised
It was like she already knows everything about me
It looks like you'll have to look for a blue object
Looks like it will let your efforts bear fruit
A blue object...
In today's ticket holders
Sumi's spot seemed to have a lot more people
I thought that too
Just by chance
Looking at the sales recently, don't you think we're doing good?
At this rate maybe we can reach Budoukan
Here we come Budoukan!
How many thousands of people would fit there?
Isn't it tens of thousands?
Then it should be 100,000
After following my fortune, my luck has turned around
With luck quickly taking effect
I get the feeling it really is thanks to her.
But after all, our goal is Tokyo Dome right?
- Yeah!
If you strive, things can really change
I'm telling you it has to be Budoukan
For your fortune telling needs, it's Nanahoshi Seira here
When I try looking at your fortune,
I can kind of see something unpleasant.
If possible, I'd like for you to come see me again
A female evil spirit?
I believe this evil spirit is preventing your success
What do you think I should do?
Why don't we try an exorcism?
Exorcism?
Since I got worried,
I asked for the exorcism
The exorcism costs 30,000
Hello? It's Hasumi
I've just deposited it
Please listen carefully okay?
Okay
I know you're getting the exorcism but
there seems to be 2 evil spirits.
For this instance, we will need a higher level of exorcism so
Unless I don't call another exorcist of my level, I won't be able to deal with it
I did ask for it but
I don't have anymore money.
If it's money then there are plenty of ways to get it
But...
This isn't your problem alone
Misfortune will befall even your family
Is that fine with you?
From then on I continued following her advice
Following everything she said, I deposited the money
Looks like the exorcism isn't enough to handle it
looks like it would be good to get a guardian spirit to protect you.
Prepare another 100,000
Okay
It seems the guardian spirit's spiritual power is too weak
We'll need to power it up even more so
quickly deposit another 300,000
I understand
You really have great luck
The guardian spirit is amazed by you, and it would be great if you can give 1 million now to seal the deal
Isn't that great?
Really?
Thank you very much
Yes....Okay, thank you very much
Well then
Hello?
I just saw the flyer and I'm calling to inquire...
Hasumi-san!
Please come out!
You're there right?
Get out of here damn it!
You know Hasumi...
Not ready yet?
It will be troublesome if you don't pay back!
You're there aren't you!
Hasumi-san!
You know it would be better to get out here quickly right?
Pay up brat!
Get out here!
I was driven into a corner
I don't know what's my reason for living
If the train were to get derailed
and just crush me, it would be better.
That's impossible right?
Sumi!
What are you doing here?
In order for Samu to not find me out, I tried to regain my composure
Out on a walk!
Come with me then if you're free
Keep at it!
It has become intense!
It's dangerous so please clear off
To the me who lives a useless life, watching pro wrestling,
I don't understand why they are trying to win.
But watching them with so much energy in front of me
I can feel their drive.
Jump!
How is it?
It was amazing
It's like I can feel my body fluttering with the excitement
I didn't know about it
that you were a pro-wrestling fan
It's not that I like it though
Let's go home
Ready?
I'm opening it
Girls! There you are just standing come on let's drink!
Stop it come on let's go there!
Sorry about that
Wanna read it in a more quiet place?
Where would that be?
That would be...
Ah thank you
It's been a while!
Komiyama-san!
It really has been!
You really came to visit
I have to go back to Tokyo now though
Once we're done here, would you give us a ride back as well?
That's fine
But to be taken away by a truck
without even noticing.
The driver said she committed suicide
Suicide?
After buying stuff?
Yes
As if
Besides, do you know what she bought?
Milk chocolate
Right
She bought a whole pack you know
33 pieces inside
33?
I was curious so I asked about it
There are 3 kinds of chocolate inside
"Ah today's this flavor" she goes
She eats that happily everyday as if drawing fortune slips.
You think a person like that would commit suicide?
Well that's true...
It's not a suicide after all
As if Samu would do something like that
Is until here fine?
Yes. Thank you very much
- Thank you very much
Ah, I heard about it
you're set to be in Budoukan right?
Congratulations
- Congratulations!
Wait a second!
Is that how you guys really feel?
Don't you guys actually feel upset and jealous, and that it can't be helped?
Of course not....
I'll tell you how I feel
I really wanted it to be you guys
Not the ones I'm handling now
I wanted to get there with you guys
I feel bad so I'll say this
"Was it that it really wasn't meant to be you guys?"
But the timing really just wasn't right.
Someday for sure in another opportunity,
the perfect timing will come with it.
May it be in work, or in love
Don't let the Budoukan then get away.
Go up that same stage and sing
Yes
We'll sing
It's the first time, that you said something when we needed it.
What's with that?
It's just Kimu's words of affirmation
Will you guys go there now?
Yes
It's room 202
202?
It's feels so nostalgic
It hasn't changed at all
I missed this
Everything's still the same
This is my spot
And this is my spot
Feels like home!
This was Samu's seat
Yeah
Enough of that,
let's take a look.
Yeah
Here we go
Ready, go
What is this?
One-click phishing?
Those malicious stuff?
Like a phishing scare will stop us
One more time
Ready, go
"Afforestation volunteer"?
Isn't this Samu?
It really is her!
Stop global warming she said
"Let's save the endangered polar bears from the effects of global warming!" it says
White bears...
Udagawa White Bears!
Isn't today the day White Bears was formed?
It is! I totally forgot about it!
This is probably a scheduled message, I heard apps can do that
Samu remembered
The day we were formed
Looks like we weren't just nothing to her
What have you guys been up to recently?
As for me right now...
I'm living together with a girl.
My girlfriend, for that matter
I'm a lesbian, actually
I didn't know
Are you happy?
Yeah
Really happy
Once we have enough money, someday we're planning on starting a cafe
That sounds nice
I am currently undergoing group therapies
People who can't stop drinking gather and talk about their experiences
But Kimu you don't drink..?
Sorry...that was a lie
Then you must've been holding back this entire time
Good job Kimu
Thanks
Right now I'm working as Kirara's manager
You two really get along well
That's not true
I've been keeping from everyone but
In all honesty, I've always envied Kirara
I've also done what haters do
For you to be her manager despite that
that's admirable.
I'm currently an OL
OL= Office Lady
While working to pay my debts, I go watch pro-wrestling at the weekends
Debt?
Yeah
But it's nothing to worry about anymore
You really worked hard
What are you doing?
TN: Lyrics made with the help of translations found in stage48.net
Hane no Kioku
It's our debut song
I really like this intro
I like the lyrics too
The costumes are super cute too
Let's sing?
I want to see, the me 10 years in the future
Where are you I wonder? What are you doing I wonder?
At that time, I wonder if I will be happy?
It would be nice to be with you, laughing together
At the usual road, where the sunlight passes through the trees
That scenery alone will never change
I've thought about our future
Will our dreams come true?
Will we not give up?
At that time, I hope the two of us are still friends
Joking around together
It would be great if our lives turn out that way
The sky exists for us to soar, not just to look up to
I thought as I see the birds flying effortlessly
What I can do now, with what is on my back
the memory of wings that I have not used, I have to believe in it.
In Samu's sudden death, it made us remember a lot of things
But in a somewhat anticlimactic event with indifference,
our daily lives continue.
Whoever dies, whatever happens, everyday life will continue to move on
without taking responsibility for your sadness; cruel, but unknowingly gentle.
Somehow, it's the exact reason why we continue living
In the advent of the end of Samu's short life,
it reminds us that there's still a long road ahead of us
With this reality, though it brings tears to our eyes,
life won't change.
Our almost dumb same as always everyday lives, as long as that is there
We'll be fine
Samu no Koto